<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DW</product>
<table>DW.EXPORT.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a PARAMETER for DW.EXPORT application</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OL.TARGET.DATABASE</field>
<desc>
		<p>This field will be used when the TAKEOVER field is specified as 'ONLINE'.</p>
		<p>The value in this field is the database that will be updated when a record of the current. </p>
		<p>DW.EXPORT record is modified or created. The table information will be obtained from the OL.TARGET.TABLE field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNICODE.STD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the format in which the data will be extracted in.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field, it will be defaulted to UTF-16BE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLD.DELIMITER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the delimiter with which the data will be delimited in the extract</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field, it will be defaulted to '~'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will have the details of the applications that will be extracted for this company</p>
            <p>The value given in this field should have a record in DW.EXPORT application</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.PATHNAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the path in which the data will be extracted to for the particular COMPANY record</p>
            <p>Different paths should be given for different company extracts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MERGE.COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>when a Company ID is specified in this field, all the records in that company will be extracted as part of the company which is the ID of the DW.EXPORT.PARAM record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field specifies for which product the extraction is going to be happen.</p>
	<p>Available Products: Insight ,Insight-Risk,Insight-Oi.
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSFER.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A routine can be attached in this field.</p>
            <p>A user defined routine which has the logic to move the extracted data from the T24 server to Insight server</p>
            <p>The user routine should have a entry in PGM.FILE with TYPE as 'S'</p>
            <p>A sample routine DW.TRANSFER.ROUTINE is provided by Temenos</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
		<p>This field specifies on which Frequency pattern the extraction is going to be happen.</p>
		<p>Frequency Pattern: </p>
		<p>1.Daily </p>
			<p>a.Daily </p>
			<p>b. Business Day </p>
		<p>2.Weekly</p>
			<p>a.Every 'n' Week(s) </p>
		<p>3.Monthly</p>
			<p>a.Twice Monthly </p>
			<p>b.Every 'n' Month(s) On 'n' th day </p>
		<p>4.Defined</p>
			<p>a.LHFYR- LAST DAY IN THIS MID YEAR </p>
			<p>b.LQUAT- LAST DAY OF THIS QUARTER </p>
			<p>c.LYEAR- LAST DAY OF THIS YEAR </p>
			<p>d.LMNTH- LAST DAY OF THIS MONTH </p>
			<p>e.LWEEK- LAST DAY OF THIS WEEK 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.RETRY</field>
<desc>
  <p>No input field. This will be updated for the online extraction.</p>
  <p>This is to note how many times the system re-tried to push the transaction from T24 to 3rd party database, in case of network failure or database failure.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A description about the DW.EXPORT.PARAM record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DW.COMPANY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID of the field, it accepts the COMPANY.ID and SYSTEM as value</p>
            <p>SYSTEM record will be defined with DW.ONLINE.UPDATE field alone.</p>
            <p>COMPANY ID will have the details of the path, Unicode format, delimiter and TRANSFER.ROUTINE</p>
            <p>Branch company ID will not be allowed as a record in DW.EXPORT.PARAM</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DW.ONLINE.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will control in which format data's will be extracted</p>
            <p>It has 3 options, ONLINE, INCREMENTAL, BOTH</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.RETRY</field>
<desc>
  <p>Input field, should accept only numbers.</p>
  <p>This is to specify how many times system should re-try to push the transaction from T24 to 3rd party database, in case of network failure or database failure.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECON</field>
<desc>
  <p>This field is used to enable or disable the reconciliation process for DW.EXPORT</p>
  <p>This field will accept only YES or NO or Null(" "),Both NULL and NO are same and default value is NULL.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>BULK.NO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>BBL.CALL</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TYPE.OF.EXTRACT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>FILE.SUFFIX</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
