<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>AC.PENDING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds the information related to debit interest and charges pending posting to the actual account. The application can be used to make adjustments to the existing interest or charge amounts. This action will trigger off accounting to raise the relevant entries. See helptext for NEW.AMT for further accounting details. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SUSP.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used in the pending interest, charge or tax posting to the suspense account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
            <p>Automatically Updated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the record will comprise of the following elements: 1. Account Number. 2. Application Date i.e. capitalisation date + number of deferment days    defined on ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION. 3. 'DR1' - Debit interest one figures indicated in the record.    'DR2' - Debit interest two figures indicated in the record.    'CHG' - Charges figures indicated in the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The record is created automatically.</p>
            <p>The record may be maintained if it already exists on the live file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This holds the accounting entry keys generated by this application when a manula adjustment is made to the pending amounts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a free formatted field that may be used to enter remarks regarding any changes made to the charges and/or debit interest. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Free formatted field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.ALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may be used to specify that all the debit interest, charges &amp; taxes specified on this record are to be waived all at once. If this field is set to 'YES' then no charges, interest or tax will be actually applied to the account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used in the pending interest, charge or tax posting to the P&amp;L category. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of entry defined in the multi-value set defined from fields PENDING.SUSP.AC to OLD.AMT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Values that can exist here will be 'DR1', 'DR2', 'CHG'. plus the following charge types</p>
            <p>ADD for Debit Int Addon, HDB for Highest debit, GOV for Government margins and INS for Interest statement.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The details of all the old tax amounts before any changes were made to the charge or debit interest amount associated with it. The tax amount is always recalculated as soon as the charge or debit interest amount associated with it has been changed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically calculated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.ADJ.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total manual adjustment for the specific type being adjusted in MAN.ADJ.TYP</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Amount</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.PENDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the total pending amount of debit interest or charges with or without taxes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records all the previous values of the pending debit interest, charge. The user may make changes to the original value by entering a new amount in the NEW.AMT field. All these manually entered changes are audited in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.CAP.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The original capitalisation date when this account capitalised the underlying details. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECD.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The P&amp;L category to which the debit interest or charge was posted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The original debit interest or charge calculated on the account. The field is updated automatically in the end of day interest capitalisation process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This amount is the total tax amount calculated on the charge or debit interest. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.ADJ.TYP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of interest or charge that was adjusted, DR1 for Debit Interest, ADD for Debit Int Addon, HDB for Highest debit, GOV for Government margins and INS for Interest statement.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to enter an adjustment to the exisiting pending debit interest, charge or tax amount. On entering an amount into this field the user is indicating to the system that the amount entered will be the new amount of debit interest, charge or tax pending. Changes made to the original amount are audited in the field OLD.AMT </p>
            <p>The application will raise approapriate accounting entries on authorisation of a record with this field entered into. The accounting entries will depend on whether the new entry is below the original entry or above it. The accounting entries have been shown below : </p>
            <p>On Reduction ------------ </p>
            <p>Back Valued entries with value date of the original capitalisation date (ORIG.CAP.DATE). </p>
            <p>Dr/Cr         Entity         Amount -----         ------         ------ </p>
            <p>DR            P&amp;L            OLD.AMT - NEW.AMT CR            SUSPENSE       OLD.AMT - NEW.AMT </p>
            <p>Forward Valued entries with value date of the original application date (2nd field separated by '.' in the ID). </p>
            <p>Dr/Cr         Entity         Amount -----         ------         ------ </p>
            <p>DR            ACCOUNT        NEW.AMT CR            SUSPENSE       NEW.AMT </p>
            <p />
            <p>On Increase ----------- </p>
            <p>Back Valued entries with value date of the original capitalisation date (ORIG.CAP.DATE). </p>
            <p>Dr/Cr         Entity         Amount -----         ------         ------ </p>
            <p>CR            P&amp;L            NEW.AMT - OLD.AMT DR            SUSPENSE       NEW.AMT - OLD.AMT </p>
            <p>Forward Valued entries with value date of the original application date (2nd field separated by '.' in the ID). </p>
            <p>Dr/Cr         Entity         Amount -----         ------         ------ </p>
            <p>DR            ACCOUNT        NEW.AMT CR            SUSPENSE       NEW.AMT </p>
            <p>This field will be cleared after the accounting entries have been raised and the latest value will be entered as the first multi-value set in the field OLD.AMT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Cannot enter if WAIVE.FLAG set to 'YES' on the current record or the old record.</p>
            <p>In order to re-instate the original amount after having accidentally waived the amount on this record, un-waive the record first by setting the WAIVE.FLAG to 'NO' and then re-enter the NEW.AMT with the original amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PENDING.TAXSUSP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the tax suspense account that is temporarily updated with the tax amount calculated on the charges and/or debit interest. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the tax code that was used for the calculation of taxes on the charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.OF.ADJ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Signifies the dates on which the last adjustments were made on this record. Dates of the changes made to the pending debit interest, charge or tax amounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PENDING.SUSP.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Signifies the suspense account that was posted with the debit interest or charge amount indicated in the field AMOUNT.DUE. This field is a part of a multi-valued associated set of fields defined below. The multi-values are used when more than one charge has been set up to be applied on an account. Also if tax was applicable on the charge or debit interest than this would appear as another set of multi-values. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Delivery id for the Adjustment advice(s) relating the type of adjustment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 delivery id </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This date denotes the date on which the actual account will be debited with the interest or charge amounts. On this date the suspense account will be credited as well with the same amounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The system calculated total amount pending. This amount is automatically adjusted when back valued corrections are made but is not affected by manual adjustments.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRM.SENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The delivery id used to send out a confirmation message '1970' type. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

