<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>AC.VIOLATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Each record is a record of violations for an account within a statement period. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TXN.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the transaction status for the associated <em>STMT.ENTRY</em> transaction of which the key is held in the </p>
            <p>STMT.ENTRY.ID</p> field.   <p>Fields </p><p>STMT.ENTRY.ID</p> to <p>NARRATIVE</p> form a related multi value set.   <p>A value of 'V' in this field signifies a transaction which adds 1 against the violation threshold. A value of 'N' in this field signifies a transaction which does not count towards the violation threshold. A value of 'R' in this field signifies a transaction which subtracts 1 against the violation threshold. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>A maximum of 1 character may be entered.</p><p>The following values are permitted: N = No Violation, R =         Reversal, V = Violation, null = No Violation.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESSING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The processing date of the STMT.ENTRY </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> EXTERN field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the IDs to the <em>STMT.ENTRY</em> file for each account at the statement date. </p>
            <p>Fields </p>
            <p>STMT.ENTRY.ID</p> to <p>NARRATIVE</p> form a related multi value set.   <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory input.</p><p>A maximum of 22 characters may be entered.</p><p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the <em>STMT.ENTRY</em>         file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VIOLATION.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether or not this particular violation record is in violation. It will either be set to Y (Yes) or N (No) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field indicates whether the transaction is considered in calculating whether an account has exceeded its threshold of qualifying transcations for the waiving of credit interest.</p>
            <p>This field is included in the </p>
            <p>STMT.ENTRY.ID</p> and <p>TXN.STATUS</p> multi-value set and will be automatically populated from the <p>WAIVE.CR.INT</p> field in <em>ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION</em><p />when the transaction code involved in the entry exists in the threshold group.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p />Valid inputs are N for No, R for Reverse and V for Violation.     </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CR.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to decide whether credit interest will be waived or not on the underlying account.</p>
            <p>Its value will be determined from the conditions set on the </p>
            <p><em>ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION </em>record for the account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid values are &amp;#145;YES&amp;#146; or &amp;#145;NO&amp;#146;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The transaction code from the STMT.ENTRY </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> EXTERN field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.STMT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to the violations file. The id will usually consist of two components, the account number and the statement date, i.e. 18999-20000101. The record details the qualifying transactions over the account for the period ending on the statement date and records whether a transaction threshold on the account was exceeded.</p>
            <p>Records with an id of the account number alone, are interim records which detail the qualifying transactions that have taken place in the current period and records whether a transaction threshold on the account has been exceeded.</p>
            <p>Qualifying transactions are those specified in the TXN.CODE.GRP field on the ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION file as counting towards a violation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-14 numeric characters Customer Account number or 6-12 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) character Internal Account number (see Details) plus Statement date in the standard T24 date format. </p>
            <p>To access an interim AC.VIOLATION record, only the account number needs to be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement. </p>
            <p>As in the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to  define  in  the violations file up to  999 Local Elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified. These Local Elements should be defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice. </p>
            <p>The name(s) of the new element(s), as well as the Format and <p>Validation Rules:</p>, must be defined in the LOCAL.TABLE, prior to the creation of any violations records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters as defined in the Local Table definition for this Local Reference field.  Multivalue field.  (Optional or Mandatory Input according to definition in LOCAL.TABLE for this Local Reference element)</p>
            <p>As defined by the User within the LOCAL.TABLE and LOCAL.REF.TABLE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the narrative relating to the addition or amendment of fields, </p>
            <p>STMT.ENTRY.ID</p> and <p>TXN.STATUS</p><p>Fields </p><p>STMT.ENTRY.ID</p> to <p>NARRATIVE</p> form a related multi value set.   <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p><p>If a </p><p>STMT.ENTRY.ID</p>         is entered or the <p>TXN.STATUS</p>         is changed, this field is mandatory  </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

