<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>AC.VIOLATION.HIST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>After s specified period the AC.VIOLATION records are moved to the AC.VIOLATION.HIST file.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TXN.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the transaction status for the associated STMT.ENTRY transaction of which the key is held in the </p>
            <p> STMT.ENTRY.ID</p>
            <p> Fields </p>
            <p> STMT.ENTRY.ID</p>
            <p> NARRATIVE</p>
            <p> A value of 'V' in this field signifies a transaction which adds 1 against the violation threshold. A value of 'N' in this field signifies a transaction which does not count towards the violation threshold. A value of 'R' in this field signifies a transaction which subtracts 1 against the violation threshold. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> A maximum of 1 character may be entered.</p>
            <p> The following values are permitted: N = No Violation, R = Reversal, V = Violation, null = No Violation.</p>
            <p> .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VIOLATION.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether or not this particular violation record is in violation. It will either be set to Y (Yes) or N (No) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.STMT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to the violations file. The id will usually consist of two components, the account number and the statement date, i.e. 18999-20000101. The record details the qualifying transactions over the account for the period ending on the statement date and records whether a transaction threshold on the account was exceeded.</p>
            <p> Records with an id of the account number alone, are interim records which detail the qualifying transactions that have taken place in the current period and records whether a transaction threshold on the account has been exceeded.</p>
            <p> Qualifying transactions are those specified in the TXN.CODE.GRP field on the ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION file as counting towards a violation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 2-14 numeric characters Customer Account number or 6-12 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) character Internal Account number (see Details) plus Statement date in the standard T24 date format. </p>
            <p> To access an interim AC.VIOLATION record, only the account number needs to be entered.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the narrative relating to the addition or amendment of fields, </p>
            <p> STMT.ENTRY.ID</p>
            <p> TXN.STATUS</p>
            <p> Fields </p>
            <p> STMT.ENTRY.ID</p>
            <p> NARRATIVE</p>
            <p> Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p> If a </p>
            <p> STMT.ENTRY.ID</p>
            <p> TXN.STATUS</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the IDs to the STMT.ENTRY file for each account at the statement date. </p>
            <p> Fields </p>
            <p> STMT.ENTRY.ID</p>
            <p> NARRATIVE</p>
            <p> Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
            <p> A maximum of 22 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p> Must be the key to a valid entry on the STMT.ENTRY file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

