<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>ACCOUNT.COMPENSATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is an internal file containing details of groups of Customer Accounts whose value dated balances and activity are combined for the calculation of interest and charges. </p>
            <p>When Accounts are to be combined for interest and charges, the Main Account is specified in the INTEREST.COMP.ACCT field in the Account records for each of the sub-accounts. </p>
            <p>The interest and conditions applicable to the Main Account are applied to the combined value dated balances and activity. </p>
            <p>The value dated balances and activity for each Account are stored separately in the Account Activity file (ACCT.ACTIVITY) and added together at the time interest and charges are calculated. </p>
            <p>Only Accounts in the same Currency can be combined. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies an Account whose value dated balances and activity are to be combined with those of the Main Account (Field 0) for the calculation of interest and charges. </p>
            <p>Any number of Accounts in the same Currency may be combined for calculation of interest and charges.  The Main Account number is entered in the INTEREST.COMP.ACCT field in the ACCOUNT record for each of the sub-accounts.  The interest and charges conditions applicable to the Main Account (Field 0) are used. The sub-accounts are defined in Fields 1 onwards, one Account per field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Account Number format. Internal field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the main Account of a group of Accounts whose value dated balances and activity are combined for calculating interest and charges. </p>
            <p>The Account Number in this field specifies the Main Account of the combined group.  The interest and charges conditions applicable to this Account are applied to the combined value dated balances and activity of all the Accounts in the group.  All Accounts in a combined group have the same Currency. </p>
            <p>The sub-accounts whose value dated balances and activity are to be included in interest and charges calculations are specified in the other fields of this record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Account Number format. Internal field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

