<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>ACCOUNT.DEBIT.LIMIT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table allows overdraft limits to be specified for individual Accounts which can then be used as the limit for the first rate of debit interest specified in the appropriate Group Debit Interest condition. </p>
            <p>If a Group Debit Interest condition record contains 2 rates, but no limit for the first rate, the overdraft limit specified for each Account in this table is used as the limit for the first rate. </p>
            <p>In this way it is possible to specify a different limit for the first rate for each Account, without having to specify separate Account Debit Interest condition records. </p>
            <p>If there is no limit specified in this table for a particular Account, a limit of zero is assumed, and the 2nd rate specified is effective for all balances. </p>
            <p>Using this facility, it is not possible to specify more than 2 rates in the Group Debit Interest condition record. </p>
            <p>The current record for an account may be updated/created automatically by the start of day processing. This is done when records currently exist for an account and the account record specifies that the limit on this record should be linked to the LIMITS file for the customers liability. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Account for which the overdraft limit specified in LIMIT applies and the Date from which it applies. </p>
            <p>If the appropriate Group Debit Interest condition record contains 2 debit interest rates and no limit is specified for the first, the overdraft limit specified in LIMIT of this record is used as the limit for the first rate when calculating Debit Interest on the Account specified in this field. </p>
            <p>If an Account Debit Interest condition is specified for this Account (instead of using the Group condition), the overdraft limit specified in this record has no effect. </p>
            <p>The corresponding CONCAT record in the file ACCOUNT.DATE will be updated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>a.   Standard Account Number format. b.   '-'      Prime Sites '.' c.   Standard Date format. (Account Number mandatory, Date optional. Default Date is today's date.)</p>
            <p>There must be a corresponding Account record on the Account file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the overdraft limit which is used as the limit for the first debit interest rate specified in the appropriate Group Debit Interest condition when calculating debit interest on the Account specified in Field 0. </p>
            <p>If the appropriate Group Debit Interest condition record contains 2 debit interest rates and no limit is specified for the first, the overdraft limit specified in this record is used as the limit for the first rate when calculating Debit Interest on the Account specified in Field 0 of this record. </p>
            <p>If an Account Debit Interest condition is specified for this Account (instead of using the Group condition), the overdraft limit specified in this record has no effect. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Amount format. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 018 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field.  </p>
            <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

