<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>ACCT.STATEMENT.CHARGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.COPY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>In the absence of any other specific charges being entered, then this amount will be applied for copy of the statement.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description used to indicate the type of charge(s) being applied.</p>
            <p>This is a multi valued language field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input. </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where charges are being calculated it is possible to place a minimum amount that will be charged to the client, amounts less than this will not create any accounting. This is specific to the currency in this set of fields.</p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHEET.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The foreign currency charge amount to be applied for producing each sheet of the statement.</p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The TRANSACTION code used on the debit entries when charges are posted. The description and details on this TRANSACTION code affects the way the entries are handled by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a Debit TRANSACTION code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.FREE.STMTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where an amount is specified to be charged each page (or sheet) of the statement produced, this field allows for the first 1 to 9999 sheets to be free of charge. Hence a system whereby only clients whose statements exceed say 5 sheets would receive an addtional charge for large statements.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Numeric input 1-9999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where charges are being calculated it is possible to place a minimum amount that will be charged to the client, amounts less than this will not create any accounting.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.CHARGE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>In the absence of any other specific charges being entered, then this default amount will be applied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.SHEET.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>In the absence of any other specific charges being entered, then this amount will be applied for each page (or sheet) of the statement.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where charges are being calculated it is possible to place a maximum amount that will be charged to the client, capping the calculated charges to a reasonable amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEQUENCE.YEAR.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default charge for supplying a copy statement. In the absence of any other specific charges being entered, then this default amount will be applied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The TRANSACTION code used on the credit entries when charges are posted. The description and details on this TRANSACTION code affects the way the entries are handled by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p>Must be a Credit TRANSACTION code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the CATEGORY code which refers to the P/L code where the charge is to be posted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file. </p>
            <p>Must be in the 50000  69999 range</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The foreign currency charge amount to be applied for producing statements.</p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COPY.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The foreign currency charge amount to be applied for producing copies of statements.</p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charges can be set for each currency and have standard round amounts instead of the current calculated equivalent of the default local amount. This allows say a DEM 15.00 charge to be inposed as standard instead of the equivalent of USD 10.00, which may be DEM 14.55 one day and DEM 15.11 the next.</p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where charges are being calculated it is possible to place a maximum amount that will be charged to the client, capping any calculated charges to a reasonable amount. This is specific to the currency in this set of fields.</p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.STMTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where an amount is specified to be charged each page (or sheet) of the statement produced, this field allows for the first 1 to 9999 sheets to be free of charge. Hence a system whereby only clients whose statements exceed say 5 sheets would receive an addtional charge for large statements.</p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Numeric input 1-9999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

