<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>ACCT.INTERIM.CAP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this table is to specify any Accounts for which interim interest application is required on a particular day.  Interim interest applications do not affect the normal cycle of interest applications for the account, specified either at group level (GROUP.CAPITALISATION Table) or at Account level (ACCT.CAPITALISATION Table). </p>
            <p>For each Account for which an interim interest application is required, it is possible to specify each type of interest separately, (Credit Interest, Debit Interest, Credit Interest 2 and Debit Interest 2). </p>
            <p>Interim interest applications may be requested in advance and will be processed on the specified day.  Interest is calculated up to the date specified, (including or not including balances with value equal to that date, as specified at Company level in the ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL table). </p>
            <p>If the date specified is not a working day, the interest application is processed on the previous working day, unless the Last Day Inclusive Field in the ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL table contains 'Y' and a month end accrual day falls before the date specified, in which case the application is processed on the next working day.  In either case, the figures are calculated as if it had been processed on the date specified. </p>
            <p>Note: There is no need to use this table to request interim interest       applications for Accounts which are being closed.  This is       handled by the Account Closure routine (Posting Restriction 90-99) </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INTERIM.CAP.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on which interim interest application(s) are required. </p>
            <p>Interest applications will be processed on this date for all Accounts specified in ACCOUNT.NUMBER.  If this date is a non-working day, the interest applications will be processed on the previous working day, unless the LAST.DAY.INCLUSIVE Field in the ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL table contains 'Y' and there is a monthend accrual day before this date, in which case the interest applications will be processed on the next working day. </p>
            <p>Interest is calculated on balances with value up to this date, (including or not including this date, as specified at Company level in the ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL table). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 standard date characters.</p>
            <p>Must not be less than today's date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.CAPITALIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not an interim application (capitalisation) of the second type of debit interest is required for the Account in the corresponding ACCOUNT.NUMBER field. </p>
            <p>Field range DR.CAPITALIS to CR2.CAPITALIS specifies which type(s) of interest should be capitalised, for each Account in ACCOUNT.NUMBER field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or nothing.  Multivalue field associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to CR2.CAPITALIS. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the Account(s) for which interim interest application(s) are required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-14 numeric character Account number     or 3-10 character Account mnemonic.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.CAPITALIS to CR2.CAPITALIS. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be an existing Account in the ACCOUNT file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.CAPITALIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not an interim application (capitalisation) of credit interest is required for the Account in the corresponding ACCOUNT.NUMBER field. </p>
            <p>Field range DR.CAPITALIS to CR2.CAPITALIS specifies which type(s) of interest should be capitalised, for each Account in ACCOUNT.NUMBER field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or nothing.  Multivalue field associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to CR2.CAPITALIS. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.CAPITALIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not an interim application (capitalisation) of the second type of credit interest is required for the Account in the corresponding ACCOUNT.NUMBER field. </p>
            <p>Field range DR.CAPITALIS to CR2.CAPITALIS specifies which type(s) of interest should be capitalised, for each Account in ACCOUNT.NUMBER field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or nothing.  Multivalue field associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to CR2.CAPITALIS. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.CAPITALIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not an interim application (capitalisation) of debit interest is required for the Account in the corresponding ACCOUNT.NUMBER field. </p>
            <p>Field range DR.CAPITALIS to CR2.CAPITALIS specifies which type(s) of interest should be capitalised, for each Account in ACCOUNT.NUMBER field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or nothing.  Multivalue field associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to CR2.CAPITALIS.  (Mandatory input if no other input in corresponding fields DR2.CAPITALIS to CR2.CAPITALIS, otherwise optional.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

