<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>ACCT.INTERIM.CHG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Indicates a series of accounts where an interim capitalisation is required. Normally capitlaisation frequency will be take place according to the setup of the relevant IC.CHARGE record.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INTERIM.CAP.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that the interim capitalisation is to take place cannot be less than the current working day.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>T24 account number for which ACCT.INTERIM.CHG is to be set.  A record should have been available in the IC.CHARGE table either at the group level or at the account level for the account mentioned here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid T24 Account Number</p>
            <p> Optional input. Mutually exclusive with field CUSTOMER.NUMBER</p>
            <p> IC.CHARGE record must be available for the account either at the account       level or at the group level</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.PRODUCTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Interim Charges that are to be collected from the account mentioned in the field above.</p>
            <p> Once the account no. is input, the values in this field is automatically populated by the system based on the values given in IC.CHARGE record for the account or to the group to which the account belongs.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Populated by the system once Account Number field is input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is now redundant        </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IC.CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the IC.CHARGE record associated with the related account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

