<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>ACCT.SUSP.SETTLE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table allows the user to request settlement of interest and/or charges which have been 'suspensed', i.e. stored in a Suspense Amount field in the Account record instead of being booked to Profit and Loss, (see note below). </p>
            <p>Separate Suspense Amounts are held for different types of interest and charges, identified by their Profit and Loss Category Codes.  Settlement may be requested for all or part of the amount of any or all the types. </p>
            <p>An End Of Day program, EOD.ACCT.SUSP, removes the amounts specified in this table from the Suspense Amount fields in Account records and generates the appropriate entries to book them to Profit and Loss. </p>
            <p>Note: If the INT.NO.BOOKING field in the Account record contains       'SUSPENSE', interest and charges are booked to the Customer's       Account, but no Profit and Loss entries are generated, instead the       amount which would have been accrued is stored in a Suspense Amount       field in the Account record, e.g. for bad and doubtful debts.       As long as any suspensed interest and/or charges remain unsettled,       it is not possible to remove 'SUSPENSE' from the Account record. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Profit and Loss Category Code of account ledger charges which have been suspensed and are to be settled.  The amount of charges to be settled are specified in the associated AMOUNT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with AMOUNT.CHARGE. (Mandatory input if no other input in fields AMOUNT.CHARGE to AMOUNT.DEBIT2, otherwise optional.)</p>
            <p>Must be a Category Code which exists in ACCR.CHG.CATEG of the Account (Main File) record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Profit and Loss Category Code of credit interest which has been suspensed and is to be settled.  The amount of interest to be settled is specified in the associated AMOUNT.CREDIT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with AMOUNT.CREDIT. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a Category Code which exists in the ACCR.CR.CATEG of the Account (Main File) record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of Debit Interest or interest related charge, of the type specified by the Category Code in the corresponding DEBIT.CATEG, to be settled. </p>
            <p>It is possible to settle all or part of the Accrual Amount Suspensed.  The Amount specified is removed from the Accrual Suspensed field in the Account record and booked to Profit and Loss. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with DEBIT.CATEG. (Mandatory input if input in corresponding DEBIT.CATEG, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>Must not be greater than the Accrual Suspensed amount in the Account record for the Category specified in the corresponding DEBIT.CATEG.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Profit and Loss Category Code of debit interest or interest related charge which has been suspensed and is to be settled.  The amount of interest or charge to be settled is specified in the associated AMOUNT.DEBIT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with AMOUNT.DEBIT. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a Category Code which exists in the ACCR.DR.CATEG of the Account record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT2.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Profit and Loss Category Code of Credit2 Interest which has been suspensed and is to be settled. The amount of interest to be settled is specified in the associated AMOUNT.CREDIT2 field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with AMOUNT.CREDIT2. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a Category Code which exists in ACCR.CR2.CATEG of the Account (Main File) record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT2.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Profit and Loss Category Code of debit2 interest which has been suspensed and is to be settled.  The amount of interest to be settled is specified in the associated AMOUNT.DEBIT2. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with AMOUNT.DEBIT2. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a Category Code which exists in ACCR.DR2.CATEG of the Account (Main File) record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the number of an Account for which interest or charges which have been suspensed are to be settled and booked to profit and loss.  The type and amount of interest or charges to be settled are defined in the following fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-14 numeric character Account Number    or 3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '-') character Account      mnemonic (converted to an Account Number). Prime Sites '.'  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>It must be a valid Account number on the ACCOUNT file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of charges, of the type specified by the Category Code in the corresponding CHARGE.CATEG, to be settled. </p>
            <p>It is possible to settle all or part of the Accrual Amount Suspensed.  The Amount specified is removed from the Accrual Suspensed field in the Account record and booked to Profit and Loss. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with CHARGE.CATEG. (Mandatory input if input in corresponding CHARGE.CATEG, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>Must not be greater than the Accrual Suspensed amount in the Account record for the Category specified in the corresponding CHARGE.CATEG.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of Credit Interest, of the type specified by the Category Code in the corresponding CREDIT.CATEG, to be settled. </p>
            <p>It is possible to settle all or part of the Accrual Amount Suspensed.  The Amount specified is removed from the Accrual Suspensed field in the Account record and booked to Profit and Loss. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with CREDIT.CATEG. (Mandatory input if input in corresponding CREDIT.CATEG, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>Must not be greater than the Accrual Suspensed amount in the Account record for the Category specified in the corresponding CREDIT.CATEG field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.CREDIT2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of Credit2 Interest, of the type specified by the Category Code in the corresponding CREDIT2.CATEG, to be settled. </p>
            <p>It is possible to settle all or part of the Accrual Amount Suspensed.  The Amount specified is removed from the Accrual Suspensed field in the Account record and booked to Profit and Loss. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format. Multivalue field associated with CREDIT2.CATEG. (Mandatory input if input in corresponding CREDIT2.CATEG, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>Must not be greater than the Accrual Suspensed amount in the Account record for the Category specified in the corresponding CREDIT2.CATEG field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.CHARGE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.DEBIT2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of Debit2 Interest, of the type specified by the Category Code in the corresponding DEBIT2.CATEG , to be settled. </p>
            <p>It is possible to settle all or part of the Accrual Amount Suspensed.  The Amount specified is removed from the Accrual Suspensed field in the Account record and booked to Profit and Loss. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with DEBIT2.CATEG. (Mandatory input if input in corresponding DEBIT2.CATEG, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>Must not be greater than the Accrual Suspensed amount in the Account record for the Category specified in the corresponding DEBIT2.CATEG.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Currency of the Account specified in Field 0 (ACCOUNT NUMBER). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 uppercase alpha characters Currency Code. (Internal field, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

