<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>CORR.ACCT.DR</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is an internal file containing details of previous calculations of Debit Interest and Interest Related Charges for capitalisation (application to the Customer's Account) which have subsequently been recalculated with different results. </p>
            <p>  Whenever any entries are processed with VALUE DATEs prior to the last Capitalisation date (as stored in the CAP.DATE.DR.INT field in the ACCOUNT record), the end of day program EOD.CAPITALIS.CORR automatically recalculates the interest and interest related charges for the capitalisation period(s) from the one containing the earliest back-valued entry, up to the last Capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>  The new STMT.ACCT.DR record is compared with the one previously calculated, and if there is any difference, the old one is stored (unchanged) in this file, the corrected one is written to the STMT.ACCT.DR file and appropriate accounting entries are processed for the differences. Each time the same capitalisation is corrected, the CORRECTION.NUMBER is incremented by 1. </p>
            <p>  Each CORR.ACCT.DR record is an exact copy of the old STMT.ACCT.DR record, except for the ID which has the Correction Number suffixed. </p>
            <p>  When interest rates or conditions are amended, back-value recalculations are not processed automatically, but can be requested via TABLE.CAPITALIS.CORR. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STMT.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the TAX record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to the Interest Statement charge. </p>
            <p>  The tax details used are those applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOV.MARGIN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where a Government Margin charge is to be made on an Account, this code specifies the GOVERNMENT.MARGIN record containing the details of the calculation and processing of Government Margin charges. </p>
            <p>  The Government Margin charge is calculated as a percentage of the debit balance.  (Shown in multivalue field GV.VAL.BALANCE). </p>
            <p>  The Government Margin details used are those applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated when debit interest is accrued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.TR.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Account entries generated when debit interest is capitalised. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HI.DR.TAX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate of Tax, to be applied to the Highest Debit charge, to calculate the Tax Amount shown in associated field HI.DR.TAX.AMT. </p>
            <p>  Multiple occurrences of field range HI.DR.TAX.RATE to HI.DR.TAXTRSCR are used where the Tax record specifies that more than one rate of Tax is applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format. Multivalue field associated with Fields 52 to 56.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNADJ.HIGHEST.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the unadjusted Highest Debit charge when an adjustment relating to the Maximum Legal Rate is needed. </p>
            <p>  This is used to store the actual Highest Debit charge when differs from the applied Highest Debit charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.MAIN.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.MAIN.INT</p>
            <p>  The amount of ICA interest posted to this account if this account is the main account of the account defined in ICA.MAIN.ACCT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No Input multi valued field associated with ICA.MAIN.ACCT</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.TAX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate of Tax applied to the debit interest amount, to calculate the Tax Amount shown in associated field DR.INT.TAX.AMT. </p>
            <p>  Multiple occurrences of field range DR.INT.TAX.RATE to DR.INT.TAXTRSCR are used where the TAX record specifies that more than one rate of Tax is applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format. Multivalue field associated with Fields 12 to 16.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOV.MRG.TRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Account entries generated for Government Margin charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDON.TAXCATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code which determines the Internal Account to be updated with Tax Provision entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Debit Interest Add-on charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with field range INT.ADDON.TRSDR to ADDON.TAX.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.NO.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>If interest and charges are to be calculated for information purposes only and not passed to the account, or if accrued interest is to be suspended and not posted to Profit and Loss, this is shown by this field. </p>
            <p>  The information in this field comes from the equivalent field in the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>  If this field contains 'SUSPENSE', interest will be booked to the Customer's Account but no Profit or Loss entries will be generated, instead, the amount which would have been accrued will be stored in a Suspense Amount field in the Account record. </p>
            <p>  If this field contains 'Y', interest is calculated for information only, no entries will be posted either to Profit and Loss or to the Customer's Account.  e.g. for Nostro Accounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  'SUSPENSE', 'Y' or nothing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.TAXTRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Tax Provision Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the debit interest amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.TAX.RATE to DR.INT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGH.DR.TRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Highest Debit charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDON.TAXTRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Tax Provision Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Debit Interest Add-on charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field range INT.ADDON.TRSDR to ADDON.TAX.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.TR.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.TR.PL</p>
            <p>  The transaction code used for posting ICA interest to profit and loss, as defined on ICA.HIERARCHY.PARAMETER relevant to the interest type and whether the posting is standard interest or a correction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 transaction code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.NO.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for which the Interest Amount shown in corresponding field DR.INT.AMT has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  The number of days is calculated according to the Basis (360/360,366/360, 366/365 or 360/365) on which the interest calculation is to be made. Where the Basis is 360/360 or 360/365, the number of days is calculated as if there are 30 days in each month.  This is achieved by ignoring the 30th if there are 31 days in a month and assuming 3 days on the 28th of February or 2 days on the 29th of February.  If the Basis is 366/360 or 366/365, the number of days is the actual number of days. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-3 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.DATE to DR.INT.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.GOV.MAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for government margin charge.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQUIDITY.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where interest and charges are to be passed to an alternative Account, the number of the alternative ACCOUNT is shown by this field. </p>
            <p>  Where interest and charges are to be passed to an alternative Account, the alternative account number should be entered in the INTEREST.LIQU.ACCT field on the original customer ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  2-16 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADDON.TRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Account entries generated for Debit Interest Add-on charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQUIDITY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency of the liquidity account which may be present on this file. </p>
            <p>  The currency may not necessarally be the currency of the main account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters       or 1-3 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of Tax calculated on the Interest Statement charge, at the rate shown in corresponding field STMT.TAX.RATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range STMT.TAX.RATE to STMT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will contain the period end date of the current capitalisation period. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.TAXCATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code which determines the Internal Account to be updated with Tax Provision entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the debit interest amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.TAX.RATE to DR.INT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNADJ.INT.ADDON</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the unadjusted Debit Interest Addon amount when an adjustment relating to the Maximum Legal Rate is needed. </p>
            <p>  This is used to store the actual Debit Interest Addon charge when differs from the applied Debit Interest Add-on charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNADJ.DR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the unadjusted amount of Debit Interest when an adjustment relating to the Maximum Legal Rate is needed. </p>
            <p>  This is used to store the actual Debit Interest amount when differs from the applied Debit Interest amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.VAL.BALANCE to DR.INT.CATEG.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.TOTAL.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total amount of deferred interest.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.TOTAL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total amount of deferred Tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPENS.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where the balances on two or more Accounts are to be netted for the purpose of calculating interest and charges, the various sub-account numbers are shown by this multivalue field. The Account Number shown in the Record Id of this file is the major Account number of the group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  2-16 numeric characters.  Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Incremented every time an interest correction takes place</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDON.TAXTRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Customer Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Debit Interest Add-on charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field range INT.ADDON.TRSDR to INT.TAX.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.TR.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated when debit interest is accrued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.TAXTRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Tax Provision Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Interest Statement charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field range STMT.TAX.RATE to STMT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGH.DR.TRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Account entries generated for Highest Debit charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADDON.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where a Debit Interest Add-on charge is to be made on an Account, this code specifies the DEBIT.INT.ADDON record containing details of the calculation and processing of Interest Add-on charge. </p>
            <p>  The Debit Interest Add-on charge is calculated as a percentage of the total value of Debit Interest shown in all occurrences of multivalue field DR.INT.AMT. </p>
            <p>  The Debit Interest Add-on charge details used are those applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDON.TAX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate of Tax to be applied to the Debit Interest Addon charge to calculate the Tax Amount shown in associated field ADDON.TAX.AMT. </p>
            <p>  Multiple occurrences of field range INT.ADDON.TRSDR to ADDON.TAX.AMT are used where the TAX record specifies that more than one rate of Tax is to be applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format.  Multivalue field associated with field range INT.ADDON.TRSDR to ADDON.TAXCATEG.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Debit Interest Rate used to calculate the Interest Amount shown in corresponding field DR.INT.AMT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.DATE to DR.INT.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.TAXCATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code which determines the Internal Account to be updated with Tax Provision entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Interest Statement charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with field range STMT.TAX.RATE to STMT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.TOTAL.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total amount of deferred debit charge.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.TAX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate of Tax applied to the Interest Statement charge to calculate the Tax Amount shown in associated field STMT.TAX.AMT. </p>
            <p>  Multiple occurrences of field range STMT.TAX.RATE to STMT.TAXTRSCR are used where the Tax record specifies that more than 1 rate of Tax is applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format.  Multivalue field associated with field range STMT.TAX.RATE to STMT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.FIRST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value date of the first balance on which the interest has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  This is the day after the previous debit  interest application (Capitalisation) as stored in the CAP.DATE.DR.INT field in the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  9 date characters - DD MMM YYYY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the corresponding CORRECTION.ID generated for a transaction. This field will be updated when the defered tax is posted. </p>
            <p> The information in this field will be updated based on the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. Once updated, this information will be cleared from the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. </p>
            <p> The value in this field is a valid record in CORR.ACCT.DR. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HI.DR.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the TAX record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to the Highest Debit charge. </p>
            <p>  The tax details used are those applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.POST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that interest was posted to the account</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.ADDON</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for deferred debit interest addon charge.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADDON.FREE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the free amount deducted from the calculated interest add-on charge, if applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.MIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that the minimum amount of credit interest has been applied. If the calculated amount of interest was less than the minimum value then this will be applied, assuming that the amount is not to be waived.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.TR.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.TR.AC</p>
            <p>  The transaction code used for posting ICA interest to the account, as defined on ICA.HIERARCHY.PARAMETER relevant to the interest type and whether the posting is standard interest or a correction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 transaction code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STMT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Interest Statement charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.HIGH.DR.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for highest debit charge Tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USED.MIDDLE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate used to convert the Account Currency into Local Currency during the Charge calculation process. </p>
            <p>  Note : This is necessary where default charges specified in local currency        are used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total of Interest Related Charges. </p>
            <p>  Made up of the following: </p>
            <p>  Debit Interest Add-on - a percentage of the amount of debit interest to                         be applied. </p>
            <p>  Government Margin     - an additional interest rate applied to each debit                         balance. </p>
            <p>  Highest Debit         - a percentage of the largest debit balance. </p>
            <p>  Interest Statement    - a charge for providing a detailed interest                         statement when debit interest is applied. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.VAL.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The debit balance on which the Interest Amount, shown in corresponding field DR.INT.AMT, has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  The value dates balances on which interest is calculated are held in the ACCT.ACTIVITY file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.DATE to DR.INT.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of Debit Interest calculated at the rate shown in corresponding field DR.INT.RATE, on the amount shown in corresponding field DR.VAL.BALANCE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.DATE to DR.INT.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.HIGH.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for highest debit charge.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HI.DR.TAXTRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Tax Provision Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Highest Debit charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field range HI.DR.TAX.RATE to HI.DR.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOV.MARGIN.MIN.MAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>After calculating the gross Government Margin charge, comparison is made with Minimum and Maximum charge amounts from the GOVERNMENT.MARGIN record.  If either the Minimum  charge or the Maximum charge is substituted for the calculated charge, 'MINIMUM' or "MAXIMUM' is recorded in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  'MINIMUM', 'MAXIMUM' or nothing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of interest before Tax. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DR.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the Highest Debit Balance found during the application period and on which the Highest Debit Balance charge is based. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WITHHELD.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted interest amount after the correction process. This is similar to the field ADJ.INT.AMT. </p>
            <p> This field will be updated only when the field TAX.CORR.CAP is set to YES in ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION. For other cases, it will be zero. </p>
            <p> The information in this field will be updated based on the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. Once updated, this information will be cleared from the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of Tax calculated on the debit interest, at the rate shown in corresponding field DR.INT.TAX.RATE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.TAX.RATE to DR.INT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.TAXTRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Customer Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Interest Statement charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field range STMT.TAX.RATE to STMT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.MIN.WAIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether credit interest is set to zero if it is less than the minimum value. Set to "YES" is interest below the minimum value is to be waived.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.MAIN.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.MAIN.ACCT</p>
            <p>  Indicates the ICA main accounts to which this account was linked between the PERIOD.FIRST.DATE and PERIOD.LAST.DATE on the statement.</p>
            <p>  If this account was a main account then this account number will also be included.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No Input field</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 account number</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STMT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the Interest Statement Charge.  This is a flat charge levied on each debit interest capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOV.MARGIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of Government Margin charge calculated at the rate shown in corresponding field GV.INT.RATE, on the amount shown in corresponding field GV.VAL.BALANCE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range GOV.MARGIN.DATE to GOV.MARGIN.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOV.MARGIN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of a period, during which the Account has been in debit and a Government Margin charge has been calculated.  Associated fields show the number of days of the calculation, the applicable rate and the balance. If the balance changes, a further set of associated fields will be generated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  9 date characters  -  DD MMM YYYY.  Multivalue field associated with field range GOV.MARGIN.DATE to GOV.MARGIN.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.ADDON.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for deferred debit interest addon charge Tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOV.MRG.TOT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the total calculated Government Margin Charge.  It is the sum of multivalue fields GOV.MARGIN.AMT adjusted to the Minimum or Maximum if appropriate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.LAST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value date of the last balance on which the interest has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  Interest is calculated on the value dated balances stored in the ACCT.ACTIVITY file, taking into account all entries over the Account up to and including the last end of day processing. </p>
            <p>  The calculation includes all balances from the day after the last debit interest capitalisation, as stored in the ACCOUNT record (in the CAP.DATE.DR.INT field) up to the capitalisation date specified, or, if the LAST.DAY.INCLUSIVE field in the ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL file contains 'NO', up to the working day prior to the processing date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  9 date characters - DD MMM YYYY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.DIST.RATIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the percentage of ICA group interest applied to this account if the ratio method of interest distribution is used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INT.STMT.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for interest statement charge Tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STMT.TRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Account entries generated for Interest Statement charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADDON.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the calculated Debit Interest Add-on Charge after Minimum or Maximum adjustment if appropriate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADDON.PERCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the Percentage applied to the Debit Interest amount to calculate the Debit Interest Add-on charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.WAIVE.ALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES indicates that all debit interest and tax was waived for this period, if set to YES then no debit interest or tax will apply to this period for back valued corrections. But it will be calculated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted tax amount after the correction process. This field will be updated only when the defered tax amount is posted. </p>
            <p> The value in this field will be zero if the field TAX.CORR.CAP is set to YES in ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION. </p>
            <p> The information in this field will be updated based on the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. Once updated, this information will be cleared from the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.DR.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for debit interest Tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGH.DR.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Highest Debit charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADDON.TRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Debit Interest Add-on charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DR.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the Percentage applied to the Highest Debit amount to calculate the Highest Debit charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.DR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for debit interest.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.INT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.INT.CATEG</p>
            <p>  Contains the category code used for ICA interest posting. This is defined on ICA.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The category code used will be that applicable to the interest type and whether it is standard interest or a correction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 category code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOV.MRG.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Government Margin charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HI.DR.TAXTRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Customer Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Highest Debit charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field range HI.DR.TAX.RATE to HI.DR.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of a period during which the Account has been in debit and debit interest has been calculated.  Associated fields show the number of days of the calculation, the applicable rate and the balance.  If either the rate or the balance change, a further set of associated fields will be generated. </p>
            <p>  Any change to the interest calculation will cause the generation of a new set of multivalue field range DR.INT.DATE to DR.INT.AMT.  These changes include: </p>
            <p>                  Change to Balance                 Interest Rate                 Interest Day Basis                 Highest/Daily/Average Balance </p>
            <p>  Where different interest rates are applicable to 'Bands' of the balance, separate sets of field range DR.INT.DATE to DR.INT.AMT are generated for each Band of the Balance on which interest is calculated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  9 date characters  -  DD MMM YYYY.  Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.DATE to DR.INT.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted interest amount after the correction process. This field will be updated only when the defered tax amount is posted. </p>
            <p> The information in this field will be updated based on the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. Once updated, this information will be cleared from the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. </p>
            <p> If this field contains the value then it indicates that the previous period correction tax amount is posted on the current period. (this period) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HI.DR.TAXCATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code which determines the Internal Account to be updated with Tax Provision entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the Highest Debit charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with field range HI.DR.TAX.RATE to HI.DR.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOV.MRG.TRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Government Margin charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNADJ.TOTAL.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The calculated total interest amount, this will differ from the total interest that is posted when a manual interest adjustment has been made</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DR.FREE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the free amount by which the calculated Highest Debit charge is reduced. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where a Highest Debit charge is to be made on an Account, this code specifies the HIGHEST.DEBIT record containing details of the calculation and processing of the Highest Debit charge. </p>
            <p>  The Highest Debit charge details used are those applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STMT.TRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Interest Statement charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADDON.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Debit Interest Add-on charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.TAXTRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Customer Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the debit interest amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field range DR.INT.TAX.RATE to DR.INT.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.POST.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether ICA interest is actually posted to this account, or is just calculated for information purposes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.SUB.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.SUB.INT</p>
            <p>  The amount of ICA interest posted to this account if this account is a sub account of the account defined in ICA.MAIN.ACCT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No Input multi valued field associated with ICA.MAIN.ACCT.</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STMT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where an Interest Statement charge is to be made on an Account, this code specifies the INTEREST.STATEMENT record containing details of the calculation and processing of Interest Statement charge. </p>
            <p>  The Interest Statement charge details used are those applicable on the Capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFERRED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the deferred application date of the debit interest in case pending debit interest processing was being performed on this account. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GV.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Interest Rate used to calculate the Government Margin charge amount shown in corresponding field GOV.MARGIN.AMT.  Although shown as a multivalue field, the rate will not change during an application period. </p>
            <p>  The rate used is the rate applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format.  Multivalue field associated with field range GOV.MARGIN.DATE to GOV.MARGIN.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.NETTING.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will be updated if CR interest is netted with corresponding DR interest. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HI.DR.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of Tax calculated on the Highest Debit charge, at the rate shown in corresponding field HI.DR.TAX.RATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range HI.DR.TAX.RATE to HI.DR.TAXTRSCR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GV.VAL.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Debit balance on which the Government Margin charge, shown in corresponding field GOV.MARGIN.AMT, has been calculated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range GOV.MARGIN.DATE to GOV.MARGIN.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the TAX record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to debit interest. </p>
            <p>  The tax details used are those applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGH.DR.MIN.MAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>After calculating the gross Highest Debit charge and subtracting the Free Amount, comparison is made with Minimum and Maximum charge amounts from the Highest Debit record.  If either the Minimum charge or the Maximum charge is substituted for the calculated charge, 'MINIMUM' or 'MAXIMUM' is recorded in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  'MINIMUM', 'MAXIMUM' or nothing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANUAL.ADJ.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The manual accrual adjustment amount for the period.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRAND.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total amount to be debited to customer's account including debit interest, any interest related charges and tax (if applicable). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the calculated Highest Debit Charge after Minimum or Maximum adjustment if appropriate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the Annual Payment Rate (or the Taux Effectif Global in France). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-10 type R (standard rate format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.DIST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.DIST.TYPE</p>
            <p>  Indicates the ICA interest distribution method for the ICA group with the account defined in ICA.MAIN.ACCT as the leader.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field</p>
            <p>  Can be set to either INTEREST or RATIO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total amount of Tax on Interest and all Charges (if applicable). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INT.STMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for interest statement charge.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.GOV.MAR.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deferred amount posted for government margin charge Tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GV.NO.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for which the Government Margin amount shown in corresponding field GOV.MARGIN.AMT has been calculated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-3 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with field range GOV.MARGIN.DATE to GOV.MARGIN.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ACCOUNT on which interest has been calculated (or the main account of a combined group, see details),the date up to which it has been calculated and the correction number. </p>
            <p>  When the balances of several ACCOUNTS are to be consolidated for Interest purposes the main ACCOUNT number has to be entered in the INTEREST.COMP.ACCT Field in the ACCOUNT records of each of the 'sub' accounts. </p>
            <p>  The Correction Number in the ID of this record corresponds to the CORRECTION.NUMBER of the new STMT.ACCT.DR2 record and is always 1 greater than the LAST.CORRECTION.NO of this record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  a.   2-14 numeric character Account Number. b.   '-'      Prime Sites '.' c.   1-9 date characters. (Stored in format YYYYMMDD, displayed as      DD MMM YYYY, but may be input in any of T24 date formats.) d.   '-' e.   3 numeric characters Correction Number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDON.MIN.MAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>After calculating the gross Debit Interest Add-on charge and subtracting the Free Amount, comparison is made with Minimum and Maximum charge amounts from the Debit Interest Addon record.  If either the Minimum charge or the Maximum charge is substituted for the calculated charge, 'MINIMUM' or 'MAXIMUM' is recorded in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  'MINIMUM', 'MAXIMUM' or nothing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDON.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of Tax calculated on the Debit Interest Add-on charge, at the rate shown in corresponding field INT.ADDON.TRSDR. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Standard amount format.  Multivalue field associated with field range INT.ADDON.TRSDR to ADDON.TAX.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDON.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the TAX record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to the Debit Interest Add-on charge. </p>
            <p>  The tax details used are those applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum waive amount in the currency of the account if the waive currency is different to the currency of the account</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WIAVE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate used for the conversion of minimum waive amount in account currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>WAIVE.RATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
