<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>GENERAL.CHARGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used to specify for groups of Accounts which charges are to be levied and what balance overrides are allowed.  The GENERAL.CHARGE record applicable to a particular Account is specified in the relevant Group or Account Debit Interest Record. </p>
            <p>Charges fall into 2 types, those that are levied at the same time as debit interest is applied (Interest Related Charges) and those which are considered to be fees for maintenance of an Account (Ledger Fee Charges). </p>
            <p>If the Account has maintained a higher balance than that specified, calculated charges can be waived.  Separate sets of balance level details are specified for Interest Related Charges and for Ledger Fee Charges. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Interest Related Charges </p>
            <p>Interest Related Charges include DEBIT.INT.ADDON, GOVERNMENT.MARGIN, HIGHEST.DEBIT Charge and INTEREST.STATEMENT Charge.  DEBIT.INT.ADDON, GOVERNMENT.MARGIN and HIGHEST.DEBIT are charged when debit one interest is applied.  Either DEBIT.INT.ADDON or HIGHEST.DEBIT may be charged but not both.  INTEREST.STATEMENT Charge is levied each time debit one interest is applied. </p>
            <p>In each case the rates applicable are those ruling on the date of debit one interest capitalisation. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Ledger Fee Charges </p>
            <p>Ledger Fee Charges may be applied monthly, quarterly or half yearly as specified in the Company record, always at the end of a calendar month. </p>
            <p>The charges can be based on Balance Requirement, Number of Credits, Number of Debits, Turnover of Credits, Turnover of Debits and non immediate Transaction charges depending on the Transaction Codes.  Either the number of credits and debits or the turnover figures can be charged, but not both.  It is possible to combine all these charges into one charge.  A notional amount of credit interest may be calculated and deducted from the charge amount. </p>
            <p>In each case the charges effective on the date of the charges capitalisation are applicable for the whold of the capitalisation period. </p>
            <p>A waive marker may be set in Account records to indicate that charges should be calculated but not applied. </p>
            <p>No Ledger Fee Charges are calculated on balances and activity in the month in which an Account is opened or closed, (unless the Account Closure date is the last day of the month). </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the required Balance (in local currency equivalent) for waiving charges for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE.  The required Balance may be the Minimum or Average Balance during the application period, depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE. </p>
            <p>Details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts, in specific Currencies may be specified in the multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>The Average or Minimum balance for the application period is calculated (depending on  the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE) and converted to local currency equivalent.  If the result is not less than the DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BALl all charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE are waived. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input if OFFSET.BAL.TYPE is input, otherwise not allowed.  Default is no waiver.) The number of decimals allowed depends on local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TURNOVER.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge depending on the total value of chargeable credit entries. </p>
            <p>The charge is calculated as a percentage of the total value of chargeable entries. </p>
            <p>If 'Y' is specified in COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT the total value of chargeable debit and credit entries is charged using the details in the TURNOVER.CREDIT record. </p>
            <p>An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in TURNOVER CHARGE field.  Reversal entries are subtracted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.  (Optional input.  Not allowed if NUMBER.OF.CREDIT is input. Default is no charge).  There must be a record in the TURNOVER.CREDIT table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.AV.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the required Balance for waiving charges for Accounts in the Currency specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY.  The required Balance may be the Minimum or Average Balance during the application period, depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE. </p>
            <p>The multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used to specify details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies. </p>
            <p>Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>The Average or Minimum balance for the application period is calculated (depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE).  If the result is not less than the MIN.AV.BAL all charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT,  TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE are waived. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  (Optional input if OFFSET.BAL.TYPE is input, otherwise not allowed.  Default is no waiver.)  The number of decimals allowed depends on the currency specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMBINED.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Tax record containing details of Tax applicable to the combined Charge. </p>
            <p>Note: If combined charges are specified (CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL = 'COM'), any Tax codes in the tables relating to the charges in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT are ignored. Only the Tax Code specified in this field is applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric character Tax code. (Optional input if CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL is 'COM', otherwise not allowed.) There must be an existing record for this code on the TAX table (Ref: General Tables), with effective date less than or equal to the effective date of this record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TURNOVER.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge depending on the total value of chargeable debit entries. </p>
            <p>The charge is calculated as a percentage of the total value of chargeable entries. </p>
            <p>If 'Y' is specified in COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT the total value of chargeable debit and credit entries is charged using the details in the TURNOVER.CREDIT record. </p>
            <p>An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in the TURNOVER.CHARGE field.  Reversal entries are subtracted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.  (Optional input if COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT is 'NO' and no input in NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, otherwise not allowed).  There must be a record in the TURNOVER.DEBIT table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for processing Transaction Code Charges accumulated under one charge. </p>
            <p>The TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables) specifies the TRANSACTION.CHARGE record applicable to each Transaction code. </p>
            <p>If there is an entry in COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE, the charges are accumulated into one charge amount and the Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts in the record specified in COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE are used.  Otherwise the charges for each Transaction code are processed separately using Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts in the individual Transaction Charge records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters Transaction Charge code. (Optional input if TRANS.CODE.CHARGE, is 'Y', otherwise not allowed.  If no input, Transaction code charges are processed individually.) There must be a record in the TRANSACTION.CHARGE table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is before than or equal to the date specified in Field 0 (Record ID).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CHRG.NEG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies that all charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE should be waived if the Account has a negative Balance at any time during the calculation period. </p>
            <p>If this field contains Y, all charges specified in the fields listed above are waived if the Balance is negative at any time during the calculation period (even if it is only negative for one day). </p>
            <p>If CALCU STEP PERIOD specifies that charges are calculated in monthly steps (M), the Balances are checked for each month separately and charges waived for any month in which the Balance is ever negative. </p>
            <p>If CALCU STEP PERIOD specifies that charges are calculated in one step for the whole period (P) as specified in the Company record, all charges are waived if the Balance is negative at any time during the whole period. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y', 'N' or 'NO'.  (Optional input.  Default is 'NO').</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.CHARGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the General Charge code by which charges and overrides applicable to a group of Accounts may be identified, and the date from which they apply. </p>
            <p>For a new record, the date may not be less than today. </p>
            <p>For details of interest related charges, the General Charge record which is in effect on the date of the charges capitalisation is applicable for the whole of the capitalisation period. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1)  1-4 numeric characters Charge Code (Mandatory input) (2)  '-' (Mandatory if Date is input, otherwise not allowed). Prime Sites '.' (3)  1-9 characters Date. (Optional input.  Default is today's date).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOVERNMENT.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating Government Margin charges. </p>
            <p>Government Margin is a supplementary flat percentage charge on debit balances calculated by the system on Debit Interest Capitalisation date and collected on behalf of the Government. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-2 numeric characters. (Optional input.  Default is no charge.) There must be a record in the GOVERNMENT.MARGIN table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Account entries generated for combined Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>   
            <p>(Mandatory input if CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL is 'COM', otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>It must be a valid code on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>The Debit Credit Indicator in the Transaction record must be 'DEBIT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.INT.ADDON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating Debit Interest Addon charges. </p>
            <p>Debit Interest Addon is a supplementary flat percentage charge which is applied to the overdraft interest amount calculated by the System on Capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>Note:      Debit Interest Addon is not applicable to the 2nd type            of Debit Interest defined in fields prefixed 'DR2' in            Group and Account Debit Interest records. </p>
            <p>This charge is similar to HIGHEST.DEBIT. They cannot both be specified for the same Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-2 numeric characters (Optional input.  Not allowed if HIGHEST.DEBIT is input. Default is no charge.) There must be a record in the DEBIT.INT.ADDON table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether charges for debit and credit entries specified in NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT and TURNOVER.DEBIT should be calculated separately or combined. </p>
            <p>If 'NO' is specified, debit and credit charges are calculated separately, otherwise a combined charge is calculated using the credit charge details specified in NUMBER.OF.CREDIT or TURNOVER.CREDIT. </p>
            <p>An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in the TURNOVER.CHARGE field.  Reversal entries are subtracted. </p>
            <p>If there is any input in NUMBER.OF.DEBIT or TURNOVER.DEBIT, 'NO' must be specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y', 'N' or 'NO'. (Mandatory input if any input in NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT or TURNOVER.DEBIT otherwise not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CHARGE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency of the Balance in the associated INT.CHARGE.BAL. For Accounts in Currencies with no input in this field, the Default Balance in local currency, INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL is used. </p>
            <p>INT.CHARGE.CCY and INT.CHARGE.BAL are used to define the required Balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges on Accounts in specific Currencies.  For any Accounts in Currencies not specified in this field, the Default (Local Currency Equivalent) Balance specified in INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL is used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1)  3 type SSS (SWIFT) characters Currency Code or     (2)  1-3 numeric characters (will be converted to Currency code). Multivalue field associated with INT.CHARGE.BAL. (Optional input). It must be a valid code on the CURRENCY table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for combined Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> (Mandatory input if CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL is 'COM', otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>It must be a valid code on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>The Debit Credit Indicator in the Transaction record must be 'CREDIT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.OF.FCY.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the charges defined in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE apply to all Accounts, or only to Accounts in local currency. </p>
            <p>'Y' means the charges apply to all Currencies.  'N' or 'NO' means they apply only to local currency Accounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y', 'N' or 'NO'. (Mandatory input if any input in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT or STATEMENT.CHARGE, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating Highest Debit charges. </p>
            <p>Highest Debit is a flat percentage charge calculated on the Highest Debit balance during each Capitalisation period. </p>
            <p>This charge is similar to DEBIT.INTEREST.ADDON. They cannot both be specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-2 numeric characters. (Optional input.  Not allowed if DEBIT.INTEREST.ADDON is input. Default is no charge.) There must be a record in the HIGHEST.DEBIT table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Can accept the following types:</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>Key</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Days/Denominator</strong>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>A</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>B</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>C</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>D</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>E</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>F</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>For illustrations of all supported </p>
            <p>INTEREST.BASIS</p> types see: <a href="INTEREST.BASIS_data.htm">INTEREST.BASIS</a><p>Specifies the Day Basis for calculating notional credit interest for offsetting charges, for Accounts in the Currency specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY. </p><p>The multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE is used to specify details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies. </p><p>Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p><p>If PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is defined, the Average or Minimum Balance for the application period is determined (depending on OFFSET.BAL.TYPE) and the notional credit interest is calculated using the PERCT.FOR.OFFSET as the rate and the Day Basis defined in this field. </p><p>If A (360/360) or F (360/360) is specified each month will be treated as having 30 days. In months with 31 days, the 30th is ignored, and in February the last day is counted as 3 days, or 2 in a leap year. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Valid input is A, B, C, D, E, or F.</p><p>(Mandatory input if PERCT.FOR.OFFSET and corresponding         OFFSET.CURRENCY are input, otherwise not allowed).</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OF.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge per chargeable debit entry. </p>
            <p>If 'Y' is specified in COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT, the numbers of debit and credit entries are combined and one charge is calculated using the details in the NUMBER.OF.CREDIT record. </p>
            <p>An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in the TURNOVER.CHARGE field.  Reversal entries are subtracted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.  (Optional input if COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT is 'NO', otherwise no input allowed).  There must be a record in the NUMBER.OF.DEBIT table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DEBIT.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p><strong>Identifies the record containing details for calculating the Highest Debit charge to be applied on the charge frequency. </strong>
            </p>
            <p>Highest Debit is a flat percentage charge that is calculated based on the Highest Debit balance on the account. The balance used depends on the way the COMPANY record has specified the CALCULATION.METHOD. If this field has been set up with monthly calculation, then the balance of each month is used for calculating the charge and so on. </p>
            <p>This is an optional field. If entered the field must point to a valid HIGHEST.DEBIT record.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOW.AMT.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the smallest amount of charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE, which will be booked, for Accounts in the Currency specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY.  If calculated charges are less than this amount they will be waived. </p>
            <p>The multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used to specify details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies. </p>
            <p>Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies for which there is no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>Depending on CHARGE CODE LEVEL, individual or combined charge amounts calculated.  If the result is less than the amount specified in this field, the charge is waived. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  (Optional input if corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY is input. Default is no waiver.)  The number of decimals allowed depends on the Currency specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFSET.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency of Accounts for which the details in MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for waiving charges and calculating offsets. </p>
            <p>The multivalue group of associated Fields MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used to specify details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies. </p>
            <p>For Accounts in Currencies with no details specified in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE, the default values (in local currency equivalent) specified in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters Currency Code or 1-3 numeric characters Numeric Currency Code.  (Optional input)  It must be a valid code on the CURRENCY table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CHARGE.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the required Balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges for Accounts in the Currency specified in the associated INT.CHARGE.CCY. </p>
            <p>INT.CHARGE.BAL and INT.CHARGE.CCY are used to define the required Balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges in specific Currencies.  The Default Balance (in local currency) in INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL is used if there are no details in INT.CHARGE.BAL and INT.CHARGE.CCY for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>Depending on INT.CHRG.BAL.TYPE, the Minimum or Average balance for the interest Capitalisation period is calculated.  If this is not less than the required Balance, Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges are waived. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Multivalue field associated with INT.CHARGE.CCY. (Mandatory input if  INT.CHARGE.CCY is input, otherwise not allowed). The number of decimals allowed depends on the Currency in the associated INT.CHARGE.CCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the smallest amount (in local currency equivalent) which will be booked for charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE.  If calculated charges are less than this amount they will be waived.  The information in this field is only used when processing Accounts in Currencies for which no defaults are specified in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>Details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies may be specified in the multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies for which there is no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>Depending on CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL, individual or combined charge amounts are converted to local currency equivalent. If the result is less than the amount specified in this field, the charge is waived. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input.  Default is no waiver.) The number of decimals allowed depends on local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge for the issue of account statements. </p>
            <p>Specifies which ACCT.STATEMENT.CHARGE record is to be used to determinne the charges for the issuing of account statements. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.  Optional input.  There must be a record in the ACCT.STATEMENT.CHARGE table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CHRG.BAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in conjunction with Fields INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL, INT.CHARGE.CCY and INT.CHARGE.BAL to specify a balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement Charges.  This field specifies whether a Minimum or Average balance is required. </p>
            <p>Depending on this field, the Minimum or Average balance for the interest Capitalisation period is calculated.  If this is not less than the appropriate balance specified in Fields  INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL, INT.CHARGE.CCY and INT.CHARGE.BAL then any DEBIT.INTEREST ADDON, HIGHEST.DEBIT or INTEREST.STATEMENT charge is waived. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'MINIMUM' or 'AVERAGE' or any abbreviation thereof. (Optional input, if any input in DEBIT.INT.ADDON, GOVERNMENT.MARGIN, HIGHEST.DEBIT or INTEREST.STATEMENT.  Otherwise not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Can accept the following types:</p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>Key</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Days/Denominator</strong>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>A</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>B</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>C</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>D</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>E</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>F</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>For illustrations of all supported </p>
            <p>INTEREST.BASIS</p> types see: <a href="INTEREST.BASIS_data.htm">INTEREST.BASIS</a><p>Specifies the Day Basis for calculating notional credit interest for offsetting charges of Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p><p>Details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies may be specified in the multivalue group of associated OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p><p>Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p><p>If PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is defined, the Average or Minimum Balance for the application period is determined (depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE) and the notional credit interest is calculated using the PERCT.FOR.OFFSET as the rate and the Day Basis defined in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Valid input is A, B, C, D, E, or F.</p><p>(Mandatory input if PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is input, otherwise         not allowed).</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OF.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge per chargeable credit entry. </p>
            <p>If 'Y' is specified in COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT), the number of debit and credit entries are combined and one charge is calculated using the details in the Number of Credit record specified. </p>
            <p>An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in TURNOVER.CHARGE.  Reversal entries are subtracted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.  (Optional input.  Default is no charge).  There must be a record in the NUMBER.OF.CREDIT table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the type of Accounts for which the charges and overrides specified are intended. </p>
            <p>The Description may be entered in each of the Languages defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: General Tables). It will be displayed in the Language specified in the User record of the person using the System. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the balance (in local currency equivalent) required before offset interest is calculated for Accounts in Currencies with no details in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>Details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies may be specified in the multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>The Average or Minimum Balance for the application period is determined (depending on OFFSET.BAL.TYPE) and converted to local currency. If the result is less than the value specified in this field, no offsetting credit interest is calculated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input if PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is defined, otherwise not allowed.) The number of decimals allowed depends on local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFSET.BAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether Average or Minimum balance should be used for calculating notional credit interest for offsetting against charges or for determining the required balance for waiving charges. </p>
            <p>The Average or Minimum balance during the application period is used to determine whether charges should be waived and whether notional credit interest should be calculated to offset charges.  If notional credit interest is calculated, the Average or Minimum balance is used in the calculation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'AVERAGE' or 'MINIMUM' or any abbreviation thereof.  (Mandatory input if PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is input, otherwise optional).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether charges (BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE) should be added together into one total before checking against balances, smallest charge etc. or whether each charge should be checked and applied individually. </p>
            <p>If 'IND' is specified, the details specified in each of the tables relating to the charges listed above are used to calculate the charges, make adjustments for Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts, calcualte tax where applicable and generate separate transactions for each charge. </p>
            <p>If 'COM' is specified, the details defined in each of the tables are used to calculate the amount of each charge, but the results are added together to generate one transaction for the total charge, using details in CATEGORY, TR.CODE.CR, TR.CODE.DR and COMBINED.TAX.CODE to determine Transaction Codes and profit and loss Category and to Calculate Tax on the total charge if appropriate. </p>
            <p>Offset amounts, minimum charge, etc. are applied to each transaction generated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'COM', 'IND' or an abbreviation thereof. (Optional input if there is input in any of BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT or STATEMENT.CHARGE, otherwise not allowed.  Default is 'IND'.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the local currency equivalent of the balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges for Accounts in Currencies with no Balance specified in Fields INT.CHARGE.CCY and INT.CHARGE.BAL. </p>
            <p>Depending on Field INT.CHRG.BAL.TYPE, the Minimum or Average balance for the interest Capitalisation period is calculated.  If there is an entry in Field INT.CHARGE.CCY for the Currency of the Account, the result is compared with the balance in the corresponding INT.CHARGE.BAL.  Otherwise, the result is converted to local currency and compared with the Default Balance in this field.  If it is not less, any Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit or Interest statement charge is waived. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. [Optional input.  Not allowed unless INT.CHRG.BAL. TYPE is specified.  Default is no waiver.] The number of decimals allowed depends on local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether charges per entry should be calculated using the charge records applicable to each Transaction code. </p>
            <p>The TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables) specifies the TRANSACTION.CHARGE record applicable to each Transaction code.  No charge is calculated unless the IMMEDIATE.CHARGE field on the Transaction record is 'NO'. </p>
            <p>If there is an entry in COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE, the charges are accumulated into one charge amount and the Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts in the record specified in COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE are used.  Otherwise the charges for each Transaction Code are processed separately using the Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts in the individual Transaction Charge records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y', 'N' or 'NO'.  (Optional input.  Default is 'NO'.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCT.FOR.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a rate for calculating notional credit interest for offsetting against Charges specified BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>Notional credit interest for offsetting charges is calculated using the credit balances during the application period, the balance type (Average or Minimum) specified in OFFSET.BAL.TYPE and the Percentage rate specified in PERCT.FOR.OFFSET. </p>
            <p>The Day Basis (360/360, 366/365 etc.) and Minimum Balance for calculating offset can be defined for specific Currencies in the multivalue associated group of Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.OFFSET and LOW.AMT.CHARGE.  For Accounts in Currencies with no details in these fields, the DEFAULT DAY BASIS and DEF BAL NO OFFSET are used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  (Optional input.  Not allowed unless CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL is 'COM', nor if TRANS.CODE.CHARGE is 'Y' and COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE is not defined. Default is no offset).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.STATEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating Interest Statement charges. </p>
            <p>Some customers require a detailed Interest Statement each time interest is applied.  The Interest Statement charge is a fixed amount which may be applied each time debit interest is applied. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-2 numeric characters.  (Optional input.  Default is no charge.)  There must be a record in the INTEREST.STATEMENT table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.NO.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the balance required for calculating notional credit interest for offsetting against charges, for Accounts in the Currency specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>The multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.OFFSET and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used to specify details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies. </p>
            <p>Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p>The Average or Minimum Balance for the application period is determined (depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE).  If the result is less than the value specified in this field, no offsetting credit interest is calculated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input if PERCT.FOR.OFFSET and corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY are input, otherwise not allowed.) The number of decimals allowed depends on the currency defined in the corresponding  OFFSET.CURRENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.REQUIREMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a maintenance charge depending on the balance in the Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters (Optional input.  Default is no Balance Requirement charge). There must be a record in the BALANCE.REQUIREMENT table with a key consisting of this code and an effective date which is less than or equal to the date specified in Field 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCUL.STEP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether charges in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT, HIGHEST.DEBIT.CHG and STATEMENT.CHARGE should be calculated once to cover the full charge period, as specified in the Company record, or in monthly steps. </p>
            <p>If 'MONTHLY' is specified, Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts apply to charges calculated for each month, otherwise the Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts are only applied to the total charges for the period. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'MONTHLY', 'PERIOD' or any abbreviation thereof.         (Mandatory input if any input in BAL.REQUIREMENT,         NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT,         TURNOVER.DEBIT, HIGHEST.DEBIT.CHG or STATEMENT.CHARGE.         Otherwise not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for combined Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric character Category code. (Mandatory input if CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL is 'COM', otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>It must be a valid code on the CATEGORY table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>System Indicator in Category record must be 'PL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

