<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>GOVERNMENT.MARGIN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Government Margin is a supplementary flat percentage charge calculated on overdraft balances by the system on capitalisation date and collected on behalf of the Government. </p>
            <p>The same Percentage charge is applicable for all Currencies.  However, it is possible to specify Minimum and Maximum Amounts for specific Currencies as well as local currency equivalent amounts which apply to all other Currencies. </p>
            <p>The General Charge table specifies whether or not this charge is applicable to associated groups of Accounts. </p>
            <p>If there are no overdraft balances during the Capitalisation period, no Government Margin charge is made. </p>
            <p>The Government Margin rate ruling on the date of the debit interest capitalisation is applicable for the whole Capitalisation period. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SEQUENCE.YEAR.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Government Margin code and effective date which form a key to which General Charge records may be linked. </p>
            <p>The date may be entered as: </p>
            <p>           1)   YYYY-MM  year-month            2)   YYYYMM   yearmonth            3)   MM-YY    month-year            4)   MMYY     monthyear            5)   MM       month (current year assumed) </p>
            <p>           The month may be 01-12 or 1-12. </p>
            <p>It is always displayed formatted YYYY-MM.  For new input the date may not be earlier than today. </p>
            <p>The Government Margin record which is in effect on the date of the debit interest Capitalisation is applicable for the whole capitalisation period. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)    1-2 numeric characters (Mandatory input).  2)    '-' (Mandatory input if date is input, otherwise no input).       Prime Site '.'  3)    1-7 date characters, year and month  (Optional input, default is current year and month).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Government Margin Charge, and can be used for reporting. </p>
            <p>The Description may be entered in each of the Languages defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: General Tables). </p>
            <p>It will be displayed in the Language specified in the User Record of the person using the System. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate to be charged on debit balances as the Government Margin. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 type R (standard rate format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Not more than 6 integers may be entered.</p>
            <p>Not more than 9 decimals may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency where Minimum and Maximum Government Margin charges apply. </p>
            <p>This multivalue field is used to record all Currencies for which specific Minimum and Maximum Government Margin charges apply.  Where the Minimum and Maximum charges are based on the Currency equivalent of the local value charges, only Fields 6 and 7 should be completed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 SWIFT character or 3 numeric character currency code. Multivalue field associated with Fields 9 and 10. (Mandatory input if any input in corresponding Fields 9 or 10 otherwise not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Maximum Amount of Government Margin charge, for Accounts in the Currency specified by associated CURRENCY field. </p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT are used to define Amounts for adjusting Government Margin Charges in specific Currencies.  The Default Amounts specified in fields DEFAULT.MIN.AMT to DEFAULT.MAX.AMT are used if there is no entry in CURRENCY field for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>If the adjusted charge is greater than the Maximum Amount, the Maximum Amount is used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters, plus a decimal point.  (Optional input only allowed if CURRENCY field is input.)  The amount entered must have the correct number of decimal places for the Currency entered in CURRENCY field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Minimum Amount of Government Margin charge, for accounts in the Currency specified in associated CURRENCY field. </p>
            <p>Fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT are used to define Amounts for adjusting Government Margin Charges in specific Currencies.  The Default Amounts specified in fields DEFAULT.MIN.AMT to DEFAULT.MAX.AMT are used if there is no entry in CURRENCY field for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>If the adjusted charge is less than the Minimum Amount, the Minimum Amount is used.  Otherwise the Maximum Amount is checked. </p>
            <p>Note : The minimum charge is not applied if there are no debit balances. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters, plus a decimal point.  (Optional input only allowed if corresponding CURRENCY field is input.)  The amount entered must have the correct number of decimal places for the currency entered into CURRENCY field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Account entries generated for Government Margin Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>It must be a valid code on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>The Debit Credit Indicator in the TRANSACTION table record must be 'DEBIT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate to be charged on debit balances as the Government Margin. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 type R (standard rate format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Not more than 6 integers may be entered.</p>
            <p>Not more than 9 decimals may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Government Margin Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>It must be a valid code on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Charges).</p>
            <p>The Debit Credit Indicator in the TRANSACTION table record must be 'CREDIT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated as a result of making a Government Margin charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric character Category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>It must be a valid code on the CATEGORY table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>System Indicator in Category record must be 'PL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency where Minimum and Maximum Government Margin charges apply. </p>
            <p>This multivalue field is used to record all Currencies for which specific Minimum and Maximum Government Margin charges apply.  Where the Minimum and Maximum charges are based on the Currency equivalent of the local value charges, only Fields 6 and 7 should be completed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 SWIFT character or 3 numeric character currency code. Multivalue field associated with Fields 9 and 10. (Mandatory input if any input in corresponding Fields 9 or 10 otherwise not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Maximum Amount of charge, in local currency equivalent, for all accounts in Currencies not entered in multivalue field CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>Amounts for adjusting Government Margin Charges in specific Currencies can be specified in the multivalue associated group of fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT.  The Default Amounts specified in fields DEFAULT.MIN.AMT to DEFAULT.MAX.AMT are used if there is no entry in CURRENCY field for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>The calculated amount is converted to local currency equivalent before making adjustments specified in fields DEFAULT.MIN.AMT and DEFAULT.MAX.AMT. </p>
            <p>If the calculated local currency charge is greater than the Default Maximum Amount, the Default Maximum Amount is used.  The result is converted to the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  (Optional input)  The number of decimals may not exceed the number for local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Minimum Amount of charge, in local currency equivalent, for all Accounts in Currencies not entered in multivalue field CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>Amounts for adjusting Government Margin Charges in specific Currencies can be specified in the multivalue associated group of fields CURRENCY to MAXIMUM.AMOUNT.  The Default Amounts specified in fields DEFAULT.MIN.AMT to DEFAULT.MAX.AMT are used if there is no entry in field CURRENCY for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>The calculated amount is converted to local currency before making adjustments specified in fields DEFAULT.MIN.AMT and DEFAULT.MAX.AMT. </p>
            <p>If the calculated local currency charge is less than the Default Minimum Amount, the Default Minimum Amount is used.  Otherwise the Default Maximum Amount is checked.  The result is converted to the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  (Optional input)  The number of decimals may not exceed the number for local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

