<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>GROUP.ACCRUAL.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a parameter file holding the options for the bulk accrual of Accounts.</p>
            <p>This is used to reduce the number of accrual accounting entries, with entries being posted at a consolidated level, application, currency market, currency, department account officer and category.</p>
            <p>If an account category is defined on this application then it will not be possible to define that account category for normal interest accruals, as defined on ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL.</p>
            <p>It is also possible to consolidate normal account accrual entries using the AC.CONSOLIDATE.COND application.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be for valid T24 applications (i.e. AC)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>All accruals defined for this category will be recalculated during the next close of business.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The category should already be defined for accrual in the PRODUCT.CATEG field.</p>
            <p>Cannot be set if REBUILD.ALL is set to YES</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category code of the account to be subject to group accrual.</p>
            <p>Care needs to be taken, if a category is defined on this application it will be ignored for normal accrual processing as defined on ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL, to avoid duplication of accrual.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid Category type</p>
            <p>In range 1000 - 9999</p>
            <p>No duplicate allowed</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for the transaction code used for the group accruals</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid Transaction Code in the system</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.ALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will indicate that all the group accruals will be re calculated during the next close of business</p>
            <p />
            <p>YES indicates that all categories defined will be recaculated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.ALL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines which types of accounts or contracts are subject to group accrual</p>
            <p>If an account category is defined for group accrual then it will be ignored for normal accrual processing set up using ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p>Possible values are:</p>
            <p>BOTH - local and Foreign accounts</p>
            <p>LOCAL - Local accounts</p>
            <p>FOREIGN - Foreign accounts</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.FQU</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the frequency for the accrual processing.</p>
            <p>Frequency can be by Business days, weekly, or monthly</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Frequency field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Only one sub-value is allowed if there is no interest         type</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Possible values are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Application to be subject to group accrual</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid T24 application ID</p>
            <p>AC for Account is the only valid value at this time</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the interest type for the associated ACCRUAL.FQU.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p>Possible values are:</p>
            <p>ALL - All Interest types</p>
            <p>CH - charges</p>
            <p>DR - Debit Interest</p>
            <p>DR2 Debit 2 Interest</p>
            <p>CR - Credit Interest</p>
            <p>CR2 - Credit2 Interest</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

