<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>IC.COB.MAIN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This record provides information regarding which accounts are due to be processed during the COB period. The key of the record will be the start date of the COB.  The level of detail in this record will increase depending on the COB processing required.</p>
            <p>For example if all customer accounts are set for daily accrual then ALL.ACCOUNTS will be set to YES.</p>
            <p>If only specific categories of account are set for processing then only the relevant categories of account will be set. </p>
            <p>IC.COB.DETAIL will provide more information regarding the actual processing required and there will be 1 record for each day of the COB EOD and SOD period.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXCL.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The account condition groups which are excluded from processing.</p>
            <p>For example all accounts are to be subject to normal accrual processing except these.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COB.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The record @ID indicates the start date of the COB processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.GTYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of account due for accrual by condition group code as defined on ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL:</p>
            <p>BOTH = both local and foreign</p>
            <p>LOCAL = local currency accounts only</p>
            <p>FGN = foreign currency accounts only</p>
            <p>Multi valued field associated with ACCR.GROUP</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the account condition groups due for some form of COB processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the account condition groups by currency due for some form of COB processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALL.ACCOUNTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES indicates that some sort of processing is due for all accounts, for example all accounts due for charge calculation or month end accrual</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Individual accounts set for processing in either REBUILD.TRANS.CHG, IC.CAPITALIS.CORR or ACCT.INTERIM.CAP.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the account categories which are due for accrual over the EOD period.</p>
            <p>Multi valued field associated with ACCR.CTYP</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.CTYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of account due for accrual by category code as defined on ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL:</p>
            <p>BOTH = both local and foreign</p>
            <p>LOCAL = local currency accounts only</p>
            <p>FGN = foreign currency accounts only</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Multi valued field associated with ACCR.CATEG</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the account condition groups due for accrual over the EOD period.</p>
            <p>Multi valued field associated with ACCR.GTYP</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORR.AT.CAP.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi valued field to indicate which account condition groups are set for correctinos to be processed at the capialisation date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The account categories which are excluded from processing.</p>
            <p>For example all accounts are to be subject to normal accrual processing except these categories.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.ACCR.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The account categories which are due for group accrual processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUE.ALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of account due for accrual when all accounts are due for accrual as defined on ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL:</p>
            <p>BOTH = both local and foreign</p>
            <p>LOCAL = local currency accounts only</p>
            <p>FGN = foreign currency accounts only</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.ACCR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of account due for group accrual processing:</p>
            <p>BOTH = both local and foreign</p>
            <p>LOCAL = local currency accounts only</p>
            <p>FGN = foreign currency accounts only</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

