<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>IC.COB.DETAIL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Holds details of accounts required during the EOD or SOD processing period</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TXN.CHG.BUILD</field>
<desc>
            <p>"SYSTEM", the key for REBUILD.TRAN.CHARGES, if transaction charge rebuild is set up for the EOD processing</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key (DATE) for TABLE.CAPITALIS.CORR if set up for this processing date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.INT.GRPCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION keys where premium interest processing is required on this COB date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that charges are to be capitalised or accrued if INCLUDE.CHARGES is set to Y on ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IC.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates which IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT's are due to be capitalised for the COB date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.INT.PREMIUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the SAVINGS.PREMIUM records realted to premium processing on this COB date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.INTERIM.CAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key (DATE) for ACCT.INTERIM.CAP is set up for this processing date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.INTERIM.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Interim charge capitalisation due on this date, as set up on ACCT.INTERIM.CHG</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The interest type due for capitlaisation on this processing date</p>
            <p>Format 6 characters</p>
            <p>__ 1 charges due for capitalisation or not</p>
            <p>__ 2 to 5 indicates interest capitalised  or not</p>
            <p>__ 6 set to S to indicate capitalisation processing</p>
            <p>C1 =  charges Y or N</p>
            <p>C2 = Credit 1 interest due for Cap Y or N</p>
            <p>C3 = Credit 2 interest due for Cap Y or N</p>
            <p>C4 = Debit 1 interest due for Cap Y or N</p>
            <p>C5 = Debit 2 interest due for Cap Y or N</p>
            <p>C6 = S (Statement) capitalisation due</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.GROUPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Groups due for capitalisation on this date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COB.PROCESS.DATES</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Key)</p>
            <p>Current working day if EOD, first day of SOD period if SOD followed by "." And the actual processing date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IC.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>IC.CHARGE records set for processing  on this date. Updated by separate development, possibly subject to change.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

