<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p> This is a LIVE file. System will update this file whenever correction happens for an account. The contents in this file will be cleared once the correction amount for previous capitalisation period is posted. </p>
            <p> The @ID is Account Number. All the fields in this file are associated multi-value fields. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the respective INTEREST.TYPE that involved in the correction process. </p>
            <p> The possible values are CR / CR2 / DR / DR2 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WITHHELD.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted interest amount after the correction process. This is similar to the field ADJ.INT.AMT. </p>
            <p> This field will be updated only when the field TAX.CORR.CAP is set to YES in ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION. For other cases, it will be zero. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted interest amount after the correction process. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted tax amount after the correction process. </p>
            <p> The value in this field will be zero if the field TAX.CORR.CAP is set to YES in ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the corresponding CORRECTION.ID generated for a transaction. This is a sub-value level field based on the account number and the date in correction ID. </p>
            <p> The value present in this field will be a valid record @ID in CORR.ACCT.XX where XX is CR / CR2 / DR / DR2 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

