<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>ICA.GROUP.HISTORY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>ICA.GROUP.DETAIL</p>
            <p>This "live" (system updated) file contains all details relevant to an ICA (Interest compensation Account hierarchy) group.</p>
            <p>An ICA.GROUP.DETAIL record is created when an account is defined as an ICA group main account.</p>
            <p>It is updated in two ways</p>
            <p />
            <p>On account authorisation when changes are made to the structure of this ICA group, i.e. changing the link to a higher level ICA group or changing links from sub accounts linked to this group</p>
            <p>On capitalisation of the account which is the leader of the group (the record key), details of the interest calculation and ICA interest distribution are stored.</p>
            <p>The ICA.GROUP.HISTORY file is identical to this file except that the key is appended with the capitalisation date. It is updated each time the main account is capitalised.</p>
            <p>Capitalisation correction processing will also cause this file to be updated.</p>
            <p>ICA.GROUP.DETAIL and ICA.GROUP.HISTORY provide a convenient way to show all relevant data for a group.</p>
            <p>The T24 system files, which provide the financial data for these ICA group files are described below. </p>
            <p>Details of ICA interest calculations and interest distribution are stored in the STMT.ACCT.XX (CR, CR2, DR, and DR2) files. </p>
            <p>Details of ICA account balances are store in the ACCT.ACTIVITY file.</p>
            <p>The keys to these files are as follows.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Main account calculation (using the combined balances of all accounts in the group) </p>
            <p />
            <p>MAIN.ACCOUNT*-DATE</p>
            <p>Sub account calculation for partial member (using only the balances for the periods when the sub account was a group member)</p>
            <p />
            <p>MAIN.ACCOUNT*SUB.ACCOUNT-DATE</p>
            <p>NB. If a sub account is also a main account then the relevant ICA type ACCT.ACTIVITY records will be used to calculate balances.</p>
            <p>The date for the ACCT.ACTIVITY file is of the YYYYMM type.</p>
            <p>The date to the STMT.ACCT.XX file is of the YYYYMMDD type.</p>
            <p>If capitalisation corrections are applied then the CORR.ACCT.XX will also be updated accordingly.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LINKED.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>LINKED.TO</p>
            <p>Contain a list of main account links between this account and the top account of the hierarchy.</p>
            <p>The number of accounts indicates the level of this main account in the hierarchy.</p>
            <p>Associated with LINK.DATE.</p>
            <p>These two fields provide a history of all links between this account and the top of the hierarchy.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Date field.</p>
            <p>Sub-valued associated with the multi-valued LINKED.TO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.INT.D2</field>
<desc>
            <p>GROUP.INT.DR2</p>
            <p>The total of DR2 interest calculated on capitalisation date for using the combined balances of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAIN.DIST.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>MAIN.DIST.CR</p>
            <p>The remaining amount of group difference for CR interest, which has been allocated to the main account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAIN.DIST.C2</field>
<desc>
            <p>MAIN.DIST.C2</p>
            <p>The remaining amount of group difference for CR2 interest, which has been allocated to the main account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.D2</field>
<desc>
            <p>INT.D2</p>
            <p>The amount of normal D2 interest earned by the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM.</p>
            <p>Not currently updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.GROUP.DETAIL.KEY</p>
            <p>The main account for this ICA (Interest Compensation Account hierarchy) group.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Account number</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.C2</field>
<desc>
            <p>INT.C2</p>
            <p>The amount of normal CR2 interest earned by the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM.</p>
            <p>Not currently updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAIN.DIST.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>MAIN.DIST.DR</p>
            <p>The remaining amount of group difference for DR interest, which has been allocated to the main account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NORMAL.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p>NORMAL.INTEREST</p>
            <p>The total of CR, CR2, DR and DR2 normal interest calculated on capitalisation date of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.INT.C2</field>
<desc>
            <p>GROUP.INT.CR2</p>
            <p>The total of CR2 interest calculated on capitalisation date for using the combined balances of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAIN.DIST.D2</field>
<desc>
            <p>MAIN.DIST.D2</p>
            <p>The remaining amount of group difference for DR2 interest, which has been allocated to the main account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NORMAL.INT.C2</field>
<desc>
            <p>NORMAL.INT.C2</p>
            <p>The total of CR2 normal interest calculated on capitalisation date of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINKED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>LINKED.DATE</p>
            <p>Contain a list of dates when a link was initiated between this account and a higher level main account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Date field.</p>
            <p>Multi valued associated with the sub-valued LINKED.TO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>END.DATE</p>
            <p>The date that the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM was unlinked from this account.</p>
            <p>If the sub account was also a main account then any accounts linked to that sub account would also be unlinked from this account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Date.</p>
            <p>Multi valued field associated with LINKED.FROM to INT.D2.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>INT.DR</p>
            <p>The amount of normal DR interest earned by the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM.</p>
            <p>Not currently updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISTRIB.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>DISTRIB.TYPE</p>
            <p>The distribution type used to allocate ICA group interest to sub account of this group.</p>
            <p>There are two types of ICA interest distribution</p>
            <p />
            <p>RATIO a straight percentage of the group interest is allocated to a sub account</p>
            <p>INTEREST the amount of interest earned by the sub account determines how much interest is allocated</p>
            <p />
            <p>ICA interest allocated = ICA group difference (Interest earned by sub account / Total normal interest earned by all accounts in the group)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Can be either INTEREST or RATIO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIST.RATIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>DIST.RATIO</p>
            <p>If the interest distribution type for this group is RATIO, then this field contains the percentage of interest allocated to the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field containing a percentage value</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIST.C2</field>
<desc>
            <p>DIST.C2</p>
            <p>The amount of ICA group difference CR2 interest allocated to the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIST.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>DIST.CR</p>
            <p>The amount of ICA group difference CR interest allocated to the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIST.D2</field>
<desc>
            <p>DIST.D2</p>
            <p>The amount of ICA group difference DR2 interest allocated to the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIST.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>DIST.DR</p>
            <p>The amount of ICA group difference DR interest allocated to the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.INT.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>GROUP.INT.DR</p>
            <p>The total of DR interest calculated on capitalisation date for using the combined balances of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.DIFFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>GROUP.DIFFERENCE</p>
            <p>The difference between the GROUP.INTEREST and the NORMAL.INTEREST calculated over the group capitalisation period.</p>
            <p>This amount is distributed to the sub accounts of the group based on either the ratio or interest distribution method.</p>
            <p>In both cases the main account will receive the remaining group difference after allocation to sub accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.INT.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>GROUP.INT.CR</p>
            <p>The total of CR interest calculated on capitalisation date for using the combined balances of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NORMAL.INT.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>NORMAL.INT.CR</p>
            <p>The total of CR normal interest calculated on capitalisation date of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p>GROUP.INTEREST</p>
            <p>The total of CR, CR2, DR and DR2 interest calculated on capitalisation date for using the combined balances of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.PROC.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>MAX.PROC.LEVEL</p>
            <p>This field stores the highest number of links (or levels) between this account and the top of the ICA hierarchies it has been a member of. </p>
            <p>An ICA hierarchy consists of linked groups of accounts, each group has a main account to which sub accounts are linked.</p>
            <p>A main account in one group can be a sub account in another group.</p>
            <p>The main account of the highest level group is the top account.</p>
            <p>In order to calculate ICA group interest the combined balances of all in the group are used.</p>
            <p>If a group contains sub accounts which are themselves main accounts of lower level groups then group interest is calculated using the group balances of the lower level group of which the sub account is the main account rather than the balance of the sub account itself.</p>
            <p>The balances of each group are combined into special ACCT.ACTIVITY records, which contain the combined balances for the whole group.</p>
            <p>This scenario requires that the lowest level groups in the hierarchy are processed first so that their combined balances are available for the group interest calculations of the higher level groups.</p>
            <p>The structure of the ICA hierarchy can also change with time as group links can be moved from one level to another or even to different hierarchies.</p>
            <p>The MAX.PROC.LEVEL field is used to store the lowest level that a group has been, (in fact the highest number of links between it and the top of a hierarchy) in order that the ICA group interest processing takes place in the correct order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINKED.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>LINKED.FROM</p>
            <p>Contains a list of all sub accounts, which have been linked to this account.</p>
            <p> Note that a sub account can also be a main account of a lower level group.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Account Number.</p>
            <p>Multi valued field associated with LINKED.FROM to INT.D2.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROCESS.LEVEL</p>
            <p>Contains the level in the ICA hierarchy was either first set or when the level changed.</p>
            <p>Level can be defined as the number of links between this main account and the top account of the hierarchy of which it is a member. </p>
            <p>Associated with PROCESS.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>Multi valued associated with PROCESS.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROCESS.DATE</p>
            <p>Contains the date when the level in the ICA hierarchy was either first set or when the level changed.</p>
            <p>Associated with PROCESS.LEVEL.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
            <p>Multi valued associated with PROCESS.LEVEL.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NORMAL.INT.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>NORMAL.INT.DR</p>
            <p>The total of DR normal interest calculated on capitalisation date of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>INT.CR</p>
            <p>The amount of normal CR interest earned by the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM.</p>
            <p>Not currently updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NORMAL.INT.D2</field>
<desc>
            <p>NORMAL.INT.D2</p>
            <p>The total of DR2 normal interest calculated on capitalisation date of all accounts that were either full or partial members of the group during the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Amount field </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>START.DATE</p>
            <p>The date that the sub account identified in LINKED.FROM was linked to this account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Date.</p>
            <p>Multi valued field associated with LINKED.FROM to INT.D2.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

