<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>INFO.GEN.CHG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This is a live file containing details of the generic charges calculated for a period on a account (Customer accounts)</p>
            <p>This is a information file.This file is built to find the generic charge calculated at any given time.</p>
            <p>Charges are calculated depending on the charging information and charging structure set in IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT and IC.CHARGE.</p>
            <p>The charges are calculated from the date of the last capitalised date , shown in the field LST.PROD.CAP.DATE in the file ACCOUNT  for an account for each charge product. Each charge product would have different capitalising frequency.</p>
            <p>The id of the file is formatted in the following way - ACCOUNT.NO.CHARGE PRODUCT.CAPITALISED.DATE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date/period from which the charge is calculated.</p>
            <p>Usually it is one working day more than the LAST.CAP.DATE stored in ACCOUNT.GEN.CHG file for this account for this particular charge (IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT) .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>A multivalue field containing a variable number of lines of 34 characters which may be printed on descriptive statements in addition to the standard narrative and/or reference.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 34 type S (upper-case alpha or numeric) characters.         Multivalue field. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TXN.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Tax Provision Account entries ( credit ) generated as a result of Tax calculations on the generic charges .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Valid Transaction code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the TAX record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to generic charges.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 2 numeric character - Valid Tax code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries or account entries (credit for internal account ) generated for generic charges.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Valid Transaction code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date/period upto which the generic charge is calculated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Account entries(debit) generated for generic charges</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Valid Transaction code.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies the amount of Tax calculated on the generic charges.</p>
            <p>The currency of the amount is the account currency on which the charges are applied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 18 numeric characters plus a decimal point.         Standard amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TXN.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Customer Account entries( debit ) generated as a result of Tax calculations on the generic charges .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Valid Transaction code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the Category code which determines the Internal Account to be updated with Tax Provision entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the generic charge.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4 or 5 numeric character - Valid Category code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.NO.CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the account on which the generic charges have been calculated with the charge product and the date.</p>
            <p>The format is - ACCT.NO.CHARGE PRODUCT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>a) Standard account number</p>
            <p>b) Valid IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for generic charges.</p>
            <p>It can also be a internal acccount to which the charges are posted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4 to 5 numeric character category code. or valid T24         internal accounts</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies the generic charge amount calculated for the period between PERIOD.TO to PERIOD.FROM.</p>
            <p>The amount is in the account currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 18 numeric characters plus a decimal point.         Standard T24 amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multivalue field containing a variable number of lines of 34 characters which may be printed on descriptive statements in addition to the standard narrative and/or reference</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 34 type S (upper-case alpha or numeric) characters.         Multivalue field. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

