<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>INTEREST.STATEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this table is to specify a flat fee which is levied at the time of production of a Debit Interest Statement.  Specific charges can be entered by Currency.  For all Currencies not specifically mentioned, a default charge can be entered in local currency equivalent. </p>
            <p>The GENERAL.CHARGE table specifies whether or not this charge is applicable to associated groups of Accounts. </p>
            <p>The Interest Statement record which is in effect on the date of the debit interest capitalisation specifies the fee charged. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>K.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Account Currency for which the Interest Statement Charge in field CHARGE.AMOUNT applies.  For Accounts in Currencies not input to this field, the Default Amount specified in field DEFAULT.CHARGE.AMT is used. </p>
            <p>Fields K.CURRENCY to CHARGE.AMOUNT are used to define an Interest Statement Charge on Accounts in specific Currencies.  For Accounts in Currencies not specified by field K.CURRENCY, the Default (local currency equivalent) Amount specified in field DEFAULT.CHARGE.AMT is used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type SSS (SWIFT) characters Currency code.      or 1-3 numeric characters (will be converted to Currency code).  Multivalue Field associated with field CHARGE.AMOUNT.  (Mandatory input if any input in associated field CHARGE.AMOUNT, otherwise not allowed.)  It must be a valid code on the CURRENCY table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Interest Statement Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>Must be a valid code on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>The Debit Credit Indicator in the Transaction record must be 'CREDIT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Interest Statement Charge, and can be used for reporting. </p>
            <p>The Description may be entered in each of the Languages defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: General Tables). </p>
            <p>It will be displayed in the Language specified in the User Record of the person using the System. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEQUENCE.YEAR.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Interest Statement code and effective date which form a key to which General Charge records may be linked. </p>
            <p>The date may be entered as: </p>
            <p>           1)   YYYY-MM  year-month            2)   YYYYMM   yearmonth            3)   MM-YY    month-year            4)   MMYY     monthyear    or      5)   MM       month (current year assumed) </p>
            <p>The month may be 01-12 or 1-12. </p>
            <p>It is always displayed formatted YYYY-MM.  For new input the date may not be earlier than today. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>a)   1-2 numeric characters (Mandatory input).  b)   '-' (Mandatory input if date is input, otherwise no input).      Prime Sites '.'  c)   1-7 date characters, year and month  (Optional input, default is current year and month).  Altering an existing INTEREST.STATEMENT record does not cause any adjustment to charges already processed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Tax record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to the Interest Statement Charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric character Tax code.  (Optional input)  There must be an existing record for this code on the TAX table (Ref: General Tables), with an effective date no later than the effective date of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Account entries generated for Interest Statement Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>It must be a valid code on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>The Debit Credit Indicator in the Transaction record must be 'DEBIT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Interest Statement Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric character Category code.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>It must be a valid code on the CATEGORY table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>System Indicator in Category record must be 'PL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Interest Statement charge for Accounts in the Currency specified in the associated field K.CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>Fields K.CURRENCY to CHARGE.AMOUNT are used to define Interest Statement Charges in specific Currencies.  The Default Amount (in local currency) specified in field DEFAULT.CHARGE.AMT is used if there is no entry in field K.CURRENCY for the Currency of the Acount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Multivalue field associated with field K.CURRENCY.  (Mandatory input if associated field K.CURRENCY is input, otherwise not allowed.)  The number of decimals may not exceed the number for Currency in field K.CURRENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Account Currency for which the Interest Statement Charge in field CHARGE.AMOUNT applies.  For Accounts in Currencies not input to this field, the Default Amount specified in field DEFAULT.CHARGE.AMT is used. </p>
            <p>Fields K.CURRENCY to CHARGE.AMOUNT are used to define an Interest Statement Charge on Accounts in specific Currencies.  For Accounts in Currencies not specified by field K.CURRENCY, the Default (local currency equivalent) Amount specified in field DEFAULT.CHARGE.AMT is used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type SSS (SWIFT) characters Currency code.      or 1-3 numeric characters (will be converted to Currency code).  Multivalue Field associated with field CHARGE.AMOUNT.  (Mandatory input if any input in associated field CHARGE.AMOUNT, otherwise not allowed.)  It must be a valid code on the CURRENCY table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.CHARGE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount, in local currency equivalent, to be charged per Interest Statement if there is no entry in field K.CURRENCY for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>Amounts for calculating Interest Statement Charges in specific Currencies can be specified in the multivalue fields K.CURRENCY and CHARGE.AMOUNT. The Default Amount specified in field DEFAULT.CHARGE.AMT is used if there is no entry in field K.CURRENCY for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  (Mandatory if no input made to field K.CURRENCY, otherwise optional.)  The number of decimals may not exceed the number for local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

