<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>PREMIUM.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TAX.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate used in the conversion of the tax amount. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax code specifying the tax to be levied on the premium amount. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the amount of Tax calculated is to be added to or subtracted from the premium amount to be paid to the customer's account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>M (minus) or P (plus). (Input Disallowed) Examples: 1) Assume Credit Interest of 100 and a Tax Rate of 15%.    a) Assume Tax Operand P (plus).       (net interest rate quoted to the customer)        Credit Customer     100        Credit Tax           15        Debit P &amp; L         115    b) Assume Tax Operand M (minus).       (gross interest rate quoted to the customer)        Credit Customer      85        Credit Tax           15        Debit P &amp; L         100</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency in which the premium will be paid, in other words the currency of the account. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the date from which any deposits qualify for premium </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of tax to be levied on the premium amount. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the start date of the period for which the movement is paid premium interest. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id to the file which contains 3 embedded fields as illustrated below : </p>
            <p>(Account Number + Premium Type + Premium Capitalisation Date) </p>
            <p>eg. 68754393-FIDELITY-19961231 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rate used to calculate premium </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.PREMIUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total calculated premium amount. This is the sum of the multi-value field CALC-PREM-AMT. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.PREMIUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The net premium amount to be credited to the account. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.TAX.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of tax to be levied on the premium amount in local currency. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the end date of the period for which the movement is paid premium interest. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days on which the premium amount is calculated based on the corresponding amount in CALC.BAL.AMT </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.BAL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount on which premium interest is to be calculated. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.BAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date from which the corresponding amount in CALC.BAL.AMT is to be used for calculating the premium amount. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.PREM.ACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The unrounded amount of premium calculated on the corresponding amount in CALC.BAL.AMT </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.PREM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rounded amount of premium calculated on the corresponding amount in CALC.BAL.AMT </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the date upto which any deposits qualify for premium </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Ids of any statement or category entries raised by movements, both debits and credits, across the account during the premium calculation period. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

