<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>REBUILD.TRAN.CHARGES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows the transaction level charge detail file, ACCR.ACCT.TRAN.CH to be rebuilt for an account, a group of accounts, or all accounts. </p>
            <p>For each account selected the entries since the last charge capitalisation will be analysed, and any with a chargeable transaction code of CHARGE.PERIOD "T", will be recalculated and stored in ACCR.ACCT.TRAN.CH for the account. </p>
            <p>This application may be required should TRANSACTION.CHARGE be altered back valued, or a GENERAL.CHARGE group is made chargeable for transaction charges back valued. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the rebuild tran charges file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be SYSTEM or any abbreviation thereof.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies an individual Customer Account for which correction is required.  The Recalculation starts from the last charge capitalisation date, held in CAP.DATE.CHARGE in the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-14 numeric character Account Number. or     3-10 type A (alphanumeric) Account Mnemonic. Multivalue field associated with Field 5. (Optional input. No default value.)</p>
            <p>Must be an existing Account on the ACCOUNT file.</p>
            <p>Duplicates are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALL.ACCOUNTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the ACCR.ACCT.TRAN.CH file should be rebuilt for all accounts. </p>
            <p>If selected all account entries since the last capitalisation date will be analysed to recalculate Transaction level charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only Y allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the ACCT.GEN.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Group of Accounts for which corrections are required. </p>
            <p>If corrections for a whole group of Accounts are required, for instance because an incorrect Group Condition or Basic Interest rate is not spotted until after interest has been applied, the Group(s) for which corrections are required may be specified in this field. Recalculation for each account starts from the last charge capitalisation date, defined in CAP.DATE.CHARGE in the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric characters Condition Group Code. Multivalue field associated with Field 3. (Optional input. No default value.)</p>
            <p>Must be the Id of an existing record on the Account General Condition file, (ACCT.GEN.CONDITION).</p>
            <p>Duplicates are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

