<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>SAVINGS.PREMIUM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the PL category code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for the premium interest paid to the customer's savings account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  5 numeric character Category code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be in the range 50000-59999.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.INC.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A flag to define whether or not to include the interest capitalised on the account into the balance for the premium calculation purposes.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Input must be either YES or NO</p>
            <p />
            <p> Input is mandatory if and only if any of the following fields :</p>
            <p> - MIN.PREM.QUAL.PRD</p>
            <p> - MAX.PREM.QUAL.PRD</p>
            <p> - MAX.PREMIUM.BAL</p>
            <p> - INT.TXN.CODE</p>
            <p> are populated, otherwise an optional field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines a list of all the valid transaction codes used for interest postings.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Input must be a valid credit transaction code.</p>
            <p />
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>             
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCLUDE.OPEN.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>A flag to define whether or not to include the opening balance in the premium calculation</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input may be only 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>  (Mandatory Input for Fidelity &amp; Growth premium processing)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Any number of the first character/s may be entered</p>
            <p>  eg. 'Y' or 'YE' will suffice for YES and also will be expanded to 'YES' on the screen</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the period within which withdrawals affect deposits. The field will also be used for deciding the number of days for which the premium is paid if the corresponding field CALCULATION.TYPE has been set to 'PERIOD'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example :-</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dates     Movements     Balance</p>
            <p>  01/02/95     +40000      +40000</p>
            <p>  01/02/96     +40000      +80000</p>
            <p>  18/04/96     -20000      +60000</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Closing 1996</p>
            <p>     ============</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Base Interest:</p>
            <p>  77 Days  x  40000  x  3,5% = 299,44</p>
            <p>  252 Days  x  20000  x  3,5% = 489,99</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Growth Premium:</p>
            <p>  329 Days  x  20000  x  2%   = 365,55</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Note : The deposit of 40000 was reduced by the withdrawal amount of 20000 because it did not remain in the account for a minimum period of 6 Months.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Fidelity Premium:</p>
            <p>  40000  x  5%  x  12 months   = 2000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Note : For the CALCULATION.TYPE defined as Period any deposit that qualifies for premium is paid for the minimum period defined on it i.e. (12 months)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input must be of the form nnM or nnnD</p>
            <p>  (Mandatory Input for Fidelity &amp; Growth premium processing)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Egs:</p>
            <p>  12M  (Signifies 12 Months)or</p>
            <p>  180D (Signifies 180 Days) or</p>
            <p>  30D  (Signifies 30 Days)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the interest calculation basis.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   In each of the options specified below the number on the left represents the number of days basis for multiplying on the top line of the interest calculation and the number on the right is the basis for dividing on the bottom line of the interest calculation.</p>
            <p>   A = 360/360</p>
            <p>   B = 366/360</p>
            <p>   E = 366/365</p>
            <p>   F = 360/365</p>
            <p />
            <p>   1 type SSS (Uppercase alpha) character in the range</p>
            <p>   A-B or E-F.</p>
            <p>   (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Where 360 is specified as the left factor, each month will be treated as having 30 days when calculating interest.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Where 366 is specified as the left factor, interest will be calculated for the actual number of days in the month.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Where 365 is specified as the right factor, the divider will always be 365 even for a leap year.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Tax record which specifies the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to the premium interest.</p>
            <p>   (Optional Input)</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Upto 2 numeric character Tax code. There must be an existing record for this code on the TAX table (Ref: General Tables)</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Upto 17 characters of a Tax Condition Type prefixed with a *. There must be an existing record for this code on the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.PREMIUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the maximum premium payable to the account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the premium calculated is greater than this amount then premium will be limited to this amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input must be numerical. 11 numeric character</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input is optional</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREM.CAP.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the next date and subsequent frequency of the application of premium interest.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The first part of the field specifies the next application date for premium interest, the 2nd part specifies the frequency of premium interest applications.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The next date is updated automatically by the system on each application day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The allowable frequencies are:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mnndd - Every nn months on the dd day</p>
            <p />
            <p>  When amending this field manually, if the next date is omitted, the system automatically generates it as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mnndd - Every nn months on the dd day</p>
            <p>  If today's date is less than dd, the next date is day dd in nn months from last month, otherwise it is day dd in nn months form the current month.  If this date does not exist (e.g. 30th February) the previous day is assumed (28th or 29th February).</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field is in two parts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Next Application Date:</p>
            <p>  1-9 Date characters.  Default value calculated by the system depending on application frequency.  (Optional Input).</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Application Frequency:</p>
            <p>  1-5 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If Date is entered, it must not be before today's date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The Frequency must be one of those listed above.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the premium type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.BAL.INC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This amount signifies the minimum balance increase required each year for premium interest payment to be made. This means that if the account was open for 5 years when premium interest was due on it and this amount was 10,000 then the account balance at the time of premium capitalisation will need to be at least 50,000 in order that the account capitalise a premium amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p> This field is optional.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate to be applied for premium calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The field may contain upto 11 numeric characters with or without a decimal point entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUAL.PERIOD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is relevant to only fidelity &amp; Growth types of premiums. The field defines the type of qualifying period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input may only be 'CALENDAR' or 'VARIABLE'</p>
            <p>  (Input becomes mandatory if any of the fidelity &amp; growth premium related fields were entered)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Any number of the first character/s may be entered</p>
            <p>  eg. 'C' or 'CA' will suffice for CALENDAR and also will be expanded to CALENDAR on the screen</p>
            <p />
            <p>  'Calendar' - Indicates that for a deposit to qualify for fidelity premium it needs to be in the account for at least one calendar year after the corresponding growth premium was acquired on it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  'Variable' - Indicates that for a deposit to qualify for fidelity premium it needs to be in the account for at least 12 consecutive months after the corresponding growth premium was acquired on it.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.PREM.QUAL.PRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the period within which the premium should have been paid from the opening year of the account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input must be of the form nnY, nnM or nnnD</p>
            <p>  Egs:</p>
            <p>  2Y   (Signifies 2 Years)   or</p>
            <p>  12M  (Signifies 12 Months) or</p>
            <p>  180D (Signifies 180 Days)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input is optional</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.PREM.QUAL.PRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the minimum period the account needs to be open before which premium can be paid on it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input must be of the form nnY, nnM or nnnD</p>
            <p>  Egs:</p>
            <p>  2Y   (Signifies 2 Years)   or</p>
            <p>  12M  (Signifies 12 Months) or</p>
            <p>  180D (Signifies 180 Days)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input is optional</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.PREM.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the maximum balance on which premium can be paid. If the balance of the account increases this amount the premium calculation will be limited to this amount. If not entered the entire account balance will be taken into consideration for premium calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p> This field is optional.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUALIFYING.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the period before which the deposit qualifies for the premium</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input must be of the form nnM or nnnD</p>
            <p>  (Mandatory Input for Fidelity &amp; Growth premium processing)</p>
            <p>  Egs:</p>
            <p>  12M  (Signifies 12 Months)or</p>
            <p>  180D (Signifies 180 Days) or</p>
            <p>  30D  (Signifies 30 Days)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the calculation method</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input may be only 'PERIOD' or 'ACTUAL'</p>
            <p>  (Mandatory Input for Fidelity &amp; Growth premium processing)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Any number of the first character/s may be entered</p>
            <p>  eg. 'P' or 'PE' will suffice for PERIOD and also will be expanded to 'PERIOD' on the screen.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  'Actual' - Indicates that the premium will be paid up to the capitalisation date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  'Period' - Indicates that the premium will be paid for the period specified on the field MINIMUM.PERIOD.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Credit transaction code for premium type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>   The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>             
            <p>   Must be defined in the TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Must be a credit type of transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The range assigned to Interest &amp; Charges in the system is 350 - 399.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Debit transaction code for premium type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>   The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>             
            <p>   Must be defined in the TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Must be a debit type of transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The range assigned to Interest &amp; Charges in the system is 350 - 399.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the premium type</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

