<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>STMT.ACCT.DR2</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is an internal file containing details of the calculation of Debit 2 Interest for capitalisation (application to the Customer's Account). It is used to provide the details on interest statements and advices. </p>
            <p>  The dates and frequency for interest capitalisation are specified for groups of Accounts in the GROUP.CAPITALISATION table or, for specific Accounts, in the ACCT.CAPITALISATION table. The capitalisation is processed during the end of day processing for the capitalisation date specified, or, if this is a non-working day, on the previous working day (except, see note below). </p>
            <p>  Debit 2 Interest is calculated according to rules specified in the fields with prefix DR2 in the appropriate ACCOUNT.DEBIT.INT record or GROUP.DEBIT.INT record. It may be Capitalised, i.e. booked to the Customer's Account, on the same dates as normal Debit Interest, or on different dates.) </p>
            <p>  Interest is calculated on the value dated balances stored in the ACCT.ACTIVITY file, taking into account all entries over the Account up to and including the day of processing. </p>
            <p>  The first balance included in the calculation is the day after the last Debit 2 Interest Capitalisation, as stored in the ACCOUNT record (in the CAP DATE DR2 INT field). </p>
            <p>  The last balance included depends on the LAST DAY INCLUSIVE field in the ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL file, if this contains 'YES', balances are included up to and including the capitalisation date, if it contains 'NO', balances are included only up to the working day prior to the processing date. The date of the last balance included is written to the ACCOUNT record as the new CAP DATE DR2 INT. </p>
            <p>  Note:      If LAST DAY INCLUSIVE in the ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL            file contains 'YES', and the Capitalisation date is on a            non-working day, before the next working day, and the            monthend accrual date also falls before the next working            day and before the Capitalisation date, the capitalisation            is processed on the NEXT working day. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>GRAND.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total amount to be debited to customer's account including debit 2 interest and tax (if applicable). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a  decimal point. Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of Debit 2 Interest calculated at the rate shown in corresponding Field 6, on the amount shown in corresponding field 5. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Standard amount format. Multivalue field associated with Fields 3 to 7.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.INT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.INT.CATEG</p>
            <p>  Contains the category code used for ICA interest posting. This is defined on ICA.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The category code used will be that applicable to the interest type and whether it is standard interest or a correction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 category code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>D2.INT.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the TAX record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to debit interest. </p>
            <p>  The tax details to be used are those applicable on the capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 2 numeric character Tax code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Debit Interest Rate used to calculate the Interest Amount shown in corresponding Field 7. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format. Multivalue field associated with Fields 3 to 7.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.DIST.RATIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the percentage of ICA group interest that is due to this account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.INT.TR.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated when debit 2 interest is accrued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQUIDITY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency of the liquidity account which may be present on this file. </p>
            <p>  The currency may not necessarally be the currency of the main account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character or 1-3 numeric character currency code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>D2.INT.TAX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate of Tax, to be applied to the debit interest amount, to calculate the Tax Amount shown in associated Field 13. </p>
            <p>  Multiple occurrences of Fields 12 to 16 are used where the TAX record specifies that more than one rate of Tax is to be applied. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.  Up to 6 integers.  Up to 9 decimals.  Standard rate format. Multivalue field associated with Fields 12 to 16.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.MAIN.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.MAIN.ACCT</p>
            <p>  Indicates the ICA main accounts to which this account was linked between the PERIOD.FIRST.DATE and PERIOD.LAST.DATE on the statement.</p>
            <p>  If this account was a main account then this account number will also be included.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No Input field</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 account number</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.WAIVE.ALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES indicates that all debit interest and tax was waived for this period, if set to YES then no debit interest or tax will apply to this period for back valued corrections. But it will be calculated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.NO.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>If interest and charges are to be calculated for information purposes only and not passed to the account, or if accrued interest is to be suspended and not posted to Profit and Loss, this is  shown by this field. </p>
            <p>  The information in this field comes from the equivalent field in the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>  If this field contains 'SUSPENSE', interest will be booked to the Customer's Account but no Profit or Loss entries will be generated, instead, the amount which would have been accrued will be stored in a Suspense Amount field in the Account record. </p>
            <p>  If this field contains 'Y', interest is calculated for information only, no entries will be posted either to Profit and Loss or to the Customer's Account.  E.g. for Nostro Accounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  'SUSPENSE', 'Y' or nothing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.MIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the minimum amount of debit interest that can be posted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the total amount of calculated interest is less than the minimum value, then if DR.MIN.WAIVE is set to YES then the total interest will be set to zero, otherwise it will be set to the minimum value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>DR.MIN.WAIVE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.TR.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.TR.AC</p>
            <p>  The transaction code used for posting ICA interest to the account, as defined on ICA.HIERARCHY.PARAMETER relevant to the interest type and whether the posting is standard interest or a correction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 transaction code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.INT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated when debit 2 interest is accrued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric character Category code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the corresponding CORRECTION.ID generated for a transaction. This field will be updated when the defered tax is posted. </p>
            <p> The information in this field will be updated based on the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. Once updated, this information will be cleared from the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. </p>
            <p> The value in this field is a valid record in CORR.ACCT.DR2. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.TOTAL.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of deferred interest that was posted on the deferred date.</p>
            <p>For the first correction after posting the deferred amounts the deferred amounts, i.e. the amounts actually posted to the customer account will be used to work out the difference between the original amount and the new calculated amount. Any subsequent corrections will use the previously calculated amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.POST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the date that interest is actually posted to the customer account. For example interest can be capitalised monthly but is actually posted every 6 months to avoid interest on interest.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.MIN.WAIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates how the total interest amount is set if it is less than the minimum value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the total amount of calculated interest is less than the minimum value, then if DR.MIN.WAIVE is set to YES then the total interest will be set to zero, otherwise it will be set to the minimum value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.FIRST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value date of the first balance on which the interest has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  This is the day after the previous debit  2 interest application (Capitalisation) as stored in the CAP DATE DR2 INT field in the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  9 date characters - DD MMM YYYY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFERRED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the deferred application date of the debit interest in case pending debit interest processing was being performed on this account. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.VAL.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The debit balance on which the Interest Amount, shown in corresponding Field 7, has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  The value dates balances on which interest is calculated are held in the ACCT.ACTIVITY file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Standard amount format. Multivalue field associated with Fields 3 to 7.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNADJ.TOTAL.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the unadjusted total amount of Debit Interest when an adjustment relating to the Maximum Legal Rate is needed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>D2.INT.TAXTRSDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to debit entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the debit 2 interest amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p> Multivalue field associated with Fields 12 to 16.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.POST.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether ICA interest is actually posted to the account or is just calculated for information purposes. If it is calculated and not posted then the interest will be allocatd to the main account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.TOTAL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of tax on deferred interest that was posted on the deferred date.</p>
            <p>For the first correction after posting the deferred amounts the deferred amounts, i.e. the amounts actually posted to the customer account will be used to work out the difference between the original amount and the new calculated amount. Any subsequent corrections will use the previously calculated amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.NETTING.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will be updated if CR interest is netted with corresponding DR interest. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.SUB.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.SUB.INT</p>
            <p>  The amount of ICA interest posted to this account if this account is a sub account of the account defined in ICA.MAIN.ACCT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No Input multi valued field associated with ICA.MAIN.ACCT.</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.INT.TR.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Account entries generated when debit 2 interest is capitalised. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANUAL.ADJ.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The manual accrual adjustment amount for the period. This could be the amount of interest earned by an account in another system if tranferred to T24 during a capitalisation period.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total amount of Tax on Interest (if applicable). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Standard amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.TR.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.TR.PL</p>
            <p>  The transaction code used for posting ICA interest to profit and loss, as defined on ICA.HIERARCHY.PARAMETER relevant to the interest type and whether the posting is standard interest or a correction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 transaction code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.DIST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.DIST.TYPE</p>
            <p>  Indicates the ICA interest distribution method for the ICA group with the account defined in ICA.MAIN.ACCT as the leader.</p>
            <p>If defined as INTEREST then the ICA interest will be distributed according to the proportion of group interest earned by this account. If defined as ratio then a set percentage of interest will be assgined, for example 100% from group interest posted to the main account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field</p>
            <p>  Can be set to either INTEREST or RATIO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WITHHELD.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted interest amount after the correction process. This is similar to the field ADJ.INT.AMT. </p>
            <p> This field will be updated only when the field TAX.CORR.CAP is set to YES in ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION. For other cases, it will be zero. </p>
            <p> The information in this field will be updated based on the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. Once updated, this information will be cleared from the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQUIDITY.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where interest and charges are to be passed to an alternative Account, the number of the alternative ACCOUNT is shown by this field. </p>
            <p>  Where interest and charges are to be passed to an alternative Account, the alternative account number should be entered in the INTEREST LIQU ACCT Field on the original customer ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard account format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.LAST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value date of the last balance on which the interest has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  Interest is calculated on the value dated balances stored in the ACCT.ACTIVITY file, taking into account all entries over the ACCOUNT up to and including the day on which the interest capitalisation is processed. </p>
            <p>  The calculation includes all balances from the day after the previous debit 2 interest capitalisation, as stored in the ACCOUNT record (in the CAP DATE DR2 INT field) up to the capitalisation date specified, or, if the LAST DAY INCLUSIVE field in the ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL file contains 'NO', up to the working day prior to the processing date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  9 date characters - DD MMM YYYY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will contain the period end date of the current capitalisation period. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.NO.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for which the Interest Amount shown in corresponding Field 7 has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  The number of days is calculated according to the Basis (360/360,366/360, 366/365 or 360/365) on which the interest calculation is to be made.  Where the Basis is 360/360 or 360/365, the number of days is calculated as if there are 30 days in each month.  This is achieved by ignoring the 30th if there are 31 days in a month and assuming 3 days on the 28th of February or 2 days on the 29th of February.  If the Basis is 366/360 or 366/365, the number of days is the actual number of days. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-3 numeric characters. Multivalue field associated with Fields 3 to 7.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>D2.INT.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of Tax calculated on the debit 2 interest, at the rate shown in corresponding Field 12. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Standard amount format. Multivalue field associated with Fields 12 to 16.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.INT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of a period during which the Account has been in debit and debit 2 interest has been calculated. Associated fields show the number of days of the calculation, the applicable rate and the balance.  If either the rate or the balance change, a further set of associated fields will be generated. </p>
            <p>  Any change to the interest calculation will cause the generation of a new set of multivalue Fields 3 to 7.  These changes include: </p>
            <p>             Change to Balance                 Interest Rate                 Interest Day Basis                 Highest/Daily/Average Balance </p>
            <p>  Where different interest rates are applicable to 'Bands' of the balance, separate sets of Fields 3 to 7 are generated for each Band of the Balance on which interest is calculated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  9 date characters  -  DD MMM YYYY. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 7.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ICA.MAIN.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>ICA.MAIN.INT</p>
            <p>  The amount of ICA interest posted to this account if this account is the main account of the account defined in ICA.MAIN.ACCT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No Input multi valued field associated with ICA.MAIN.ACCT</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>D2.INT.TAXCATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code which determines the Internal Account to be updated with Tax Provision entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the debit 2 interest amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric character Category code. Multivalue field associated with Fields 12 to 16.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of interest before Tax. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>D2.INT.TAXTRSCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Tax Provision Account entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the debit 2 interest amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with Fields 12 to 16.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sequential number of corrected record generated after back-valued entries, rate changes or condition changes. Only present in records which have been corrected. </p>
            <p>  If any entries are processed with VALUE DATES prior to the last Capitalisation date (as stored in the CAP DATE DR2 INT field in the ACCOUNT record), COB job IC.BVAL automatically recalculates the interest for the capitalisation period(s) from the one containing the earliest back-valued entry, up to the last Capitalisation date. </p>
            <p>  The new STMT.ACCT.DR2 record is compared with the one previously calculated, and if there is any difference,  the old one is stored in the CORR.ACCT.DR2 file, the corrected one is written in this file and appropriate accounting entries are processed for the differences. </p>
            <p>If the correction takes place after deferred interest and charges have been posted then the first correction will use these values to work out the difference, as it is possible to adjust the calculated amount prior to posting either manually or via a back valued posting into the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p>Each time the same capitalisation is corrected, the correction number is incremented by 1. </p>
            <p>  When interest rates or conditions are amended, back-value recalculations are not processed automatically, but can be requested via the table TABLE CAPITALIS CORR. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  3 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ACCOUNT on which interest has been calculated (or the main account of a combined group, see details) and the date up to which it has been calculated. </p>
            <p>  When the balances of several accounts are to be consolidated for Interest purposes the main acccount number has to be entered in the INTEREST COMP ACCT field in the ACCOUNT records of each of the 'sub' accounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  a.   Standard account format. b.   '-' Prime Sites '.' c.   1-9 date characters. (Stored in format YYYYMMDD, displayed as DD MMM YYYY, but may be input in any of T24 date formats.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted interest amount after the correction process. This field will be updated only when the defered tax amount is posted. </p>
            <p> The information in this field will be updated based on the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. Once updated, this information will be cleared from the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. </p>
            <p> If this field contains the value then it indicates that the previous period correction tax amount is posted on the current period. (this period) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold the adjusted tax amount after the correction process. This field will be updated only when the defered tax amount is posted. </p>
            <p> The value in this field will be zero if the field TAX.CORR.CAP is set to YES in ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION. </p>
            <p> The information in this field will be updated based on the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. Once updated, this information will be cleared from the file IC.CORRECTION.DETAILS. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPENS.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where the balances on two or more Accounts are to be netted for the purpose of calculating interest and charges, the various sub-account numbers are shown by this multivalue field. The Account Number shown in the Record Id of this file is the major Account number of the group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard account format. Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum waive amount in the currency of the account if the waive currency is different to the currency of the account</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WIAVE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate used for the conversion of minimum waive amount in account currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>WAIVE.RATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
