<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>STMT.GEN.CHG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a live file containing details of the generic charges capitalised for a period on a account (Customer accounts)</p>
            <p>Charges are calculated depending on the charging information and charging structure set in IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT and IC.CHARGE. The charges may be capitalised Monthly, Quaterly. Half yearly or Yearly. If Quarterly is specified, the Quarters begin on the 1st of January, April, July and October. If Half Yearly is specified, the period begins on the 1st of January and July. If Yearly is specified then period begins on the 1st of January . Interim capitalisation is also possible. </p>
            <p>The charges are calculated from the date of the last capitalised date , shown in the field LAST.CAP.DATE in the file ACCOUNT.GEN.CHG for an account for each charge product. Each charge product would have different capitalising frequency.</p>
            <p>The id of the file is formatted in the following way - ACCOUNT.NO.CHARGE PRODUCT.CAPITALISED.DATE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries or account entries (credit for internal account ) generated for generic charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p> Valid Transaction code. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A multivalue field containing a variable number of lines of 34 characters which may be printed on descriptive statements in addition to the standard narrative and/or reference</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 34 type S (upper-case alpha or numeric) characters.         Multivalue field. (Internal file, no input.) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IC.CHARGE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the IC.CHARGE set for the account . </p>
            <p>The IC.CHARGE file is used to set the charging structure.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Alpha numeric characters</p>
            <p>Valid code in IC.CHARGE .</p>
            <p>Noinput field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date/period from which the charge is calculated.</p>
            <p>Usually it is one working day more than the LAST.CAP.DATE stored in ACCOUNT.GEN.CHG file for this account for this particular charge (IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT) . </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>A multivalue field containing a variable number of lines of 34 characters which may be printed on descriptive statements in addition to the standard narrative and/or reference.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 34 type S (upper-case alpha or numeric) characters.         Multivalue field. (Internal file, no input.) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TXN.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Tax Provision Account entries( credit ) generated as a result of Tax calculations on the generic charges . </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p> Valid Transaction code. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies the amount of Tax calculated on the generic charges.</p>
            <p>The currency of the amount is the account currency on which the charges are applied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 18 numeric characters plus a decimal point.         Standard amount format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TXN.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Customer Account entries( debit ) generated as a result of Tax calculations on the generic charges .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p> Valid Transaction code. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies the Category code which determines the Internal Account to be updated with Tax Provision entries generated as a result of Tax calculations on the generic charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 or 5 numeric character - Valid Category code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date/period upto which the generic charge is calculated.</p>
            <p>Usually last calendar day of the month the generic charges is calculated . During interim capitalisation , its the interim capitalised date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the TAX record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to generic charges.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 2 numeric character - Valid Tax code</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field identifies the Transaction code to be assigned to Account entries(debit) generated for generic charges</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p> Valid Transaction code. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.CHG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the account on which the generic charges have been calculated with the capitalised charge product and the date.</p>
            <p>The format is - ACCT.NO.CHARGE PRODUCT.CAPITALISED.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>a) Standard account number</p>
            <p>b) Valid IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT.</p>
            <p>c) Standard T24 date .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for generic charges. </p>
            <p>It can also be a internal acccount to which the charges are posted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 to 5 numeric character category code. or valid T24         internal accounts.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the generic charge amount calculated for the period between PERIOD.TO to PERIOD.FROM.</p>
            <p>The amount is in the account currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 19 numeric characters plus a decimal point.         Standard amount format.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field describes the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE key attached to the IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT (this forms the part of the id of this file)</p>
            <p>The basic charging information for generic charges is stored in the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE .</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 15 Alpha numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Valid code in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

