<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>STMT.ACCT.TRAN.CH</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction Charge Code calculated for the transaction pointed to by the statement id in the associated field STMT.ENTRY.ID </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUANTITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of transactions indicated by the transaction id in associated field TRANSACTION.ID that were passed on the account and for which charges were calculated </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total amount of transaction charge calculated for the corresponding transaction id in field TRANSACTION.ID </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction Id/s for which transaction charges have been calculated </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.ID.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Statement id points to the transaction/s created to debit the account for the charge amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CHRG.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields TRANS.CHRG.ID to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 8 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields STMT.ENTRY.ID to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 date field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Statement-Id of the transaction that corresponds to the charge/s in the associated charge fields TRANS.CHARGE &amp; CHARGE.AMT </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Entry Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YR.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields TRANS.CHRG.ID to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 6 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.ID.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account number and capitalisation date for transaction based charges </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be of the form Valid Account Number - YYYYMM</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction Charge calculated for the transaction pointed to by the statement id in field STMT.ENTRY.ID </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHRG.TOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields TRANS.CHRG.ID to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

