<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IC</product>
<table>TURNOVER.CREDIT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used to specify a Percentage charge on the total value of chargeable credit entries which pass over an Account during the Capitalisation period.  Alternatively, the NUMBER.OF.CREDIT table may be used to specify a fixed charge per entry. Only one of these two types of charges can be specified for each Account. </p>
            <p>  The GENERAL.CHARGE Record referred to in the relevant GROUP.DEBIT.INT Record or ACCOUNT.DEBIT.INT Record, specifies whether or not this charge is applicable to an Account. </p>
            <p>  Entries are chargeable only if the record on the TRANSACTION table (ref: General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code in the entry contains 'Y' in TURNOVER CHARGE (Field 10). </p>
            <p>  If the associated GENERAL.CHARGE record indicates that charges for debit and credit entries should be combined, the total value of chargeable entries is calculated and then the details from the TURNOVER.CREDIT table are used. </p>
            <p>  Free, Minimum and Maximum Amounts may be defined for specific Currencies.  Default amounts in local currency equivalent may also be defined and are used for Accounts in Currencies for which no amounts are specified. </p>
            <p>  The associated GENERAL.CHARGE record specifies whether this charge should be applied to the Account as a separate entry, or combined into one entry with other Account Maintenance Charges which may include: </p>
            <p>             BALANCE.REQUIREMENT            NUMBER.OF.DEBIT or TURNOVER.DEBIT            TRANSACTION.CHARGE </p>
            <p>  All Account Maintenance Charges are applied on the same day, monthly, quarterly or six monthly, at the end of the appropriate month, as specified in the COMPANY record (ref: General Tables). </p>
            <p>  The Turnover Credit record which is in effect on the date of the charges capitalisation is applicable for the whole of the charges capitalisation period. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Maximum Amount to be charged to the Account, for Accounts in the Currency specified in the associated Field 10. </p>
            <p>  Fields 10-13 are used to define Amounts for calculating Credit Turnover Charges in specific Currencies.  The Default Amounts specified in Fields 7-9 are used if there is no entry in Field 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  If after the Free Amount has been subtracted from the calculated charge the result is greater than the Maximum Amount, the Maximum Amount is used. </p>
            <p>  The COMPANY record specifies when the charges are to be applied.  If, however, the associated GENERAL.CHARGE record specifies that charges should be calculated on a monthly basis (Calcul Step Period = M), the charge for each month is compared with the Maximum Amount and adjusted if necessary. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Multivalue field associated with Fields 10-13. (Optional input, only allowed if Field 10 is input.) The number of decimals may not exceed the number for CURRENCY in Field 10.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Tax record containing details of the calculation and processing of Tax applicable to the Credit Turnover Charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 2 numeric character Tax code. (Optional input) There must be an existing record for this code on the TAX table, with an effective date no later than the effective date of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Minimum Amount to be charged to the Account, for Accounts in the Currency specified in the associated Field 10. </p>
            <p>  Fields 10-13 are used to define Amounts for calculating Credit Turnover Charges in specific Currencies.  The Default Amounts specified in Fields 7-9 are used if there is no entry in Field 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  If after the Free Amount has been subtracted from the calculated charge the result is less than the Minimum Amount, the Minimum Amount is used.  Otherwise the Maximum Amount is checked. </p>
            <p>  The COMPANY record specifies when the charges are to be applied.  If, however, the associated GENERAL.CHARGE record specifies that charges should be calculated on a monthly basis (Calcul Step Period = M), the charge for each month is compared with the Minimum Amount and adjusted if necessary. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Multivalue Field associated with Fields 10-13. (Optional input, only allowed if Field 10 is input.) The number of decimals may not exceed the number for CURRENCY in Field 10.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Account entries generated for Turnover Credit Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>  It must be a valid code on the TRANSACTION table.</p>
            <p>  The Debit Credit Indicator in the Transaction record must be 'DEBIT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEQUENCE.YEAR.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Turnover Credit code and effective date which form a key to which GENERAL.CHARGE records may be linked. </p>
            <p>  The date may be entered as: </p>
            <p>             1)   YYYY-MM  year-month            2)   YYYYMM   yearmonth            3)   MM-YY    month-year            4)   MMYY     monthyear    or      5)   MM       month (current year assumed) </p>
            <p>  The month may be 01-12 or 1-12. </p>
            <p>  It is always displayed formatted YYYY-MM.  For new input the date may not be earlier than today. </p>
            <p>  The Turnover Credit record which is in effect on the date of the charges capitalisation is applicable for the whole of the capitalisation period. </p>
            <p>  Note:     Altering an existing TURNOVER.CREDIT            record does not cause any adjustment to            charges already processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1)  1-2 numeric characters (Mandatory input). 2)  '-' (Mandatory input if date is input, otherwise no input). Prime Sites '.' 3)  1-7 date characters, year and month (Optional input, default is current year and month).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate used to calculate the charge amount as a Percentage of the total value of chargeable credit entries. </p>
            <p>  Entries are chargeable only if the Transaction record corresponding to the Transaction Code in the entry contains 'Y' in the Turnover charge field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 10 type R characters plus a decimal point, (standard rate format). (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>  Not more than 6 integers may be entered.</p>
            <p>  Not more than 9 decimals may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Turnover Credit Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>  Must be a valid code on the TRANSACTION table.</p>
            <p>  The Debit Credit Indicator in the Transaction record must be 'CREDIT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount to be deducted from the total charge calculated, subject to Minimum and Maximum Amounts, for Accounts in the Currency specified in the associated field 10. </p>
            <p>  Fields 10-13 are used to define Amounts for calculating Credit Turnover Charges in specific Currencies.  The Default Amounts specified in Fields 7-9 are used if there is no entry in Field 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  The Free Amount is subtracted from the calculated charge and further adjustments are made as specified in Fields 12 and 13. </p>
            <p>  The COMPANY record specifies when the charges are to be applied.  If, however, the associated GENERAL.CHARGE record specifies that charges should be calculated on a monthly basis (Calcul Step Period = M), the Free Amount is subtracted from the charge calculated for each month. </p>
            <p>  Note:       (i) The result may be zero, but not                  negative, i.e. the Customer will not                  receive a Credit. </p>
            <p>              (ii) Even if the Free Amount is greater                  than the calculated charge, any                  Minimum specified in Field 12,                  MINIMUM AMOUNT, is still applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Multivalue field associated with Fields 10-13. (Optional input, only allowed if Field 10 is input.) The number of decimals may not exceed the number for CURRENCY in Field 10.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Turnover Credit Charge, and can be used for reporting. </p>
            <p>  The Description may be entered in each of the Languages defined in the LANGUAGE table (ref: General Tables). </p>
            <p>  It will be displayed in the Language specified in the User Record of the person using the System. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Minimum Amount, in local currency equivalent, to be charged to the Account, if there is no entry in Field 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  Amounts for calculating Credit Turnover Charges in specific Currencies can be specified in the multivalue associated group of Fields 10-13.  The Default Amounts specified in Fields 7-9 are used if there is no entry in Field 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  The calculated amount is converted to local currency before making adjustments specified in Fields 7-9. </p>
            <p>  If after the Default Free Amount has been subtracted from the calculated local currency charge, the result is less than the Default Minimum Amount, the Default Minimum Amount is used.  Otherwise the Default Maximum Amount is checked.  The result is converted to the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  The COMPANY record specifies when the charges are to be applied.  If, however, the associated GENERAL.CHARGE record specifies that charges should be calculated on a monthly basis (Calcul Step Period = M), the charge for each month is compared with the Minimum Amount and adjusted if necessary. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input, default value is zero.) The number of decimals may not exceed the number for local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries generated for Turnover Credit Charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 or 5 numeric character Category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>  It must be a valid code on the CATEGORY table (ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>  System Indicator in CATEGORY record must be 'PL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Currency for which the Credit Turnover Charge details in the associated Fields 10-13 apply.  For Accounts in Currencies not specified by this Field, the Default Amounts specified in Fields 7-9 are used. </p>
            <p>  Fields 10-13 are used to define Amounts for calculating Credit Turnover Charges on Accounts in specific Currencies.  For any Accounts in Currencies not specified in Field 10, the Default (local currency equivalent) Amounts specified in Fields 7-9 are used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  3 type SSS (SWIFT) characters Currency code. or     1-3 numeric characters (will be converted to Currency code). Multivalue Field associated with fields 10-13. (Mandatory input if any input in associated Fields 10-13 otherwise optional). It must be a valid code on the CURRENCY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.FREE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Free Amount, in local currency equivalent, to be deducted from the total charge calculated, subject to Minimum and Maximum Amounts, if there is no entry in Field 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  Amounts for calculating Credit Turnover Charges in specific Currencies can be specified in the multivalue associated group of Fields, 10-13. The Default Amounts specified in Fields 7-9 are used if there is no entry in Field 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  The calculated amount is converted to local currency before making adjustments specified in Fields 7-9. </p>
            <p>  The Default Free Amount is subtracted from the calculated local currency charge and further adjustments are made as specified in Fields 8 and 9. The result is converted to the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  The COMPANY record specifies when the charges are to be applied.  If, however, the associated GENERAL.CHARGE record specifies that charges should be calculated on a monthly basis (Calcul Step Period = M), the Free Amount is subtracted from the charge calculated for each month. </p>
            <p>  Note:       (i) The result may be zero, but not                  negative, i.e. the Customer will not                  receive a Credit. </p>
            <p>             (ii)  Even if the Free Amount is greater                  than the calculated charge, any                  Minimum specified in Field 8,                  DEFAULT MIN AMT, is still                  applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input) The number of decimals may not exceed the number for local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Maximum Amount, in local currency equivalent, to be charged to the Account, if there is no entry in Field 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  Amounts for calculating Credit Turnover Charges in specific Currencies can be specified in the multivalue associated group of Fields 10-13.  The Default Amounts specified in Fields 7-9 are used if there is no entry in Fields 10 for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  The calculated amount is converted to local currency before making adjustments specified in Fields 7-9. </p>
            <p>  If after the Default Free Amount has been subtracted from the calculated local currency charge, the result is greater than the Default Maximum Amount, the Default Maximum Amount is used.  The result is converted to the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p>  The COMPANY record specifies when the charges are to be applied.  If, however, the associated GENERAL.CHARGE record specifies that charges should be calculated on a monthly basis (Calcul Step Period = M), the charge for each month is compared with the Maximum Amount and adjusted if necessary. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input, default value is zero.) The number of decimals may not exceed the number for local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

