<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CM</product>
<table>CM.MESSAGE.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OUT.OPTION.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multiple entry </p>
            <p>Outgoing SWIFT field tag or field identifier for matching. Fields which do not have tags and use an identifier are "MESSAGE.TYPE", "RECEIVER" and "SENDER".</p>
            <p>This identifies a tag on the outgoing message whose content must match that of the associated tag in the incoming message for an automatic match to be made.The associated tag is entered in IN.OPTION.TAG.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>12 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input. No default value.) </p>
            <p>No duplicate SWIFT tags allowed in OUT.OPTION.TAG or. </p>
            <p>A SWIFT tag entered must exist as a valid SWIFT tag (SWnn or SWnna) in DE.TRANSLATION application. </p>
            <p>If this field is entered into then the corresponding IN.OPTION.TAG cannot be left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.MATCH.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Incoming matching SWIFT field tag or field identifier. Fields which do not have tags and use an identifier are "MESSAGE.TYPE", "RECEIVER" and "SENDER".</p>
            <p>This identifies a tag on the incoming message whose content must match that of the associated tag in the outgoing message for an automatic key match to be made. The associated tag is entered in OUT.MATCH.TAG.</p>
            <p>If all the match key field contents match an incoming record message then the automatic matching process considers them a probable match. Only if the all the fields defined in IN.MATCH.TAG and IN.OPTION.TAG match are the messages fully matched automatically.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-25 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>No duplicate SWIFT tags allowed in IN.OPTION.TAG.</p>
            <p>A SWIFT tag entered must exist as a valid SWIFT tag (SWnn or SWnna) in DE.TRANSLATION application.</p>
            <p>If this field is entered into then the corresponding OUT.MATCH.TAG cannot be left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.OPTION.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multiple entry</p>
            <p>Outgoing SWIFT field tag or field identifier for matching. Fields which do not have tags and use an identifier are "MESSAGE.TYPE", "RECEIVER" and "SENDER".</p>
            <p>This identifies a tag on the outgoing message whose content must match that of the associated tag in the incoming message for an automatic match to be made.The associated tag is entered in IN.OPTION.TAG.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>12 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input. No default value.)</p>
            <p>No duplicate SWIFT tags allowed in OUT.OPTION.TAG or. </p>
            <p>A SWIFT tag entered must exist as a valid SWIFT tag (SWnn or SWnna) in DE.TRANSLATION application.</p>
            <p>If this field is entered into then the corresponding IN.OPTION.TAG cannot be left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the general classification of the message defined in this record, and should generally be the same as the SWIFT message number corresponding to the same type of transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid key on DE.MESSAGE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUT.MATCH.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Outgoing matching SWIFT field tag or field identifier. Fields which do not have tags and use an identifier are "MESSAGE.TYPE", "RECEIVER" and "SENDER".</p>
            <p>This identifies a tag on the outgoing message whose content must match that of the associated tag in the incoming message for an automatic key match to be made. The associated tag is entered in IN.MATCH.TAG.</p>
            <p>If all the match key field contents match an incoming record message then the automatic matching process considers them a probable match. Only if the all the fields defined in OUT.MATCH.TAG and OUT.OPTION.TAG match are the messages fully matched automatically.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-25 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>No duplicate SWIFT tags allowed in OUT.OPTION.TAG.</p>
            <p>A SWIFT tag entered must exist as a valid SWIFT tag (SWnn or SWnna) in DE.TRANSLATION application.</p>
            <p>If this field is entered into then the corresponding IN.MATCH.TAG cannot be left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

