<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FE</product>
<table>FATCA.BASE.MANUAL.UPDATE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>FATCA TAX BASE is updated automatically at year end with the details of name, address, TIN, Account balances and owner details,</p>
			<p>Since it is a live file, a provision is required to add records to the base, modify existing records in the base and delete records from the base.</p>
			<p>The ID of FATCA BASE MANUAL UPDATE will be the same as the ID of the FATCA TAX BASE record that needs to be amended .</p>
            
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field is used to identify the action to be performed on the base.</p>
			<p>NEW will be used to add records to the base for clients missing from the base; </p>
			<p>Amend will be for amending the records in the base; Delete will be for deleting the entire record from the base.</p>
			<p>For Amend and Delete the record should already exist in the base.</p>
            	<p>
            	<p>Validation Rules:</p>
            	</p>
			<p>NEW, AMEND or DELETE.</p>
       </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSOC.FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field associated with the field in FIELD NAME MV above for which the value needs to be changed (e.g. ACC BALANCE) .</p>
			<p>
			<p>Validation Rules:</p>
			</p>
            <p>A field, in FATCA TAX BASE, that is part of the associated multi-value set with the field in FIELD NAME MV.</p>	
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSOC.FIELD.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The new value for the field in ASSOC FIELD NAME above.</p>
			<p>
			<p>Validation Rules:</p>
			</p>
            <p>A valid value for the field being amended</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the field, in FATCA TAX BASE, for which the value needs to be added (New/Amend function) or Changed (Amend).</p>
			<p>
			   <p>Validation Rules:</p>
			</p>
            <p>A field in FATCA TAX BASE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME.MV</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will be used to change the values of associated multi-value fields. Only the first field in an associated multi-value set from the base 
			(e.g. Relation Cust for changing the ownership details, Account for the Account balance details) can be specified here </p>
            <p>
              <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A field, in FATCA TAX BASE, that is the first field of an associated multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field is used to specify the new value for the field in FIELD.NAME.</p>
			<p>If the field value is blank or Null, then while amending, the existing field values will be cleared. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A valid value for the field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.VALUE.MV</field>
<desc>
            <p> The value of the field, given in Field Name MV, to identify the corresponding multi-value set that needs to be modified.</p>
			<p>For e.g. if three accounts are updated in the base and the balance in the second account needs to be changed,</p>
			<p>Field Name MV will be ‘ACCOUNT’ and Field Value MV will be the Account number in the second multi-value (e.g.109298654.</p>            
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A valid value for the field from base.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>