<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FE</product>
<table>FATCA.XML.REQUEST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The FATCA.XML.REQUEST is used to generate the XML message, as per the FORM 8966,</p>
			<p>for all the reportable clients. The report can be generated for either a single CUSTOMER,</p>
			<p>ACCOUNT.OFFICER or ALL customers. If a Pool report has to be generated, the ID will be POOL .</p>
            
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>YEAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field identifies the year to which the generated XML pertains to.</p>
            	<p>
            		<p>Validation Rules:</p>
            	</p>
			<p>A valid year.</p>
       </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This fields will accept values NEW/CORRECTION/VOID/AMEND.</p>
            <p>The default value will be NEW which means the message is being generated for the first time. </p>
            <p>When a XML that has been generated needs to be corrected then Corrected Data is used for records being re-transmitted after the IRS has notified the sender of a </p>
             <p>problem with the file or underlying data. Corrected Data should ONLY be used when responding </p>
             <p>to an IRS request to correct the data. (not used for Decryption, XML or other file-level errors).</p>
            <p>Void Data is used to erase previously-filed records when data needs to be re-transmitted.</p>
            <p>Amended Data is used to amend a record(s) previously transmitted to, received and processed </p>
             <p>by the IRS, but is later found to contain erroneous information.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on ACTION selection following  need to updated in REPORT.TYPE.</p>
            <p>FATCA1 = New Data</p>
            <p>FATCA2 = Corrected Data</p>
            <p>FATCA3 = Void Data</p>
            <p>FATCA4 = Amended Data</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to record any narrative.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POOL.STATUS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Pool reports are generated for certain classifications in certain jurisdictions.</p> 
			<p>The field is used to identify the statuses (RECALCITRANT, DORMANT, NON-PARTICIPATING) for which the pool reports need to be generated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field will be open editable only when the @ID is pool.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POOL.INDICIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Pool reports are generated for certain classifications in certain jurisdictions.</p>
			<p>The field is associated with POOL.STATUS.TYPE and is used to specify whether the report has to be generated for clients with indicia or without indicia.</p>
			<p>If the field is left blank, the report will be generated for all the clients with FATCA STATUS equal to the status in POOL.STATUS.TYPE..</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field will be open editable only when the @ID is pool.‘YES’ if ‘with indicia’ is required.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POOL.REPORT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p> The field identifies the date on which the pool report is extracted.</p> 
            <p>This field will be defaulted from fatca reporting parameter extract date if @id is pool.</p>            
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field will be open editable only when the @ID is pool.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
        <p>Standard T24 reserved field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 reserved field.</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
         <p>Standard T24 reserved field.</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
          <p>Standard T24 reserved field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 reserved field.</p>
     </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>