<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FX</product>
<table>EB.AGREEMENT.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to store the types of agreements used in contracts.   E.g.. ISDA, BBAIRS, MASTER etc.   Each contract must be linked to an agreement type. The field AGREEMENT.TYPE on the contract is validated against the agreement type definitions on this file and enriched with the associated description. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LL.DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field used to fully define the agreement type.</p>
            <p>The first line of the description is used for field enrichments. E.g.. On the NDF contract field  AGREEMENT.TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-25 Alpha-numeric characters. (Multi-valued field). </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.AGREEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the master agreement type is entered but no further information is supplied on the contract this field is used to specify the type of master agreement followed by the date on which the agreement was signed and also the version of the agreement.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be a key to a valid full EB.AGREEMENT.TYPE record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Description of the agreement type. </p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.AGREEMENT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id defines the type of agreement used in contracts.   Eg. ISDA, BBAIRS, MASTER etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-30 Alpha-numeric characters. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Input must be either TYPE for master agreement type or TYPE / DATE // VERSION for full agreement types. </p>
            <p>TYPE is mandatory and can be up to six alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>If present, DATE must be six numeric characters in the form YYMMDD. </p>
            <p>If present, VERSION must be two numeric characters. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISDA.DEF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to show the year of the version of the ISDA definitions. The contents of this field are used in field 14C for SWIFT messages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input is only allowed for full agreement types. </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

