<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FX</product>
<table>FX.GEN.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this table is to identify a specific group of customers which will then be cross-related to the Group Condition table, to define FX default margin conditions applicable to that group. </p>
            <p>The FX General Condition record must exist before any associated group condition record can be specified. The key(Record Id) to general conditions is also the key to the associated FX Group Condition record.

</p>
            <p>A  group of customers or portfolios can be identified by an ID  based on the conditions and the values against them  held within this table.  </p>
            <p>In other words, those customers or Portfolios that satisfy the given values against the conditions defaulted from the condition Priority table, form a group and that group is identified by an ID. 

 </p>
            <p>Amending a customer record or Security Account Master (SAM)  may result in reclassification of a customer into another group ,during Close of Business for changes in Customer Record and online for changes in SAM.

 </p>
            <p> Values for any one of the FX.GEN.CONDITION record should be left blank for all the priority items so that it gets classified as the default group.</p>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field> DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the General Condition Code. </p>
            <p>This description of the General Condition is used for reporting or enrichment purposes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> Input is Mandatory up to 35 alphanumeric characters. </p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FX.GROUP.NO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ITEM</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>PRIORITY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>VALUE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>MULTIVALUE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
