<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FX</product>
<table>FX.PARAMETERS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Within this file are defined parameters which determine some of the rules by which the system operates.  These are as follows: </p>
            <p>       1. Classification of the contracts between SPOT and FORWARD according to local Central Bank and internal reporting rules. </p>
            <p>       2. Definition of the 'Spot' default value date. </p>
            <p>       3. Specification of the interpolation and revaluation marker. </p>
            <p>       4. Definition of the default revaluation method for FORWARD and SWAP foreign exchange transactions. </p>
            <p>       5. Definition of the default category code for SPOT, FORWARD and SWAP Foreign Exchange transactions. </p>
            <p>       6. An indicator stating the number of days after maturity that a contract is removed for the 'Live' file and written to History. </p>
            <p>       7. Parameters determining the frequency and content of certain reports produced at End of Day. </p>
            <p>       8. Conditions under which deals may be entered with split value dates. </p>
            <p>       9. Indicators showing whether P/L and EXCHADS entries are to be booked when revaluation of FORWARD and SPOT contracts takes           place. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESSWAPDR.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
    Holds the category code applicable for Accrual entries on account of a Forex Swap Deal
     with revaluation type other than RB method. As this is a NOINPUT field, 
    updation for the first time is done online by giving a value in the field NEW.RESSWAPDR.CAT and
    on authorization of FX.PARAMETERS. Subsequent changes, if required, will be updated  during the COB. 
    The code reflected  in this field should be a valid ID in CATEGORY application and 
    should be in the range of 10000 to 19999.
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.TYPE.FWD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the default method in which all deal types 'FORWARD' will be revalued. </p>
            <p>A detailed explanation of these 3 revaluation methods can be found in the Forex Main File documentation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field can be completed by any of the following two character code values: IN = Interest method RB = Rebate method SL = Straight line method (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.CODE.SPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines into which product category code the spot contract will be classified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The category code used must exist on the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p>The category code defined in this field must have the 'FX' application identifier on the CATEGORY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.RESSWAPCR.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
   The category code entered in this field will be updated to RESSWAPCR.CAT online for the first time
   and  subsequent changes in the following cob, if RESSWAPCR.CAT already holds a category code. 
   The code entered here should be a valid id in CATEGORY application and should be in the range 10000 to 19999.
   This field becomes null after the value given herein is updated to the field RESSWAPCR.CAT
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESFWDDR.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
  Holds the category code applicable for Accrual entries on account of a Forex Forward Deal 
  with revaluation type other than RB method. As this is a NOINPUT field, 
  updation for the first time is done online by giving a value in the field NEW.RESFWDDR.CAT and
  on authorization of FX.PARAMETERS. Subsequent changes, if required, will be updated  during the COB.
  The code reflected  in this field should be a valid ID in CATEGORY application and
 should be in the range of 10000 to 19999.
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.LIST.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies how many days before the Maturity (i.e. value date) the user wants to see the Foreign Exchange contracts with incomplete delivery instructions to appear in the Forex 'Incomplete delivery instructions' report. </p>
            <p>The contracts to appear in this report will be identified by the fact that the 'OUR ACCOUNT PAY' still contains the suspense account from the FX.TEXT file.  They will disappear from the report whenever they reach their value date or when proper liquidation instructions have been entered (i.e. OUR ACCOUNT PAY = Customer or NOSTRO account). </p>
            <p>Note : If 0 days is input in this field, no incomplete delivery instructions report will be produced in the Forex End of Day process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 numeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the parameter level rounding rule for calculating AMOUNT.BOUGHT or AMOUNT.SOLD</p>
            <p> in Forex Contracts for a given rate and given AMOUNT.SOLD or AMOUNT.BOUGHT </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be a valid EB.ROUNDING.RULE id.</p>
            <p>For detailed options on different rounding types help text on EB.ROUNDING.RULE file can be referred.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.MKR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not used at present and is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.OS.RP.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MKT.EXCH.ACCT.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field offers the options available for two different methods of Accounting for the Marketing Exchange on an FX deal.The application handles two different types:</p>
            <p> (1) INTERNAL</p>
            <p> (2) PANDL</p>
            <p>INTERNAL Historical method wherein the Marketing Exchange profit will be booked using an Internal Suspense account and Profit and Loss.</p>
            <p>PANDL Introduced subsequently wherein the Marketing Exchange profit will be booked using two Profit and Loss entries with DAO of Treasury and the DAO of the Customer. </p>
            <p>The revised Accounting (PANDL) method is applicable only deals involving SPOT and FW with ‘RB’ Method of Revaluation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.CENTRAL.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies, by means of a number of days, the local Central Bank rule for the reporting of Foreign Exchange contracts between SPOT and FORWARD.  For example, the market may treat contracts maturing in up to two days as a Spot but the Central Bank may wish the bank to report contracts maturing in up to seven days as Spot. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters in the range 0 to 14.  (Mandatory input)  The number of days must be in the range 0-14.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.DEAL.POST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the revaluation process post the unrealised P&amp;L amounts by contract or groups them by dealer desk. </p>
            <p>YES = Deal </p>
            <p>NO  = Dealer Desk       (Default) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>YES or NO</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FASB.REVALUATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the revaluation uses the mid rate or the bid and offer rates. </p>
            <p>YES = Bid and Offer rates </p>
            <p>NO  = Mid rate (Default) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>YES or NO</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Input can only be made to this field if there are no FX.TRANSACTION records on the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.BASE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field to specify additional currencies that should be used in the calculation of forex spot dates.</p>
            <p>The date determined by the normal calculation of spot date for a contract will be advanced to a day which is a working day for the currencies of the contract and the currencies specified in this field. The holiday region for a currency is the country code for the currency followed by "00".</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid currency</p>
            <p>There must be a valid holiday table for the currency</p>
            <p>Duplicates not allowed</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Spot Date Calculation</p>
            <p>The default operation of the system spot date calculation is described below. The default calculation will take place if the fields FX.LCL.REGION and SPOT.BASE.CCY are not specified in the FX.PARAMETERS record.</p>
            <p>When no SPOT.DATE or in the case of a Spot deal (or the first leg of a Swap), the VALUE.DATE.BUY/SELL is not entered, the system will attempt to default the dates. The dates are calculated by addition of the SPOT.MARKET number of days defined in FX.PARAMETERS to the DEAL.DATE to give a common working day for the country of the two currencies involved in the deal.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 1</p>
            <p>Local Currency - GBP</p>
            <p> Local Country - GB(defined in COMPANY)</p>
            <p>Spot Market - 2</p>
            <p>System Date - 2nd July</p>
            <p>Spot Deal - USD/GBP</p>
            <p>Holidays</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>US00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Comm</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>Using the common holidays (Comm) 2 working days gives a spot date of 5th July</p>
            <p>The SPOT.DATE, VALUE.DATE.BUY and VALUE.DATE.SELL would therefore be 5th July, this is a common working day in both countries and respects the Spot Market period for both.</p>
            <p>Example 2</p>
            <p>If the holidays were as follows for the same deal:</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>US00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Comm</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>Using the common holidays in this case gives a spot date of 6th July</p>
            <p>The default date would therefore be 6th July.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Spot Base Currency</p>
            <p>Some Banks and markets operate on the principal that Spot Dates should always fall on a working day in a certain currency, e.g. USD, even if the deal does not involve that currency. This method of spot date calculation, referred to as the SPOT.BASE.CCY , is controlled by the field of the same name in FX.PARAMETERS. </p>
            <p>Figure  FX.PARAMETERS - Defining the SPOT.BASE.CCY</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If this mode of date calculation is used the following rules are followed:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Deal Involves SPOT.BASE.CCY</p>
            <p />
            <p>The spot date for the NON spot base currency is calculated. If a FX.LCL.REGION is defined this will be used as per the rules in the previous section. This date is then compared to the Spot Base Ccy holidays, if the date is a holiday it is adjusted to the next common working day in both currencies after this date</p>
            <p />
            <p>Deal Does not involve SPOT.BASE.CCY</p>
            <p />
            <p>A common spot date is obtained for the two currencies involved in the same way as the standard processing. If a FX.LCL.REGION is defined this will be used as per the rules in the previous section. </p>
            <p>The common date calculated will then be compared to the SPOT.BASE.CCY holidays. If the date is a holiday it is adjusted to the next common working day for both currencies and the SPOT.BASE.CCY</p>
            <p />
            <p>Both sides of the deal are SPOT.BASE.CCY</p>
            <p />
            <p>A common working day is obtained for both currencies.</p>
            <p>The common date calculated is compared to all the SPOT.BASE.CCY holidays. If the date is a holiday it is adjusted to the next common date for both deal currencies and all currencies defined in SPOT.BASE.CCY.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This method can result in a different date calculation to the standard calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 3</p>
            <p />
            <p>Local Currency - GBP</p>
            <p> Local Country - GB</p>
            <p>Spot Market - 2</p>
            <p>Spot Base CCY - USD</p>
            <p>System Date  - 2nd July</p>
            <p>Holidays</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>US00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>CH00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p>Deal USD/GBP</p>
            <p>GB spot date is 4th July.</p>
            <p>This is a holiday in Spot Base Ccy so the date is adjusted to the next common working day in GB and US,  i.e. 6th July.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If this deal were done on 3rd July the spot date would also be 6th July. The spot date calculated for GB would be 6th July which is a working day in US. In the standard calculation the spot date would be calculated as 9th July as 2 common working days would be taken between US and GB.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 4</p>
            <p>Deal GBP/CHF on 2nd July</p>
            <p>Neither currency is a SPOT.BASE.CCY so a common spot date is obtained for GB/CH:</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>CH00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Comm</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p>This gives a SPOT.DATE of 4th July.</p>
            <p>This is a holiday in SPOT.BASE.CCY so the date (4th July) is adjusted to the next common working day for all three countries:</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>US00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>CH00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Comm</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p>The next common day after 4th July for all three countries is 9th July.</p>
            <p>Using the standard rules a spot date of 4th July would be generated as the US holidays would not be taken into consideration.</p>
            <p>If the same deal were entered on 3rd July the spot date would also be 9th July using the SPOT.BASE.CCY:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Common Spot GB/CH is 9th July</p>
            <p>In US 9th July is a working day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the same deal were entered on 3rd July using the standard calculation would also result in a spot date of 9th July.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPLIT.VALUE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether input of split value dated contracts will be allowed by the system and, if so, for which currencies. </p>
            <p>No value in this field signifies that the system will not accept Forex contracts which have different Buy and Sell value dates. The main input program will automatically assign any date input to one of these fields to both of them. </p>
            <p>Any number of currency codes may be entered in this field to signify that split value dates should be allowed on deals involving the sale or purchase of one of these currencies,  In this case, the main input program will accept input to the fields VAL.DATE.BUY and VAL.DATE.SELL independently of each other.  An override message is provided if they are not the same. </p>
            <p>The value 'ALL' may be entered to signify that the above rule is to apply to all currencies.  Split value dates will be accepted by the main Forex input program irrespective of the two currencies of the deal. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alphabetic characters.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid currency code or the literal 'ALL'.</p>
            <p>The value 'ALL' will not be accepted in conjunction with a list of currency codes - it must be a single input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.OUTST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Noinput field. (Multivalue field associated with the fields DEAL TYPE to this field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESSWAPCR.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
   Holds the category code applicable for Accrual entries on account of a Forex Swap Deal 
   with revaluation type other than RB method. As this is a NOINPUT field, 
   updation for the first time is done online by giving a value in the field NEW.RESSWAPCR.CAT and 
   on authorization of FX.PARAMETERS. Subsequent changes, if required, will be updated  during the COB.
   The code reflected  in this field should be a valid ID in CATEGORY application and
   should be in the range of 10000 to 19999.
 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.REVAL.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not P/L and EXCHADS entries are to be booked when contracts with a REVALUATION TYPE of 'RB' are revalued. </p>
            <p>After authorisation of this record, the value in this field may only be changed by using the application FX.REVAL.PARAMETERS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>YES or NO.  Mandatory input.  This field may not be changed after the record has been authorised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.PARAMETERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>FX.PARAMETERS</p>
            <p>This is the main file which controls the activities of FOREX APPLICATION.</p>
            <p>ID is FX.PARAMETERS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.TYPE.SWAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the default method in which all deal types 'SWAP' will be revalued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field can be completed by any of the following two character code values: IN = Interest method RB = Rebate method SL = Straight line method (Mandatory input) Details;   A detailed explanation of these 3 revaluation methods can be found in the Forex Main File documentation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.RESSWAPDR.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
The category code entered in this field will be updated to RESSWAPDR.CAT online for the first time 
and  subsequent changes in the following cob, if RESSWAPDR.CAT already holds a category code.
The code entered here should be a valid id in CATEGORY application and should be in the range 10000 to 19999.
This field becomes null after the value given herein is updated to the field RESSWAPDR.CAT.
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.AL.REVAL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>P &amp; L category to use for revaluation of currency positions generated by contingent movements in a value dated accounting system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>50000 - 59999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DFLT.FLD.FRM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field on the 'Nostro' deal from where the details have to be defaulted. </p>
            <p>The field on the Nostro deal from where the information has to be defaulted is to be defined here. The field number entered here can be any field in the FOREX application. The field number entered here will be enriched with the field description from the FOREX file. </p>
            <p>It is to be noted that this field has to be setup properly since improper setup could default the incorrect data in the client Forex contract. For example, if the BUY.CCY of the Nostro deal should be defaulted into the SELL.CCY of the Client deal, this field should be set to '6' (CURRENCY.BOUGHT on the FOREX file) and the next field must be set to '9' (CURRENCY.SOLD on the FOREX file). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric characters.  Has to be a valid field Number in the FOREX application.  (Multi-valued and Sub-valued field associated with the fields DEAL.TYPE to RESERVE1 so that more than one field can be defaulted from the 'Nostro' deal to the 'Client' deal)</p>
            <p>Can be any valid field on the FOREX file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRECIOUS.METALS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Currency Codes to be used for precious metals. </p>
            <p>Any number of currency codes may be entered in this field. The currency code which is entered must be defined in the Currency File. A numeric code may be entered to obtain the currency code, using the routine IN2CCY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Currency Code (3 uppercase alpha characters or 1-3 numeric characters.)  (Multivalue field.)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid currency code.</p>
            <p>A currency code should not appear more than once in this field.</p>
            <p>Input of a local currency should not be allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.RESFWDCR.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
  The category code entered in this field will be updated to RESFWDCR.CAT online for the first time and
  subsequent changes in the following cob, if RESFWDCR.CAT already holds a category code.
  The code entered here should be a valid id in CATEGORY application and should be in the range 10000 to 19999.
  This field becomes null after the value given herein is updated to the field RESFWDCR.CAT
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Extra processing of the Forex contract for certain Special Deal types can be done by entering the Deal type in this field. </p>
            <p>For BULK Forex deals extra processing can be done during the Input of the Bulk deal. This will default fields from the main (Nostro) contract into the client deal. </p>
            <p>In a Bulk deal one Forex contract will be done with a Nostro Counterparty followed by many Forex deals with clients. For example, a 'Bulk' Forex contract for USD 15 million- GBP 10 million could be split up into 15 'Client' deals of USD 1.5 Million - GBP 1 Million.  In this case the system will store the Bulk FX reference in each of the 'Client' deals and to facilitate easier input fields can be defaulted from the 'Bulk' deal to the 'Client' deal. These fields have to be defined in the next two fields in this file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The only value currently allowed is 'BULK'.  (Multivalue field)  Start of an associated multivalue field range DEAL.TYPE to DFLT.FLD.TO.</p>
            <p>Can be Null or the literal 'BULK'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF.VAL.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.INT.PROFIT.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>P &amp; L category code for forward interest cover profit.</p>
            <p>For Amortise FX Position this should be set equal to the Interest Receivable Category and the FWD.INT.LOSS.CAT should be set equal to the Interest Payable Category.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be in range 50000 - 59999.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field if CAT.CODE.FWD.INT field has a value.</p>
            <p>Defaults to null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVALUE.FWD.AL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag (Y, No) to specify that currency positions, generated by contingent movements in a value dated accounting system, should be revalued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or No.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DFLT.FLD.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field on the 'Client' Forex deal into which the information has to be defaulted. </p>
            <p>The field on the Client Forex contract into which the information present in the Nostro deal field (defined in the previous field DFLT.FLD.FRM) is to be defaulted has to be entered here. The field number enterd in this field will be enriched with the field description from the Forex file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric characters.  (Multi-valued and Sub-valued field associated with the earlier field DFLT.FLD.FRM so that more than one field can be setup to be defaulted)</p>
            <p>Has to be a valid field on the Forex file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.CODE.FWD.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Product category code for forward interest cover. </p>
            <p>For position amortisation to take place this field must be set. The ACCOUNT.CLASS record FXCCYPOS must also be set up with a category code to be used in reserve account numbers. </p>
            <p>The SYSTEM record on PM.PARAMETER must also contain a position class for forward interest cover in the field FX.FWD.INT.COVER. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be in range 20000 - 20999.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CATEGORY table with FX application specified.</p>
            <p>Defaults to null.</p>
            <p>No change field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.REVAL.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not P/L and EXCHADS entries are to be booked when contracts with a REVALUATION TYPE that is NOT 'RB', are revalued. </p>
            <p>After authorisation of the record, the value in this field may only be changed by using the application FX.REVAL.PARAMETERS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>YES or NO Mandatory input This field may not be changed if the record has been authorised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.INTERNAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the banks' internal rule for the classification of Foreign Exchange transactions between Spot and Forward.  For example, the market might define spot as being two working days after the deal date, while the bank may want contracts maturing within seven days to be reported as 'Spot'. </p>
            <p>The Foreign Exchange application will make reference to the number of days specified in this field to cross-validate the deal type of a Forex transaction (SPOT or FORWARD) with its value date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters in the range 0-14 (number of working days).  (Mandatory input)  The number of days must be in the range 0-14.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.INT.LOSS.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>P &amp; L category code for forward interest cover loss. </p>
            <p>For Amortise FX Position this should be set equal to the Interest Payable Category </p>
            <p>and the FWD.INT.PROFIT.CAT should be set equal to the Interest Payable  Category. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be in range 50000 - 59999.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field if CAT.CODE.FWD.INT field has a value.</p>
            <p>Defaults to null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the market practice concerning the value date of a SPOT contract. The standard 'Spot' value date is two business days following the day the deal was struck. The condition defined in this field will be used to default the value date on Spot Foreign Exchange contracts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters in the range 0-14 (number of working days). </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>The number of days must be in the range 0-14. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.LIST.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies how many days before the maturity (i.e. value date) the user wants to see the Foreign Exchange contracts to appear in the Forex Maturity report. </p>
            <p>The Foreign Exchange contracts will then appear every day in the report from the first day of appearance to their value date. </p>
            <p>Note : If 0 days is input in this field, no maturity report will be        produced in the Forex End of Day process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 numeric characters.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.CODE.SWAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines into which product category code the swap contract will be classified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The category code used must exist on the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p>The category code defined in this field must have the 'FX' application identifier on the CATEGORY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.ORD.OFS.SRC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies the OFS.SOURCE used to input the FX order, from FX.LIM.ORDER </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Should contain a valid OFS.SOURCE record ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESFWDCR.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
   Holds the category code applicable for Accrual entries on account of a Forex Forward Deal
   with revaluation type other than RB method. As this is a NOINPUT field, 
   updation for the first time is done online by giving a value in the field NEW.RESFWDCR.CAT and 
   on authorization of FX.PARAMETERS. Subsequent changes, if required, will be updated during the COB.
   The code reflected  in this field should be a valid ID in CATEGORY application and
   should be in the range of 10000 to 19999.
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement. </p>
            <p>As in the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to define in the Customer file up to 999 Local elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified.  These local elements should be defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice. </p>
            <p>The name of the new element(s), as well as the Format and <p>Validation Rules:</p>, must be defined in the LOCAL table (Ref: UTILITIES) and LOCAL.REFERENCE table (Ref: UTILITIES) prior to their use in the Customer Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 characters as defined in the LOCAL table (Ref: UTILITIES) definition for this local reference field.  Multivalue field.  (Optional or Mandatory input according to definition in LOCAL table (Ref: UTILITIES) for this Local Reference element.)  As defined by the User within the individual LOCAL Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.RESFWDDR.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
   The category code entered in this field will be updated to RESFWDDR.CAT online for the first time and
   subsequent changes in the following cob, if RESFWDDR.CAT already holds a category code. 
   The code entered here should be a valid id in CATEGORY application and should be in the range 10000 to 19999.
   This field becomes null after the value given herein is updated to the field RESFWDDR.CAT
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILLER1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future used. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the revaluation is calculated against the local currency or the currency specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 Alpha-numeric currency code (type CCY).</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Input can only be made if there are no FX.TRANSACTION records on the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL.REVAL.REP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the frequency for the production of the 'Detailed Revaluation Report' produced by the Forex End of Day process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Frequency code. Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.POST.MATURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of days after maturity that a contract will be written to history. (Closed). </p>
            <p>This field states the number of days after maturity that a contract is removed from the live Foreign Exchange file and written to history. A typical input would be '30' so that monthly reports could include contracts that matured during the month without having to interrogate history files. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-3 numeric characters, within the range 1 to 999. (Mandatory input; minimum value is '1' meaning that the contract will be written to history one day after maturity).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIM.ORDER.INT.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The VERSION id present this field is used as VERSION to populate/create FX LIM ORDER records. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on VERSION table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIM.ORDER.OFS.SRC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The OFS.SOURCE id present in this field is used to perform FX.LIM.ORDER. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on OFS.SOURCE table.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.LCL.REGION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field to define the alternative local holiday region for FOREX spot date determination. The holiday table(s) for the country and region specified here are used in place of the holiday table for the local country and region in the COMPANY record to calculate the FOREX spot date.</p>
            <p>More than one country or region may be specified to accommodate additional holidays.</p>
            <p>To refer to region "00" enter only the country code.</p>
            <p>Standard spot date calculation and alternative FX currency holidays are explained below.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be valid Country or Region.</p>
            <p>Duplicates not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Spot Date Calculation</p>
            <p>The default operation of the system spot date calculation is described below. The default calculation will take place if the fields FX.LCL.REGION and SPOT.BASE.CCY are not specified in the FX.PARAMETERS record.</p>
            <p>When no SPOT.DATE or in the case of a Spot deal (or the first leg of a Swap), the VALUE.DATE.BUY/SELL is not entered, the system will attempt to default the dates. The dates are calculated by addition of the SPOT.MARKET number of days defined in FX.PARAMETERS to the DEAL.DATE to give a common working day for the country of the two currencies involved in the deal.</p>
            <p>Example 1</p>
            <p>Local Currency - GBP</p>
            <p> Local Country - GB(defined in COMPANY)</p>
            <p>Spot Market - 2</p>
            <p>System Date - 2nd July</p>
            <p> Spot Deal - USD/GBP</p>
            <p>Holidays</p>
            <p />
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>US00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Comm</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p>Using the common holidays (Comm) 2 working days gives a spot date of 5th July</p>
            <p>The SPOT.DATE, VALUE.DATE.BUY and VALUE.DATE.SELL would therefore be 5 th July, this is a common working day in both countries and respects the Spot Market period for both.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 2</p>
            <p>If the holidays were as follows for the same deal:</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>US00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Comm</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>Using the common holidays in this case gives a spot date of 6th July</p>
            <p>The default date would therefore be 6th July.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Alternative Local Currency FX Holidays</p>
            <p>There may be cases where an alternative holiday table is required for FX trading in the local currency. A possible scenario is described as follows:</p>
            <p>A system with LOCAL.CURRENCY GBP is running in London, the local country is GB giving a local holiday table of GB00. The system is also used to enter trades by the New York office. As a result the system must be available to the New York users on UK holidays. This means that the local holiday table is in fact a common table of working days between the two countries. Using the previous example :</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>US00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Comm</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>Both 4th July (holiday in US) and 5th July (holiday in UK) are working days in the system so that the New York users can work on 5th&gt; July.</p>
            <p>If a FX deal was done involving GBP and USD on 2nd July as in the previous example a spot date of 5th July would result. This date should not be defaulted in practice as 5th July is not a true working day in the UK, the correct date would be 6th July.</p>
            <p>To avoid this problem an alternative holiday table for the local currency can be defined, and if specified in the FX.LCL.REGION field of the FX.PARAMETERS record this will be used instead of the default holiday table for the currency (in this case GB00). It is recommended that a REGION be created for the local currency for FX trading, a specific holiday table containing the true local holidays can then be created for this region. The region code should then be defined in FX.PARAMETERS as shown.</p>
            <p>Region GB99</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB99</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Figure  FX.PARAMETERS - definition of alternative local holidays</p>
            <p>Any deal involving the local currency will now use the FX.LCL.REGION defined GB99 rather than the standard GB00. Using this definition the previous deal will give the following results:</p>
            <p>Example 3</p>
            <p>Local Currency - GBP</p>
            <p> Local Country - GB(defined in COMPANY)</p>
            <p>Spot Market - 2</p>
            <p>System Date - 2nd July</p>
            <p> Spot Deal - USD/GBP</p>
            <p>Holidays</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tues</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wed</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Thur</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Fri</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sat</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Sun</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mon</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>9</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB99</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>US00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Comm</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>GB00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>H</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p>(Note that GB00 is shown for information only).</p>
            <p>The common holiday table between GB99 and US00 now give the correct spot date of 6th July.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.CHILD.VER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The VERSION id present this field is used as OPERATION for OFS.SOURCE to populate/create FX BULK.ORDER child records</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on VERSION table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.MASTER.VER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The VERSION id present this field is used as VERSION to populate/create FX BULK DEAL master records. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on VERSION table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.OFS.SRC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The OFS.SOURCE id present in this field is used to perform FX.BULK.ORDER. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on OFS.SOURCE table.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.CODE.FWD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines into which product category code the forward contract will be classified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The category code used must exist on the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p>The category code defined in this field must have the 'FX' application identifier on the CATEGORY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUS.MARGIN.DEFAULT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This top level Parameter option deals with  the functionality, where in the margin applicable for a customer in an FX deal can be applied automatically to arrive at the Customer Rate. </p>
            <p> To group the customers/Portfolios of the customers based on certain conditions/criteria and then define the margin percentages to be applied for them, when FX deals are done with the bank, is achieved by using the Condition Priority, FX.GEN.CONDITION and FX.GROUP.CONDITION tables. The value in this field decides whether the Group Condition ID applicable to a Customer / Portfolio is to be defaulted into FX contract at the time of input of the deal .</p>
            <p> Allowed values: YES or NO </p>
            <p> Group Condition ID will be defaulted either from SEC.ACC.MASTER ( if given in FX deal) else from CUSTOMER.CHARGE record. </p>
            <p> NO  = System does not default  FX Group Condition ID in FX deal. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input. </p>
            
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FTT.COLL.CPTY.TAX</field>
<desc>
<p>Provides the option to T24 bank to collect the Financial Transaction Tax payable by the Counterparty also. If yes, accounting entries are raised to collect counterparty’s tax wherein customer Account is debited and Tax suspense Account is credited. The values No or Null means T24 bank does not collect the FTT payable by the counterparty or in other words the counterparty himself remits the FTT. This option is provided on the premise that where the counterparty is a customer of the bank ( not an interbank counterparty) the T24 bank assumes responsibility to collect and pay the FTT payable by the customer</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
	    <p>Values allowed are Yes, No or Null.</p>
	    <p>Value present in this field is defaulted to FTT.COLL.CPTY.TAX field on FOREX which can be overridden by the User. </p>
        </desc>
</t>

</menu>
</t24help>

