<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FX</product>
<table>RE.FOREX.OPTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEL.DATE.SELL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the sell date in the delivery information on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEL.DATE.BUY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the buy date in the delivery information on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.DEL.SELL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the unused sell amount on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.UPDT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field corresponds to the date when this record was last updated by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the status of the delivery set as at the last end of day. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.PAID.INDIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the delivery sell amount corresponding to this multivalue set has already been paid. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
            <p>Set to 'Y' when the delivery sell date is before today.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.LST.CRF.BUY.EOP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the last value date with which the outstanding unused amount was updated in the CRF. The field is used for the internal workings of CRF. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.LCY.EQUIV.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the local equivalent of the unused amount on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID of the RE.FOREX.OPTION record. The ID of this record corresponds to the ID on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A Valid Forex Contract ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEL.AMT.SELL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the sell amount in the delivery information on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.DEL.BUY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the unused buy amount on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEL.LCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This amount signifies the local equivalent amount of the buy or sell delivery amounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORG.VALSELL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the sell value date held on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.LST.CRF.SEL.EOP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the last value date with which the outstanding unused amount was updated in the CRF. The field is used for the internal workings of CRF. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORG.VALBUY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the buy value date held on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUY.PAID.INDIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the delivery buy amount corresponding to this multivalue set has already been paid. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
            <p>Set to 'Y' when the delivery buy date is before today.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.BOUGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the bought currency specified on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
            <p>Must be the same as the bought currency on the FOREX contract pointed to by the ID of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.SOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the sold currency specified on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
            <p>Must be the same as the sold currency on the FOREX contract pointed to by the ID of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEL.AMT.BUY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the old value of the buy amount in the delivery information on the FOREX contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

