<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MG</product>
<table>MG.ACTIVITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to define and control the delivery output from the mortgage module. </p>
            <p>Activities that produce delivery output are defined by the records on this file. These activities relate to specific events during the life a contract. </p>
            <p>The delivery relating to each of these events may, if required, be produced prior to the event itself. If this is the case then the number of days in advance of the event that the advices are produced is defined on this file. </p>
            <p>Whenever delivery output is produced via the mortgage module the activity code of the relevant advice is recorded on the originating record, either MG.MORTGAGE or MG.PARAMETER. When this record is subsequently viewed these activity codes will be displayed and enriched with the description recorded on this file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc>
        <p>Uniquely identifies each record on this file and each activity code within the system. This field identifies the system activity code defined by this record. This ID has two components. Firstly the message type as defined on the DE.MESSAGE table. This must be in the range 1320 to 1323. The second component identifies the particular activity in relation to the message type entered. These message activity codes vary between each type of message. Example : MG.ACTIVITY ID 1321.10 MESSAGE TYPE 1321 Pre-advice message MESSAGE ACTIVITY 10 repayment advice. This activity code is therefore used for pre-advices for repayments. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 7 numeric characters. This field has three components as follows: a) 4 numeric message type code b) "." separator c) 2 numeric activity reference First four characters must be in the range 1320 to 1323.</p>
        <p>DAYS.PRIOR.EVENT</p>
        <p>Specifies the number of calendar days prior to an event that a pre-advice is produced. Activity codes with a message type code of 1321 are pre-advice messages. The delivery output related to these activities may be produced prior to the event to which they relate. This field defines the number of days prior to the event that the delivery output is to be produced. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Numeric input in the range 1 - 25. (optional input) Input only allowed for pre-advice activities, ie. 1321.NN activity codes.</p>
        <p>DESCRIPTION</p>
        <p>Describes the system activity code identified by this record. This field allows for a description to be entered for the activity code identified by the ID of this record. This will be used as an screen enrichment for the activity code identified by this record. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 - 35 alphanumeric characters Multilanguage field.</p>
        <p>HANDOFF.ROUTINE</p>
        <p>HANDOFF.ROUTIN.</p>
        <p>MANUAL.REQUEST</p>
        <p>Specifies whether or not an advice may be requested manually for the activity code defined by the record in question. It is possible to manually request the production of advices for certain activities via the MG.MORTGAGE application. This field controls whether or not an advice may be manually requested for the activity code concerned. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 - 3 alphanumeric characters YES or NO. (mandatory input.</p>
        <p>OVERRIDE</p>
        <p>OVERRIDe</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Uniquely identifies each record on this file and each activity code within the system. </p>
            <p>This field identifies the system activity code defined by this record. This ID has two components. Firstly the message type as defined on the DE.MESSAGE table. This must be in the range 1320 to 1323. </p>
            <p>The second component identifies the particular activity in relation to the message type entered. These message activity codes vary between each type of message. </p>
            <p>Example : </p>
            <p>       MG.ACTIVITY ID      1321.10        MESSAGE TYPE        1321    Pre-advice message        MESSAGE ACTIVITY    10      repayment advice. </p>
            <p>       This activity code is therefore used for pre-advices for repayments. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>7 numeric characters. This field has three components as follows: a)  4 numeric message type code b)  "." separator c)  2 numeric activity reference</p>
            <p>First four characters must be in the range 1320 to 1323.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.PRIOR.EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of calendar days prior to an event that a pre-advice is produced. </p>
            <p>Activity codes with a message type code of 1321 are pre-advice messages. The delivery output related to these activities may be produced prior to the event to which they relate. This field defines the number of days prior to the event that the delivery output is to be produced. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric input in the range 1 - 25. (optional input)</p>
            <p>Input only allowed for pre-advice activities, ie. 1321.NN activity codes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the system activity code identified by this record. </p>
            <p>This field allows for a description to be entered for the activity code identified by the ID of this record. </p>
            <p>This will be used as an screen enrichment for the activity code identified by this record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 35 alphanumeric characters Multilanguage field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>OVERRIDE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANUAL.REQUEST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not an advice may be requested manually for the activity code defined by the record in question. </p>
            <p>It is possible to manually request the production of advices for certain activities via the MG.MORTGAGE application. This field controls whether or not an advice may be manually requested for the activity code concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 alphanumeric characters YES or NO. (mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HANDOFF.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>HANDOFF.ROUTINE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

