<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MG</product>
<table>MG.PAYMENT.CONTROL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The MG.PAYMENT.CONRTOL application is used internally by the system to control the input of MG.PAYMENT records for each contract entered in the system. </p>
            <p>This record will be created automatically when the first payment for the contract concerned is input to the MG.PAYMENT file. This record is subsequently updated automatically whenever a payment record is input, authorised, reversed or deleted. </p>
            <p>There is no facility for the manual maintenance of this file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the next available payment number for the contract in question. </p>
            <p>This field records the next payment number to be used for the contract in question when inputting a new payment via MG.PAYMENT application. </p>
            <p>The value in this field is incremented whenever an unauthorised record is input on the MG.PAYMENT file. Similarly the value in this field will be decremented if an unauthorised input to the MG.PAYMENT file is deleted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc>
        <p>Records the payment number of any unauthorised record on the MG.PAYMENT file for the contract in question. This field records the payment number of any unauthorised payment on the MG.PAYMENT file. This field is updated whenever an unauthorised record is input to the MG.PAYMENT file or an unauthorised record is deleted or authorised. The presence of this field indicates the existance of an unauthorised payment. It is only possible to have one unauthorised payment on the MG.PAYMENT file at any given time. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 - 3 numeric characters.</p>
        <p>PAYMENT.NO</p>
        <p>Uniquely identifies each record on this file. This field uniquely identifies each record on this file. This is the same ID that is used on the main file MG.MORTGAGE and is the identifier assigned to each contract at first input. The format of the key is as follows: MG YYDDD NNNNN A where: MG - Mortgage module identifier. YYDDD - Year and date of contract input, in julian date format. NNNNN - Sequence number which is unique for the date of input. A - Contract suffix which must be defined on the MG.PARAMETER table. It is not necessary to enter the full contract number when viewing a MG.PAYMENT.CONTROL record. The "MG" prefix is not required, neither is the julian date protion if the contract was entered during the current day. In all cases leading zeroes in the final sequence number portion of the key need no be entered. Example : Current date : 22/01/90 Contract no. : MG9012300012 (input 12/01/90) The minimum input required is: 9012312 This will be expanded to give the full id: MG9012300012 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 10 numeric characters prefixed by MG with an optional suffix of 1 alpha character. MGYYDDDNNNNNA (see details) (mandatory input) Must reference an valid contract on the MG.MORTGAGE file.</p>
        <p>PAYMENT.NUMBER</p>
        <p>Identifies the next available payment number for the contract in question. This field records the next payment number to be used for the contract in question when inputting a new payment via MG.PAYMENT application. The value in this field is incremented whenever an unauthorised record is input on the MG.PAYMENT file. Similarly the value in this field will be decremented if an unauthorised input to the MG.PAYMENT file is deleted. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 - 3 numeric characters</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAU.RECORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the payment number of any unauthorised record on the MG.PAYMENT file for the contract in question. </p>
            <p>This field records the payment number of any unauthorised payment on the MG.PAYMENT file. </p>
            <p>This field is updated whenever an unauthorised record is input to the MG.PAYMENT file or an unauthorised record is deleted or authorised. </p>
            <p>The presence of this field indicates the existance of an unauthorised payment. It is only possible to have one unauthorised payment on the MG.PAYMENT file at any given time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Uniquely identifies each record on this file. </p>
            <p>This field uniquely identifies each record on this file. This is the same ID that is used on the main file MG.MORTGAGE and is the identifier assigned to each contract at first input. </p>
            <p>The format of the key is as follows: </p>
            <p>           MG YYDDD NNNNN A </p>
            <p>where:     MG       -  Mortgage module identifier.            YYDDD    -  Year and date of contract input, in julian date                    format.            NNNNN    -  Sequence number which is unique for the date of                    input.            A        -  Contract suffix which must be defined on the                       MG.PARAMETER table. </p>
            <p>It is not necessary to enter the full contract number when viewing a MG.PAYMENT.CONTROL record. The "MG" prefix is not required, neither is the julian date protion if the contract was entered during the current day. In all cases leading zeroes in the final sequence number portion of the key need no be entered. </p>
            <p>Example : </p>
            <p>           Current date :  22/01/90            Contract no. :  MG9012300012 (input 12/01/90) </p>
            <p>The minimum input required is: 9012312 </p>
            <p>This will be expanded to give the full id: </p>
            <p>           MG9012300012 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10 numeric characters prefixed by MG with an optional suffix of 1 alpha character. MGYYDDDNNNNNA (see details) (mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must reference an valid contract on the MG.MORTGAGE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

