<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MG</product>
<table>MG.SCHEDULES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The MG.SCHEDULES application records any future events on contracts by individual event date. The types of event that are recorded on this file are: </p>
            <p>           -    Repayments of principal and interest.            -    Repayments of additional payment types.            -    Penalty interest processing.            -    Principal movements.            -    Levying of charges. </p>
            <p>For each of these event types listed only the next occurence of this event is recorded on this file. For example a contract may require 300 repayments over the duration of its life. However, at any given time there will only be one repayment schedule for the next repayment date. </p>
            <p>Each record on this file is for a specific contract and a specific date. Therefore a single contract is likely to produce a number of records on this file. </p>
            <p>This file is maintained automatically by the system. There is no facility to manually update this file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>ADVICE.SCH </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PENALTY.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that a check for, and a possible payment of, penalty interest is scheduled for the date in question. </p>
            <p>The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that a check for the requirement of a penalty fee, and the possible debiting of such a fee, is required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric character - (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REL.SCHED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>REL.SCHED.DATE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINCIPAL.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that a principal movement is scheduled for the date in question. </p>
            <p>The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that a principal movement is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. This movement will be in respect of the drawdown of funds at contract initiation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric character - (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.ADVICE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIN.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>PRIN.ADVICE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Uniquely identifies each record on this file. </p>
            <p>This field uniquely identifies each record on this file. It is made up of two components, the contract number and the date of the schedule, separated by a dot.  Both elements of the ID must be entered although there are shorthand forms of both. </p>
            <p>In the case of the schedule date this is a standard T24 date. A such only the elements of the date that differ from the current system date need be entered. </p>
            <p>The format of the contract number is as follows: </p>
            <p>           MG YYDDD NNNNN A </p>
            <p>where:     MG        -        Mortgage module identifier.            YYDDD     -        Year and date of contract input, in julian                             date format.            NNNNN     -        Sequence number which is unique for the date                               of input.            A         -        Contract suffix which must be defined on the                               MG.PARAMETER table. </p>
            <p>It is not necessary to enter the full contract number when viewing a schedule. The "MG" prefix is not required, neither is the julian date portion if the contract was entered during the current day. In all cases leading zeroes in the final sequence number portion of the key need no be entered. </p>
            <p>Example : </p>
            <p>           Current date  :     22/01/90            Schedule date :     28/02/90            Contract no.  :     MG9012300012 (input 12/01/90) </p>
            <p>The minimum input required is : 9012312.2802 </p>
            <p>This will be expanded to give the full schedule id: </p>
            <p>           MG9012300012.19900228 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field has three components as follows: a)   A valid contract ID, 10 numeric characters prefixed by MG with      an optional 1 alpha suffix. b)   "." c)   8 numeric characters - standard date format. MGYYDDDNNNNNA.YYYYMMDD (see details) (mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must reference an valid contract on the MG.MORTGAGE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE1.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.CHANGE.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that an interest rate change is scheduled for the date in question. </p>
            <p>The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that a change in the contract interest rate is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric character - (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PENALTY.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>PENALTY.ADVICE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MG.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal Descriptor field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that the application of a charge is scheduled for the date in question. </p>
            <p>The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that the application of a charge is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric character - (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that a repayment is scheduled for the date in question. </p>
            <p>This field indicates that a repayment is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. It also defines the type of repayment. Repayments may be for principal only, interest only, or both. This is indicated in this field by "P", "I" or "PI" respectively. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 2 alpha characters either "P", "I" or "PI".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE2.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSURE.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>CLOSURE.SCH </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.CHANGE.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>RATE.CHANGE.ADVICE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAY.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>REPAY.ADVICE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that a brokerage amount is scheduled for the date  specified in the ID of MG.SCHEDULES. Holds the value 'Y' if brokerage is scheduled for ID date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCHED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal Descriptor field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc>
        <p>ADD.PAY.ADVIC.</p>
        <p>ADD.PAY.SCH</p>
        <p>Indicates that a repayment of an additional payment type is scheduled for the date in question. The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that a repayment of an additional payment type is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. This field does not indicate the specific additional types which are to be repaid but merely the requirement for a repayment. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 alphanumeric character - (Y)e.</p>
        <p>ADVICE.SCH</p>
        <p>ADVICE.SC.</p>
        <p>CHARGE.ADVICE</p>
        <p>CHARGE.ADVIC.</p>
        <p>CHARGE.SCH</p>
        <p>Indicates that the application of a charge is scheduled for the date in question. The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that the application of a charge is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 alphanumeric character - (Y)e.</p>
        <p>CLOSURE.SCH</p>
        <p>CLOSURE.SC.</p>
        <p>CONTRACT.DATE</p>
        <p>Uniquely identifies each record on this file. This field uniquely identifies each record on this file. It is made up of two components, the contract number and the date of the schedule, separated by a dot. Both elements of the ID must be entered although there are shorthand forms of both. In the case of the schedule date this is a standard T24 date. A such only the elements of the date that differ from the current system date need be entered. The format of the contract number is as follows: MG YYDDD NNNNN A where: MG - Mortgage module identifier. YYDDD - Year and date of contract input, in julian date format. NNNNN - Sequence number which is unique for the date of input. A - Contract suffix which must be defined on the MG.PARAMETER table. It is not necessary to enter the full contract number when viewing a schedule. The "MG" prefix is not required, neither is the julian date portion if the contract was entered during the current day. In all cases leading zeroes in the final sequence number portion of the key need no be entered. Example : Current date : 22/01/90 Schedule date : 28/02/90 Contract no. : MG9012300012 (input 12/01/90) The minimum input required is : 9012312.2802 This will be expanded to give the full schedule id: MG9012300012.19900228 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> This field has three components as follows: a) A valid contract ID, 10 numeric characters prefixed by MG with an optional 1 alpha suffix. b) "." c) 8 numeric characters - standard date format. MGYYDDDNNNNNA.YYYYMMDD (see details) (mandatory input) Must reference an valid contract on the MG.MORTGAGE file.</p>
        <p>PENALTY.ADVICE</p>
        <p>PENALTY.ADVIC.</p>
        <p>PENALTY.SCH</p>
        <p>Indicates that a check for, and a possible payment of, penalty interest is scheduled for the date in question. The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that a check for the requirement of a penalty fee, and the possible debiting of such a fee, is required. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 alphanumeric character - (Y)e.</p>
        <p>PRIN.ADVICE</p>
        <p>PRIN.ADVIC.</p>
        <p>PRINCIPAL.SCH</p>
        <p>Indicates that a principal movement is scheduled for the date in question. The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that a principal movement is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. This movement will be in respect of the drawdown of funds at contract initiation. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 alphanumeric character - (Y)e.</p>
        <p>RATE.CHANGE.ADVICE</p>
        <p>RATE.CHANGE.ADVIC.</p>
        <p>RATE.CHANGE.SCH</p>
        <p>Indicates that an interest rate change is scheduled for the date in question. The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that a change in the contract interest rate is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 alphanumeric character - (Y)e.</p>
        <p>REL.SCHED.DATE</p>
        <p>REL.SCHED.DAT.</p>
        <p>REPAY.ADVICE</p>
        <p>REPAY.ADVIC.</p>
        <p>REPAYMENT.SCH</p>
        <p>Indicates that a repayment is scheduled for the date in question. This field indicates that a repayment is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. It also defines the type of repayment. Repayments may be for principal only, interest only, or both. This is indicated in this field by "P", "I" or "PI" respectively. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 - 2 alpha characters either "P", "I" or "PI".</p>
        <p>RESERVE1.SCH</p>
        <p>This field is reserved for future expansion.</p>
        <p>RESERVE2.SCH</p>
        <p>This field is reserved for future expansion.</p>
        <p>ADD.PAY.TYPE</p>
        <p>Please refer helptext of MG.MORTGAG.</p>
        <p>SCHED.DATE</p>
        <p>Internal Descriptor fiel.</p>
        <p>MG.ID</p>
        <p>Internal Descriptor fiel.</p>
        <p>BROKER.SCH</p>
        <p>Indicates that a brokerage amount is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of MG.SCHEDULES. Holds the value 'Y' if brokerage is scheduled for ID date.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.PAY.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>ADD.PAY.ADVICE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.PAY.SCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that a repayment of an additional payment type is scheduled for the date in question. </p>
            <p>The presence of a "Y" in this field indicates that a repayment of an additional payment type is scheduled for the date specified in the ID of the schedule. This field does not indicate the specific additional types which are to be repaid but merely the requirement for a repayment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric character - (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.PAY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Please refer helptext of MG.MORTGAGE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

