<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CO</product>
<table>COLLATERAL.EXCLUSION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p> The main purpose of the file is to mark the collaterals for exclusion</p>
            <p> When user wants to exclude certain collaterals, so that the collateral value is not considered as asset, then the criteria can be defined in this application </p>
            <p> Based on the values defined, the collateral records will be selected and can be marked for exclusion</p>
            <p />
            <p> COUNTRY, CURRENCY, SECURITY.CODE, INDUSTRY, ISSUER &amp; COUNTERPARTY</p>
            <p> The above mentioned six values are the criteria based on which collaterals can be selected</p>
            <p> It is mandatory to define any one criteria in the collateral exclusion record</p>
            <p> Once the required criteria are defined, the collaterals can be marked for exclusion as follows:</p>
            <p>
            <p> New exclusion can be included in collaterals using three ways:</p>
            <p>
            <p> 1. When EXCLUDE.ALL field is set to Yes, then CO.EXCLUDE.SERVICE will select all the collaterals falling under that criteria and update exclusion id in collateral record</p>
            <p> 2. When EXCLUDE.ALL field is set No, then on verifying COLLATERAL.EXCLUSION record, the fast path enquiry CO.EXCLUSION will be launched with the list of collaterals falling under the criteria</p>
               <p> The collaterals required to be marked for exclusion can be selected and committed</p>
               <p> The collaterals marked for exclusion in the enquiry CO.EXCLUSION, can be authorized using CO.EXCLUSION.AUTH enquiry </p>
            <p> 3. Manually include the collateral exclusion id in the collateral record</p>    
            </p> 
            <p>
            <p> Amendment of exclusion can be processed only through CO.EXCLUDE.SERVICE</p>
            <p> When the exclusion criteria is amended, the collateral exclusion id will be removed from the existing collaterals (collaterals with existing criteria) and updated in the collaterals falling under the new criteria</p>
            </p>
            <p> Removal of exclusion can be done in three ways: </p>
            <p> 
            <p> 1. To remove an exclusion from all the collaterals, the collateral exclusion record can be reversed. CO.EXCLUDE.SERVICE will remove the reversed exclusion id from the collateral records</p>
            <p> 2. For removing only specific collaterals from exclusion, the fast path enquiry CO.REMOVE.EXCLUSION can be used</p>
                <p> By giving the collateral exclusion id in CO.REMOVE.EXCLUSION enquiry, list of collaterals falling under that exclusion will be listed</p>
                <p> The exclusion id field of collateral will be editable field in that enquiry. The field can be cleared for the required collaterals and committed</p>
                <p> The records for which exclusion has been removed can be authorized using the enquiry CO.REMOVE.EXCLUSION.AUTH</p>
            <p> 3. Manually remove an exclusion id from collateral. If EXCLUDE.ALL field is set to Yes in the collateral exclusion, then it cannot be removed from collateral record</p>    
            </p>
            </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the collateral exclusion </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters free text.  Multi-value field</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>        
<t>
<field>COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The country whose collateral's are to be excluded</p>
            <p>The country field in collateral specifies where the collateral is held. </p>
            <p>To exclude the collaterals belonging to a specific country, the country name can be defined in this field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 5 alphabetic characters (country code)</p>
            <p>Mandatory input when other criteria fields are not defined</p>
            <p>Valid record in Country file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the collateral which is to be excluded </p>
            <p>The currency in the collateral is that in which the collateral values are expressed. </p>
            <p>If the collaterals of a specific currency to be excluded, then the currency can be defined in this field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alphabetic characters (currency format)</p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Valid record in Currency file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Security code whose collateral's are to be excluded</p>
            <p>The collateral attached can be specific to a Security Master</p>
            <p>If those collaterals are to be excluded, then the Security Master id can be defined in this field</p>
            <p>The value "NULL" in this field is used to exclude the security collaterals without Security Master</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>12 digit optional field</p>
            <p>Valid SECURITY.MASTER record or value NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Industry of the security collateral which is to be excluded</p>
            <p>The Industry field in collateral indicates the industry to which the security belongs </p>
            <p>For excluding the security collaterals belonging to a specific industry, the value can be defined in this field</p>
            <p>The value "NULL" in this field is used to exclude the collaterals which does not have Industry</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 characters</p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in SC.INDUSTRY file or the value "NULL"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field defines the Issuer of the security collateral to be excluded</p>
            <p>To mark the collaterals belonging to a specific issuer for exclusion, this field can be used</p>
            <p>The value "NULL" in this field is used to exclude the collaterals which does not have Issuer</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10 digit multi-value field</p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTERPARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Counterparty i.e. Customer of the collateral whose collaterals are to be marked for exclusion</p>
            <p>If a customer's collateral to be excluded, then customer id can be defined in this field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10 digit optional field</p>
            <p>Valid customer record or the value "NULL"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.ALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate whether all collaterals belonging to the criteria defined in other fields are to be excluded or not</p>
            <p>When the field is set to Yes, the service CO.EXCLUDE.SERVICE, will select all the collaterals falling under the criteria and will update the exclusion id</p>
            <p>When the field is set to No, then the collaterals can be excluded using the fast-path enquiry CO.EXCLUSION</p>
            <p>On verify the collateral exclusion record, the fast path enquiry CO.EXCLUSION will be launched with the list of collaterals based on the criteria</p>
            <p>The collaterals required to be excluded can be selected and committed</p>
            <p>Other fast path enquiry CO.EXCLUSION.AUTH can be used to authorized the collateral records from exception</p>
            <p>When this field is set to Yes, then the new collaterals if fall under the exclusion criteria, then exclusion id will be automatically defaulted in the EXCLUSION id field of collateral</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Values allowed are Yes or No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
