<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CO</product>
<table>COLLATERAL.CODE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                  COLLATERAL CODE </p>
            <p />
            <p>The information on this file is used to identify categories of collateral right. </p>
            <p>The collateral code file permits definition of the allowable collateral (object) types which may occur under each category of right and permits the definition of a default frequency of review of these rights. </p>
            <p>This collateral code is also used in determining how collateral values are reallocated across central bank reporting lines. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PERCENT.DATE.FQU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines when the system is to perform a recalculation of the percentage of cover applicable to collateral rights held under this code. </p>
            <p>A combined date &amp; frequency field which determines if and when the system is to automatically recalculate the value of the PERCENTAGE COVER (field 4) of collateral right main file records belonging to this code. </p>
            <p>When such a recalculation is performed, the date part of this field is automatically cycled according to the frequency part. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>17 type FQU (frequency format). (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVIEW.FQU</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default review frequency applicable to this category of collateral right. </p>
            <p>The content of this field is used to generate a default value for the REVIEW DATE FQU (field 6) when input is made to the collateral right main file using this code. </p>
            <p>The permitted values of the frequency code are as follows: </p>
            <p>BSNSS - business (working) days; date is to be cycled each business day, </p>
            <p>DAILY - date is to be cycled daily (ie. each calendar day), </p>
            <p>WEEKn - where n is a number in the range 1 to 9; date is to be cycled every n weeks, </p>
            <p>TWMTH - twice monthly; date cycles twice monthly on the 15th and last day of each month, </p>
            <p>Mmmdd - where mm is a number in the range 1 to 12 and dd is a number in the range 1 to 31; describes a cycle on a particular day (dd) each month or every mm months. </p>
            <p>These frequency codes correspond to the equivalent codes contained in the standard date/frequency combined format. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters (frequency code). (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Short name of the category of collateral right. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 15 characters free text. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLATERAL.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique identification of collateral code. </p>
            <p>The identifier of a category of collateral rights. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 3-digit numeric.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLATERAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The collateral type or types which are normally associated with this code. </p>
            <p>Input to this field must be a valid collateral type defined on the collateral type file. </p>
            <p>The collateral code usually relates to a particular type of object, in which case this type may be entered in this field. </p>
            <p>When more than one possible type of object occurs under a given type of right, all the allowable types should be mentioned here. </p>
            <p>In either case, the first value entered in this field (for the code which has been allocated to the corresponding right) is taken as the default value of the COLLATERAL TYPE (field 1) on the collateral main file. Input of any other type of collateral may be made on the main file, but will require acceptance of an override. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:      If no input is made to this field, the system will            not link automatically from the collateral right            application to the collateral (object) application            when this code has been used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 3-digit numeric. Multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Values may not be duplicated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the category of collateral right. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters free text. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

