<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CO</product>
<table>CUSTOMER.COLLATERAL.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc>
        <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext">
            <p />
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the type of Collateral</p>
            <p>VALIDATION RULES</p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters free text. Multi-language field. (Mandatory input)     Defaults from the main collateral type record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXECUTION.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Execution value as a percentage of Nominal Value but different from that  in the main Collateral Type record. </p>
            <p>Example.</p>
            <p>COLLATERAL.TYPE-100-cash collaterals-EXECUTION.VALUE-100%N</p>
            <p>CUSTOMER.COLLATERAL.TYPE-100053-100-EXECUTION.VALUE-75%N.</p>
            <p>In the above case Execution Value for the collaterals under Collateral Type 100 for the customer 100053 will be calculated at 75%N only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input; Allowed as  %N only, in the range 0-100. (E.g.50%N, 60%N     Etc.)</p>
            <p>Duplication of the percentage in the main record not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique identification of customer collateral type. The format is a valid customer number followed by a valid collateral type separated by a hyphen. </p>
            <p>Example:</p>
            <p>COLLATERAL.TYPE: ID=100</p>
            <p>NOMINAL. VALUE=F</p>
            <p>EXECUTION.VALUE=100%N</p>
            <p>When collaterals are created under this collateral type, the execution value will be calculated at100% of the nominal value for all customers. </p>
            <p>If the user desires to fix the execution value differently @ 50%N, for the collaterals under this collateral type to a particular customer say 100053, then this table can be used. The ID of the CUSTOMER.COLLATERAL.TYPE record will be 100053-100, in which user can input the desired percentage in the field EXECUTION.VALUE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Customer Number followed by a valid Collateral Type separated by a     hyphen. </p>
            <p>Input allowed only if the EXECUTION.VALUE  in main COLLATERAL.TYPE is %N. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

