<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CO</product>
<table>CUSTOMER.PLEDGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PLEDGE.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The priority given by ID customer to recipient customer mentioned in PLEDGE.CUSTOMER</p>
            <p />
            <p>The priority cannot be duplicated in the same record or in any other  record. </p>
            <p />
            <p>For example. If A is offering priority 1 to B, then no other customer can offer the same priority (i.e. 1) to B. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Similarly, if A offers priority 1 to B, then he cannot duplicate the same priority either in the same record or in any other record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-value field associated with the field     PLEDGE.CUSTOMER</p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 Numeric Character</p>
            <p />
            <p>The priority cannot be duplicated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLEDGE.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field indicates the customer to whom a pledge is given by the ID customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-Value field</p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p>Valid Customer Number other than the ID customer</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Could be any valid customer ID</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be a valid customer</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERNAL.PLEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This is an indication whether the customer in PLEDGE. CUSTOMER is eligible for allocation of internal pledge by the account officer. If this field is set to YES then, it means that internal pledge is available, for the customer mentioned in field 1 above.  Otherwise, internal pledge is not available.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Multi-value field associated with the field PLEDGE.CUSTOMER</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES or NO.</p>
            <p>If left blank, the default value will be NO.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.PLEDGE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maximum amount of pledge amount that can be allotted to the recipient customer mentioned in PLEDGE.CUSTOMER,  from the available pledge amount of the ID customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount format </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Multi-value field associated with the field PLEDGE.CUSTOMER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

