<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DM</product>
<table>DM.APPLICATION.INFO</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This application stores  the details of T24</p>
            <p />
            <p />applications for which DM Module processing should be invoked; it also specifies the Customer Types in the applications, for which documents should be tracked.  <p />  This is a Company specific application and <p>records of this application could not be reversed.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>APPLN.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies Mnemonic for the application, for Document Tracking purposes. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory     field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum     four and minimum two alphanumeric characters with the first character alphabet.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Once     authorized can not be changed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Should     be unique.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.DOC.OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies whether an error message is to be displayed or an override message is to be displayed while tracking non-contract specific documents, which have already been tracked by a transaction different from that of</p>
            <p />the application. <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional field</p><p>Acceptable values are YES or NO or NULL</p><p>If Yes is given, Override will be generated otherwise Error will be     generated.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the names of customer fields in the Application. Documents would be tracked only for the  customer(s)  whose IDs equal the values  of the fields  defined here.</p>
            <p>If no field is defined, then  documents for this application could  be tracked only from a related application.</p>
            <p>Example.1</p>
            <p>Record ID-FUNDS.TRANSFER</p>
            <p>APPLN.MNEMONIC-FT</p>
            <p>CUST.FIELD.NAME-DEBIT.CUSTOMER</p>
            <p>CUST.FIELD.NAME-CREDIT.CUSTOMER</p>
            <p>When an FT is input,   T24 will track  required documents for  customers whose IDs equal to the values of  the fields DEBIT.CUSTOMER and CREDIT.CUSTOMER in the FT.  </p>
            <p>Example.2</p>
            <p>Record ID- SEC.TRADE</p>
            <p>APPLN.MNEMONIC-SETR</p>
            <p>CUST.FIELD.NAME-CUSTOMER.NO</p>
            <p>When a SEC.TRADE is input, since CUSTOMER.NO is a multi-value field, T24 will track required documents for  all customers whose IDs equal to the values of  the field CUSTOMER.NO in the SEC.TRADE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example.3</p>
            <p>Record ID-SECURITY.MASTER</p>
            <p>APPLN.MNEMONIC-SEMR</p>
            <p>CUST.FIELD.NAME- Null </p>
            <p>In the above case, documents will not be tracked when a record is directly input in SECURITY.MASTER. However, if  SECURITY.MASTER  is defined as a related application for SEC.TRADE (in the application  DOCUMENT.REQUIRED),  when a record is input in  SEC.TRADE,  documents for SECURITY.MASTER  will be also tracked along with those required for SEC.TRADE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Value     allowed only if  the application specified in the ID is a CUS or FIN     type application (Value of the field  CLASSIFICATION in FILE.CONTROL      is CUS or FIN for the application specified in the ID).</p>
            <p />
            <p>Any     valid field defined in the Standard Selection of the application. However     care must to taken to define only those fields which represent a Customer     ID. </p>
            <p />
            <p>For     CUSTOMER application, only allowed value would be @ID i.e. the ID of the     Customer record itself. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DM.APPLN.INFO.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Record ID could be any valid T24 application for which documents need to be tracked. </p>
            <p>When a record is input in an application, documents would be tracked only if the application is defined in this file. </p>
            <p>Example </p>
            <p>LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS </p>
            <p>SEC.TRADE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid T24 application whose product is installed in the company.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Records of this application could not be reversed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

