<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DM</product>
<table>DOCUMENT.STATUS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This application  stores the details of Status codes used in the document data files TRANS.DOCUMENT.  </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Records with IDs </p>
            <p>1 </p>
            <p>(Received), </p>
            <p>2 </p>
            <p>(Not Received) and </p>
            <p>3 </p>
            <p>(Expired) are supplied during installation and these records should not be modified, since these Status ID values  are  used by T24 </p>
            <p />in processing. While Status <p>1 </p><p>is a valid one, both Status </p><p>2 </p><p>and </p><p>3 </p><p>are invalid. </p><p /><p /><p /><p>Users could define their own Status codes in this application which could be either Valid or Invalid (Field: </p><p>VALID </p><p>set to </p><p>YES</p><p> or </p><p>NO</p><p>).</p><p /><p /><p /><p>This is an installation level application shared by all Companies and records of this application could not be reversed.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VALID.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>For a valid status (Value of the Field VALID is YES), this field specifies the period up to which a Document of this status is valid. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The validity  period could be calculated  either from Status-Date or from its calendar year beginning for  a document of this status.</p>
            <p>Refer to the help text for the field END.DATE in the file CUST.DOCUMENT for calculation of expiry date using this field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example</p>
            <p />
            <p>VALID.PERIOD=Null, No End date would be calculated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Calculation from Status-Date: VALID.PERIOD= 12M.  For a document with  this status and  a STATUS.DATE of  20.2.2002,  its End date would be calculated as 19.2.2003.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Calculation from Status-Date's calendar year beginning: VALID.PERIOD= 12MS.  For a document of this status and  a STATUS.DATE of  20.2.2002,  its End date would be calculated as 31.12.2002.</p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>For invalid status (value of the field VALID is NO), no value would be     allowed.</p>
            <p>Must be in the format xxxD, xxxM or  xxxY to specify the  number     of days, months or  years respectively  from Status-Date. </p>
            <p>Must be in the format xxxDS, xxxMS or xxxYS to specify the number of days,     months or years respectively from Status-Date's calendar year     beginning. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the status.</p>
            <p>Example</p>
            <p>Fax copy, Email, Signature incomplete, etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input Mandatory.</p>
            <p>1-35 Alpha numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Multi language  field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.STAT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This file stores the details of Status codes used in the document files CUST.DOCUMENT and TRANS.DOCUMENT.</p>
            <p>ID can be  any positive integer subject to a maximum of 10 characters. </p>
            <p>Records with IDs 1 (Received), 2 (Not Received) and 3 (Expired) are supplied during installation and they are  used by T24 in processing.</p>
            <p>Records in this file could not be reversed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>For user input, 1-10 numeric characters other than the values of 1, 2 or 3.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether this  status,  if attached to a Document tracked for a customer would make it  valid (Value of YES) or  invalid (Value of NO).</p>
            <p>If the status attached to a  required document is invalid, then T24 may  do additional processing like generating overrides, etc. for the document.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input mandatory.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are YES/NO.</p>
            <p>Input not allowed for System generated records with IDs 2 and 3.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

