<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DM</product>
<table>DOCUMENT.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This application records common characteristics of Document Types, which is a second level of classification of  Documents after Document Type. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is an installation level application shared by all Companies and records of this application could not be reversed.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VALID.COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Companies in which Documents of  this  Type needs to be tracked.</p>
            <p>Example: For an LD contract, Document Type A is specified as a required Document Type in all Companies. However, if the Document Type A is restricted here to only Companies BNK and BN2, then Document A would be tracked,  only when an  LD contract is input from either Company BNK or BN2.</p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-value Optional field.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid id of the table MNEMONIC.COMPANY.</p>
            <p>A value of Null signifies that there is  no Company dependent     restriction for tracking documents of this type. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifes the version of the Document Type.</p>
            <p>For information purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-35 alpha numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Optional.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the Document Type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi value language field.</p>
            <p>Input mandatory.</p>
            <p>1-35 Alpha numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>     The date and frequency of review for the document type.</p>
            <p>A combined date &amp; frequency field which is automatically cycled by the system as part of the document type application's end-of-day.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>10 type FQU (combined date &amp; frequency code). (Optional input)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.TYPE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of the DOCUMENT.TYPE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10 alpha characters.</p>
            <p>Records of this application could not be reversed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALID.BASE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies which of the fields STAUS.DATE or SIG.DATE   would be used to calculate the  validity for  a Document of  this type. </p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory if the field VALID.PERIOD has a value.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values are STATUS.DATE or  SIG.DATE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Value     </p>
            <p>of SIG.DATE is allowed only if  the value of the field SIGNATURE.REQD is Yes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUIV.DOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies document type(s) which are considered as equivalent to this document type,  in terms of purpose and processing.  </p>
            <p>If an equivalent document type exists  with a valid status, it would be treated for the purposes of document tracking as if  the main document type exists  with a valid status.</p>
            <p>Equivalence of document types would be checked at only one level. i.e. If Document Type A has an equivalent Document Type B and Document Type B has an equivalent Document Type C, when A is tracked only the existence of B with a valid status would be checked and any status of C would be ignored.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the ID of a valid record in the file DOCUMENT.TYPE except ID of     the current Document Type. </p>
            <p>Not allowed for Contract specific documents (Field CONTACT.SPECIFIC is     YES) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The desired period, prior to the expiry date of a document of this type, notices need to be sent to Customers, could be specified here.</p>
            <p />
            <p>For information purposes only.</p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>1-999 D (day), M (month) or Y (year) accepted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the date up to  which the document type would be effective for tracking purposes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input optional.</p>
            <p>Date entered should be greater than or equal to BEGIN. DATE.</p>
            <p>Date entered should be greater than or equal to Bank Date.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 date format. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALID.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the period up to which a Document of this type would be  valid from the date specified in the field VALID.BASE.DATE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The validity  period could be specified  either from the date specified in the field VALID.BASE.DATE or from its  calendar year beginning.</p>
            <p>If the status attached to a document of this type is invalid, then T24 would not calculate its expiry date, using the definition of this field.</p>
            <p>Refer to the help text for the field END.DATE in the file CUST.DOCUMENT for calculation of expiry date using this field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example</p>
            <p />
            <p>VALID.PERIOD=Null, No End date would be calculated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>VALID.PERIOD= 12M, VALID.BASE.DATE=STATUS.DATE. For a document of this type with a STATUS.DATE of  20.2.2002,  its End date would be calculated as 19.2.2003.</p>
            <p />
            <p>VALID.PERIOD= 12MS, VALID.BASE.DATE=STATUS.DATE -  calculation to be done from year Beginning. For a document of this type with a STATUS.DATE of  20.2.2002,  its End date would be calculated as 31.12.2002.</p>
            <p />
            <p>VALID.PERIOD= 12M, VALID.BASE.DATE=SIG.DATE. For a document of this type with a SIG.DATE of  19.2.2002,  its End date would be calculated as 18.2.2003.</p>
            <p />
            <p>VALID.PERIOD= 12MS, VALID.BASE.DATE=SIG.DATE - calculation to done from year beginning. For a document of this type with a SIG.DATE of  19.2.2002,  its End date would be calculated as 31.12.2002.</p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Must be in the format xxxD, xxxM or  xxxY to specify the  number     of days, months or  years respectively  from the VALID.BASE.DATE. </p>
            <p>Must be in the format xxxDS, xxxMS or xxxYS to specify the number of days,     months or years respectively from the VALD.BASE.DATE's calendar year     beginning. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.ALL.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the document type (if required for Customer creation),  needs to be tracked only for new Customers created on or after the BEGIN.DATE.</p>
            <p>If the value of this field is YES:</p>
            <p>Document type would be tracked  for new customers created  on or     after the BEGIN.DATE, provided it is a required document type for     them. </p>
            <p>When an existing  Customer  is modified, and if this document     type is a required one, it  would be tracked (its Status would be     tested  for processing) only if it has been already tracked (record     exists in the file  CUST.DOCUMENT) for that  Customer.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input with allowed values YES/NO.</p>
            <p>A Null value would be interpreted as NO. </p>
            <p>YES  not allowed if the field CONTRACT.SPECIFIC is YES. </p>
            <p>YES not allowed when equivalent documents (Field: EQUIV.DOC) are     specified. </p>
            <p>This Document Type could be specified as a required document type only for     a Customer document group.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEGIN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the date from which the document type would be  tracked. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory.</p>
            <p>Defaults to Bank Date.</p>
            <p>Cannot be less than Bank Date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the document class  to which the document type belongs to.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input Mandatory.</p>
            <p>Must be ID of a valid record in the file DOCUMENT.CLASS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.SPECIFIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether a document of this type needs to be obtained separately for each contract (Transaction) from the customer.</p>
            <p>Example: A Promissory Note might be obtained for each loan granted to a Customer.</p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input mandatory.</p>
            <p>Allowed values YES/NO. Defaults to NO.</p>
            <p>Once input and authorized can not be changed.</p>
            <p>Both the fields NEW.ALL.CUST and CONTRACT.SPECIFIC cannot be YES.</p>
            <p>If YES, the document type cannot be specified as a required document type     for a Customer Document Group.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.TO.ARCHIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is a samle help text.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVIEW.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a  frequency and next date of review  for the document type. A document type could be periodically reviewed for its format, usefulness, etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Standard frequency format.</p>
            <p>Date should be greater or equal to Bank Date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGNATURE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether a signature is required for this document type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values NO/YES. </p>
            <p>A value of Null would be interpreted as NO. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   Unique reference for each type of document in free format text.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10 Alphanumeric characters. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

