<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DM</product>
<table>TRANS.DOCUMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This file stores details of  Contract specific documents tracked for customers, in all applications other than CUSTOMER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When a transaction  is authorized, Contract specific documents tracked for it  would be created by T24 in this application. Users also could create or modify the records in this application.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>Records of this application could not be reversed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When a transaction is reversed in an application, its related documents in this application  would be reversed by T24.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LAST.UPD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>T24 maintained field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Date of last update to the record.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the expiry  date in case of  a document with a  valid status. The document would be valid till  the date specified here and would expire afterwards. </p>
            <p>If for a valid document, this field is not specified (Null), then the document would be valid for ever with no expiry date.</p>
            <p>In case a document is invalid, this field conveys no special meaning for processing; for invalid documents it  might be used to set up a date for reminder purposes. For example, in case a document is not received (an invalid status) and a reminder is sent to the customer, this field might be used to specify a date on which a chaser has to be sent to the customer.</p>
            <p>T24 would not update  the value of this field for documents with an invalid status, exception being when a document is created by T24 with a Status 1 (based on User Confirmation of YES to T24 confirmation message: "Have you received...."), irrespective of whether Status 1 is valid or invalid. For invalid  documents, user might input any date greater than or equal to Bank date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>T24 would calculate the value of this field for documents  as follows:</p>
            <p>1. As per the definition of  document  validity  in the record with ID equal to attached status (Field STATUS) in the file DOCUMENT.STATUS.  </p>
            <p>2. As per the definition of  document  validity  in the record with ID equal to the value of Document Type (specified in the first part of ID)  in the file DOCUMENT.TYPE.  </p>
            <p> 3. The calculated END.DATE would be the least of the dates calculated as per 1 and 2 above. </p>
            <p>User could override a T24 calculated END.DATE with a  lesser date.</p>
            <p>Example </p>
            <p>The following table shows how the END.DATE is calculated by T24 and how  User could override it. The table shows the calculations for Documents with any valid Status. The Bank Date is  20.03.02. In column 9, in all cases,  user input should be greater than or equal to Bank Date 20.03.02. LE means "Less than or Equal to"</p>
            <p />
            <p>STATUS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>VALID.</p>
            <p />
            <p>PERIOD</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(IN DOCUMENT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>STATUS)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>End-Date as per       STATUS</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>VALID.</p>
            <p />
            <p>PERIOD</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(</p>
            <p>IN</p>
            <p />
            <p>DOCUMENT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>TYPE)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>VALID.BASE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p>(in DOCUMENT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>TYPE)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>SIG.DATE </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>End-Date </p>
            <p />
            <p>as per DOCUMENT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>TYPE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>T24</p>
            <p />
            <p>Calculated</p>
            <p>       End-Date</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(Lesser of 3 and 7)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>User Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Final End-Date</p>
            <p />
            <p>(1)</p>
            <p>(2)</p>
            <p>(3)</p>
            <p>(4)</p>
            <p>(5)</p>
            <p>(6)</p>
            <p>(7)</p>
            <p>(8)</p>
            <p>(9)</p>
            <p>(10)</p>
            <p />
            <p>15.3.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>30 Days</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 Year</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>STATUS.DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Not Relevant</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>14.3.03</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Any date LE 13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02 or User Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>15.3.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>30 Days</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 Year</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>STATUS.DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Not Relevant</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>14.3.03</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Any date LE 13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02 or User Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>15.3.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>30 Days</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>60 Days</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>SIG.DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p>10.3.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>8.5.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Any date LE 13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02 or User Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>15.3.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>60 Days</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>SIG.DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p>10.3.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>8.5.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>8.5.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Any date LE 8.5.02</p>
            <p />
            <p>8.5.02 or User Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>15.3.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>30 Days</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Not Relevant</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Any date LE 13.4.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>13.4.02 or User Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>15.3.02</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Not Relevant</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null or any date       greater than or equal to 20.3.02 (Bank Date) </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null</p>
            <p />or User Input <p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional.</p><p>Standard T24 date format.</p><p>Must be Greater than or Equal to the Bank Date.</p><p>Calculation, default and user input rules as per above defined conditions.</p><p>If END.DATE is less than Bank Date, then only allowed Status would be     "Expired" (value of 3).</p><p>If the status is changed to "Expired", End Date would default to     previous working  Date and can not be changed.</p><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the expiry  date in case of  a next document (document to replace the current one). </p>
            <p>T24 would not calculate the value of this field, if the next document is with an invalid status (Field: NEXT.STATUS). </p>
            <p>T24 would calculate the value of this field, if the next  document is  with a valid status, as follows:</p>
            <p>1. As per  document  validity  defined in  the record with ID equal to attached status (Field: NEXT.STATUS), in the file DOCUMENT.STATUS.  </p>
            <p>2. As per document  validity defined in  the  record with ID equal to  value of Document Type (specified in the first part of ID),  in the file DOCUMENT.TYPE.  </p>
            <p> 3. The calculated NEXT.END.DATE would be the least of the dates calculated as per 1 and 2 above. </p>
            <p>User could override a T24 calculated NEXT.END.DATE with a  lesser date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
            <p>Value allowed only if NEXT.STATUS is specified.</p>
            <p>If NEXT.STATUS is invalid, it is optional; if specified, it must be     greater than or equal to the Bank Date.</p>
            <p>If NEXT.STATUS is valid, then calculated or user input NEXT.END.DATE, if     not null, should be greater than or equal to NEXT.EFF.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on which Signature has been obtained on the Document. </p>
            <p>Value of this field might   be  used by T24 in calculation of Expiry Date (Field: END.DATE), of a Document with valid status.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
            <p>Date, if entered, should be less than or equal to Bank Date.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only if  value of the filed SIGNATURE.REQD is YES       in  the document type's record  in the file DOCUMENT.TYPE.</p>
            <p>If the attached status is a valid one, and value of the field      SIGNATURE.REQD is YES  in  the document type's record  in the     file DOCUMENT.TYPE, then input is mandatory for this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.SIG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on which Signature has been obtained on the Next Document (document to replace the current one).</p>
            <p>Value of this field might   be  used by T24 in calculation of Expiry Date (Field: NEXT.END.DATE) of  the next document, if it  has  a valid status.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
            <p>Value not allowed if NEXT.STATUS is not specified.</p>
            <p>Date, if entered, should be less than or equal to Bank Date.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only if  value of the filed SIGNATURE.REQD is YES       in  the document type's record  in the file DOCUMENT.TYPE.</p>
            <p>If the attached status (Field: NEXT.STATUS) is a valid one, and value of     the field  SIGNATURE.REQD is YES  in  the document type's     record  in the file DOCUMENT.TYPE, then input is mandatory for this     field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p>T24 maintained field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Value would be MANUAL if updated by User.</p>
            <p>Value would be SYSTEM is updated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the mandatory</p>
            <p />future effective date of<p />a next document (document to replace the current one), with a valid status.  <p /><p>When a next document is obtained from a Customer before the expiry of the current one, it could  be made immediately effective,  by directly updating the fields for the current document i.e. REFERENCE.NO to DOC.SEQUENCE</p><p>However, if the next document is with a valid status (Field: NEXT.STATUS is valid), then it would  be possible to make it effective from any  future date. </p><p /><p>If the status of the next document is valid (Field: NEXT.STATUS is valid), on the start-of-day of  its effective date, T24 would update the details of the current document with that of the next one as follows:  STATUS by NEXT.STATUS, STATUS.DATE by NEXT.STATUS.DATE,  END.DATE by NEXT.END.DATE,  STAT.DETAILS by NEXT.DETAILS,  SIG.DATE by NEXT.SIG.DATE; also the DOC.SEQUENCE would be incremented by 1.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Value allowed only if the status of the next document (Field:     NEXT.STATUS)  is specified.</p><p /><p /><p>Value not     allowed if  the status of the next document (Field: NEXT.STATUS)      is invalid.</p><p /><p /><p>Value     mandatory if the status of the next document (Field: NEXT.STATUS) is valid.</p><p /><p /><p>If specified,     its value should be greater than Bank Date.</p><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the remarks if any, on the status of the next document (document to replace the current one).</p>
            <p>For information purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only if the field NEXT.STATUS is specified.</p>
            <p>1-35 Alpha numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is to input any comments on the status of the document.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>1- 35 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Any valid DOCUMENT.TYPE ID can be input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-35 Alphanumeric characters.   </p>
            <p>Optional Field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAT.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the remarks if any, on the current status of the document. </p>
            <p>For information purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional.</p>
            <p>1-35 Alpha numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.UPD.APPLN</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When the document record is updated by </p>
            <p>T24</p>, this field specifies the application from which T24 is updating it.<p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional.</p><p>If specified, should be same as the Application mnemonic forming part of     the ID of the record. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.DOC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This file stores details of  contract specific documents tracked for customers.</p>
            <p>Format of the ID must be "Customer ID.*  Application Mnemonic * Transaction ID * Document Type ID",  where the first part refers to  the ID of a valid CUSTOMER record, second part refers to  the Mnemonic of an  application (field APPLN.MNEMONIC in DM.APPLICATION.INFO), third part refers to the ID of a valid  record in the application, and the last part refers to the  ID  of a valid DOCUMENT.TYPE record. </p>
            <p>Value of the last  part of ID (DOCUMENT.TYPE)  would be  used by T24 in calculation of Expiry Date  (Field: END.DATE) of  a  Document with valid status. </p>
            <p>Records in this file cannot be reversed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>First part of the ID should be the ID of a valid CUSTOMER record.</p>
            <p>Second part of the ID should be a valid value of the field APPLN.MNEMONIC     in DM.APPLICATION.INFO for an application. </p>
            <p>Third part must be the ID of  a valid record in the application     referred to in the second part.</p>
            <p>Last part must be the ID of a valid DOCUMENT.TYPE record.</p>
            <p>Value of the field CONTRACT.SPECIFC in the relevant DOCUMENT.TYPE record     should be YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the status of the document.</p>
            <p>Value of this field would  be  used by T24 in calculation of Expiry Date (Field: END.DATE), of a Document with valid status.</p>
            <p>T24 would update the value of  this field to 3 ("Expired") at Batch processing on Expiry Date (Field: END.DATE), if this field refers to a valid status.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Should be the ID of  a valid record in the file      DOCUMENT.STATUS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLN.TXN.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When the document record is updated by </p>
            <p>T24</p>, this field specifies the transaction reference number of the application,<p />from which T24 is updating it.<p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory if LAST.UPD.APPLN is specified.</p><p>Value not allowed if LAST.UPD.APPLN is not specified.</p><p>If specified, its value should be same as the Transaction ID which forms a     part of the record ID. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEGIN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date from which the document is tracked in T24.</p>
            <p>For information purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field. </p>
            <p>Defaults to Bank Date of  original input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.SEQUENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the sequence number of  a document, to distinguish a new document obtained on expiry of the original one.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when one of  the fields STATUS or STATUS.DATE     is  updated.</p>
            <p>Value could be updated only in increments of 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the status of the next document (document to replace the current one).</p>
            <p>This might be used to specify user defined status such as "Advice sent", etc. for the next document, when an advice is sent to the customer for a new document,  before the expiry of the current one. It might also represent the status of the next document which might have been obtained from the Customer before the expiry of the current one, and which could be effective from a future date.</p>
            <p>Value of this field would  be  used by T24 in calculation of  Expiry  Date (Field: NEXT.END.DATE) of the Next Document, if it  has  a  valid status.</p>
            <p>On the End-of-day of  the current document expiry (Field: END.DATE), if the  next document is with an  invalid status and its end date (Field:NEXT.END.DATE) is either null or not less than next working day, then T24 would update the current document details with that of the next one. i.e. the fields  </p>
            <p>STATUS by NEXT.STATUS, STATUS.DATE by NEXT.STATUS.DATE,  END.DATE by NEXT.END.DATE,  STAT.DETAILS by NEXT.DETAILS,  SIG.DATE by NEXT.SIG.DATE; also the DOC.SEQUENCE would be incremented by 1.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Should be the ID of  a valid record in the file      DOCUMENT.STATUS.</p>
            <p>Value of 3 ("Expired") not allowed.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Date from which the status applies to the document.</p>
            <p>Value of this field might   be  used by T24 in calculation of Expiry Date (Field: END.DATE), of a Document with valid status.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory. </p>
            <p>Defaults to the Bank Date.</p>
            <p>Can not be greater than the Bank Date.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.STATUS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Date from which the status (Field: NEXT.STATUS) applies to the next document (document to replace the current one).</p>
            <p>Value of this field might   be  used by T24 in calculation of Expiry  Date (Field: NEXT.END.DATE) of the next document, if it  has a valid status.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Value now allowed if the field NEXT.STATUS is not specified.</p>
            <p>Mandatory if the field NEXT.STATUS is specified. </p>
            <p>Defaults to Bank Date if NEXT.STATUS is invalid and to NEXT.EFF.DATE if     NEXT.STATUS is valid.</p>
            <p>If NEXT.STATUS is invalid, it should be less than or equal to Bank Date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If NEXT.STATUS is valid, it should be less than or     equal to NEXT.EFF.DATE.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Reference for the document, if any.</p>
            <p>For information purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional.</p>
            <p>1-35 Alpha numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

