<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LM</product>
<table>LMM.ACCOUNT.BALANCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The LMM.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file contains the financial information pertinent to all LOANS AND DEPOSITS &amp; MONEY MARKET contracts. There is only one version of the record and it is established when a contract is first input and validated. </p>
            <p>The information that this record contains can be classified into four main sections: </p>
            <p>      (i) Principal movements over the life of the contract. </p>
            <p>     (ii) Interest accrual details. </p>
            <p>    (iii) Commission accrual details. </p>
            <p>     (iv) Funds paid/received on the contract. </p>
            <p>All updates to this file are effected automatically by the system and the only functions users are allowed to perform are (L)IST, (S)EE and (P)RINT. </p>
            <p>When a contract is written to history, either due to reversal or maturity, its LMM.ACCOUNT.BALANCES record is also written to history, although this may be "n" days after the reversal or maturity (as per field DAYS.POST.MATURITY on LMM.INSTALL.CONDS record). </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CUM.PRIN.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The cumulative principal that the customer has ever received on a contract. Used by payment routines to ensure that payments are not duplicated and consequently updated when payments are physically sent rather than 'accounted for'. </p>
            <p>This field records the amounts sent to a customer either for drawdowns on asset contracts or for repayments on liability contracts. It is used to control the sending of 'principal' funds, ensuring that whatever part of the LD or MM module is used to send funds to a customer, money cannot be sent twice. </p>
            <p>This field is not classified as a 'financial' field because firstly, it is often updated before the accounting entries for a payment are passed; and secondly, is purpose is one of control rather than providing financial information. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with Field 10.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMITTED.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The calculated commission amount for the current commission period. </p>
            <p>This fields holds the amount of commission due on the contract for the current commission period. </p>
            <p>It is a signed amount and is always negative. </p>
            <p>For commission bearing contracts this amount will be an estimated figure for the period, based on the schedules, principal changes, rate changes, etc. currently affecting the contract.  This amount will always be updated immediately when subject to any further changes.  For discounted contracts it will be the actual committed amount which has been paid or received and will not be subject to any changes during the period. </p>
            <p>The value in this field will correspond to the value in field TOTAL COM AMT on the main contract. </p>
            <p>An amount will be generated in this field immediately upon </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. is subject to financial changes. If this is a multiple period contract the field will be reset at the end of the commission period and an amount inserted which will represent the commission for the following period.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RMB.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the accrual amount calculated by the system.  The accrual is calculated using the number of days in RMB.ACCR.DAYS and   REIMBURSE.PL.AMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.ACCR.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date to which accruals have been made for the current accrual period, used to calculate accruals.</p>
            <p>Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.ACCR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for which accruals have been made for the current accrual period.</p>
            <p>Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.ACCR.TO.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount accrued to date over the current interest period.</p>
            <p>The sign of the amount will be equivalent to that of the CRF.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.DATE.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the receipt. </p>
            <p>This is the date the fee was received. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details off charges on the contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:-           OUTS FEE DUE           FEE DUE DATE           FEE CHRG CODE           CUM FEE REC           LAST DATE REC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue associations: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MTHLY.AMORT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the fee or charge which is to be amortised each month end. </p>
            <p>This field represents the amortisation amount of fees on the contract. It is signed and is always positive. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into Profit and Loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          FEES PAID IN ADV           CHRGS CCY           MTHLY AMORT AMT           NO OF MTHS LEFT           ORIGIN AMOR MTH           CHRGS CODE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.CAP.END.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end dates for previous capital accrual periods.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Multi value associated with fields PREV.CAP.AMOUNT to PREV.CAP.END.DTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHRGS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The charge code of the fee or charge. </p>
            <p>This is the code indicated on the main contract and refers an entry on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The value in field CATEGORY CODE on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS indicates which profit and loss account the fees or charges will be posted to. Also indicated is the period over which the contract is to be amortised plus the charge description. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          FEES PAID IN ADV           CHRGS CCY           MTHLY AMORT AMT           NO OF MTHS LEFT           ORIGIN AMOR MTH           CHRGS CODE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 2 numeric characters. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RET.COM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date on which the Loan contract is preclosed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rounded amount accrued to date for the current accrual period.</p>
            <p>The sign of the accrual will agree with the CRF posting, i.e. Loans Positive Deposits negative.</p>
            <p>Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CONSOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the key of the Consolidation record (in the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file) into which the details of this contract are consolidated for interest. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 70 type A (alphanumeric) characters, as specified in the Consolidate Conditions file (CONSOLIDATE.COND). (Internal field).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of tax on the commission or the current period. </p>
            <p>The amount of commission tax charged on the commission liquidation date. </p>
            <p>Commission tax will always result in the customer being charged with the obligation. </p>
            <p>The corresponding credit will be passed to the category indicated on the table TAX . </p>
            <p>At the end of the interest period the value in this field will equal the value in field TOT COM TAX on LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.ADJ.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to hold the total of difference between the User defined commission amount and System calculated commission amount  when SPECIAL.COMM.BASIS is defined</p>
            <p>Standard AMT type field.</p>
            <p>Applicable only for LD product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.PERIOD.COM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the start of the current commission period. </p>
            <p>The first commission period of a contract is the one that starts on the contract VALUE DATE and so at initiation, this field will contain the VALUE DATE. If a contract has more than one commission period in its life then this date will always be the start date of the current period and it will always equal the end date (END PERIOD COM) of the previous commission period, irrespective of any accrual method. </p>
            <p>With daily accruals, the first day accrual method will cause an accrual for the current period to take place on the START PERIOD COM date.  The last day accrual method will cause the first accrual in the current period to occur on the day after the START PERIOD COM date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate used in the financial charge calculation for accrual periods for the flexible schedules 'FS' and reducing balance 'RB' types.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGIN.AMOR.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total number of months over which the fee or charge is to be amortised. </p>
            <p>This is the original number of months over which the charge or fee is to be amortised.  It is set up on the due date and is not changed. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          FEES PAID IN ADV           CHRGS CCY           MTHLY AMORT AMT           NO OF MTHS LEFT           ORIGIN AMOR MTH           CHRGS CODE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 3 numeric characters. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUM.FEE.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the fee which has been received. </p>
            <p>This is the amount of the particular fee which has been received. </p>
            <p>The field is updated by the receipt entry system in respect of the payment of fees. </p>
            <p>This field is signed and is always positive. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details off charges on the contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          OUTS FEE DUE           FEE DUE DATE           FEE CHRG CODE           CUM FEE REC           LAST DATE REC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.ACCR.ACTAMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual i.e. unrounded amount accrued to date for the current accrual period.</p>
            <p>Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.ACCR.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of the current accrual period, used to calculate accruals.</p>
            <p>Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields DEP.ACCR.FROM to DEP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.CALC.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to hold the System calculated interest amount for the current period when SPECIAL.INT.BASIS is defined</p>
            <p>Standard AMT type field</p>
            <p>Applicable only for LD product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.CALC.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to hold the System calculated commission amount for the current period when SPECIAL.COMM.BASIS is defined.</p>
            <p>Standard AMT type field.</p>
            <p>Applicable only for LD product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CANCEL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of principal cancelled. </p>
            <p>The value in this field is the same as the value in field TRANS.PRIN.AMT for the multivalue defined in the corresponding CANCEL.MV.NO. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 type AMT numeric characters. (Associated multivalue field).</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHRGS.AMT.DUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the fee or charge which is due. </p>
            <p>This field represents the amount of the charge which is due on the contract. That is those charges which have a value date prior to or equal to the process date. </p>
            <p>Each charge on the contract will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the claim date of the charge. </p>
            <p>This field is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the contract. It contains of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          CHRGS AMT DUE           CHRGS DUE DATE           CHRG CODE           AMT REC           DATE RECEIVED </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.MTHS.LEFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of months remaining until the fee or charge is fully amortised. </p>
            <p>This field is initialised on the due date of the charge or fee to the total number of months in the amortisation period.  It is decremented every month end when the amortisation amount is taken into profit and loss. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          FEES PAID IN ADV           CHRGS CCY           MTHLY AMORT AMT           NO OF MTHS LEFT           ORIGIN AMOR MTH           CHRGS CODE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 3 numeric characters. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.COM.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the commission receipt referred to in field CUM COM AMT REC. </p>
            <p>The date of the commission receipt referred to in field           CUM COM AMT REC. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>This association of fields is used by the receipt application to record the amount of commission actually received on the contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:-           CUM COM AMT REC           DATE COM REC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: CUM COM AMT REC to DATE COM REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is automatically updated by system and applicable only for MM contracts created through REPO with REPO TYPE having EFFECTIVE RATE set to YES.</p>
            <p>This rate is used for non linear accruals. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.INT.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The interest spread that formed part of the  AC INT RATE that was used in the calculation of interest in this set of accrual fields (fields 52 to 57). </p>
            <p>Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, AC INT SPREAD contains the interest spread that was applied to the floating rate (BASIC INTEREST table) to derive the AC INT RATE for use in the calculation of interest in the multivalue set of accrual fields. </p>
            <p>An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FEE.CHRG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The charge code of the fee. </p>
            <p>This is the code indicated on the main contract and refers to an entry on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The value in field CATEGORY CODE on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS indicates which profit and loss account the fees or charges will be posted to. Also indicated is the period over which the contract is to be amortised plus the charge description. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details off charges on the contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:-           OUTS FEE DUE           FEE DUE DATE           FEE CHRG CODE           CUM FEE REC           LAST DATE REC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 2 numeric characters. Multivalue association: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end date of the current capital accrual period.</p>
            <p>This is equal to the end date of the current interest period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.PERIOD.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the start of the current interest period. </p>
            <p>The first interest period of a contract is the one that starts on the contract VALUE DATE and so at initiation, this field will contain the VALUE DATE. If a contract has more than one interest period in its life then this date will always be the start date of the current period and it will always equal the end date (END PERIOD INT) of the previous interest period, irrespective of any accrual method. </p>
            <p>With daily accruals, the first day accrual method will cause an accrual for the current period to take place on the START PERIOD INT date.  The last day accrual method will cause the first accrual in the current period to occur on the day after the START PERIOD INT date. </p>
            <p>It should be noted that the system assumes that all contracts have an interest period, even if they have no interest rate. Consequently, this field will always have a value even if the contract type is one that has no interest e.g. account receivable, Sundry deposit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHRG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The charge code of the charge. </p>
            <p>This is the code indicated on the main contract and refers to an entry on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The value in field CATEGORY CODE on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS indicates which profit and loss account the charges will be posted to. Also indicated is the period over which the contract is to be amortised plus the charge description. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the main contract. It contains details of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:-           CHRGS AMT DUE           CHRGS DUE DATE           CHRG CODE           AMT REC           DATE RECEIVED </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 3 numeric characters. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RMB.AMT.ACCR.TO.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YLD.DATE.FR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields YIELD.RATE , YLD.DATE.FR, YLD.DATE.TO  form an associated set.This field is used for accrual interest amount calculation.It stores the date from which the interest rate in YIELD.RATE is applicable</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.TO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. </p>
            <p>AC.TO.DATE contains the dates interest is accrued to for the period. </p>
            <p>The other 6 fields are for date accrued from (AC.FROM.DATE) no.of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). </p>
            <p>These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.SUSP.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total Commission Amount that is suspended.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RET.AC.OR.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields RET.INT.AMT, RET.AC.OR.PL, RET.INT.DATE form a multi value set.If RETURN.INT field in LD is set to YES then this field will get updated 'AC-customer account'.This indicates that the adjusted interest amount has to be credited to the customer account. If RETURN.INT is not set then this field  will hold 'PL- PL category' taken from  LMM.INSTALL.CONDS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the contract customer</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.CURR.PRINC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current outstanding principal on the contract (excluding pre-payments) as of the 'EFFECTIVE DATE' field in this multivalue set of fields (fields 2 to 8). </p>
            <p>This field, along with fields 2 to 8 records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the process date of that movement is written into DATE FROM (Field 2), the value date is written into EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3),the principal movement amount is written into TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. </p>
            <p>This OUTS CURR PRINC field will only contain an amount (other than zero) when a contract has a value date less than or equal to the process date, and in the case of a fixed maturity contract, a maturity date greater than or equal to the process date. This field, along with fields 6 to 8, can have negative values (shown by a negative sign preceding the number) and positive values (shown with no sign preceding the number). Asset contracts with amounts outstanding are signed negative (as are pre-payments on deposits in the OUTS OD PRINC field); and liability contracts with amounts outstanding are positive (as are pre-payments on asset contracts in the OUTS OD PRINC field). </p>
            <p>To obtain the 'net' amount of principal outstanding (i.e. including pre-payments), this field needs to be added to the following field, OUTS OD PRINC (Field 6). </p>
            <p>An example of the possible movements is shown in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 8.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the key of the Consolidation record (in the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file) into which the details of this contract are consolidated </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Alphanumeric, as specified in the Consolidate Conditions file (CONSOLIDATE.COND). (Internal field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DLY.COM.ACCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the suspended commission amount from the NAB.START.DATE to the next working day, when the LD is not in NAB and the accrual date is greater than or equal to the NAB.START.DATE and SUSPEND.INCOME(in PD.PARAMETER) is set to YES.  Fields DLY.ACCR.DATE, DLY.COM.ACCR, and DLY.INT.ACCR form an associated multi-value set. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.CHRG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PEN.INT.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the cumulative amount of penalty interest received. </p>
            <p>This field contains the cumulative amount of penalty interest received on the contract.  The value in field OS INT ACC ON OD P plus PEN I LAST DAY ACC less the value in this field will be used by LD.RECEIPT.ENTRY to represent the total penalty interest outstanding on the contract. </p>
            <p>This field is associated with field PEN I LAST DAY ACC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RET.COM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a Discount Loan Contract is preclosed, The field RETURN.COM field in the contract indicates whether the commission that is taken up front should be returned to the Customer, or placed in a PL bucket. This Field holds the amount commission amount that is to be returned or placed in a PL bucket.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.AMT.TODATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of interest calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 52 to 57). </p>
            <p>Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, INT AMT TODATE, contains the result of the interest calculation, rounded according to the currency.  It is signed negative for asset contracts and positive for liability contracts. </p>
            <p>An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of field 52, PRINC INT BAL. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.PERIOD.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that the contracts current interest period ends. </p>
            <p>This field contains the end date of the current interest period.  The first interest period of a contract is the one that starts on the value date and ends on the maturity or interest due date.  Consequently, at contract initiation, this field will contain the INTEREST DUE DATE (if Call or Notice) or MATURITY DATE (if fixed maturity). </p>
            <p>If a contract has more than one interest period in its life then this date will always be the end date of the current period and it will always equal the start date (START PERIOD INT) of the next interest period, irrespective of any accrual method. </p>
            <p>With daily accruals, the first day accrual method will not require an accrual for the current period on the END PERIOD INT date.  The last day accrual method will require an accrual on this date for the current period. </p>
            <p>It should be noted that the system assumes that all contracts have an interest period, even if they have no interest rate. Consequently, this field will always have a value even if the contract type is one that has no interest e.g. account receivable, Sundry deposit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.PRIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction amount that has affected the principal balances on the contract. </p>
            <p>This field, along with fields 2 to 8 records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the value date of that movement is written into EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3), the process date of the movement is written into DATE FROM (Field 2), the principal movement amount is written into this field, and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. </p>
            <p>This TRANS PRIN AMT field will contain an amount WHENEVER there is a principal movement, irrespective of whether there is a movement of funds into or out of the bank. e.g. it will show an amount when a current contract becomes 'due' as well as when the due amount is liquidated. This field can have negative values (shown by a negative sign preceding the number) and positive values (shown with no sign preceding the number). </p>
            <p>Movements on asset contracts are always shown as negative values except for reductions in principal which are shown as positive. </p>
            <p>Movements on liability contracts are always shown as positive values except for reductions in principal which are shown as negative. </p>
            <p>An example of the possible movements is shown in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 7.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.SUSP.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field holds the total suspended interest from the NAB.START.DATE </p>
            <p>till the last accrual (suspension) date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.PRINCIPAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. </p>
            <p>AC.PRINCIPAL contains the principal effective for the accrual period. </p>
            <p>The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). </p>
            <p>These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field 19 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CMMT.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will get updated for foreign currency commitment contracts.The exchange rate is stored in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency in which the interest is to be paid/accrued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 character currency mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADJ.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to hold the total of difference between the User defined interest amount and the System calculated interest amount when the SPECIAL.INT.BASIS is defined</p>
            <p>Standard AMT type field</p>
            <p>Applicable only for LD product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CANCEL.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of interest cancelled by the split current month, previous month and previous year. </p>
            <p>The first subvalue specifies the amount for the current month, the second subvalue for the previous month and the third subvalue for the previous year. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 type AMT numeric characters. (Associated subvalue field).</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.ACCR.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date to which accruals have been made for the current accrual period.</p>
            <p>Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The record identification. </p>
            <p>This field is the key of the record and is always the contract number, e.g. LD/86255/00123 or MM/86255/00123, plus a two digit suffix. The two digit suffix identifies the nature and type of record ie:- </p>
            <p>00        For LD contracts, the 00 relates to the extent of "our           share". All MM contracts end with 00. 01-98     relates to Syndicated contracts and identifies the           participant's number and share. 99        relates to the total of the syndication. Therefore type           "99" will reflect the total exposure to the customer in           relation to fields "00" to "98". </p>
            <p>There is only one of these records at any one time representing either the unauthorised or authorised record on the LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS or MM.MONEY.MARKET main files. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard contract number plus two digit suffix which results in a 14 character key.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.ACCR.PRIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The absolute value of the depreciation/obligation amount used to calculate accruals for the current accrual period.</p>
            <p>Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ON.REPAY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When Interest amount is collected on Repayment Date then the interest amount is held in this field INT.ON.REPAY.AMT. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FEE.DUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The due date of the fee. </p>
            <p>This is the date that the particular fee was due for payment. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details off charges on the contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          OUTS FEE DUE           FEE DUE DATE           FEE CHRG CODE           CUM FEE REC           LAST DATE REC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.CHRG.IND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CHRGS.AMT.DUE to CAP.CHRG.IND form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       Y      NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>HHolds the contrac category</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RMB.ACCR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from RMB.ACCR.FROM to RMB.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set    to store reimburse accrual data. The difference between RMB.ACCR.FROM and RMB.ACCR.TO is stored in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOATING.INT.ADJUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ACCR.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>The recent interest accrual start date is stored in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual i.e. unrounded amount accrued to date for the current accrual period.</p>
            <p>Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PEN.C.LAST.DAY.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the accrual amount for today/tomorrow. </p>
            <p>For contracts on a last day accrual basis it is necessary to compute the penalty commission for today/tomorrow, the resulting value will be reflected in this field. </p>
            <p>This field is associated with field PEN COM REC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.COM.ACC.ON.OD.P</field>
<desc>
            <p>The penalty commission that has been accrued on overdue principal when this is done on a financial basis. </p>
            <p>Penalty commission is additional to the normal commission and is accrued on overdue principal on either a financial basis, when it is taken into Profit and Loss, or on a memo basis, where no entries are made but the amount is still accrued. The method used is determined by the value in field PEN C ACC FIN MEM on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for LOAN type contracts.  It is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>It is also used by the receipt entry system in respect of the liquidation of penalty commission. Penalty commission can never be prepaid. </p>
            <p>The value in this field represents the Balance Sheet contra entry to the Profit and Loss category indicated in field PL O SET CR PEN. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINC.COMM.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The outstanding principal balance as of the DATE COM ACC TO field in this multivalue set of accrual fields (fields 63 to 66). </p>
            <p>Whenever a commission accrual takes place, fields 63 to 66 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC COMM BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC COMM RATE (the actual commission rate used in the calculation); DATE COM ACC TO (the date commission is accrued to); and the resulting commission amount field - COMM AMT TODATE. </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, PRINC COMM BAL, is calculated by summing the OUTS CURR PRINC and OUTS OD PRINC fields to arrive at a net outstanding principal balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 14 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FEE.PAID.IN.ADV</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of each individual fee or charge which has been collected from the customer and is to be amortised over a period. </p>
            <p>This field is signed and is always positive. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          FEES PAID IN ADV           CHRGS CCY           MTHLY AMORT AMT           NO OF MTHS LEFT           ORIGIN AMOR MTH           CHRGS CODE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.ACC.WHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of withholding tax which has accrued for the current interest period. </p>
            <p>The value in this field represents the amount of withholding tax which has accrued during the current interest period. </p>
            <p>At the end of the current interest period the value in this field will equal the value in field TOTAL WHT on LD LOANS AND DEPOSITS. </p>
            <p>During the end of day processing for the interest period end date the value in this field will be transferred to field WHT CERT AMT EXP on LD ACCOUNT BALANCES. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DLY.INT.ACCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the suspended interest amount from the NAB.START.DATE to the next working day, when the LD is not in NAB and the accrual date is greater than or equal to the NAB.START.DATE and SUSPEND.INCOME(in PD.PARAMETER) is set to YES.  Fields DLY.ACCR.DATE, DLY.COM.ACCR, and DLY.INT.ACCR form an associated multi-value set. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.PAYABLE.UCL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The interest amount on a liability contract that is due to be paid. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.OVER.DUE.COM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of commission on a LOAN or COMMITMENT contract which is due but has not been received and/or any prepayment received. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for LOAN and COMMITMENT contracts.  It records the net amount of commission that is due but has not been received. </p>
            <p>The field is signed and will be negative if commission is outstanding, and positive if there is a net prepayment, created via the LD.Receipt.Entry system. </p>
            <p>Updating occurs on commission due dates at End Of Day when the interest is manually liquidated and by the payment or receipt applications when manual liquidations are entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.FEE.DUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of fees due which have not been liquidated. </p>
            <p>This field holds the amount of the fee which has fallen due but has not been liquidated. It is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details of charges on the contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:-           OUTS FEE DUE           FEE DUE DATE           FEE CHRG CODE           CUM FEE REC           LAST DATE REC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.INT.ACC.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that interest is accrued to using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 52 to 57). </p>
            <p>Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, DATE INT ACC TO contains the end date that the set of accrual values is for.  The period of accrual is from the previous value of DATE INT ACC TO (or START PERIOD INT  if this is the first set of accrual values) to the value of DATE INT ACC TO in the current set of accrual values. An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RET.AC.OR.PL.COM</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a Discount Loan Contract is preclosed, The field RETURN.COM field in the contract indicates whether the commission that is taken up front should be returned to the Customer, or placed in a PL bucket. If that field is set to YES, RET.AC.OR.PL.COM  will have an ACCOUNT number prefixed by 'AC', else it would have a PL Category prefixed by 'PL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.PRINC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the next principal repayment schedule. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.PAID.IN.ADV</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of discounted interest on a DEPOSIT contract which has been paid in advance. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for DEPOSITS where the interest is discounted. It reflects the amount of interest for the interest period which has been paid in advance. At the start of the period it will equal the committed interest and will be reduced by each interest accrual to zero at the end of the period. </p>
            <p>The field is signed and will always be negative. </p>
            <p>The contents of this field are accrued into field PL O SET IPA on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>M.OS.I.ACC.ON.OD.P</field>
<desc>
            <p>The penalty interest that has been accrued on overdue principal when this is done on a memo basis. </p>
            <p>Penalty interest is additional to the normal interest and is accrued on overdue principal on either a financial basis, when it is taken into profit and loss, or on a memo basis, where no entries are made but the amount is still accrued. The method used is determined by the value in field PEN I ACC FIN MEM on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for LOAN type contracts. It is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>The offset to this value is posted to the category indicated in field PL O SET IR PEN M on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE.IR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINCIPAL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of principal tax taken on the drawdown or principal increase amount. </p>
            <p>The amount of principal tax charged on the drawdown or principal increase amount. The tax will be levied on the relevant value date. </p>
            <p>Principal tax will always result in the customer receiving the net disbursement. In the case of loans the customer will receive the net of principal less tax, in the case of deposits the customer will be charged principal plus tax. </p>
            <p>The corresponding credit will be passed to the category indicated on the table TAX . </p>
            <p>At the end of the interest period the value in this field will equal the value in field TOT PRINC TAX on LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.REC.IN.ADV</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of discounted commission on a LD.LOAN or COMMITMENT contract which has been received in advance. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for LOANS and COMMITMENTS where the commission is discounted.  It hold the amount of commission for the commission period which has been received in advance (and consequently not yet earned). At the start of the period it will equal the committed commission and will be reduced by each commission accrual to zero at the end of the period. </p>
            <p>The field is signed and will always be negative. </p>
            <p>The contents of this field will be accrued into field PL O SET IRA on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHRGS.DUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The claim date of the charge. </p>
            <p>This is the value date when the particular charge has been claimed.  It is taken directly from the contract. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the contract. It contains of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          CHRGS AMT DUE           CHRGS DUE DATE           CHRG CODE           AMT REC           DATE RECEIVED </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The unrounded amount of interest calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 52 to 57). </p>
            <p>Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, ACTUAL ACC AMT, contains the result of the interest calculation, without rounding.  It is signed negative for asset contracts and positive for liability contracts. An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of field 52, PRINC INT BAL. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINC.INT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The outstanding principal balance as of the DATE INT ACC TO field in this multivalue set of accrual fields (fields 52 to 57). </p>
            <p>Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, PRINC INT BAL, is calculated by summing the OUTS CURR PRINC  and OUTS OD PRINC fields to arrive at a net outstanding principal balance.  It is signed negative for asset contracts and positive for liability contracts. An example of how this field, and the other accrual fields are used is shown below: </p>
            <p>Example:  Asset contract, valued 11th February 1987, Maturing           11th March 1987.  Principal is one million pounds,           interest rate is fixed at 10%, accruals are performed           daily and the first day accrual method is employed. </p>
            <p>State of fields prior to first accrual: </p>
            <p>CURRENCY            :         GBP DATE FROM           :         11th February 1987 EFFECTIVE DATE      :         11th February 1987 TRANS PRIN AMT      :         - 1,000,000 OUTS FWD PRINC      :         0 OUTS CURR PRINC     :         - 1,000,000 OUTS OD PRINC       :         0 OUTS ACCRUED INT    :         " " </p>
            <p>START PERIOD INT    :         11th February 1987 END PERIOD INT      :         11th March 1987 COMMITTED INT       :         - 7,671.23 </p>
            <p>PRINC INT BAL       :         " " INT AMT TODATE      :         " " AC INT RATE         :         " " AC INT SPREAD       :         " " DATE INT ACC TO     :         " " ACTUAL ACC AMT      :         " " </p>
            <p>NB:       " " = NULL OR BLANK </p>
            <p>State of fields after first accrual: </p>
            <p>CURRENCY            :         GBP DATE FROM           :         11th February 1987 EFFECTIVE DATE      :         11th February 1987 TRANS PRIN AMT      :         - 1,000,000 OUTS FWD PRINC      :         0 OUTS CURR PRINC     :         - 1,000,000 OUTS OD PRINC       :         0 </p>
            <p>OUTS ACCRUED INT    :         - 273.97 </p>
            <p>START PERIOD INT    :         11th February 1987 END PERIOD INT      :         11th March 1987 COMMITTED INT       :         - 7,671.23 PRINC INT BAL       :         - 1,000,000 INT AMT TODATE      :         -   273.97 AC INT RATE         :         10% AC INT SPREAD       :         " " DATE INT ACC TO     :         11th February 1987 ACTUAL ACC AMT      :         -   273.9726 </p>
            <p>Note:     One days interest has been calculated, the fields in           the calculation have been updated and the final field           OUTS ACCRUED INT has been updated. </p>
            <p>State of fields after second accrual: </p>
            <p>CURRENCY            :         GBP DATE FROM           :         11th February 1987 EFFECTIVE DATE      :         11th February 1987 TRANS PRIN AMT      :         - 1,000,000 OUTS FWD PRINC      :         0 OUTS CURR PRINC     :         - 1,000,000 OUTS OD PRINC       :         0 </p>
            <p>OUTS ACCRUED INT    :         - 547.95 START PERIOD INT    :         11th February 1987 END PERIOD INT      :         11th March 1987 COMMITTED INT       :         - 7,671.23 PRINC INT BAL       :         -1,000,000 INT AMT TODATE      :         -  547.95 AC INT RATE         :         10% AC INT SPREAD       :         " " DATE INT ACC TO     :         12th February 1987 ACTUAL ACC AMT      :         -  547.94521 </p>
            <p>Note:     Another days interest has been calculated and added           to OUTS ACCRUED INT.  Because the components in           the interest calculation were no different to the first           accrual, a new set of accrual details were not added           but the amount and date fields were changed. </p>
            <p>If, prior to the third accrual, a prepayment of 250,000 principal was made, valued 13th February, the state of the fields after the third accrual would be as follows: </p>
            <p>State of fields after third accrual: </p>
            <p>CURRENCY        :   GBP DATE FROM       :   11th February 1987 EFFECTIVE DATE  :   11th February 1987 TRANS PRIN AMT  :   - 1,000,000 OUTS FWD PRINC  :   0 OUTS CURR PRINC :   - 1,000,000 OUTS OD PRINC   :      250,000 OUTS ACCRUED INT    :         - 753.43 </p>
            <p>START PERIOD INT    :         11th February 1987 END PERIOD INT  :   11th March 1987 COMMITTED INT   :   - 5,890.42 </p>
            <p>PRINC INT BAL   :   -1,000,000- 750,000 INT AMT TODATE  :   -  547.95 -     205.48 AC INT RATE     :   10%       10% AC INT SPREAD   :   " "       " " DATE INT ACC TO :   12th February 1987 13th February 1987 ACTUAL ACC AMT  :   -  547.94521-     205.47945                     1ST SET   2ND SET </p>
            <p>Note:     This time, another set of accrual fields have been           written because the principal balance has changed.           Another result of the principal change is that the           COMMITTED INT field has been re-calculated. </p>
            <p>An example for a deposit contract would be similar to the one above with the following exceptions: </p>
            <p>1.        Amounts would have the opposite sign. </p>
            <p>2.        The OUTS ACCRUED INT field would be replaced by           the OUTS CUR ACC I PAY field. </p>
            <p>The field AC INT SPREAD is only used when the contract is tied to a floating interest rate.  In this case the AC INT RATE is still the actual interest rate used in the calculation but this time it includes the interest spread as shown in AC INT SPREAD. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 14 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the actual accrued amount without rounding.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.ACT.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p> Stores the unrounded commision accrual amounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.OD.PRINC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current outstanding principal on the contract that is due to be paid/received  as of the 'DATE FROM field in this multivalue set of fields (fields 2 to 8). </p>
            <p>This field, along with fields 2 to 8 records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the process date of that movement is written into DATE FROM (Field 2), the value date is written into EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3) the principal movement amount is written into TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. </p>
            <p>This OUTS OD PRINC field will only contain an amount (other than zero) in two situations: </p>
            <p>(i)       For LD contracts that have a scheduled principal           amount due for payment but not yet liquidated due to           non-receipt of funds. </p>
            <p>(ii)      Whenever there is a pre-payment of principal through           the LD.RECEIPT.ENTRY, MM.RECEIPT.ENTRY or           MM.PAYMENT.ENTRY applications. In this situation           the sign of the amount will always be opposite to the           sign in the OUTS CURR PRINC field. (To calculate the           net outstanding principal on a contract, i.e. taking           pre-payments into account, this field should be added           to OUTS CURR PRINC (Field 6). </p>
            <p>This field, along with fields 6 to 8, can have negative values (shown by a negative sign preceding the number) and positive values (shown with no sign preceding the number). Asset contracts with amounts outstanding are signed negative (as are pre-payments on deposits); and liability contracts with amounts outstanding are positive (as are pre-payments on asset contracts). </p>
            <p>An example of the possible movements is shown in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 8.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATE.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WHT.CERT.AMT.EXP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total amount of withholding tax certificates which the customer is required to submit to the bank. </p>
            <p>This field represents the total value of withholding tax certificates for which the customer is liable. This amount can represent the certificate obligations for multiple interest periods. </p>
            <p>The value in this field is increased by the amount indicated in field OUTS ACC WHT on LMM ACCOUNT BALANCES during the end of day processing on the interest period end date. It is decremented by the amount of witholding tax certificates submitted via the withholding tax function LD WITHOLDING TAX </p>
            <p>The value in this field will always agree with the value in field TAX AMOUNT EXP on LD WITHOLDIMG TAX. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.AMT.TODATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of commission calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 60 to 66). </p>
            <p>Whenever a commission accrual takes place, fields 63 to 66 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC COMM BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC COMM RATE (the actual commission rate used in the calculation); DATE COM ACC TO (the date commission is accrued to); and the resulting commission amount field - COMM AMT TODATE. </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, COMM AMT TODATE, contains the result of the commission calculation, rounded according to the currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end date of the current depreciation period</p>
            <p>This is equal to the end date of the current interest period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.AMT.ACCR.TO.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.FWD.PRINC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The outstanding forward valued principal on the contract as of the 'EFFECTIVE DATE' field in this multivalue set of fields (Fields 2 to 8). </p>
            <p>This field, along with fields 2 to 8 records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the process date of that movement is written into DATE FROM (Field 2), the value date of the movement is written to EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3), the principal movement amount is written into TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. </p>
            <p>This OUTS FWD PRINC field will only contain an amount (other than zero) when a contract has a forward valued drawdown pending. e.g. a new contract with a value date greater than the process date, or a forward valued principal increase. </p>
            <p>This field, along with fields 6 to 8, can have negative values (shown by a negative sign preceding the number) and positive values (shown with no sign preceding the number). Asset contracts with amounts outstanding are signed negative (as are pre-payments on deposits in the OUTS OD PRINC field); and liability contracts with amounts outstanding are positive (as are pre-payments on asset contracts in the OUTS OD PRINC field). </p>
            <p>An example of the possible movements is shown in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 8.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.INT.REV.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the next interest revision. </p>
            <p>This field is used for periodic interest contracts and contains the date of the next interest revision.  This will be either the final maturity date of the contract or the date of the next Revision Schedule. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.COMM.ON.NAB</field>
<desc>
            <p>Outstanding commission on the contract when it is on non-accrual basis. </p>
            <p>When a contract is transferred to  non-accrual basis the following actions occur :- </p>
            <p>1) The values contained in fields OUTS ACCRUED COM and OS COM ACC ON OD P are transferred to this field. This sum now represents the total of commission which has been written off by virtue of the status change to "NAB". The contract now ceases to attract normal or penalty commission accruals. </p>
            <p>2) The system calculates the commission which would have accrued and updates this field accordingly. </p>
            <p>This field is held on a memorandum basis therefore no further profit and loss entries will be generated by the system. The offset to this field is PL O SET CR SUS on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>The field is only used for LOAN contract.  It is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>When a contract has been put on non-accrual basis the commission which should be due is still accrued into this field.  No profit and loss entries are made for this interest. </p>
            <p>The field is only used for LOAN contract.  It is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used when Interest Schedules are generated using the INTEREST.DUE.DATE field. This is required to generate the next interest due date when the BASE.DATE.KEY is set to BASE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>M.OS.C.ACC.ON.OD.P</field>
<desc>
            <p>The penalty commission that has been accrued on overdue principal when this is done on a memo basis. </p>
            <p>Penalty commission is additional to the normal commission and is accrued on overdue principal on either a financial basis, when it is taken into profit and loss, or on a memo basis, where no entries are made but the amount is still accrued. The method used is determined by the value in field PEN C ACC FIN MEM on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for LOAN type contracts.  It is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>The offset to this value is posted to the category indicated in field PL O SET CR PEN M on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.ACCRUED.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The outstanding accrued interest on an asset contract, as of the last accrual date. Often called 'interest earned not collected' and 'current interest receivable'. </p>
            <p>This field holds the balance of accrued interest, that has not yet been received, on an asset contract. The amount is correct up to the date of the last accrual which is the last value in DATE INT ACC TO (Field 56).  Whenever an accrual is performed on an asset contract, the details of the interest calculation are recorded in Fields 52 to 57, and the result of the calculation added to this field. </p>
            <p>When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no accrual has yet been performed on the contract for the current interest period as shown in START PERIOD INT (Field 49) and END PERIOD INT (Field 50). i.e. no interest has been earnt (but not received from the customer) for the current period. </p>
            <p>When this amount is negative it signifies that at least one accrual has taken place in the current interest period and that this interest amount has been earnt (and recorded as profit) but has not been collected from the customer yet. This field can never be positive. </p>
            <p>Each time this field has an amount added to it (e.g. an accrual for $100, implying a debit of $100), then an entry is posted to profit and loss, interest received. (e.g. a credit of $100 to the profit and loss category code as input in field 28 on LMM.INSTALL.CONDS). </p>
            <p>To calculate the net interest outstanding on a contract (i.e. including pre-payments), this field should be added to OUTS OVER DUE INT (Field 12). </p>
            <p>An example of the updates to this field, and fields 52 to 57, is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.REC.IN.ADV</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of discounted interest on a LOAN or COMMITMENT contract which has been received in advance. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for LOANS and COMMITMENTS where the interest is discounted. It holds the amount of interest for the interest period which has been received in advance (and consequently not yet earned). At the start of the period it will equal the committed interest and will be reduced by each interest accrual to zero at the end of the period. </p>
            <p>The field is signed and will always be negative. </p>
            <p>The content of this field will be accrued into the profit and loss category indicated in field PL O SET IRA indicated on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.Loans and Deposits only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.ACCR.PRIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from ISS.ACCR.FROM to ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set  to store issue accrual data. This field holds the ISSUE.PL.AMOUNT which has to be accrued.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The financial charge amount to be depreciated for loans or the amount of financial obligation for deposits for the current interest period.</p>
            <p>This amount will be accrued as follows: -</p>
            <p>Loans - debit P&amp;L and credit CRF, stored as a negative vale.</p>
            <p>Deposits - credit P&amp;L and debit CRF, stored as a positive value.</p>
            <p>The actual accrual amounts will be stored with the opposite sign.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.PRINC.NAB</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of overdue principal outstanding on the contract after the principal movement has been effected when it is on a non-accrual basis. </p>
            <p>When the contract is put on a non-accrual basis all the outstanding principal is moved to this field.  This is done by the routine LD.NAB.TRANSFER during the end of day processing when the number of days after the contract has become overdue when it should go to NAB as defined on the LMM.INSTALL.CONDS record is reached. </p>
            <p>It is also used by the receipt entry system in respect of the liquidation of outstanding principal on an "NAB" basis. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue associated fields DATE FROM to OUTS PRINC NAB hold the history of all principal movements to the contract. They are maintained for all contract types. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          DATE FROM           EFFECTIVE DATE           TRANS PRIN AMT           OUTS FWD PRINC           OUTS CURR PRINC           OUTS OD PRINC           OUTS PRINC NAB </p>
            <p>Each multivalue set in the association records details of the particular movement which occurred on the date in the field DATE FROM. </p>
            <p>These fields hold historic data with the exception of the last multivalue association which shows the current principal position of the contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association with fields 2 to 8. (For LD.Loans and deposits only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PEN.I.LAST.DAY.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the accrual amount for today/tomorrow. </p>
            <p>For contracts on a last day accrual basis it is necessary to compute the penalty interest for today/tomorrow, the resulting value will be reflected in this field. </p>
            <p>This field is associated with field PEN INT REC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RMB.ACCR.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from RMB.ACCR.FROM to RMB.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set   to store reimburse accrual data.   This field holds the date from which REIMBURSE.PL.AMT is to be accrued.  This set of fields store data in reverse order. The most recent is found in the   first multivalue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DLY.ACCR.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value of DATE.INT.ACC.TO when the OVERDUE.STATUS Is not NAB and DATE.INT.ACC.TO is greater than or equal to NAB.START.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.ACCR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from ISS.ACCR.FROM to ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set to store issue accrual data.  The difference between ISS.ACCR.FROM and ISS.ACCR.TO is stored in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.RECEIVED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the receipt of the charge. </p>
            <p>This is the date the charge was received and will usually be the same as the due date. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the contract. It contains of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          CHRGS AMT DUE           CHRGS DUE DATE           CHRG CODE           AMT REC           DATE RECEIVED </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RMB.ACCR.ACTAMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the actual accrued amount without rounding. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE.IR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPITAL.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The principal component of the current Annuity repayment amount. </p>
            <p>Used to determine capital accruals for finance leasing contracts. </p>
            <p>This amount will be accrued over the current repayment period.</p>
            <p>The sign will be positive for loans and negative for deposits, with the associated accruals being the opposite sign.</p>
            <p>The accruals will conform to interest accruals in that P&amp;L will be credited and CRF debited for loans (vice versa for deposits)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual interest rate used in the calculation of interest in this set of accrual fields (fields 52 to 57). </p>
            <p>Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, AC INT RATE, contains the interest rate that was used in the calculation of interest in the multi set of accrual fields of which this field is part. </p>
            <p>An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIXED.FLOATING.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RET.INT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields RET.INT.AMT, RET.AC.OR.PL, RET.INT.DATE form a multi value set.This field holds the date on which the adjustment amount is credited to customer account or P and L.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.FROM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. </p>
            <p>AC.FROM.DATE contains the dates from which interest accruals for the period. </p>
            <p>The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). </p>
            <p>These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date when the contract had the principal balance and movement as shown by the following five fields. </p>
            <p>This field, along with the following five fields records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the value date of that movement is written into this field, the date the drawdown was input is written to DATE FROM (Field 2), the principal movement amount is written to TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. </p>
            <p>Example:  An example of the possible movements is shown below: </p>
            <p>Event 1:  A 12,000 US dollar placement is loaded onto the system           on 11th February 1987, valued 16th February 1987 and           maturing on 23rd February 1987. </p>
            <p>Event 2:  During the 'off-line' processing of 16th February, the           placement moves from a 'Forward valued' asset, to a           'Current' asset. </p>
            <p>Event 3:  During the 'off-line' processing of 23rd February, the           placement matures with the principal becoming due           and then being fully repaid. </p>
            <p>          LMM.ACCOUNT.BALANCES RECORD (FIELDS 2 TO 8)           1 2 3 DUE 3 PAID </p>
            <p>DATE FROM       11 FEB 87  16 FEB 87  23 FEB 87  23 FEB 87 EFFECTIVE DATE  11 FEB 87  16 FEB 87  23 FEB 87  23 FEB 87 TRANS PRIN AMT  -12,000    -12,000    -12,000     12,000 OUTS FWD PRINC  -12,000        0          0          0 OUTS CURR PRINC  0         -12,000        0          0 OUTS OD PRINC    0             0      -12,000        0 OUTS PRINC NAB   0             0          0          0 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 8.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rounded amount accrued to date for the current accrual period.</p>
            <p>Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RMB.ACCR.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from RMB.ACCR.FROM to RMB.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set   to store reimburse accrual data.   This field holds the date to which REIMBURSE.PL.AMT is to be accrued.  This set of fields store data in reverse order. The most recent is found in the   first multivalue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of tax on the interest for the current period. </p>
            <p>The amount of interest tax charged on the interest liquidation date. </p>
            <p>Interest tax will always result in the customer being charged with the obligation. </p>
            <p>The corresponding credit will be passed to the category indicated on the table TAX . </p>
            <p>At the end of the interest period the value in this field will equal the value in field TOT INT TAX on LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS or MM.MONEY.MARKET main files. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CANCEL.MV.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the multivalue number of the set of associated fields from DATE.FROM to OUTS.PRINC.NAB which relate to this cancellation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 numeric characters. (Associated multivalue field).</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.INT.SCH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the recent interest received date </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. </p>
            <p>AC.RATE contains the rate at which interest accrues over the period. </p>
            <p>The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). </p>
            <p>These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-11 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.COM.ACC.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date commission is accrued to using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 63 to 66). </p>
            <p>Whenever a commission accrual takes place, fields 63 to 66 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC COMM BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC COMM RATE (the actual commission rate used in the calculation); DATE COM ACC TO (the date commission is accrued to); and the resulting commission amount field - COMM AMT TODATE. </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, DATE COM ACC TO contains the end date that the set of accrual values is for.  The period of accrual is from the previous value of DATE COM ACC TO (or START PERIOD COM  if this is the first set of accrual values) to the value of DATE COM ACC TO in the current set of accrual values. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.ACCR.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from ISS.ACCR.FROM to ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set  to store issue accrual data. This field holds the date till which ISSUE.PL.AMOUNT is to be accrued This set of fields store data in reverse order. The most recent is found in the  first multivalue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.ACCR.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of the current capital accrual period</p>
            <p>Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CANCEL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value date which was used for the cancellation of the interest amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>11 type D characters - standard date format. (Associated multivalue field).</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.SUSP.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The outstanding suspended Commission as of the last accrual date. This field holds the balance of suspended commission, that has not yet been received, on a contract. The amount is correct up to the date of the last suspension which is the last value in DATE COM ACC TO (Field 67). </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Whenever an suspension is performed on a contract, the  details of the commission calculation are recorded  in Fields 63 to 67, and the result of the calculation added to this field. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no suspension has yet been performed on the contract for the current commission period  as shown in START PERIOD COM (Field 60) and END PERIOD COM (Field 61). </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> When this amount is negative it signifies that at least one suspension has taken place in the current commission period and that this commission amount has been suspended and has not been collected from the customer yet. This field can never be positive.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.OVER.DUE.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>If negative, the interest amount on an asset contract that is due to be received. If positive, the amount of pre-paid interest on an asset contract. </p>
            <p>This OUTS OVER DUE INT field will only contain an amount (other than zero or null) in two situations: </p>
            <p>1.        For LD contracts that have a scheduled interest           amount due for payment but not yet liquidated due to           non-receipt of funds. </p>
            <p>2.        Whenever there is a pre-payment of interest through           the MM.RECEIPT.ENTRY application. In this situation           the sign of the amount will always be positive which is           opposite to the sign of the amount in  OUTS ACCRUED           INT (Field 11). In order to calculate the net interest           outstanding on a contract, i.e. taking pre-payments           into account, this field should be added to OUTS           ACCRUED INT (Field 11). </p>
            <p>An example of the updates to this field, and fields 52 to 57, is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Descriptor field .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the contract customer </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.INT.ON.NAB</field>
<desc>
            <p>Outstanding interest on the contract when it is on non-accrual basis. </p>
            <p>When a contract is transferred to  non-accrual basis the following actions occur :- </p>
            <p>1) The values contained in fields OUTS ACCRUED INT and OS INT ACC ON OD P are transferred to this field. This sum now represents the total of interest which has been written off by virtue of the status change to "NAB". The contract now ceases to attract normal or penalty interest accruals. </p>
            <p>2) The system calculates the interest which would have accrued and updates this field accordingly. </p>
            <p>This field is held on a memorandum basis therefore no further profit and loss entries will be generated by the system. The offset to this field is PL O SET IR SUS on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>The field is only used for LOAN contract.  It is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.ACCR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for which accruals have been made for the current interest period.</p>
            <p>Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSP.INT.TODATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The amount of interest calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 54 to 60).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Whenever an interest suspension takes place, fields 54 to </p>
            <p>60 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - SUSP.INT.TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the </p>
            <p>current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field, SUSP.INT.TODATE, contains the result of the interest </p>
            <p>calculation, rounded according to the currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Descriptot field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that a change in the principal of the contract is processed.  This is not necessarily the value date of the principal change. </p>
            <p>This field, along with the following six fields records the principal movements of the contract.  Whenever there is a movement in principal then the process date that the movement is input to the System is written to this field, the value date of the movement is written to EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3), the amount is written to TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (Fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly.  So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. </p>
            <p>This field will always contain the same value as in EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3) except in the following two cases: </p>
            <p>1.        When a back valued contract or principal increase in           loaded. </p>
            <p>          In this, the DATE FROM field will contain the date           that the change was input and the EFFECTIVE DATE           field will contain the value date of the change. </p>
            <p>2.        When the LD.RECEIPT.ENTRY, MM.PAYMENT.ENTRY           or MM.RECEIPT.ENTRY applications are used to           record principal decreases with a value date different           to the process date.  In this case the process date will           be in the DATE FROM field and the value date of the           decrease will be in the EFFECTIVE DATE field. </p>
            <p>An example of the operation of this field and the other principal fields appears in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue associated with fields 3 to 8.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RMB.ACCR.PRIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the REIMBURSE.PL.AMT which has to be accrued.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of the current capital accrual period.</p>
            <p>This is equal to the start date of the current interest period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RECEIVED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields INT.RECVD.DATE and INT.RECEIVED form an associated multivalue set.The INT.RECEIVED field contains the interest amount received from the customer on principal repayment date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.INT.REV.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the last interest revision. </p>
            <p>This field is used for periodic interest contracts and contains the date of the last interest revision.  This will be either the value date of the contract or the date of the last Revision Schedule. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RECVD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields INT.RECVD.DATE and INT.RECEIVED form an associated multivalue set.The INT.RECVD.DATE field contains the principal repayment date when interest amount is received from the customer on principal repayment date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields YIELD.RATE , YLD.DATE.FR, YLD.DATE.TO  form an associated set. This field is used to store the yield interest rate when the rate calculation is  Done by yield method. This field gets populated when YIELD.METHOD  In LD is set to "YES"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of the current depreciation period</p>
            <p>This is equal to the start date of the current interest period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.DEP.END.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The accrual period end date for previous financial charge accruals.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Multi value associated with fields PREV.DEP.AMOUNT to PREV.DEP.RATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.CURR.DEP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current outstanding financial charge amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>A multivalue field containing the keys to the Category Entry records generated by the accrual process </p>
            <p>Each time interest is accrued on a contract, the LMM ACCOUNT BALANCES fields are updated (e.g. OUTS ACCRUED INT is debited on a placement contract) and an entry is posted to Profit and Loss (e.g. INTEREST RECEIVED is credited on a placement contract).  The keys to the Category entry records produced in this accrual process are stored in this field. </p>
            <p>It should be noted that it is only the Category entry numbers that relate to the current interest period that are held in this field. Previous interest period information is held on the LMM.SCHEDULES.PAST file. </p>
            <p>Because one accrual period can have many Category Entries then this field will also accept sub values. </p>
            <p>The key to the Category Entry file is made up of 2 parts, Statement Number and Sequence Number. </p>
            <p>If a transaction generates several Entries, all the entries have the same Statement Number, the Entries on the same file are distinguished from each other by their Sequence Number. </p>
            <p>The Statement Number consists of: </p>
            <p>1.        4 digit date expressed as the number of days since           31st December 1967. 2.        Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5           integers and (usually) 2 decimals.  If the time is an           exact number of seconds since midnight, the decimals           are omitted. </p>
            <p>The Sequence Number is a 4 digit number from 0001 to 9999. </p>
            <p>Field 80.1 contains the Statement Number which is the first part of the key for all the Category Entries. </p>
            <p>Field 80.3 contains the range of Sequence Numbers used for the Category Entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>a)    Field 80.1 - Statement Number 9 integers and (usually) 2 decimals. b)    Field 80.2 - not applicable for category entries. c)    Field 80.3 - range of Category Entry Sequence Numbers Up to 5 numeric characters with '-' after the first. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMBURSE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.CUR.ACC.I.PAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The outstanding accrued interest on a liability contract, as of the last accrual date. Often called 'current interest payable'. </p>
            <p>This field holds the balance of accrued interest, that has not yet been paid, on a liability  contract. The amount is correct up to the date of the last accrual which is the last value in DATE INT ACC TO (Field 56).  Whenever an accrual is performed on a liability contract, the details of the interest calculation are recorded in Fields 52 to 57, and the result of the calculation added to this field. </p>
            <p>When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no accrual has yet been performed on the contract for the current interest period as shown in START PERIOD INT (Field 49) and END PERIOD INT (Field 50). </p>
            <p>When this amount is positive (no sign is shown) it signifies that at least one accrual has taken place in the current interest period and that this interest amount has been recorded but has not been paid to the customer yet. </p>
            <p>This field can never be negative. Each time this field has an amount added to it (e.g. an accrual for $100, implying a credit of $100), then an entry is posted to profit and loss, interest paid. (e.g. a debit of $100 to the profit and loss category code as input in field 32 on LMM.INSTALL.CONDS). </p>
            <p>An example of the updates to this field, and fields 52 to 57, is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.ACCR.TO.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of capital accrued to date for the current interest period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of extra interest accrued for grace period to be added to discount amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) Up to 19 numeric characters including</p>
            <p>    commas and a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.SUSP.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The outstanding suspended interest on an asset </p>
            <p>contract, as of the last accrual date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The amount is correct up to the date of the last </p>
            <p>suspension which is the last value in DATE INT ACC TO (Field 56).</p>
            <p />
            <p>asset contract, the details of the interest calculation are recorded in Field 56, and the result of the calculation added to this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no suspension has yet </p>
            <p>been performed on the contract for the current interest period as shown in START PERIOD INT (Field 49) and END PERIOD INT (Field 50).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMITTED.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of interest that is due at the end of the current interest period. </p>
            <p>This field contains the amount of interest that is due to be paid to the customer (liability contract), or due from the customer (asset contract), at the date specified in END.PERIOD.INT.  This amount is signed negative for an asset contract and positive for a liability contract but its absolute value is always the same as that contained in the TOT. INTEREST.AMT field on the contract. </p>
            <p>It is calculated by a following formula:                   INTEREST RATE        NUMBER OF DAYS PRINCIPAL   X          100        X       DAYS BASIS </p>
            <p>where: </p>
            <p>.         PRINCIPAL           is the outstanding principal                               on the contract. </p>
            <p>.         INTEREST RATE       is the rate of interest                               (including spread)                               applicable to the Contract. .         NUMBER OF DAYS      is the difference between                               START PERIOD INT and                               END PERIOD INT taking the                               various rules of INTEREST                               BASIS into account. </p>
            <p>.         DAYS BASIS          is determined by the                               INTEREST BASIS (365,360                               and 366) </p>
            <p>If there are no interest rate or principal changes within a given interest period then the value in this field will not change throughout the life of the interest period.  If one of these components change, or indeed the interest period itself is changed, then the Committed interest amount will be recalculated. </p>
            <p>Discounted contracts will show the amount of interest paid/received at the start of the current interest period and will not change this field during the current interest period. </p>
            <p>This field has three main uses: </p>
            <p>1.        On the Confirmation of the deal to the customer,           specifying the interest amount for the interest period. </p>
            <p>2.        As an internal piece of information such as a forecast           of an interest movement across an account           (FWD.ENTRY file). </p>
            <p>3.        As a check against rounding errors.  e.g. Three days           interest may compute 10 yet three daily accruals may           calculate 9.99 (3 x 3.33).  In this eventuality, the           last accrual is adjusted to 3.34 so that the sum of the           accruals always equals the COMMITTED INT amount at           the end of the interest period. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.ACCR.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from ISS.ACCR.FROM to ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set  to store issue accrual data. This field holds the date from which ISSUE.PL.AMOUNT is to be accrued. This set of fields store data in reverse order. The most recent is found in the  first multivalue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the originating application</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.PERIOD.COM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the end of the current commission period. </p>
            <p>This field contains the end date of the current commission period.  The first commission period of a contract is the one that starts on the value date and ends on the maturity or commission due date.  Consequently, at contract initiation, this field will contain the COMMISSION DUE DATE (if Call or Notice) or MATURITY DATE (if fixed maturity). </p>
            <p>If a contract has more than one commission period in its life then this date will always be the end date of the current period and it will always equal the start date (START PERIOD COM) of the next commission period, irrespective of any accrual method. </p>
            <p>With daily accruals, the first day accrual method will not require an accrual for the current period on the END PERIOD COM date.  The last day accrual method will require an accrual on this date for the current period. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PEN.COM.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the cumulative amount of penalty commission received. </p>
            <p>This field contains the cumulative amount of penalty commission received on the contract.  The value in field OS COMM ACC ON OD P plus PEN C LAST DAY ACC less the value in this field will be used by LD.RECEIPT.ENTRY to represent the total penalty commission outstanding on the contract. </p>
            <p>This field is associated with field PEN C LAST DAY ACC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.PRIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Previous financial charge principal value as used in the reducing balance financial charge type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field </p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields PREV.DEP.AMOUNT to PREV.DEP.RATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHOW.PD.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Selection promt for ENQUIRIES. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.PRIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current principal value as used for the reducing balance 'RB' financial charge type calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.PRIN.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that principal was last sent to a customer. This field is updated whenever CUM PRIN REC (Field 9.1) is updated and is for information only. </p>
            <p>This field records the date that funds are  sent to a customer either for drawdowns on asset contracts or for repayments on liability contracts. It is for information purposes only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue associated with field 9.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.INT.ACC.ON.OD.P</field>
<desc>
            <p>The penalty interest that has been accrued on overdue principal when this is done on a financial basis. </p>
            <p>Penalty interest is additional to the normal interest and is accrued on overdue principal on either a financial basis, when it is taken into profit and loss, or on a memo basis, where no entries are made but the amount is still accrued. The method used is determined by the value in field PEN I ACC FIN MEM on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for LOAN type contracts.  It is signed and is always negative. </p>
            <p>It is also used by the receipt entry system in respect of the liquidation of penalty interest. Penalty interest can never be prepaid. </p>
            <p>The value in this field represents the balance sheet contra entry to the profit and loss category indicated in field PL O SET IR PEN. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.ACCR.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds he recent commission accrual start date is stored in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.DEP.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate used in the financial charge calculation for previous accrual periods for the flexible schedules 'FS' and reducing balance 'RB' types.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Multi value associated with fields PREV.DEP.AMOUNT to PREV.DEP.RATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency in which the contract is denominated. </p>
            <p>This field represents the currency in which the contract plus all of the amount fields in this record are denominated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 character currency mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RET.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields RET.INT.AMT, RET.AC.OR.PL, RET.INT.DATE form a multi value set.If there is any interest adjusment in discounted type contract then the adjustment amount has to be paid back to the customer account or credited to the P and L .This adjustment amount is stored in this field.This adjustment is based on the RETURN.INT field in LD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.CAP.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The capital amounts for previous capital accrual periods.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Multi value associated with fields PREV.CAP.AMOUNT to PREV.CAP.END.DTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHRGS.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the fee or charge. This will always be in the same currency as the main contract. </p>
            <p>This field will always be denominated in the currency indicated in the CURRENCY field. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. </p>
            <p>The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          FEES PAID IN ADV           CHRGS CCY           MTHLY AMORT AMT           NO OF MTHS LEFT           ORIGIN AMOR MTH           CHRGS CODE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type CCY (Currency code). Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAB.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is updated when the SUSPEND.INCOME is set to YES. </p>
            <p>It holds the date from which the PD changes status to NAB and OVERDUE.STATUS in LD changes status to NAB.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the Contract ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUM.INT.AMT.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The cumulative interest that the customer has ever received on a contract. Used by payment routines to ensure that payments are not duplicated and consequently updated when payments are physically sent rather than 'accounted for'. </p>
            <p>This field records the amounts of interest sent to a customer on liability contracts. It is used to control the sending of 'interest' funds, ensuring that whatever money market or loans module is used to send funds to a customer, money cannot be sent twice. </p>
            <p>This field is not classified as a 'financial' field because firstly, it is often updated before the accounting entries for a payment are passed; and secondly, is purpose is one of control rather than providing financial information. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with Field 59.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YLD.DATE.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields YIELD.RATE , YLD.DATE.FR, YLD.DATE.TO  form an associated set.This field is used for accrual interest amount calculation.It stores the date till which the interest rate in YIELD.RATE is applicable. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.ACCR.PRIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The absolute value of the principal amount used for the accrual calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.ACCRUED.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The outstanding accrued Commission on a fiduciary deposit contract, as of the last accrual date. Often called 'commission earnt not collected' and 'current commission receivable'. </p>
            <p>This field holds the balance of accrued commission, that has not yet been received, on a contract. The amount is correct up to the date of the last accrual which is the last value in DATE COM ACC TO (Field 66).  Whenever an accrual is performed on a contract, the details of the commission calculation are recorded in Fields 63 to 66, and the result of the calculation added to this field. </p>
            <p>When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no accrual has yet been performed on the contract for the current commission period as shown in START PERIOD COM (Field 60) and END PERIOD COM (Field 61). i.e. no commission has been earnt (but not received from the customer) for the current period. </p>
            <p>When this amount is negative it signifies that at least one accrual has taken place in the current commission period and that this commission amount has been earnt (and recorded as profit) but has not been collected from the customer yet. This field can never be positive. </p>
            <p>Each time this field has an amount added to it (e.g. an accrual for $100, implying a debit of $100), then an entry is posted to profit and loss, commission received. (e.g. a credit of $100 to the profit and loss category code as input in field 29 on LMM.INSTALL.CONDS). </p>
            <p>To calculate the net commission outstanding on a contract (i.e. including pre-payments), this field should be added to OUTS OVER DUE COM (Field 15). </p>
            <p>It should be noted that the Money Market System only allows commission on fiduciary deposits and that fiduciary commission is only accrued when a commission rate has been input on the fiduciary contract.  If an amount of fiduciary commission (but no rate) is present on the contract then no commission accruals will take place.  Commission accruals will only take place when there is a value in the field FID COMM RATE on the contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDIVIDUAL.MVMTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Descriptor field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the accrual amount calculated by the system.  The accrual is calculated using the number of days in ISS.ACCR.DAYS and  ISSUE.PL.AMOUNT. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSP.COM.TODATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The amount of commission calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 63 to 70).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Whenever a commission suspension takes place, fields 66 to 70 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added.  </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field, SUSP.COMM.TODATE, contains the result of the commission calculation, rounded according to the currency.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.DEP.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end dates of the previous accrual periods.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Multi valued associated with PREV.DEP.AMOUNT to PREV.DEP.RATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.NO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. </p>
            <p>AC.NO.DAYS contains the number of days in the accrual period </p>
            <p>The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). </p>
            <p>These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUM.COM.AMT.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of commission paid on the contract. </p>
            <p>This association of fields is used by the payment functions to record the amount of commission  actually paid on the contract. </p>
            <p>It will be updated at authorisation or on the appropriate value date (if a forward date)of the appropriate event. </p>
            <p>Its purpose is one of control rather than providing financial information. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>This association of fields is used by the receipt application to record the amount of commission actually received on the contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:-           CUM COM AMT REC           DATE COM REC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: CUM COM AMT REC to DATE COM REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the charge which has been received. </p>
            <p>This is the amount of the particular charge which has been received.  Usually it  will be equal to the CHRGS AMT DUE (due amount) as all charges are liquidated automatically. Exceptionally, if for instance the charge liquidation account is closed, it can be different. The field is always signed and it is always positive. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the contract. It contains of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:-           CHRGS AMT DUE           CHRGS DUE DATE           CHRG CODE           AMT REC           DATE RECEIVED </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.INT.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the interest receipt or payment. </p>
            <p>The date of the interest receipt or payment referred           to in field CUM INT AMT REC. </p>
            <p>Associated Field Considerations. </p>
            <p>This association of fields is used by the payment and receipt applications to record the amount of interest actually paid or received on the contract. </p>
            <p>The associated fields are as follows:- </p>
            <p>          CUM INT AMT REC           DATE INT REC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: CUM INT AMT REC to DATE INT REC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.INT.ST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the previous interest start date </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.AMT.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc>
        <p>The interest amount on a liability contract that is due to be paid. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>INT.REC.IN.ADV</p>
        <p>The amount of discounted interest on a LOAN or COMMITMENT contract which has been received in advance. This field is only used for LOANS and COMMITMENTS where the interest is discounted. It holds the amount of interest for the interest period which has been received in advance (and consequently not yet earned). At the start of the period it will equal the committed interest and will be reduced by each interest accrual to zero at the end of the period. The field is signed and will always be negative. The content of this field will be accrued into the profit and loss category indicated in field PL O SET IRA indicated on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.Loans and Deposits only..</p>
        <p>INT.RECEIVED</p>
        <p>The fields INT.RECVD.DATE and INT.RECEIVED form an associated multivalue set.The INT.RECEIVED field contains the interest amount received from the customer on principal repayment date.</p>
        <p>INT.RECVD.DATE</p>
        <p>The fields INT.RECVD.DATE and INT.RECEIVED form an associated multivalue set.The INT.RECVD.DATE field contains the principal repayment date when interest amount is received from the customer on principal repayment date.</p>
        <p>INTEREST.TAX</p>
        <p>The amount of tax on the interest for the current period. The amount of interest tax charged on the interest liquidation date. Interest tax will always result in the customer being charged with the obligation. The corresponding credit will be passed to the category indicated on the table TAX . At the end of the interest period the value in this field will equal the value in field TOT INT TAX on LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS or MM.MONEY.MARKET main files. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        <p>ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        <p>Holds the actual accrued amount without rounding.</p>
        <p>ISS.ACCR.AMT</p>
        <p>This field stores the accrual amount calculated by the system. The accrual is calculated using the number of days in ISS.ACCR.DAYS and ISSUE.PL.AMOUNT.</p>
        <p>ISS.ACCR.DAYS</p>
        <p>The set of fields from ISS.ACCR.FROM to ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set to store issue accrual data. The difference between ISS.ACCR.FROM and ISS.ACCR.TO is stored in this field.</p>
        <p>ISS.ACCR.FROM</p>
        <p>The set of fields from ISS.ACCR.FROM to ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set to store issue accrual data. This field holds the date from which ISSUE.PL.AMOUNT is to be accrued. This set of fields store data in reverse order. The most recent is found in the first multivalue.</p>
        <p>ISS.ACCR.PRIN</p>
        <p>The set of fields from ISS.ACCR.FROM to ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set to store issue accrual data. This field holds the ISSUE.PL.AMOUNT which has to be accrued.</p>
        <p>AC.TO.DATE</p>
        <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. AC.TO.DATE contains the dates interest is accrued to for the period. The other 6 fields are for date accrued from (AC.FROM.DATE) no.of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>ISS.ACCR.TO</p>
        <p>The set of fields from ISS.ACCR.FROM to ISS.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set to store issue accrual data. This field holds the date till which ISSUE.PL.AMOUNT is to be accrued This set of fields store data in reverse order. The most recent is found in the first multivalue.</p>
        <p>ISS.AMT.ACCR.TO.DT</p>
        <p>
        </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> A maximum of 19 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        <p>ISSUE.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>
        </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> A maximum of 19 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        <p>LAST.DATE.REC</p>
        <p>The date of the receipt. This is the date the fee was received. Associated Field Considerations. Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details off charges on the contract. The associated fields are as follows:- OUTS FEE DUE FEE DUE DATE FEE CHRG CODE CUM FEE REC LAST DATE REC </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue associations: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>LAST.INT.REV.DATE</p>
        <p>The date of the last interest revision. This field is used for periodic interest contracts and contains the date of the last interest revision. This will be either the value date of the contract or the date of the last Revision Schedule. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>LAST.INT.SCH.DATE</p>
        <p>Holds the recent interest received dat.</p>
        <p>M.OS.C.ACC.ON.OD.P</p>
        <p>The penalty commission that has been accrued on overdue principal when this is done on a memo basis. Penalty commission is additional to the normal commission and is accrued on overdue principal on either a financial basis, when it is taken into profit and loss, or on a memo basis, where no entries are made but the amount is still accrued. The method used is determined by the value in field PEN C ACC FIN MEM on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. This field is only used for LOAN type contracts. It is signed and is always negative. The offset to this value is posted to the category indicated in field PL O SET CR PEN M on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>M.OS.I.ACC.ON.OD.P</p>
        <p>The penalty interest that has been accrued on overdue principal when this is done on a memo basis. Penalty interest is additional to the normal interest and is accrued on overdue principal on either a financial basis, when it is taken into profit and loss, or on a memo basis, where no entries are made but the amount is still accrued. The method used is determined by the value in field PEN I ACC FIN MEM on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. This field is only used for LOAN type contracts. It is signed and is always negative. The offset to this value is posted to the category indicated in field PL O SET IR PEN M on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>MTHLY.AMORT.AMT</p>
        <p>The amount of the fee or charge which is to be amortised each month end. This field represents the amortisation amount of fees on the contract. It is signed and is always positive. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into Profit and Loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. The associated fields are as follows:- FEES PAID IN ADV CHRGS CCY MTHLY AMORT AMT NO OF MTHS LEFT ORIGIN AMOR MTH CHRGS CODE </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>NAB.START.DATE</p>
        <p>This field is updated when the SUSPEND.INCOME is set to YES. It holds the date from which the PD changes status to NAB and OVERDUE.STATUS in LD changes status to NAB.</p>
        <p>ACTUAL.ACC.AMT</p>
        <p>The unrounded amount of interest calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 52 to 57). Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, ACTUAL ACC AMT, contains the result of the interest calculation, without rounding. It is signed negative for asset contracts and positive for liability contracts. An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of field 52, PRINC INT BAL. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        <p>NEXT.INT.REV.DATE</p>
        <p>The date of the next interest revision. This field is used for periodic interest contracts and contains the date of the next interest revision. This will be either the final maturity date of the contract or the date of the next Revision Schedule. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>NEXT.PRINC.DATE</p>
        <p>The date of the next principal repayment schedule. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>NO.OF.MTHS.LEFT</p>
        <p>The number of months remaining until the fee or charge is fully amortised. This field is initialised on the due date of the charge or fee to the total number of months in the amortisation period. It is decremented every month end when the amortisation amount is taken into profit and loss. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. The associated fields are as follows:- FEES PAID IN ADV CHRGS CCY MTHLY AMORT AMT NO OF MTHS LEFT ORIGIN AMOR MTH CHRGS CODE </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 to 3 numeric characters. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>ORIGIN.AMOR.MTH</p>
        <p>The total number of months over which the fee or charge is to be amortised. This is the original number of months over which the charge or fee is to be amortised. It is set up on the due date and is not changed. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. The associated fields are as follows:- FEES PAID IN ADV CHRGS CCY MTHLY AMORT AMT NO OF MTHS LEFT ORIGIN AMOR MTH CHRGS CODE </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 to 3 numeric characters. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>OS.COM.ACC.ON.OD.P</p>
        <p>The penalty commission that has been accrued on overdue principal when this is done on a financial basis. Penalty commission is additional to the normal commission and is accrued on overdue principal on either a financial basis, when it is taken into Profit and Loss, or on a memo basis, where no entries are made but the amount is still accrued. The method used is determined by the value in field PEN C ACC FIN MEM on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. This field is only used for LOAN type contracts. It is signed and is always negative. It is also used by the receipt entry system in respect of the liquidation of penalty commission. Penalty commission can never be prepaid. The value in this field represents the Balance Sheet contra entry to the Profit and Loss category indicated in field PL O SET CR PEN. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>OS.INT.ACC.ON.OD.P</p>
        <p>The penalty interest that has been accrued on overdue principal when this is done on a financial basis. Penalty interest is additional to the normal interest and is accrued on overdue principal on either a financial basis, when it is taken into profit and loss, or on a memo basis, where no entries are made but the amount is still accrued. The method used is determined by the value in field PEN I ACC FIN MEM on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. This field is only used for LOAN type contracts. It is signed and is always negative. It is also used by the receipt entry system in respect of the liquidation of penalty interest. Penalty interest can never be prepaid. The value in this field represents the balance sheet contra entry to the profit and loss category indicated in field PL O SET IR PEN. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>OUTS.ACC.WHT</p>
        <p>The amount of withholding tax which has accrued for the current interest period. The value in this field represents the amount of withholding tax which has accrued during the current interest period. At the end of the current interest period the value in this field will equal the value in field TOTAL WHT on LD LOANS AND DEPOSITS. During the end of day processing for the interest period end date the value in this field will be transferred to field WHT CERT AMT EXP on LD ACCOUNT BALANCES. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>OUTS.ACCRUED.COMM</p>
        <p>The outstanding accrued Commission on a fiduciary deposit contract, as of the last accrual date. Often called 'commission earnt not collected' and 'current commission receivable'. This field holds the balance of accrued commission, that has not yet been received, on a contract. The amount is correct up to the date of the last accrual which is the last value in DATE COM ACC TO (Field 66). Whenever an accrual is performed on a contract, the details of the commission calculation are recorded in Fields 63 to 66, and the result of the calculation added to this field. When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no accrual has yet been performed on the contract for the current commission period as shown in START PERIOD COM (Field 60) and END PERIOD COM (Field 61). i.e. no commission has been earnt (but not received from the customer) for the current period. When this amount is negative it signifies that at least one accrual has taken place in the current commission period and that this commission amount has been earnt (and recorded as profit) but has not been collected from the customer yet. This field can never be positive. Each time this field has an amount added to it (e.g. an accrual for $100, implying a debit of $100), then an entry is posted to profit and loss, commission received. (e.g. a credit of $100 to the profit and loss category code as input in field 29 on LMM.INSTALL.CONDS). To calculate the net commission outstanding on a contract (i.e. including pre-payments), this field should be added to OUTS OVER DUE COM (Field 15). It should be noted that the Money Market System only allows commission on fiduciary deposits and that fiduciary commission is only accrued when a commission rate has been input on the fiduciary contract. If an amount of fiduciary commission (but no rate) is present on the contract then no commission accruals will take place. Commission accruals will only take place when there is a value in the field FID COMM RATE on the contract. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        <p>OUTS.ACCRUED.INT</p>
        <p>The outstanding accrued interest on an asset contract, as of the last accrual date. Often called 'interest earned not collected' and 'current interest receivable'. This field holds the balance of accrued interest, that has not yet been received, on an asset contract. The amount is correct up to the date of the last accrual which is the last value in DATE INT ACC TO (Field 56). Whenever an accrual is performed on an asset contract, the details of the interest calculation are recorded in Fields 52 to 57, and the result of the calculation added to this field. When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no accrual has yet been performed on the contract for the current interest period as shown in START PERIOD INT (Field 49) and END PERIOD INT (Field 50). i.e. no interest has been earnt (but not received from the customer) for the current period. When this amount is negative it signifies that at least one accrual has taken place in the current interest period and that this interest amount has been earnt (and recorded as profit) but has not been collected from the customer yet. This field can never be positive. Each time this field has an amount added to it (e.g. an accrual for $100, implying a debit of $100), then an entry is posted to profit and loss, interest received. (e.g. a credit of $100 to the profit and loss category code as input in field 28 on LMM.INSTALL.CONDS). To calculate the net interest outstanding on a contract (i.e. including pre-payments), this field should be added to OUTS OVER DUE INT (Field 12). An example of the updates to this field, and fields 52 to 57, is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        <p>OUTS.COMM.ON.NAB</p>
        <p>Outstanding commission on the contract when it is on non-accrual basis. When a contract is transferred to non-accrual basis the following actions occur :- 1) The values contained in fields OUTS ACCRUED COM and OS COM ACC ON OD P are transferred to this field. This sum now represents the total of commission which has been written off by virtue of the status change to "NAB". The contract now ceases to attract normal or penalty commission accruals. 2) The system calculates the commission which would have accrued and updates this field accordingly. This field is held on a memorandum basis therefore no further profit and loss entries will be generated by the system. The offset to this field is PL O SET CR SUS on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. The field is only used for LOAN contract. It is signed and is always negative. When a contract has been put on non-accrual basis the commission which should be due is still accrued into this field. No profit and loss entries are made for this interest. The field is only used for LOAN contract. It is signed and is always negative. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>AMT.REC</p>
        <p>The amount of the charge which has been received. This is the amount of the particular charge which has been received. Usually it will be equal to the CHRGS AMT DUE (due amount) as all charges are liquidated automatically. Exceptionally, if for instance the charge liquidation account is closed, it can be different. The field is always signed and it is always positive. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the contract. It contains of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. The associated fields are as follows:- CHRGS AMT DUE CHRGS DUE DATE CHRG CODE AMT REC DATE RECEIVED </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>OUTS.CUR.ACC.I.PAY</p>
        <p>The outstanding accrued interest on a liability contract, as of the last accrual date. Often called 'current interest payable'. This field holds the balance of accrued interest, that has not yet been paid, on a liability contract. The amount is correct up to the date of the last accrual which is the last value in DATE INT ACC TO (Field 56). Whenever an accrual is performed on a liability contract, the details of the interest calculation are recorded in Fields 52 to 57, and the result of the calculation added to this field. When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no accrual has yet been performed on the contract for the current interest period as shown in START PERIOD INT (Field 49) and END PERIOD INT (Field 50). When this amount is positive (no sign is shown) it signifies that at least one accrual has taken place in the current interest period and that this interest amount has been recorded but has not been paid to the customer yet. This field can never be negative. Each time this field has an amount added to it (e.g. an accrual for $100, implying a credit of $100), then an entry is posted to profit and loss, interest paid. (e.g. a debit of $100 to the profit and loss category code as input in field 32 on LMM.INSTALL.CONDS). An example of the updates to this field, and fields 52 to 57, is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        <p>OUTS.CURR.DEP</p>
        <p>The current outstanding financial charge amount. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input fiel.</p>
        <p>OUTS.CURR.PRINC</p>
        <p>The current outstanding principal on the contract (excluding pre-payments) as of the 'EFFECTIVE DATE' field in this multivalue set of fields (fields 2 to 8). This field, along with fields 2 to 8 records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the process date of that movement is written into DATE FROM (Field 2), the value date is written into EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3),the principal movement amount is written into TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. This OUTS CURR PRINC field will only contain an amount (other than zero) when a contract has a value date less than or equal to the process date, and in the case of a fixed maturity contract, a maturity date greater than or equal to the process date. This field, along with fields 6 to 8, can have negative values (shown by a negative sign preceding the number) and positive values (shown with no sign preceding the number). Asset contracts with amounts outstanding are signed negative (as are pre-payments on deposits in the OUTS OD PRINC field); and liability contracts with amounts outstanding are positive (as are pre-payments on asset contracts in the OUTS OD PRINC field). To obtain the 'net' amount of principal outstanding (i.e. including pre-payments), this field needs to be added to the following field, OUTS OD PRINC (Field 6). An example of the possible movements is shown in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 8.</p>
        <p>OUTS.FEE.DUE</p>
        <p>The amount of fees due which have not been liquidated. This field holds the amount of the fee which has fallen due but has not been liquidated. It is signed and is always negative. Associated Field Considerations. Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details of charges on the contract. The associated fields are as follows:- OUTS FEE DUE FEE DUE DATE FEE CHRG CODE CUM FEE REC LAST DATE REC </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>OUTS.FWD.PRINC</p>
        <p>The outstanding forward valued principal on the contract as of the 'EFFECTIVE DATE' field in this multivalue set of fields (Fields 2 to 8). This field, along with fields 2 to 8 records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the process date of that movement is written into DATE FROM (Field 2), the value date of the movement is written to EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3), the principal movement amount is written into TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. This OUTS FWD PRINC field will only contain an amount (other than zero) when a contract has a forward valued drawdown pending. e.g. a new contract with a value date greater than the process date, or a forward valued principal increase. This field, along with fields 6 to 8, can have negative values (shown by a negative sign preceding the number) and positive values (shown with no sign preceding the number). Asset contracts with amounts outstanding are signed negative (as are pre-payments on deposits in the OUTS OD PRINC field); and liability contracts with amounts outstanding are positive (as are pre-payments on asset contracts in the OUTS OD PRINC field). An example of the possible movements is shown in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 8.</p>
        <p>OUTS.INT.ON.NAB</p>
        <p>Outstanding interest on the contract when it is on non-accrual basis. When a contract is transferred to non-accrual basis the following actions occur :- 1) The values contained in fields OUTS ACCRUED INT and OS INT ACC ON OD P are transferred to this field. This sum now represents the total of interest which has been written off by virtue of the status change to "NAB". The contract now ceases to attract normal or penalty interest accruals. 2) The system calculates the interest which would have accrued and updates this field accordingly. This field is held on a memorandum basis therefore no further profit and loss entries will be generated by the system. The offset to this field is PL O SET IR SUS on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. The field is only used for LOAN contract. It is signed and is always negative. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>OUTS.OD.PRINC</p>
        <p>The current outstanding principal on the contract that is due to be paid/received as of the 'DATE FROM field in this multivalue set of fields (fields 2 to 8). This field, along with fields 2 to 8 records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the process date of that movement is written into DATE FROM (Field 2), the value date is written into EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3) the principal movement amount is written into TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. This OUTS OD PRINC field will only contain an amount (other than zero) in two situations: (i) For LD contracts that have a scheduled principal amount due for payment but not yet liquidated due to non-receipt of funds. (ii) Whenever there is a pre-payment of principal through the LD.RECEIPT.ENTRY, MM.RECEIPT.ENTRY or MM.PAYMENT.ENTRY applications. In this situation the sign of the amount will always be opposite to the sign in the OUTS CURR PRINC field. (To calculate the net outstanding principal on a contract, i.e. taking pre-payments into account, this field should be added to OUTS CURR PRINC (Field 6). This field, along with fields 6 to 8, can have negative values (shown by a negative sign preceding the number) and positive values (shown with no sign preceding the number). Asset contracts with amounts outstanding are signed negative (as are pre-payments on deposits); and liability contracts with amounts outstanding are positive (as are pre-payments on asset contracts). An example of the possible movements is shown in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 8.</p>
        <p>OUTS.OVER.DUE.COM</p>
        <p>The amount of commission on a LOAN or COMMITMENT contract which is due but has not been received and/or any prepayment received. This field is only used for LOAN and COMMITMENT contracts. It records the net amount of commission that is due but has not been received. The field is signed and will be negative if commission is outstanding, and positive if there is a net prepayment, created via the LD.Receipt.Entry system. Updating occurs on commission due dates at End Of Day when the interest is manually liquidated and by the payment or receipt applications when manual liquidations are entered. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        <p>OUTS.OVER.DUE.INT</p>
        <p>If negative, the interest amount on an asset contract that is due to be received. If positive, the amount of pre-paid interest on an asset contract. This OUTS OVER DUE INT field will only contain an amount (other than zero or null) in two situations: 1. For LD contracts that have a scheduled interest amount due for payment but not yet liquidated due to non-receipt of funds. 2. Whenever there is a pre-payment of interest through the MM.RECEIPT.ENTRY application. In this situation the sign of the amount will always be positive which is opposite to the sign of the amount in OUTS ACCRUED INT (Field 11). In order to calculate the net interest outstanding on a contract, i.e. taking pre-payments into account, this field should be added to OUTS ACCRUED INT (Field 11). An example of the updates to this field, and fields 52 to 57, is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point.</p>
        <p>OUTS.PRINC.NAB</p>
        <p>The amount of overdue principal outstanding on the contract after the principal movement has been effected when it is on a non-accrual basis. When the contract is put on a non-accrual basis all the outstanding principal is moved to this field. This is done by the routine LD.NAB.TRANSFER during the end of day processing when the number of days after the contract has become overdue when it should go to NAB as defined on the LMM.INSTALL.CONDS record is reached. It is also used by the receipt entry system in respect of the liquidation of outstanding principal on an "NAB" basis. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue associated fields DATE FROM to OUTS PRINC NAB hold the history of all principal movements to the contract. They are maintained for all contract types. The associated fields are as follows:- DATE FROM EFFECTIVE DATE TRANS PRIN AMT OUTS FWD PRINC OUTS CURR PRINC OUTS OD PRINC OUTS PRINC NAB Each multivalue set in the association records details of the particular movement which occurred on the date in the field DATE FROM. These fields hold historic data with the exception of the last multivalue association which shows the current principal position of the contract. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association with fields 2 to 8. (For LD.Loans and deposits only..</p>
        <p>APPLICATION</p>
        <p>Holds the originating applicatio.</p>
        <p>OUTS.SUSP.COMM</p>
        <p>The outstanding suspended Commission as of the last accrual date. This field holds the balance of suspended commission, that has not yet been received, on a contract. The amount is correct up to the date of the last suspension which is the last value in DATE COM ACC TO (Field 67). Whenever an suspension is performed on a contract, the details of the commission calculation are recorded in Fields 63 to 67, and the result of the calculation added to this field. When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no suspension has yet been performed on the contract for the current commission period as shown in START PERIOD COM (Field 60) and END PERIOD COM (Field 61). When this amount is negative it signifies that at least one suspension has taken place in the current commission period and that this commission amount has been suspended and has not been collected from the customer yet. This field can never be positive.</p>
        <p>OUTS.SUSP.INT</p>
        <p>The outstanding suspended interest on an asset contract, as of the last accrual date. The amount is correct up to the date of the last suspension which is the last value in DATE INT ACC TO (Field 56). asset contract, the details of the interest calculation are recorded in Field 56, and the result of the calculation added to this field. When this amount is null or zero it signifies that no suspension has yet been performed on the contract for the current interest period as shown in START PERIOD INT (Field 49) and END PERIOD INT (Field 50).</p>
        <p>PEN.C.LAST.DAY.ACC</p>
        <p>This field contains the accrual amount for today/tomorrow. For contracts on a last day accrual basis it is necessary to compute the penalty commission for today/tomorrow, the resulting value will be reflected in this field. This field is associated with field PEN COM REC. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>PEN.COM.REC</p>
        <p>This field contains the cumulative amount of penalty commission received. This field contains the cumulative amount of penalty commission received on the contract. The value in field OS COMM ACC ON OD P plus PEN C LAST DAY ACC less the value in this field will be used by LD.RECEIPT.ENTRY to represent the total penalty commission outstanding on the contract. This field is associated with field PEN C LAST DAY ACC. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>PEN.I.LAST.DAY.ACC</p>
        <p>This field contains the accrual amount for today/tomorrow. For contracts on a last day accrual basis it is necessary to compute the penalty interest for today/tomorrow, the resulting value will be reflected in this field. This field is associated with field PEN INT REC. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>PEN.INT.REC</p>
        <p>This field contains the cumulative amount of penalty interest received. This field contains the cumulative amount of penalty interest received on the contract. The value in field OS INT ACC ON OD P plus PEN I LAST DAY ACC less the value in this field will be used by LD.RECEIPT.ENTRY to represent the total penalty interest outstanding on the contract. This field is associated with field PEN I LAST DAY ACC. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>PREV.CAP.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>The capital amounts for previous capital accrual periods. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Multi value associated with fields PREV.CAP.AMOUNT to PREV.CAP.END.DT.</p>
        <p>PREV.CAP.END.DT</p>
        <p>The end dates for previous capital accrual periods. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Multi value associated with fields PREV.CAP.AMOUNT to PREV.CAP.END.DT.</p>
        <p>PREV.DEP.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>The end dates of the previous accrual periods. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi valued associated with PREV.DEP.AMOUNT to PREV.DEP.RAT.</p>
        <p>PREV.DEP.END.DT</p>
        <p>The accrual period end date for previous financial charge accruals. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Multi value associated with fields PREV.DEP.AMOUNT to PREV.DEP.RAT.</p>
        <p>BASE.DATE</p>
        <p>This field is used when Interest Schedules are generated using the INTEREST.DUE.DATE field. This is required to generate the next interest due date when the BASE.DATE.KEY is set to BASE. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format.</p>
        <p>PREV.DEP.RATE</p>
        <p>The rate used in the financial charge calculation for previous accrual periods for the flexible schedules 'FS' and reducing balance 'RB' types. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Multi value associated with fields PREV.DEP.AMOUNT to PREV.DEP.RAT.</p>
        <p>PREV.INT.ST.DATE</p>
        <p>Holds the previous interest start dat.</p>
        <p>PREV.PRIN.VALUE</p>
        <p>The Previous financial charge principal value as used in the reducing balance financial charge type. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi value associated with fields PREV.DEP.AMOUNT to PREV.DEP.RAT.</p>
        <p>PRINC.COMM.BAL</p>
        <p>The outstanding principal balance as of the DATE COM ACC TO field in this multivalue set of accrual fields (fields 63 to 66). Whenever a commission accrual takes place, fields 63 to 66 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC COMM BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC COMM RATE (the actual commission rate used in the calculation); DATE COM ACC TO (the date commission is accrued to); and the resulting commission amount field - COMM AMT TODATE. So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, PRINC COMM BAL, is calculated by summing the OUTS CURR PRINC and OUTS OD PRINC fields to arrive at a net outstanding principal balance. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 to 14 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        <p>PRINC.INT.BAL</p>
        <p>The outstanding principal balance as of the DATE INT ACC TO field in this multivalue set of accrual fields (fields 52 to 57). Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, PRINC INT BAL, is calculated by summing the OUTS CURR PRINC and OUTS OD PRINC fields to arrive at a net outstanding principal balance. It is signed negative for asset contracts and positive for liability contracts. An example of how this field, and the other accrual fields are used is shown below: Example: Asset contract, valued 11th February 1987, Maturing 11th March 1987. Principal is one million pounds, interest rate is fixed at 10%, accruals are performed daily and the first day accrual method is employed. State of fields prior to first accrual: CURRENCY : GBP DATE FROM : 11th February 1987 EFFECTIVE DATE : 11th February 1987 TRANS PRIN AMT : - 1,000,000 OUTS FWD PRINC : 0 OUTS CURR PRINC : - 1,000,000 OUTS OD PRINC : 0 OUTS ACCRUED INT : " " START PERIOD INT : 11th February 1987 END PERIOD INT : 11th March 1987 COMMITTED INT : - 7,671.23 PRINC INT BAL : " " INT AMT TODATE : " " AC INT RATE : " " AC INT SPREAD : " " DATE INT ACC TO : " " ACTUAL ACC AMT : " " NB: " " = NULL OR BLANK State of fields after first accrual: CURRENCY : GBP DATE FROM : 11th February 1987 EFFECTIVE DATE : 11th February 1987 TRANS PRIN AMT : - 1,000,000 OUTS FWD PRINC : 0 OUTS CURR PRINC : - 1,000,000 OUTS OD PRINC : 0 OUTS ACCRUED INT : - 273.97 START PERIOD INT : 11th February 1987 END PERIOD INT : 11th March 1987 COMMITTED INT : - 7,671.23 PRINC INT BAL : - 1,000,000 INT AMT TODATE : - 273.97 AC INT RATE : 10% AC INT SPREAD : " " DATE INT ACC TO : 11th February 1987 ACTUAL ACC AMT : - 273.9726 Note: One days interest has been calculated, the fields in the calculation have been updated and the final field OUTS ACCRUED INT has been updated. State of fields after second accrual: CURRENCY : GBP DATE FROM : 11th February 1987 EFFECTIVE DATE : 11th February 1987 TRANS PRIN AMT : - 1,000,000 OUTS FWD PRINC : 0 OUTS CURR PRINC : - 1,000,000 OUTS OD PRINC : 0 OUTS ACCRUED INT : - 547.95 START PERIOD INT : 11th February 1987 END PERIOD INT : 11th March 1987 COMMITTED INT : - 7,671.23 PRINC INT BAL : -1,000,000 INT AMT TODATE : - 547.95 AC INT RATE : 10% AC INT SPREAD : " " DATE INT ACC TO : 12th February 1987 ACTUAL ACC AMT : - 547.94521 Note: Another days interest has been calculated and added to OUTS ACCRUED INT. Because the components in the interest calculation were no different to the first accrual, a new set of accrual details were not added but the amount and date fields were changed. If, prior to the third accrual, a prepayment of 250,000 principal was made, valued 13th February, the state of the fields after the third accrual would be as follows: State of fields after third accrual: CURRENCY : GBP DATE FROM : 11th February 1987 EFFECTIVE DATE : 11th February 1987 TRANS PRIN AMT : - 1,000,000 OUTS FWD PRINC : 0 OUTS CURR PRINC : - 1,000,000 OUTS OD PRINC : 250,000 OUTS ACCRUED INT : - 753.43 START PERIOD INT : 11th February 1987 END PERIOD INT : 11th March 1987 COMMITTED INT : - 5,890.42 PRINC INT BAL : -1,000,000- 750,000 INT AMT TODATE : - 547.95 - 205.48 AC INT RATE : 10% 10% AC INT SPREAD : " " " " DATE INT ACC TO : 12th February 1987 13th February 1987 ACTUAL ACC AMT : - 547.94521- 205.47945 1ST SET 2ND SET Note: This time, another set of accrual fields have been written because the principal balance has changed. Another result of the principal change is that the COMMITTED INT field has been re-calculated. An example for a deposit contract would be similar to the one above with the following exceptions: 1. Amounts would have the opposite sign. 2. The OUTS ACCRUED INT field would be replaced by the OUTS CUR ACC I PAY field. The field AC INT SPREAD is only used when the contract is tied to a floating interest rate. In this case the AC INT RATE is still the actual interest rate used in the calculation but this time it includes the interest spread as shown in AC INT SPREAD. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 to 14 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        <p>PRINCIPAL.TAX</p>
        <p>The amount of principal tax taken on the drawdown or principal increase amount. The amount of principal tax charged on the drawdown or principal increase amount. The tax will be levied on the relevant value date. Principal tax will always result in the customer receiving the net disbursement. In the case of loans the customer will receive the net of principal less tax, in the case of deposits the customer will be charged principal plus tax. The corresponding credit will be passed to the category indicated on the table TAX . At the end of the interest period the value in this field will equal the value in field TOT PRINC TAX on LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>REIMBURSE.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>
        </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> A maximum of 19 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        <p>RESERVED.1</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>RESERVED.2</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>RESERVED.3</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>CANCEL.AMT</p>
        <p>Specifies the amount of principal cancelled. The value in this field is the same as the value in field TRANS.PRIN.AMT for the multivalue defined in the corresponding CANCEL.MV.NO. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 19 type AMT numeric characters. (Associated multivalue field). Noinput field.</p>
        <p>RESERVED.4</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>RESERVED.5</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>RESERVED.6</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>RET.AC.OR.PL</p>
        <p>The fields RET.INT.AMT, RET.AC.OR.PL, RET.INT.DATE form a multi value set.If RETURN.INT field in LD is set to YES then this field will get updated 'AC-customer account'.This indicates that the adjusted interest amount has to be credited to the customer account. If RETURN.INT is not set then this field will hold 'PL- PL category' taken from LMM.INSTALL.CONDS.</p>
        <p>RET.AC.OR.PL.COM</p>
        <p>When a Discount Loan Contract is preclosed, The field RETURN.COM field in the contract indicates whether the commission that is taken up front should be returned to the Customer, or placed in a PL bucket. If that field is set to YES, RET.AC.OR.PL.COM will have an ACCOUNT number prefixed by 'AC', else it would have a PL Category prefixed by 'PL'.</p>
        <p>RET.COM.AMT</p>
        <p>When a Discount Loan Contract is preclosed, The field RETURN.COM field in the contract indicates whether the commission that is taken up front should be returned to the Customer, or placed in a PL bucket. This Field holds the amount commission amount that is to be returned or placed in a PL bucket.</p>
        <p>RET.COM.DATE</p>
        <p>This field holds the date on which the Loan contract is preclosed.</p>
        <p>RET.INT.AMT</p>
        <p>The fields RET.INT.AMT, RET.AC.OR.PL, RET.INT.DATE form a multi value set.If there is any interest adjusment in discounted type contract then the adjustment amount has to be paid back to the customer account or credited to the P and L .This adjustment amount is stored in this field.This adjustment is based on the RETURN.INT field in L.</p>
        <p>RET.INT.DATE</p>
        <p>The fields RET.INT.AMT, RET.AC.OR.PL, RET.INT.DATE form a multi value set.This field holds the date on which the adjustment amount is credited to customer account or P and L.</p>
        <p>RMB.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        <p>Holds the actual accrued amount without rounding.</p>
        <p>CANCEL.DATE</p>
        <p>Contains the value date which was used for the cancellation of the interest amount. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 11 type D characters - standard date format. (Associated multivalue field). Noinput field.</p>
        <p>RMB.ACCR.AMT</p>
        <p>This field stores the accrual amount calculated by the system. The accrual is calculated using the number of days in RMB.ACCR.DAYS and REIMBURSE.PL.AM.</p>
        <p>RMB.ACCR.DAYS</p>
        <p>The set of fields from RMB.ACCR.FROM to RMB.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set to store reimburse accrual data. The difference between RMB.ACCR.FROM and RMB.ACCR.TO is stored in this field.</p>
        <p>RMB.ACCR.FROM</p>
        <p>The set of fields from RMB.ACCR.FROM to RMB.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set to store reimburse accrual data. This field holds the date from which REIMBURSE.PL.AMT is to be accrued. This set of fields store data in reverse order. The most recent is found in the first multivalue.</p>
        <p>RMB.ACCR.PRIN</p>
        <p>This field holds the REIMBURSE.PL.AMT which has to be accrued.</p>
        <p>RMB.ACCR.TO</p>
        <p>The set of fields from RMB.ACCR.FROM to RMB.ACCR.ACTAMT form an associated set to store reimburse accrual data. This field holds the date to which REIMBURSE.PL.AMT is to be accrued. This set of fields store data in reverse order. The most recent is found in the first multivalue.</p>
        <p>RMB.AMT.ACCR.TO.DT</p>
        <p>
        </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> A maximum of 19 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        <p>SHOW.PD.INFO</p>
        <p>Selection promt for ENQUIRIES.</p>
        <p>START.DATE</p>
        <p>Descriptor field.</p>
        <p>START.DATE.IR</p>
        <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> A maximum of 11 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        <p>START.PERIOD.COM</p>
        <p>The date of the start of the current commission period. The first commission period of a contract is the one that starts on the contract VALUE DATE and so at initiation, this field will contain the VALUE DATE. If a contract has more than one commission period in its life then this date will always be the start date of the current period and it will always equal the end date (END PERIOD COM) of the previous commission period, irrespective of any accrual method. With daily accruals, the first day accrual method will cause an accrual for the current period to take place on the START PERIOD COM date. The last day accrual method will cause the first accrual in the current period to occur on the day after the START PERIOD COM date. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>CANCEL.INT</p>
        <p>Specifies the amount of interest cancelled by the split current month, previous month and previous year. The first subvalue specifies the amount for the current month, the second subvalue for the previous month and the third subvalue for the previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 19 type AMT numeric characters. (Associated subvalue field). Noinput field.</p>
        <p>START.PERIOD.INT</p>
        <p>The date of the start of the current interest period. The first interest period of a contract is the one that starts on the contract VALUE DATE and so at initiation, this field will contain the VALUE DATE. If a contract has more than one interest period in its life then this date will always be the start date of the current period and it will always equal the end date (END PERIOD INT) of the previous interest period, irrespective of any accrual method. With daily accruals, the first day accrual method will cause an accrual for the current period to take place on the START PERIOD INT date. The last day accrual method will cause the first accrual in the current period to occur on the day after the START PERIOD INT date. It should be noted that the system assumes that all contracts have an interest period, even if they have no interest rate. Consequently, this field will always have a value even if the contract type is one that has no interest e.g. account receivable, Sundry deposit. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>STMT.NO</p>
        <p>A multivalue field containing the keys to the Category Entry records generated by the accrual process Each time interest is accrued on a contract, the LMM ACCOUNT BALANCES fields are updated (e.g. OUTS ACCRUED INT is debited on a placement contract) and an entry is posted to Profit and Loss (e.g. INTEREST RECEIVED is credited on a placement contract). The keys to the Category entry records produced in this accrual process are stored in this field. It should be noted that it is only the Category entry numbers that relate to the current interest period that are held in this field. Previous interest period information is held on the LMM.SCHEDULES.PAST file. Because one accrual period can have many Category Entries then this field will also accept sub values. The key to the Category Entry file is made up of 2 parts, Statement Number and Sequence Number. If a transaction generates several Entries, all the entries have the same Statement Number, the Entries on the same file are distinguished from each other by their Sequence Number. The Statement Number consists of: 1. 4 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st December 1967. 2. Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers and (usually) 2 decimals. If the time is an exact number of seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted. The Sequence Number is a 4 digit number from 0001 to 9999. Field 80.1 contains the Statement Number which is the first part of the key for all the Category Entries. Field 80.3 contains the range of Sequence Numbers used for the Category Entries. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> a) Field 80.1 - Statement Number 9 integers and (usually) 2 decimals. b) Field 80.2 - not applicable for category entries. c) Field 80.3 - range of Category Entry Sequence Numbers Up to 5 numeric characters with '-' after the first. (Internal file, no input..</p>
        <p>SUSP.COM.TODATE</p>
        <p>The amount of commission calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 63 to 70). Whenever a commission suspension takes place, fields 66 to 70 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, SUSP.COMM.TODATE, contains the result of the commission calculation, rounded according to the currency.</p>
        <p>SUSP.INT.TODATE</p>
        <p>The amount of interest calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 54 to 60). Whenever an interest suspension takes place, fields 54 to 60 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - SUSP.INT.TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, SUSP.INT.TODATE, contains the result of the interest calculation, rounded according to the currency.</p>
        <p>SYS.CALC.COMM</p>
        <p>Field to hold the System calculated commission amount for the current period when SPECIAL.COMM.BASIS is defined. Standard AMT type field. Applicable only for LD produc.</p>
        <p>SYS.CALC.INT</p>
        <p>Field to hold the System calculated interest amount for the current period when SPECIAL.INT.BASIS is defined Standard AMT type field Applicable only for LD produc.</p>
        <p>TOT.SUSP.COMM</p>
        <p>Total Commission Amount that is suspended.</p>
        <p>TOT.SUSP.INT</p>
        <p>This field holds the total suspended interest from the NAB.START.DATE till the last accrual (suspension) date.</p>
        <p>TRANS.PRIN.AMT</p>
        <p>The transaction amount that has affected the principal balances on the contract. This field, along with fields 2 to 8 records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the value date of that movement is written into EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3), the process date of the movement is written into DATE FROM (Field 2), the principal movement amount is written into this field, and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. This TRANS PRIN AMT field will contain an amount WHENEVER there is a principal movement, irrespective of whether there is a movement of funds into or out of the bank. e.g. it will show an amount when a current contract becomes 'due' as well as when the due amount is liquidated. This field can have negative values (shown by a negative sign preceding the number) and positive values (shown with no sign preceding the number). Movements on asset contracts are always shown as negative values except for reductions in principal which are shown as positive. Movements on liability contracts are always shown as positive values except for reductions in principal which are shown as negative. An example of the possible movements is shown in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 7.</p>
        <p>WHT.CERT.AMT.EXP</p>
        <p>The total amount of withholding tax certificates which the customer is required to submit to the bank. This field represents the total value of withholding tax certificates for which the customer is liable. This amount can represent the certificate obligations for multiple interest periods. The value in this field is increased by the amount indicated in field OUTS ACC WHT on LMM ACCOUNT BALANCES during the end of day processing on the interest period end date. It is decremented by the amount of witholding tax certificates submitted via the withholding tax function LD WITHOLDING TAX The value in this field will always agree with the value in field TAX AMOUNT EXP on LD WITHOLDIMG TAX. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>CANCEL.MV.NO</p>
        <p>Specifies the multivalue number of the set of associated fields from DATE.FROM to OUTS.PRINC.NAB which relate to this cancellation. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 3 numeric characters. (Associated multivalue field). Noinput field.</p>
        <p>YIELD.RATE</p>
        <p>The fields YIELD.RATE , YLD.DATE.FR, YLD.DATE.TO form an associated set. This field is used to store the yield interest rate when the rate calculation is Done by yield method. This field gets populated when YIELD.METHOD In LD is set to "YES.</p>
        <p>YLD.DATE.FR</p>
        <p>The fields YIELD.RATE , YLD.DATE.FR, YLD.DATE.TO form an associated set.This field is used for accrual interest amount calculation.It stores the date from which the interest rate in YIELD.RATE is applicabl.</p>
        <p>YLD.DATE.TO</p>
        <p>The fields YIELD.RATE , YLD.DATE.FR, YLD.DATE.TO form an associated set.This field is used for accrual interest amount calculation.It stores the date till which the interest rate in YIELD.RATE is applicable.</p>
        <p>CAP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        <p>The actual i.e. unrounded amount accrued to date for the current accrual period. Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>AC.ACCR.AMT</p>
        <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. AC.ACCR.AMT contains the amount of interest accrued for the period rounded to the number of decimals for the currency. The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard T24 amount field of up to 19 characters.</p>
        <p>CAP.ACCR.AMT</p>
        <p>The rounded amount accrued to date for the current accrual period. Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>CAP.ACCR.DAYS</p>
        <p>The number of days for which accruals have been made for the current accrual period. Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>CAP.ACCR.FROM</p>
        <p>The start date of the current capital accrual period Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>CAP.ACCR.PRIN</p>
        <p>The absolute value of the principal amount used for the accrual calculation. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>CAP.ACCR.TO</p>
        <p>The date to which accruals have been made for the current accrual period. Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>CAP.ACCR.TO.DT</p>
        <p>The amount of capital accrued to date for the current interest period. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input fiel.</p>
        <p>CAP.CHRG.IND</p>
        <p>Fields CHRGS.AMT.DUE to CAP.CHRG.IND form a related multi value set. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> A maximum of 3 characters may be entered. The following values are permitted: Y N.</p>
        <p>CAP.END.DATE</p>
        <p>The end date of the current capital accrual period. This is equal to the end date of the current interest period. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input.</p>
        <p>CAP.START.DATE</p>
        <p>The start date of the current capital accrual period. This is equal to the start date of the current interest period. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input fiel.</p>
        <p>CAPITAL.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>The principal component of the current Annuity repayment amount. Used to determine capital accruals for finance leasing contracts. This amount will be accrued over the current repayment period. The sign will be positive for loans and negative for deposits, with the associated accruals being the opposite sign. The accruals will conform to interest accruals in that P&amp;L will be credited and CRF debited for loans (vice versa for deposits) </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input fiel.</p>
        <p>AC.ACT.ACCR</p>
        <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. AC.ACT.ACCR contains the amount of interest accrued rounded to six decimal places. The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard T24 amount field of up to 19 characters.</p>
        <p>CATEGORY</p>
        <p>HHolds the contrac categor.</p>
        <p>CHRG.CODE</p>
        <p>The charge code of the charge. This is the code indicated on the main contract and refers to an entry on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The value in field CATEGORY CODE on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS indicates which profit and loss account the charges will be posted to. Also indicated is the period over which the contract is to be amortised plus the charge description. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the main contract. It contains details of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. The associated fields are as follows:- CHRGS AMT DUE CHRGS DUE DATE CHRG CODE AMT REC DATE RECEIVED </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 3 numeric characters. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>CHRGS.AMT.DUE</p>
        <p>The amount of the fee or charge which is due. This field represents the amount of the charge which is due on the contract. That is those charges which have a value date prior to or equal to the process date. Each charge on the contract will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the claim date of the charge. This field is signed and is always negative. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the contract. It contains of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. The associated fields are as follows:- CHRGS AMT DUE CHRGS DUE DATE CHRG CODE AMT REC DATE RECEIVED </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>CHRGS.CCY</p>
        <p>The currency of the fee or charge. This will always be in the same currency as the main contract. This field will always be denominated in the currency indicated in the CURRENCY field. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. The associated fields are as follows:- FEES PAID IN ADV CHRGS CCY MTHLY AMORT AMT NO OF MTHS LEFT ORIGIN AMOR MTH CHRGS CODE </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 3 type CCY (Currency code). Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>CHRGS.CODE</p>
        <p>The charge code of the fee or charge. This is the code indicated on the main contract and refers an entry on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The value in field CATEGORY CODE on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS indicates which profit and loss account the fees or charges will be posted to. Also indicated is the period over which the contract is to be amortised plus the charge description. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated on in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. The associated fields are as follows:- FEES PAID IN ADV CHRGS CCY MTHLY AMORT AMT NO OF MTHS LEFT ORIGIN AMOR MTH CHRGS CODE </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 2 numeric characters. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>CHRGS.DUE.DATE</p>
        <p>The claim date of the charge. This is the value date when the particular charge has been claimed. It is taken directly from the contract. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the contract. It contains of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. The associated fields are as follows:- CHRGS AMT DUE CHRGS DUE DATE CHRG CODE AMT REC DATE RECEIVED </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>CMMT.EXCH.RATE</p>
        <p>This field will get updated for foreign currency commitment contracts.The exchange rate is stored in this field.</p>
        <p>COM.ACCR.START</p>
        <p>Holds he recent commission accrual start date is stored in this field.</p>
        <p>COM.ACT.ACC.AMT</p>
        <p>Stores the unrounded commision accrual amounts.</p>
        <p>COM.REC.IN.ADV</p>
        <p>The amount of discounted commission on a LD.LOAN or COMMITMENT contract which has been received in advance. This field is only used for LOANS and COMMITMENTS where the commission is discounted. It hold the amount of commission for the commission period which has been received in advance (and consequently not yet earned). At the start of the period it will equal the committed commission and will be reduced by each commission accrual to zero at the end of the period. The field is signed and will always be negative. The contents of this field will be accrued into field PL O SET IRA on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>AC.COM.RATE</p>
        <p>The actual commission rate used in the calculation of commission in this set of accrual fields (field 63 to 66). Whenever a commission accrual takes place, fields 63 to 66 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC COMM BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC COMM RATE (the actual commission rate used in the calculation); DATE COM ACC TO (the date commission is accrued to); and the resulting commission amount field - COMM AMT TODATE. So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, AC COM RATE contains the commission rate that was used in the calculation of commission in the multi set of accrual fields of which this field is part. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard rate format.</p>
        <p>COMM.ADJ.AMT</p>
        <p>Field to hold the total of difference between the User defined commission amount and System calculated commission amount when SPECIAL.COMM.BASIS is defined Standard AMT type field. Applicable only for LD produc.</p>
        <p>COMM.AMT.TODATE</p>
        <p>The amount of commission calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 60 to 66). Whenever a commission accrual takes place, fields 63 to 66 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC COMM BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC COMM RATE (the actual commission rate used in the calculation); DATE COM ACC TO (the date commission is accrued to); and the resulting commission amount field - COMM AMT TODATE. So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, COMM AMT TODATE, contains the result of the commission calculation, rounded according to the currency. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        <p>COMMISSION.TAX</p>
        <p>The amount of tax on the commission or the current period. The amount of commission tax charged on the commission liquidation date. Commission tax will always result in the customer being charged with the obligation. The corresponding credit will be passed to the category indicated on the table TAX . At the end of the interest period the value in this field will equal the value in field TOT COM TAX on LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>COMMITTED.COMM</p>
        <p>The calculated commission amount for the current commission period. This fields holds the amount of commission due on the contract for the current commission period. It is a signed amount and is always negative. For commission bearing contracts this amount will be an estimated figure for the period, based on the schedules, principal changes, rate changes, etc. currently affecting the contract. This amount will always be updated immediately when subject to any further changes. For discounted contracts it will be the actual committed amount which has been paid or received and will not be subject to any changes during the period. The value in this field will correspond to the value in field TOTAL COM AMT on the main contract. An amount will be generated in this field immediately upon </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. is subject to financial changes. If this is a multiple period contract the field will be reset at the end of the commission period and an amount inserted which will represent the commission for the following period.</p>
        <p>COMMITTED.INT</p>
        <p>The amount of interest that is due at the end of the current interest period. This field contains the amount of interest that is due to be paid to the customer (liability contract), or due from the customer (asset contract), at the date specified in END.PERIOD.INT. This amount is signed negative for an asset contract and positive for a liability contract but its absolute value is always the same as that contained in the TOT. INTEREST.AMT field on the contract. It is calculated by a following formula: INTEREST RATE NUMBER OF DAYS PRINCIPAL X 100 X DAYS BASIS where: . PRINCIPAL is the outstanding principal on the contract. . INTEREST RATE is the rate of interest (including spread) applicable to the Contract. . NUMBER OF DAYS is the difference between START PERIOD INT and END PERIOD INT taking the various rules of INTEREST BASIS into account. . DAYS BASIS is determined by the INTEREST BASIS (365,360 and 366) If there are no interest rate or principal changes within a given interest period then the value in this field will not change throughout the life of the interest period. If one of these components change, or indeed the interest period itself is changed, then the Committed interest amount will be recalculated. Discounted contracts will show the amount of interest paid/received at the start of the current interest period and will not change this field during the current interest period. This field has three main uses: 1. On the Confirmation of the deal to the customer, specifying the interest amount for the interest period. 2. As an internal piece of information such as a forecast of an interest movement across an account (FWD.ENTRY file). 3. As a check against rounding errors. e.g. Three days interest may compute 10 yet three daily accruals may calculate 9.99 (3 x 3.33). In this eventuality, the last accrual is adjusted to 3.34 so that the sum of the accruals always equals the COMMITTED INT amount at the end of the interest period. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        <p>CONSOL.KEY</p>
        <p>This field contains the key of the Consolidation record (in the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file) into which the details of this contract are consolidated </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Alphanumeric, as specified in the Consolidate Conditions file (CONSOLIDATE.COND). (Internal field..</p>
        <p>CONTRACT.ID</p>
        <p>Holds the Contract ID.</p>
        <p>CONTRACT.NUMBER</p>
        <p>The record identification. This field is the key of the record and is always the contract number, e.g. LD/86255/00123 or MM/86255/00123, plus a two digit suffix. The two digit suffix identifies the nature and type of record ie:- 00 For LD contracts, the 00 relates to the extent of "our share". All MM contracts end with 00. 01-98 relates to Syndicated contracts and identifies the participant's number and share. 99 relates to the total of the syndication. Therefore type "99" will reflect the total exposure to the customer in relation to fields "00" to "98". There is only one of these records at any one time representing either the unauthorised or authorised record on the LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS or MM.MONEY.MARKET main files. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard contract number plus two digit suffix which results in a 14 character key.</p>
        <p>CUM.COM.AMT.REC</p>
        <p>The amount of commission paid on the contract. This association of fields is used by the payment functions to record the amount of commission actually paid on the contract. It will be updated at authorisation or on the appropriate value date (if a forward date)of the appropriate event. Its purpose is one of control rather than providing financial information. Associated Field Considerations. This association of fields is used by the receipt application to record the amount of commission actually received on the contract. The associated fields are as follows:- CUM COM AMT REC DATE COM REC </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: CUM COM AMT REC to DATE COM REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>CUM.FEE.REC</p>
        <p>The amount of the fee which has been received. This is the amount of the particular fee which has been received. The field is updated by the receipt entry system in respect of the payment of fees. This field is signed and is always positive. Associated Field Considerations. Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details off charges on the contract. The associated fields are as follows:- OUTS FEE DUE FEE DUE DATE FEE CHRG CODE CUM FEE REC LAST DATE REC </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>AC.FROM.DATE</p>
        <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. AC.FROM.DATE contains the dates from which interest accruals for the period. The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>CUM.INT.AMT.REC</p>
        <p>The cumulative interest that the customer has ever received on a contract. Used by payment routines to ensure that payments are not duplicated and consequently updated when payments are physically sent rather than 'accounted for'. This field records the amounts of interest sent to a customer on liability contracts. It is used to control the sending of 'interest' funds, ensuring that whatever money market or loans module is used to send funds to a customer, money cannot be sent twice. This field is not classified as a 'financial' field because firstly, it is often updated before the accounting entries for a payment are passed; and secondly, is purpose is one of control rather than providing financial information. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with Field 59.</p>
        <p>CUM.PRIN.REC</p>
        <p>The cumulative principal that the customer has ever received on a contract. Used by payment routines to ensure that payments are not duplicated and consequently updated when payments are physically sent rather than 'accounted for'. This field records the amounts sent to a customer either for drawdowns on asset contracts or for repayments on liability contracts. It is used to control the sending of 'principal' funds, ensuring that whatever part of the LD or MM module is used to send funds to a customer, money cannot be sent twice. This field is not classified as a 'financial' field because firstly, it is often updated before the accounting entries for a payment are passed; and secondly, is purpose is one of control rather than providing financial information. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 14 AMT (standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue associated with Field 10.</p>
        <p>CURR.PRIN.VALUE</p>
        <p>The current principal value as used for the reducing balance 'RB' financial charge type calculation. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input fiel.</p>
        <p>CURRENCY</p>
        <p>The currency in which the contract is denominated. This field represents the currency in which the contract plus all of the amount fields in this record are denominated. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 3 character currency mnemonic.</p>
        <p>CUSTOMER</p>
        <p>Holds the contract custome.</p>
        <p>CUSTOMER.NO</p>
        <p>Holds the contract custome.</p>
        <p>DATE.COM.ACC.TO</p>
        <p>The date commission is accrued to using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 63 to 66). Whenever a commission accrual takes place, fields 63 to 66 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC COMM BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC COMM RATE (the actual commission rate used in the calculation); DATE COM ACC TO (the date commission is accrued to); and the resulting commission amount field - COMM AMT TODATE. So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, DATE COM ACC TO contains the end date that the set of accrual values is for. The period of accrual is from the previous value of DATE COM ACC TO (or START PERIOD COM if this is the first set of accrual values) to the value of DATE COM ACC TO in the current set of accrual values. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>DATE.COM.REC</p>
        <p>The date of the commission receipt referred to in field CUM COM AMT REC. The date of the commission receipt referred to in field CUM COM AMT REC. Associated Field Considerations. This association of fields is used by the receipt application to record the amount of commission actually received on the contract. The associated fields are as follows:- CUM COM AMT REC DATE COM REC </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: CUM COM AMT REC to DATE COM REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>DATE.FROM</p>
        <p>The date that a change in the principal of the contract is processed. This is not necessarily the value date of the principal change. This field, along with the following six fields records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal then the process date that the movement is input to the System is written to this field, the value date of the movement is written to EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3), the amount is written to TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (Fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. This field will always contain the same value as in EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3) except in the following two cases: 1. When a back valued contract or principal increase in loaded. In this, the DATE FROM field will contain the date that the change was input and the EFFECTIVE DATE field will contain the value date of the change. 2. When the LD.RECEIPT.ENTRY, MM.PAYMENT.ENTRY or MM.RECEIPT.ENTRY applications are used to record principal decreases with a value date different to the process date. In this case the process date will be in the DATE FROM field and the value date of the decrease will be in the EFFECTIVE DATE field. An example of the operation of this field and the other principal fields appears in the details of EFFECTIVE DATE (Field 3). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue associated with fields 3 to 8.</p>
        <p>DATE.INT.ACC.TO</p>
        <p>The date that interest is accrued to using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 52 to 57). Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, DATE INT ACC TO contains the end date that the set of accrual values is for. The period of accrual is from the previous value of DATE INT ACC TO (or START PERIOD INT if this is the first set of accrual values) to the value of DATE INT ACC TO in the current set of accrual values. An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>AC.INT.RATE</p>
        <p>The actual interest rate used in the calculation of interest in this set of accrual fields (fields 52 to 57). Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, AC INT RATE, contains the interest rate that was used in the calculation of interest in the multi set of accrual fields of which this field is part. An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard rate format.</p>
        <p>DATE.INT.REC</p>
        <p>The date of the interest receipt or payment. The date of the interest receipt or payment referred to in field CUM INT AMT REC. Associated Field Considerations. This association of fields is used by the payment and receipt applications to record the amount of interest actually paid or received on the contract. The associated fields are as follows:- CUM INT AMT REC DATE INT REC </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: CUM INT AMT REC to DATE INT REC.</p>
        <p>DATE.PRIN.REC</p>
        <p>The date that principal was last sent to a customer. This field is updated whenever CUM PRIN REC (Field 9.1) is updated and is for information only. This field records the date that funds are sent to a customer either for drawdowns on asset contracts or for repayments on liability contracts. It is for information purposes only. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue associated with field 9.</p>
        <p>DATE.RECEIVED</p>
        <p>The date of the receipt of the charge. This is the date the charge was received and will usually be the same as the due date. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED contains details of charges defined on the contract. It contains of both cash (non amortised) and amortised charges. The associated fields are as follows:- CHRGS AMT DUE CHRGS DUE DATE CHRG CODE AMT REC DATE RECEIVED </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: CHRGS AMT DUE to DATE RECEIVED. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>DEP.ACCR.ACTAMT</p>
        <p>The actual i.e. unrounded amount accrued to date for the current accrual period. Accruals over an interest period will be split into current month, previous months, and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>DEP.ACCR.AMT</p>
        <p>The rounded amount accrued to date for the current accrual period. The sign of the accrual will agree with the CRF posting, i.e. Loans Positive Deposits negative. Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>DEP.ACCR.DAYS</p>
        <p>The number of days for which accruals have been made for the current interest period. Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>DEP.ACCR.FROM</p>
        <p>The start date of the current accrual period, used to calculate accruals. Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field Multi value associated with fields DEP.ACCR.FROM to DEP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>DEP.ACCR.PRIN</p>
        <p>The absolute value of the depreciation/obligation amount used to calculate accruals for the current accrual period. Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field.</p>
        <p>DEP.ACCR.TO</p>
        <p>The date to which accruals have been made for the current accrual period, used to calculate accruals. Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field Multi value associated with fields CAP.ACCR.FROM to CAP.ACCR.ACTAM.</p>
        <p>DEP.ACCR.TO.DT</p>
        <p>The amount accrued to date over the current interest period. The sign of the amount will be equivalent to that of the CRF. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input fiel.</p>
        <p>AC.INT.SPREAD</p>
        <p>The interest spread that formed part of the AC INT RATE that was used in the calculation of interest in this set of accrual fields (fields 52 to 57). Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, AC INT SPREAD contains the interest spread that was applied to the floating rate (BASIC INTEREST table) to derive the AC INT RATE for use in the calculation of interest in the multivalue set of accrual fields. An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of PRINC INT BAL (Field 52). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard rate format.</p>
        <p>DEP.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>The financial charge amount to be depreciated for loans or the amount of financial obligation for deposits for the current interest period. This amount will be accrued as follows: - Loans - debit P&amp;L and credit CRF, stored as a negative vale. Deposits - credit P&amp;L and debit CRF, stored as a positive value. The actual accrual amounts will be stored with the opposite sign. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input fiel.</p>
        <p>DEP.END.DATE</p>
        <p>The end date of the current depreciation period This is equal to the end date of the current interest period. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input fiel.</p>
        <p>DEP.RATE</p>
        <p>The rate used in the financial charge calculation for accrual periods for the flexible schedules 'FS' and reducing balance 'RB' types.</p>
        <p>DEP.START.DATE</p>
        <p>The start date of the current depreciation period This is equal to the start date of the current interest period. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input fiel.</p>
        <p>DLY.ACCR.DATE</p>
        <p>This field holds the value of DATE.INT.ACC.TO when the OVERDUE.STATUS Is not NAB and DATE.INT.ACC.TO is greater than or equal to NAB.START.DAT.</p>
        <p>DLY.COM.ACCR</p>
        <p>This field holds the suspended commission amount from the NAB.START.DATE to the next working day, when the LD is not in NAB and the accrual date is greater than or equal to the NAB.START.DATE and SUSPEND.INCOME(in PD.PARAMETER) is set to YES. Fields DLY.ACCR.DATE, DLY.COM.ACCR, and DLY.INT.ACCR form an associated multi-value set.</p>
        <p>DLY.INT.ACCR</p>
        <p>This field holds the suspended interest amount from the NAB.START.DATE to the next working day, when the LD is not in NAB and the accrual date is greater than or equal to the NAB.START.DATE and SUSPEND.INCOME(in PD.PARAMETER) is set to YES. Fields DLY.ACCR.DATE, DLY.COM.ACCR, and DLY.INT.ACCR form an associated multi-value set.</p>
        <p>EFF.INT.RATE</p>
        <p>This field is automatically updated by system and applicable only for MM contracts created through REPO with REPO TYPE having EFFECTIVE RATE set to YES. This rate is used for non linear accruals.</p>
        <p>EFFECTIVE.DATE</p>
        <p>The date when the contract had the principal balance and movement as shown by the following five fields. This field, along with the following five fields records the principal movements of the contract. Whenever there is a movement in principal (e.g. a drawdown) then the value date of that movement is written into this field, the date the drawdown was input is written to DATE FROM (Field 2), the principal movement amount is written to TRANS PRIN AMT (Field 4), and the principal balances (fields 5 to 8) are updated accordingly. So as to keep the history of principal movements, these fields are multivalue associated and each time there is a movement, rather than overwrite the fields existing values, a new 'set of values' are added. Example: An example of the possible movements is shown below: Event 1: A 12,000 US dollar placement is loaded onto the system on 11th February 1987, valued 16th February 1987 and maturing on 23rd February 1987. Event 2: During the 'off-line' processing of 16th February, the placement moves from a 'Forward valued' asset, to a 'Current' asset. Event 3: During the 'off-line' processing of 23rd February, the placement matures with the principal becoming due and then being fully repaid. LMM.ACCOUNT.BALANCES RECORD (FIELDS 2 TO 8) 1 2 3 DUE 3 PAID DATE FROM 11 FEB 87 16 FEB 87 23 FEB 87 23 FEB 87 EFFECTIVE DATE 11 FEB 87 16 FEB 87 23 FEB 87 23 FEB 87 TRANS PRIN AMT -12,000 -12,000 -12,000 12,000 OUTS FWD PRINC -12,000 0 0 0 OUTS CURR PRINC 0 -12,000 0 0 OUTS OD PRINC 0 0 -12,000 0 OUTS PRINC NAB 0 0 0 0 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue associated with fields 2 to 8.</p>
        <p>END.DATE</p>
        <p>Descriptot fiel.</p>
        <p>AC.NO.DAYS</p>
        <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. AC.NO.DAYS contains the number of days in the accrual period The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 4 numeric characters.</p>
        <p>END.DATE.IR</p>
        <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> A maximum of 11 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        <p>END.PERIOD.COM</p>
        <p>The date of the end of the current commission period. This field contains the end date of the current commission period. The first commission period of a contract is the one that starts on the value date and ends on the maturity or commission due date. Consequently, at contract initiation, this field will contain the COMMISSION DUE DATE (if Call or Notice) or MATURITY DATE (if fixed maturity). If a contract has more than one commission period in its life then this date will always be the end date of the current period and it will always equal the start date (START PERIOD COM) of the next commission period, irrespective of any accrual method. With daily accruals, the first day accrual method will not require an accrual for the current period on the END PERIOD COM date. The last day accrual method will require an accrual on this date for the current period. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>END.PERIOD.INT</p>
        <p>The date that the contracts current interest period ends. This field contains the end date of the current interest period. The first interest period of a contract is the one that starts on the value date and ends on the maturity or interest due date. Consequently, at contract initiation, this field will contain the INTEREST DUE DATE (if Call or Notice) or MATURITY DATE (if fixed maturity). If a contract has more than one interest period in its life then this date will always be the end date of the current period and it will always equal the start date (START PERIOD INT) of the next interest period, irrespective of any accrual method. With daily accruals, the first day accrual method will not require an accrual for the current period on the END PERIOD INT date. The last day accrual method will require an accrual on this date for the current period. It should be noted that the system assumes that all contracts have an interest period, even if they have no interest rate. Consequently, this field will always have a value even if the contract type is one that has no interest e.g. account receivable, Sundry deposit. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters.</p>
        <p>FEE.CHRG.CODE</p>
        <p>The charge code of the fee. This is the code indicated on the main contract and refers to an entry on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The value in field CATEGORY CODE on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS indicates which profit and loss account the fees or charges will be posted to. Also indicated is the period over which the contract is to be amortised plus the charge description. Associated Field Considerations. Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details off charges on the contract. The associated fields are as follows:- OUTS FEE DUE FEE DUE DATE FEE CHRG CODE CUM FEE REC LAST DATE REC </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 2 numeric characters. Multivalue association: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>FEE.DUE.DATE</p>
        <p>The due date of the fee. This is the date that the particular fee was due for payment. Associated Field Considerations. Each fee defined on the schedules will have a set of multivalues entered into this association on the due date if it has not been successfully liquidated. This may be because the contract is set to manual liquidation or because certain account posting restrictions exist. The multivalue association OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC contains details off charges on the contract. The associated fields are as follows:- OUTS FEE DUE FEE DUE DATE FEE CHRG CODE CUM FEE REC LAST DATE REC </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format of 11 characters. Multivalue association: OUTS FEE DUE to LAST DATE REC. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>FEE.PAID.IN.ADV</p>
        <p>The amount of each individual fee or charge which has been collected from the customer and is to be amortised over a period. This field is signed and is always positive. Associated Field Considerations. The multivalue association FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE contains details of all fees and charges on the contract which are to be amortised into profit and loss over the period indicated in field AMORTSN PERIOD on LMM CHARGE CONDITIONS. The association will reflect both fees and/or charges which have been specified a) in the case of fees via the SCHEDULE DEFINE facility and b) in the case of charges via field CHARGE AMOUNT on the main contract. The associated fields are as follows:- FEES PAID IN ADV CHRGS CCY MTHLY AMORT AMT NO OF MTHS LEFT ORIGIN AMOR MTH CHRGS CODE </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. Multivalue association: FEES PAID IN ADV to CHRGS CODE. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>FIXED.FLOATING.RATE</p>
        <p>This field is reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>FLOATING.INT.ADJUST</p>
        <p>This field is reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>GEN.AMT.REC</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>GEN.CHRG.AMT</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>AC.PRINCIPAL</p>
        <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. AC.PRINCIPAL contains the principal effective for the accrual period. The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard T24 amount field 19 characters.</p>
        <p>GEN.DATE.REC</p>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>GRACE.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>Amount of extra interest accrued for grace period to be added to discount amount. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> (1) Up to 19 numeric characters including commas and a decimal point.</p>
        <p>INDIVIDUAL.MVMTS</p>
        <p>Descriptor fiel.</p>
        <p>INT.ACCR.START</p>
        <p>The recent interest accrual start date is stored in this field.</p>
        <p>INT.ADJ.AMT</p>
        <p>Field to hold the total of difference between the User defined interest amount and the System calculated interest amount when the SPECIAL.INT.BASIS is defined Standard AMT type field Applicable only for LD produc.</p>
        <p>INT.AMT.TODATE</p>
        <p>The amount of interest calculated using the components in this multivalue set of fields (fields 52 to 57). Whenever an interest accrual takes place, fields 52 to 57 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation. These fields are PRINC INT BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC INT RATE (the actual interest rate used in the calculation); AC INT SPREAD (the interest spread, if applicable); DATE INT ACC TO (the date interest is accrued to); and the resulting interest amount fields - INT AMT TODATE (rounded) and ACTUAL ACC AMT (not rounded). So as to keep a full history of the interest accrual during the current interest period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. This field, INT AMT TODATE, contains the result of the interest calculation, rounded according to the currency. It is signed negative for asset contracts and positive for liability contracts. An example of how this field and the other accrual fields are used is shown in the details of field 52, PRINC INT BAL. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        <p>INT.CCY</p>
        <p>Specifies the currency in which the interest is to be paid/accrued. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 3 character currency mnemonic.</p>
        <p>INT.CONSOL</p>
        <p>Contains the key of the Consolidation record (in the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file) into which the details of this contract are consolidated for interest. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Up to 70 type A (alphanumeric) characters, as specified in the Consolidate Conditions file (CONSOLIDATE.COND). (Internal field).</p>
        <p>INT.ON.REPAY.AMT</p>
        <p>When Interest amount is collected on Repayment Date then the interest amount is held in this field INT.ON.REPAY.AMT.</p>
        <p>INT.PAID.IN.ADV</p>
        <p>The amount of discounted interest on a DEPOSIT contract which has been paid in advance. This field is only used for DEPOSITS where the interest is discounted. It reflects the amount of interest for the interest period which has been paid in advance. At the start of the period it will equal the committed interest and will be reduced by each interest accrual to zero at the end of the period. The field is signed and will always be negative. The contents of this field are accrued into field PL O SET IPA on LMM INSTALL CONDITIONS. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Upto 14 AMT (Standard amount format) type characters plus decimal point. (For LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS only..</p>
        <p>AC.RATE</p>
        <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. AC.RATE contains the rate at which interest accrues over the period. The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1-11 numeric characters.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. </p>
            <p>AC.ACCR.AMT contains the amount of interest accrued for the period rounded to the number of decimals for the currency. </p>
            <p>The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). </p>
            <p>These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field of up to 19 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.ACT.ACCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The set of fields from AC.FROM.DATE to AC.ACT.ACCR form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed, or the principal or interest rate is changed. </p>
            <p>AC.ACT.ACCR contains the amount of interest accrued rounded to six decimal places. </p>
            <p>The other 6 fields are for date accrued to (AC.TO.DATE), number of days in the accrual period (AC.NO.DAYS), interest rate (AC.RATE), rounded accrued amount (AC.ACCR.AMT), and unrounded accrued amount (AC.ACT.ACCR). </p>
            <p>These 7 fields store data in reverse chronological order (the most recent being found in the first multivalue). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field of up to 19 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.COM.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual commission rate used in the calculation of commission in this set of accrual fields (field 63 to 66). </p>
            <p>Whenever a commission accrual takes place, fields 63 to 66 inclusive are updated with the components used in the accrual calculation.  These fields are PRINC COMM BAL (the balance of principal on the Contract); AC COMM RATE (the actual commission rate used in the calculation); DATE COM ACC TO (the date commission is accrued to); and the resulting commission amount field - COMM AMT TODATE. </p>
            <p>So as to keep a full history of the commission accrual during the current commission period, these fields are multivalue associated and each time one of the calculation components changes, a new set of values is added. </p>
            <p>This field, AC COM RATE contains the commission rate that was used in the calculation of commission in the multi set of accrual fields of which this field is part. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>TOT.LIVE.INTEREST</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>OUTS.LIVE.INTEREST</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
