<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LM</product>
<table>LMM.ACTIVITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The LMM.ACTIVITY file is a list of advice related activities which is used by the Loans &amp; Deposits and Money Market systems. </p>
            <p>Each activity has been assigned a numeric code, and this table allows the input of a meaningful description. </p>
            <p>For example:- </p>
            <p>CODE   ACTIVITY/EVENT       TYPICAL INPUT DESCRIPTION 1010   A new contract has          New contract        been input 1030   A contract has been        Cancelled contract.        reversed </p>
            <p>The codes are hard-coded in the program and are used, in conjunction with the LMM.ADVICES table, to decide whether an advice/confirmation should be sent when the system has recognised a particular activity e.g. a new contract entered (1010). </p>
            <p>The codes/activities used by the Loans &amp; Deposits and Money Market Systems are as follows:- </p>
            <p>Code         Activity </p>
            <p>1010         New Contract 1020         Changed Contract 1030         Cancelled Contract 1040         Liquidation Of Contract 1050         Early Liquidation Of Contract 1060         Adjustment Of Contract 1070         Rollover Schedules 1090         Interest Payment Advice 2010         Payment Schedules 2020         Payment Details 2030         Intra Account Transfer (Debit) 2040         Intra Account Transfer (Credit) 2050         Interest Capitalisation 2060         Customer Remarks (Basic details) 2070         Receipt Entry Confirmation 2080         Adjustment Entry Confirmation 3010         Claim Fees/Charges 3020         Claim Fees/Charges 3030         Claim Prin/Int/Comm 3040         Chaser One 3050         Chaser Two 3060         Chaser Three 3070         WHT Advice </p>
            <p>The last digit of the any of the codes, used by the System, may also be 1, 4, or 8. These other codes represent the same activities as those listed above, and therefore,have the same descriptions. The reason for the alternative last digits is to differentiate between Fixed Contracts (xxx0), Call/Notice Contracts (xxx1), and Syndicated Contracts (xxx4) and (xxx8) for S.W.I.F.T. purposes. </p>
            <p>Whenever one of the above activities occurs, the System looks at the LMM.ADVICES table to see if, for that contract, a confirmation/advice should be sent. </p>
            <p>If the LMM.ADVICES table states that a confirmation should be sent, then the activity code used would be the relevant code from the table above. </p>
            <p>This code is then used in the preparation of the message, and is written to the contract, along with the delivery reference number, as soon as the delivery system accepts the message. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc>
        <p>Represents the reference number which uniquely identifies a particular activity. Each activity that can occur in the life of a contract in the Loans and Deposit module has a specific code. e.g. 1010 = New Contract. The full list of codes used by the Loans and Deposit module is printed on the "OVERVIEW" pages of this document. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 4 Numeric characters. (Mandatory input). Input must be 4 valid numeric characters.</p>
        <p>DESCRIPTION</p>
        <p>This field describes the activity code. This is a descriptive field and is simply a way of recording the title of the Activity Code. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1-35 Type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input. Multilingual field). Input must be up to 35 valid alphanumeric characters.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the reference number which uniquely identifies a particular activity. </p>
            <p>Each activity that can occur in the life of a contract in the Loans and Deposit module has a specific code. e.g. 1010 = New Contract. The full list of codes used by the Loans and Deposit module is printed on the "OVERVIEW" pages of this document. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 Numeric characters. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Input must be 4 valid numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field describes the activity code. </p>
            <p>This is a descriptive field and is simply a way of recording the title of the Activity Code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input. Multilingual field).</p>
            <p>Input must be up to 35 valid alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

