<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AZ</product>
<table>AZ.SCHEDULES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p> AZ ALL INE ONE SCHEDULES FILES AZ.SCHEDULES All in One Account module enables the Banks to define Account based Loan and Deposit products. The loan/ deposit accounts opened under this module, based on a pre defined All in One Products, are different from the Contract based Loans and Deposits, in view of flexibility in operations, like a normal account. Multiple repayment options can be defined for a loan, with the help of Schedules. The schedule types, frequency, date and amount fields of the schedule define a particular repayment option for the loan account. The schedules in All In One module, are for the purpose of reference only, and no actions are automatically performed by the system based on the schedules. Schedules are used for updating the limit, ADI and comparing the AZ account balance on scheduled dates, to arrive at the arrears or the redraw value. The file AZ.SCHEDULES is generated by the system automatically, based on the definitions given in AZ.ACCOUNT. By giving the ID of the AZ account in AZ.SCHEDULES, the complete schedule details of the account can be viewed. Changes in Principal amount, Rate of interest, Term, or Frequency may result in Re scheduling, when opted by the user by choosing either 'Y' or 'N' in the field Term Priority in AZ.ACCOUNT 
</p>
        <p>CHANGE.DATE</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES CHANGE. DATE The date from which the new principal (field no.32) and calculation base (field no.33) becomes effective. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Only date can be input. A change in principal or Basis is a essential for populating this date.
</p>
        <p>CHG.AMT</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. AMT Amount defaulted from FT. CHARGE. TYPE for the CHARGE. CODE so input. Can be changed at Account level. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Defaulted from FT. CHARGE. TYPE. 
</p>
        <p>CHG.CALC.BASE</p>
        <p>
Refer to helptext of AZ.ACCOUNT
</p>
        <p>CHG.CCY</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. CCY NO input-Defaulted to the Account currency. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> none
</p>
        <p>CHG.CODE</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. CODE Populated from AZ.ACCOUNT application when input. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> none.
</p>
        <p>CHG.LIQ.ACCT</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. LIQ. ACCT An a/c specified here is debited for the charge amount specified. Populated from inputs in AZ.Account 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> none . 
</p>
        <p>CHG.PL.ACCT</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. PL. ACCT If the repayment. type is CREDIT-CARD then during repayment if the charges need to be posted to an account or category to setoff the one that was posted online then it needs to be specified here Populated from input in AZ.Account 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> none 
</p>
        <p>CURR.HIST.NO</p>
        <p>
Holds the last DATE and history number components of Key to AZ.SCHEDULES.HIST application.
</p>
        <p>CURRENCY</p>
        <p>
Holds the AZ.ACCOUNT currency
</p>
        <p>DATE</p>
        <p>
Indicates the date on which the schedule is effective with respect to various events like, Principal Repayment, Interest Repayment, Rate revision etc. This date has been already defined by the user, in AZ.ACCOUNT, under schedule details. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE Standard Date Format
</p>
        <p>ACCR.INT</p>
        <p>
Holds the intermediate accrued interest amount. Will be set if there is any B/P/N/R schedule and no "I" schedule
</p>
        <p>DATE.RESCH</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES DATE. RESCH There is an option to change the TERM, amount or interest rate of an AZ. LOAN. The date of such rescheduling is written in this field. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Applicable only in case of loans should be read along with Term priority to know whether such change is effective on amount or on term. 
</p>
        <p>EXCEEDS.TOLERANCE</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES EXCEEDS. TOLERANCE This is the field that decides whether to charge late payment fee, levy penalty (on loan arrears) etc. This is decided by the system based on the inputs made in the field LIAB. TO.PENALTY (field in APP) in case of deposits and from GRACE. PERIOD (field in APP) field in case of loans. The parameters for the charges are drawn from AZ. PRODUCT. PARAMETER (APP) and Penalty from AZ. ACCOUNT. TO illustrate: For a savings plan deposit if LIAB. TO .PENALTY is defined as 2- then it will not charge penalty for defaults made upto 2 installments. If a 3rd installment is defaulted -then this field is activated to charge penalty as designed in APP 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Input in fields LIAB. TO. PENALTY and GRACE. PERIOD is optional. Once input the period is reckoned before calculating penalty. Or else penalty is calculated from DAY ONE. 
</p>
        <p>EXPOSURE.DATE</p>
        <p>
Not used
</p>
        <p>FIXED.RATE</p>
        <p>
Indicates the annual fixed interest rate applicable for the R schedule defined under the AZ loan account. The fixed interest can be defined for the entire amount outstanding or to a percentage of the outstanding amount. The fixed interest can be defined for the entire period of the loan account or in parts. Example: As per the above R schedule, a rate revision will happen on 22-05-2001, with 60% of the outstanding amount by a variable interest (key1 and spread 6 on Basic Interest) and 40% of the outstanding amount by fixed interest 15% 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE (defined in AZ.ACCOUNT) 
</p>
        <p>GRACE.DATE</p>
        <p>
Holds the grace processing date for each schedule. 
</p>
        <p>GRACE.END.DATE</p>
        <p>
This field will be updated only for deposit type of az.accounts.
</p>
        <p>GRACE.OD.AMT</p>
        <p>
Holds the grace OVERDUE amount for each schedule. Associated with GRACE.DATE
</p>
        <p>I.SCH.FREQ</p>
        <p>
Not used
</p>
        <p>INT.KEY</p>
        <p>
This field, as a part of R type schedule, contains the linking reference number (key) of the appropriate interest rate defined in BASIC.INTETEST table, which will be used for interest computation purposes. Based on the key defined here, the interest rate will be taken by the system from the BASIC.INTEREST table for interest calculation, from the date defined under Frequency. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input in AZ.SCHEDULE part of a set of multi value fields Allowed only for R type Schedules Should have been defined in BASIC.RATE.TEXT and in BASIC.INTEREST 
</p>
        <p>INT.OPERND</p>
        <p>
Determines the method by which the basic interest rate is to be adjusted by the RATE.SPREAD to arrive at the Variable interest rate for the loan account under R schedule.. This field specifies whether the Spread Rate is to be added to, subtracted from or multiplied by the basic interest rate to arrive at the final variable interest rate. If Multiply is specified the final rate is (100 + M) percent of the effective interest rate , where M is the Margin Rate percentage. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE. This field is already defined in AZ.ACCOUNT Part of a multi value set of fields under R type schedule.
</p>
        <p>ACT.I.AMT</p>
        <p>
Holds the actual interest capitalised amount. Will be updated during online repayment or Interest event date
</p>
        <p>INT.PERCENT</p>
        <p>
Defines the percentage of outstanding amount up to which the Variable interest rate is applicable, under a R type schedule of AZ account. For the rest of the percentage amount, fixed interest rate will be applicable. Example: If 60 is defined here, variable interest will be applied on 60% of the outstanding amount and Fixed interest will be applied on the remaining 40% of the outstanding amount. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE. (Defined already in AZ.ACCOUNT) 1-5 numeric rate type like 60, 45.50 etc.; Maximum value 100 Part of a multi value set under R type of Schedules.
</p>
        <p>INT.SPREAD</p>
        <p>
Indicates the spread or margin of interest, which has to be applied to the Basic interest rate defined in BASIC.INTEREST ( and linked through RATE.KEY ), to arrive at the variable interest. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE (defined already in AZ.ACCOUNT) 1-5 numeric characters of rate type (example 3.25, 99.99); Cannot be greater than 100 A margin, which will result in a negative interest rate is prohibited. Part of a set of multi value fields Allowed only for R type Schedules
</p>
        <p>INTEREST.KEY</p>
        <p>
Holds the Basic Interest key linked to the contract for the current period
</p>
        <p>K.DATE</p>
        <p>
Internal field
</p>
        <p>KEY</p>
        <p>
Key to this application. Same as AZ Account ID
</p>
        <p>LAST.CIGEN.DATE</p>
        <p>
Holds the date on which the "CI" amount was lastly calculated. Applicable only for credit cards
</p>
        <p>LAST.PAY.DATE</p>
        <p>
Applicable only in case of Deposits with B schedules. This field is updated with last date on which the B schedule was honored. The system matches the B schedule date and amount with the date in this field and in case they differ it concludes that installments are in arrears. The field AMOUNT.DUE is updated by the system based on this field.
</p>
        <p>N.SCH.FREQ</p>
        <p>
Not used
</p>
        <p>NEW.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES NEW. AMOUNT This field is updated for both AZ deposits and Loan a/cs. When the principal amount is changed - due to draw down/repayment in case of Loans and part redemption/roll over in case of Deposits- this field gets updated. VALUE. DATE is an associated multi-value field which stores the DATE from which the above changes become effective. To illustrate:- Loan sanctioned is 3 million and 2 million is already drawn and the customer makes a draw down of the remaining principal on 15.02.2002 NEW. AMOUNT will be input with 1 million and the associated multi-value field VALUE. DATE will be input with the date 15.02.2002. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Change in principal either increase or decrease is a pre-requisite. 
</p>
        <p>NEW.PRINCIPAL</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES NEW. PRINCIPAL Change in PRINCIPAL (either increase or decrease) or when there is any change in CALCULATION.BASE. For ex:-&gt; A deposit might have been made for Rs.1million and after the second day 0.25million might have been drawn prematurely. Though for the first two days the principal is Rs.1million the for the next period it is only 0.75million (and not 1million) Here 0.75million would have been the NEW principal. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Increase in principal due to INCREASE in deposit or FURTHER draw down in case of loan Permitted values that alter the field Principal balance Scheduled balance or Current balance.
</p>
        <p>ADDITIONAL.SPREAD</p>
        <p>
Refer to helptext of AZ.ACCOUNT
</p>
        <p>NO.ACCT</p>
        <p>
Holds the value of CHARGE.IMMED Refer to helptext of AZ.ACCOUNT for charge immed
</p>
        <p>NOTES</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES NOTES:- The field contains the record of VARIOUS stages that the AZ account has passed through before it is finally closed. For ex. An FD input on say 14.05.2001 for say 2 million Stage -(1)Partly redeemed for 1 million on 15.05.2001 Stage-(2) On 17.05.2001 may be rolled over further period of 2 days Stage-(3)On 19.05.2001 when the deposit is closed by transferring the balance to nominated a/c In the above the notes will contain the following :- Stage (1) "Early redemption of 1 million on 15.05.2001" Stage(2) "Deposit rolled over" and Stage (3)"Closed contract" 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> 1-35 characters in length permitted.
</p>
        <p>ONLINE.AMT</p>
        <p>
Holds the Online repayment amount.
</p>
        <p>P.SCH.FREQ</p>
        <p>
Not used
</p>
        <p>PRD.RATE.KEY</p>
        <p>
Holds the Periodic Key linked to AZ deposit .
</p>
        <p>R.SCH.FREQ</p>
        <p>
Internal decriptor field.
</p>
        <p>REPAY.AMT</p>
        <p>
Defines the total repayment amount. This amount includes the Principal Repayment amount, Interest Repayment amount and Charges to be paid on the scheduled date. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field; Only for reference Standard T24 amount field
</p>
        <p>REPAY.TYPE</p>
        <p>
Internal descriptor field.
</p>
        <p>SCH.CALC.BASE</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES SCH. CALC. BASE Indicates the basis on which the calculation of interest is done for the AZ account. The input is populated from AZ Account. Permitted options are (1) Principal (2)Scheduled Balance (3)Current Balance 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Permitted values :-Principal, Scheduled balance and Current balance- in case of loans Restricted to Principal in case of fixed deposits and Scheduled balance in case of Savings plan.
</p>
        <p>SCHEDULE.BAL</p>
        <p>
The field indicates BALANCE in the account as per SCHEDULES. The balance indicates a FUTURE position assuming a pattern of INFLOW over the period. For Ex:=&gt;A Savings plan with a monthly installment of Rs.1000 is opened on 01.02.02. The schedules ASSUME that every month the installments are received and projects a balance of 2000 as on 01.03.02 3000 as on 01.04.02 4000 as on 01.05.02 and so on and the interest amounts are calculated and capitalized accordingly. But in reality the inflows might not have come for the month of March and April which makes the actual balance as 1000 (while the scheduled balance on that date would be 3000) In case of LOAN accounts the SCHEDULED balance will be diminishing over the periods assuming a fixed pattern of repayment over the periods. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Rule 1:- It is simply a projection of FUTURE cash inflow into the account Rule 2:- Actual balance may differ from the scheduled balance.
</p>
        <p>AMOUNT.DUE</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES AMOUNT. DUE When B schedules for Deposits and P schedules for loan are defined- on the designated dates the system will look for balance in the REPAY a/c for appropriating the above scheduled amounts. In case a lesser balance exists than what is actually needed - the system will appropriate the balance available and write the difference amount in this field AMOUNT. DUE. To illustrate:- If for savings plan an amount of 15000 is defined in B schedule and the amount actually available in the REPAY a/c is only 10000 then the system would appropriate 10000 and puts the balance due for collection in this field i.e. in the present case 5000. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p>: Applicable to deposit account with defined B schedules [ only savings plan] 
</p>
        <p>TAX.ACCT</p>
        <p>
Holds the credit account for computed TAX Amount.
</p>
        <p>TAX.AMOUNT</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES TAX. AMOUNT Amount OR rate as specified in tax code in tax application. If rate is specified then the rate is applied as a percentage on the charge amount. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> none 
</p>
        <p>TAX.AMT.LCY</p>
        <p>
Holds the local equivalent of the amount in TAX.AMOUNT field
</p>
        <p>TAX.CODE</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES TAX. CODE Populated from Tax code attached to the FT. COMMISSION. TYPE or FT. CHARGE. TYPE. Rate is derived from Tax application of the tax code so attached above. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> none 
</p>
        <p>TAX.KEY</p>
        <p>
Represents a reference on the TAX table which will indicate the rate to be used for the computation of taxation.
</p>
        <p>TOT.REPAY.AMT</p>
        <p>
Defines the total repayment amount. This amount includes the Principal Repayment amount, Interest Repayment amount and Charges to be paid on the scheduled date. In addition, this field includes the tax amount also, which has been calculated as an exclusive one. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field; Only for reference Standard T24 amount field
</p>
        <p>TOT.TAX</p>
        <p>
Indicates the total tax amount that has to be recovered on the scheduled date. Based on the tax related values defined under AZ.ACCOUNT, tax amount is calculated and displayed here. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input Field Standard T24 amount field.
</p>
        <p>TYPE.B</p>
        <p>
Holds the "B" schedule amount 
</p>
        <p>TYPE.B.SYS</p>
        <p>
Holds the amount of drawdown in case of loans
</p>
        <p>TYPE.C</p>
        <p>
This field indicates the type of schedule defined by the user in AZ account for handling Charges. This field is reserved for future development. The other types of schedules are: A - For defining annuity type of repayment, where a constant repayment amount is generated based on the frequency. B - This type is used for effecting loan drawdowns on pre-defined dates. On the specified dates the system will transfer the draw down amount to the credit of the nominated account. From G14.0.00 the repayment type can be CREDIT CARD also. I - Defines schedule for interest payments. For I type schedule, amount cannot be specified by the user. Total period of all I type schedules are validated against the Maximum Interest Only period defined for the AZ account. P- This type defines the Repayment of Principal R - This type is used for effecting Interest Rate revision on specified dates. Both Variable interest rate and Fixed Interest rate can be fixed to a loan account, through this type, for a certain percentage of the outstanding amount and also for various periods within the life of the loan account. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input in AZ.SCHEDULE Part of a multi value set of fields Manual input for C schedule not allowed. "C" -schedule generation is automatic (based on setup)
</p>
        <p>ANNUITY.ADJUST</p>
        <p>
Valid in case of ANNUITY contracts. If the REPAY amount calculated from annuity is less than the interest amount, then this field will HOLD the differential interest and the OUTSTANDING balance will be increased by this AMOUNT. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Rule 1: Rule 2
</p>
        <p>TYPE.CC</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES TYPE. CC CC- This schedule is for repayment of Principal. Defaulted from Az. Account 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> None 
</p>
        <p>TYPE.CI</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES TYPE. CI CI- This is committed interest schedule. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Manual input for CI schedule not allowed. "CI" -schedule generation is automatic (based on setup)
</p>
        <p>TYPE.I</p>
        <p>
This field indicates the schedule defined by the user in AZ account, for repayment of Interest. For I type schedule, amount cannot be specified by the user, in the AZ account. The amount shown in AZ.SCHEDULE under I type is the amount of interest calculated by the system and to be paid by the customer on the date specified. Total period of all I type schedules are validated against the Maximum Interest Only period defined for the AZ account. Based on the schedule types defined in the AZ account, AZ.SCHEDULE is generated by the system. By giving the ID of the AZ account in AZ.SCHEDULE, the complete schedule details of the account can be viewed. Schedule is automatically generated by the system and no user input is allowed . Further, no automatic actions like in LD/ MG are done by the system based on AZ.SCHEDULE . In All in One Module, the SCHEDULE is used only as a reference point, for updating the limit, ADI and comparing the AZ account balance on scheduled dates, for arriving the arrears or the redraw value. The other types of schedules are: A - For defining annuity type of repayment, where a constant repayment amount is generated based on the frequency. B - This type is used for effecting loan drawdowns on pre-defined dates. On the specified dates the system will transfer the draw down amount to the credit of the nominated account. P- This type defines the Repayment of Principal R - This type is used for effecting Interest Rate revision on specified dates. Both Variable interest rate and Fixed Interest rate can be fixed to a loan account, through this type, for a certain percentage of the outstanding amount and also for various periods within the life of the loan account. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE Part of a multi value set of fields
</p>
        <p>TYPE.N</p>
        <p>
Holds the "N" schedule amount. The amount that has to be either collected/ paid to the customer .
</p>
        <p>TYPE.P</p>
        <p>
This field indicates the type of schedule defined by the user in AZ account, for repayment of Principal amount. In the case of AZ loan account, the amount shown here is the amount of Principal Repayment to be made by the customer on the specified date. According to the type of repayment like Annuity, Linear and Others, the schedule takes care of defining the Principal repayment. When 'Other' type of Repayment is specified in AZ account, unstructured Principal repayments can be defined in P type schedule by specifying the amount and the date. Based on the schedule types defined in the AZ account, AZ.SCHEDULE is generated by the system. By giving the ID of the AZ account in AZ.SCHEDULE, the complete schedule details of the account can be viewed. Schedule is automatically generated by the system and no user input is allowed . Further, no automatic actions like in LD/ MG are done by the system based on AZ.SCHEDULE . In All in One Module, the SCHEDULE is used only as a reference point, for updating the limit, ADI and comparing the AZ account balance on scheduled dates, for arriving the arrears or the redraw value. The other types of schedules are: A - For defining annuity type of repayment, where a constant repayment amount is generated based on the frequency. It is possible to define multiple 'A' type of schedules within an AZ loan account for different periods during the term of the loan. In such cases, it is necessary to input at least one 'A' type schedule that includes the maturity date and brings the loan balance to zero (or the residual amount). B - This type is used for effecting loan drawdowns on pre-defined dates. On the specified dates the system will transfer the draw down amount to the credit of the nominated account. I - Defines schedule for interest payments. For I type schedule, amount cannot be specified by the user. Total period of all I type schedules are validated against the Maximum Interest Only period defined for the AZ account. R- This type defines the Interest rate revision on a defined date. This type takes care of both variable interest and fixed interest based on the percentage of outstanding amount as well as on various periods of the loan. In order to change the interest rates defaulted from the AZ Product Parameter, a R type schedule can be defined at the start of loan itself, with new values. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE Part of a multi value set of fields
</p>
        <p>TYPE.R</p>
        <p>
This field indicates the type of schedule defined by the user in AZ account for interest Rate related events like rate revision etc. The value shown here indicates the effective Rate of Interest applied to the account. Schedule Type R - This type is used for effecting Interest Rate revision on specified dates. The value defined under Term Priority will be taken into account for effecting this type of schedule. Both Variable interest rate and Fixed Interest rate can be fixed to a loan account, through this type, for a certain percentage of the outstanding amount and also for various periods within the life of the loan account. Example: As per the above R schedule, a rate revision will happen on 22-05-2001, with 60% of the outstanding amount by a variable interest (key1 and spread 6 on Basic Interest) and 40% of the outstanding amount by fixed interest 15% Based on the schedule types defined in the AZ account, AZ.SCHEDULE is generated by the system. By giving the ID of the AZ account in AZ.SCHEDULE, the complete schedule details of the account can be viewed. Schedule is automatically generated by the system and no user input is allowed . Further, no automatic actions like in LD/ MG are done by the system based on AZ.SCHEDULE . In All in One Module, the SCHEDULE is used only as a reference point, for updating the limit, ADI and comparing the AZ account balance on scheduled dates, for arriving the arrears or the redraw value. The other types of schedules are: A - For defining annuity type of repayment, where a constant repayment amount is generated based on the frequency. B - This type is used for effecting loan drawdowns on pre-defined dates. On the specified dates the system will transfer the draw down amount to the credit of the nominated account. I - Defines schedule for interest payments. For I type schedule, amount cannot be specified by the user. Total period of all I type schedules are validated against the Maximum Interest Only period defined for the AZ account. P- This type defines the Repayment of Principal 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE Part of a multi value set of fields
</p>
        <p>TYPE.Z</p>
        <p>
NOT USED
</p>
        <p>VALUE.DATE</p>
        <p>
Defines the date from which the loan/ deposit account is effective. Any date entered earlier than the business date, is validated against the MAX.BACK.DATE defined under the respective AZ Product parameter. The future date entered here cannot be greater than the Forward Maximum Date defined under DATES. The value is populated from AZ.ACCOUNT. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> Standard date format; Default is current Business Date. No input field
</p>
        <p>APPLY.DATE</p>
        <p>
Not used.
</p>
        <p>AZ.INT.RATE</p>
        <p>
AZ. SCHEDULES AZ. INT. RATE Implies the interest rate governing the particular loan draw down. Populated to the AZ. Schedules from the AZ.account. 

</p>
        <b>Validation Rules</b>
        <p> No input field.
</p>
        <p>B.SCH.FREQ</p>
        <p>
Internal descriptor field
</p>
        <p>C.SCH.FREQ</p>
        <p>
Internal descriptor field
</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>C.SCH.FREQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>Internal descriptor field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.RESCH</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES DATE. RESCH There is an option to change the TERM, amount or interest rate of an AZ. LOAN. The date of such rescheduling is written in this field. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Applicable only in case of loans should be read along with Term priority to know whether such change is effective on amount or on term.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ACCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the credit account for computed TAX Amount.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES NEW. AMOUNT This field is updated for both AZ deposits and Loan a/cs. When the principal amount is changed - due to draw down/repayment in case of Loans and part redemption/roll over in case of Deposits- this field gets updated. VALUE. DATE is an associated multi-value field which stores the DATE from which the above changes become effective. To illustrate:- Loan sanctioned is 3 million and 2 million is already drawn and the customer makes a draw down of the remaining principal on 15.02.2002 NEW. AMOUNT will be input with 1 million and the associated multi-value field VALUE. DATE will be input with the date 15.02.2002. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Change in principal either increase or decrease is a pre-requisite.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.N</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the "N" schedule amount. The amount that has to be either collected/ paid to the customer .</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicates the date on which the schedule is effective with respect to various events like, Principal Repayment, Interest Repayment, Rate revision etc. This date has been already defined by the user, in AZ.ACCOUNT, under schedule details. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE Standard Date Format</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.PRINCIPAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES NEW. PRINCIPAL Change in PRINCIPAL (either increase or decrease) or when there is any change in CALCULATION.BASE. For ex:-&gt; A deposit might have been made for Rs.1million and after the second day 0.25million might have been drawn prematurely. Though for the first two days the principal is Rs.1million the for the next period it is only 0.75million (and not 1million) Here 0.75million would have been the NEW principal. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Increase in principal due to INCREASE in deposit or FURTHER draw down in case of loan Permitted values that alter the field Principal balance Scheduled balance or Current balance.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the local equivalent of the amount in TAX.AMOUNT field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.PAY.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Applicable only in case of Deposits with B schedules. This field is updated with last date on which the B schedule was honored. The system matches the B schedule date and amount with the date in this field and in case they differ it concludes that installments are in arrears. The field AMOUNT.DUE is updated by the system based on this field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>N.SCH.FREQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>Not used</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. CODE Populated from AZ.ACCOUNT application when input. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> none.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES TAX. AMOUNT Amount OR rate as specified in tax code in tax application. If rate is specified then the rate is applied as a percentage on the charge amount. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> none</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Key to this application. Same as AZ Account Id</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.KEY</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field, as a part of R type schedule, contains the linking reference number (key) of the appropriate interest rate defined in BASIC.INTETEST table, which will be used for interest computation purposes. Based on the key defined here, the interest rate will be taken by the system from the BASIC.INTEREST table for interest calculation, from the date defined under Frequency. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input in AZ.SCHEDULE part of a set of multi value fields Allowed only for R type Schedules Should have been defined in BASIC.RATE.TEXT and in BASIC.INTERESt</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. AMT Amount defaulted from FT. CHARGE. TYPE for the CHARGE. CODE so input. Can be changed at Account level. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Defaulted from FT. CHARGE. TYPE.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.CC</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES TYPE. CC CC- This schedule is for repayment of Principal. Defaulted from Az. Account </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> None</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines the date from which the loan/ deposit account is effective. Any date entered earlier than the business date, is validated against the MAX.BACK.DATE defined under the respective AZ Product parameter. The future date entered here cannot be greater than the Forward Maximum Date defined under DATES. The value is populated from AZ.ACCOUNT. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Standard date format; Default is current Business Date. No input field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.KEY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Represents a reference on the TAX table which will indicate the rate to be used for the computation of taxation.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSURE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Not used</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Internal field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. CCY NO input-Defaulted to the Account currency. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> none</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.C</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field indicates the type of schedule defined by the user in AZ account for handling Charges. This field is reserved for future development. The other types of schedules are: A - For defining annuity type of repayment, where a constant repayment amount is generated based on the frequency. B - This type is used for effecting loan drawdowns on pre-defined dates. On the specified dates the system will transfer the draw down amount to the credit of the nominated account. From G14.0.00 the repayment type can be CREDIT CARD also. I - Defines schedule for interest payments. For I type schedule, amount cannot be specified by the user. Total period of all I type schedules are validated against the Maximum Interest Only period defined for the AZ account. P- This type defines the Repayment of Principal R - This type is used for effecting Interest Rate revision on specified dates. Both Variable interest rate and Fixed Interest rate can be fixed to a loan account, through this type, for a certain percentage of the outstanding amount and also for various periods within the life of the loan account. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input in AZ.SCHEDULE Part of a multi value set of fields Manual input for C schedule not allowed. "C" -schedule generation is automatic (based on setup)</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.R</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field indicates the type of schedule defined by the user in AZ account for interest Rate related events like rate revision etc. The value shown here indicates the effective Rate of Interest applied to the account. Schedule Type R - This type is used for effecting Interest Rate revision on specified dates. The value defined under Term Priority will be taken into account for effecting this type of schedule. Both Variable interest rate and Fixed Interest rate can be fixed to a loan account, through this type, for a certain percentage of the outstanding amount and also for various periods within the life of the loan account. Example: As per the above R schedule, a rate revision will happen on 22-05-2001, with 60% of the outstanding amount by a variable interest (key1 and spread 6 on Basic Interest) and 40% of the outstanding amount by fixed interest 15% Based on the schedule types defined in the AZ account, AZ.SCHEDULE is generated by the system. By giving the ID of the AZ account in AZ.SCHEDULE, the complete schedule details of the account can be viewed. Schedule is automatically generated by the system and no user input is allowed . Further, no automatic actions like in LD/ MG are done by the system based on AZ.SCHEDULE . In All in One Module, the SCHEDULE is used only as a reference point, for updating the limit, ADI and comparing the AZ account balance on scheduled dates, for arriving the arrears or the redraw value. The other types of schedules are: A - For defining annuity type of repayment, where a constant repayment amount is generated based on the frequency. B - This type is used for effecting loan drawdowns on pre-defined dates. On the specified dates the system will transfer the draw down amount to the credit of the nominated account. I - Defines schedule for interest payments. For I type schedule, amount cannot be specified by the user. Total period of all I type schedules are validated against the Maximum Interest Only period defined for the AZ account. P- This type defines the Repayment of Principal </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE Part of a multi value set of fields</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines the percentage of outstanding amount up to which the Variable interest rate is applicable, under a R type schedule of AZ account. For the rest of the percentage amount, fixed interest rate will be applicable. Example: If 60 is defined here, variable interest will be applied on 60% of the outstanding amount and Fixed interest will be applied on the remaining 40% of the outstanding amount. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE. (Defined already in AZ.ACCOUNT) 1-5 numeric rate type like 60, 45.50 etc.; Maximum value 100 Part of a multi value set under R type of Schedules.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.B.SYS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the amount of drawdown in case of loans</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field will be updated only for deposit type of az.accounts.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.TAX</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicates the total tax amount that has to be recovered on the scheduled date. Based on the tax related values defined under AZ.ACCOUNT, tax amount is calculated and displayed here. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input Field Standard T24 amount field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLY.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Not used.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R.SCH.FREQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>Internal decriptor field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.HIST.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the last DATE and history number components of Key to AZ.SCHEDULES.HIST application.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ONLINE.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the Online repayment amount.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>B.SCH.FREQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>Internal descriptor field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.CI</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES TYPE. CI CI- This is committed interest schedule. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Manual input for CI schedule not allowed. "CI" -schedule generation is automatic (based on setup)</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.KEY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the Basic Interest key linked to the contract for the current period</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.REPAY.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines the total repayment amount. This amount includes the Principal Repayment amount, Interest Repayment amount and Charges to be paid on the scheduled date. In addition, this field includes the tax amount also, which has been calculated as an exclusive one. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field; Only for reference Standard T24 amount field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTES</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES NOTES:- The field contains the record of VARIOUS stages that the AZ account has passed through before it is finally closed. For ex. An FD input on say 14.05.2001 for say 2 million Stage -(1)Partly redeemed for 1 million on 15.05.2001 Stage-(2) On 17.05.2001 may be rolled over further period of 2 days Stage-(3)On 19.05.2001 when the deposit is closed by transferring the balance to nominated a/c In the above the notes will contain the following :- Stage (1) "Early redemption of 1 million on 15.05.2001" Stage(2) "Deposit rolled over" and Stage (3)"Closed contract" </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1-35 characters in length permitted.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.CIGEN.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the date on which the "CI" amount was lastly calculated. Applicable only for credit cards</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.OD.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the grace OVERDUE amount for each schedule. Associated with GRACE.DATe</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CALC.BASE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Refer to helptext of AZ.ACCOUNt</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the AZ.ACCOUNT currency</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.SCH.FREQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>Not used</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES CHANGE. DATE The date from which the new principal (field no.32) and calculation base (field no.33) becomes effective. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Only date can be input. A change in principal or Basis is a essential for populating this date.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCH.CALC.BASE</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES SCH. CALC. BASE Indicates the basis on which the calculation of interest is done for the AZ account. The input is populated from AZ Account. Permitted options are (1) Principal (2)Scheduled Balance (3)Current Balance </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Permitted values :-Principal, Scheduled balance and Current balance- in case of loans Restricted to Principal in case of fixed deposits and Scheduled balance in case of Savings plan.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.P</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field indicates the type of schedule defined by the user in AZ account, for repayment of Principal amount. In the case of AZ loan account, the amount shown here is the amount of Principal Repayment to be made by the customer on the specified date. According to the type of repayment like Annuity, Linear and Others, the schedule takes care of defining the Principal repayment. When 'Other' type of Repayment is specified in AZ account, unstructured Principal repayments can be defined in P type schedule by specifying the amount and the date. Based on the schedule types defined in the AZ account, AZ.SCHEDULE is generated by the system. By giving the ID of the AZ account in AZ.SCHEDULE, the complete schedule details of the account can be viewed. Schedule is automatically generated by the system and no user input is allowed . Further, no automatic actions like in LD/ MG are done by the system based on AZ.SCHEDULE . In All in One Module, the SCHEDULE is used only as a reference point, for updating the limit, ADI and comparing the AZ account balance on scheduled dates, for arriving the arrears or the redraw value. The other types of schedules are: A - For defining annuity type of repayment, where a constant repayment amount is generated based on the frequency. It is possible to define multiple 'A' type of schedules within an AZ loan account for different periods during the term of the loan. In such cases, it is necessary to input at least one 'A' type schedule that includes the maturity date and brings the loan balance to zero (or the residual amount). B - This type is used for effecting loan drawdowns on pre-defined dates. On the specified dates the system will transfer the draw down amount to the credit of the nominated account. I - Defines schedule for interest payments. For I type schedule, amount cannot be specified by the user. Total period of all I type schedules are validated against the Maximum Interest Only period defined for the AZ account. R- This type defines the Interest rate revision on a defined date. This type takes care of both variable interest and fixed interest based on the percentage of outstanding amount as well as on various periods of the loan. In order to change the interest rates defaulted from the AZ Product Parameter, a R type schedule can be defined at the start of loan itself, with new values. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE Part of a multi value set of fields</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.I</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field indicates the schedule defined by the user in AZ account, for repayment of Interest. For I type schedule, amount cannot be specified by the user, in the AZ account. The amount shown in AZ.SCHEDULE under I type is the amount of interest calculated by the system and to be paid by the customer on the date specified. Total period of all I type schedules are validated against the Maximum Interest Only period defined for the AZ account. Based on the schedule types defined in the AZ account, AZ.SCHEDULE is generated by the system. By giving the ID of the AZ account in AZ.SCHEDULE, the complete schedule details of the account can be viewed. Schedule is automatically generated by the system and no user input is allowed . Further, no automatic actions like in LD/ MG are done by the system based on AZ.SCHEDULE . In All in One Module, the SCHEDULE is used only as a reference point, for updating the limit, ADI and comparing the AZ account balance on scheduled dates, for arriving the arrears or the redraw value. The other types of schedules are: A - For defining annuity type of repayment, where a constant repayment amount is generated based on the frequency. B - This type is used for effecting loan drawdowns on pre-defined dates. On the specified dates the system will transfer the draw down amount to the credit of the nominated account. P- This type defines the Repayment of Principal R - This type is used for effecting Interest Rate revision on specified dates. Both Variable interest rate and Fixed Interest rate can be fixed to a loan account, through this type, for a certain percentage of the outstanding amount and also for various periods within the life of the loan account. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE Part of a multi value set of fields</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCEEDS.TOLERANCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES EXCEEDS. TOLERANCE This is the field that decides whether to charge late payment fee, levy penalty (on loan arrears) etc. This is decided by the system based on the inputs made in the field LIAB. TO.PENALTY (field in APP) in case of deposits and from GRACE. PERIOD (field in APP) field in case of loans. The parameters for the charges are drawn from AZ. PRODUCT. PARAMETER (APP) and Penalty from AZ. ACCOUNT. TO illustrate: For a savings plan deposit if LIAB. TO .PENALTY is defined as 2- then it will not charge penalty for defaults made upto 2 installments. If a 3rd installment is defaulted -then this field is activated to charge penalty as designed in APP </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Input in fields LIAB. TO. PENALTY and GRACE. PERIOD is optional. Once input the period is reckoned before calculating penalty. Or else penalty is calculated from DAY ONE.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>I.SCH.FREQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>Not used</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAY.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines the total repayment amount. This amount includes the Principal Repayment amount, Interest Repayment amount and Charges to be paid on the scheduled date. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field; Only for reference Standard T24 amount field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.LIQ.ACCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. LIQ. ACCT An a/c specified here is debited for the charge amount specified. Populated from inputs in AZ.Account </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> none .</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.ACCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the value of CHARGE.IMMED Refer to helptext of AZ.ACCOUNT for charge immed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the grace processing date for each schedule.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES TAX. CODE Populated from Tax code attached to the FT. COMMISSION. TYPE or FT. CHARGE. TYPE. Rate is derived from Tax application of the tax code so attached above. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> none</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.Z</field>
<desc>
        <p>NOT USEd</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCHEDULE.BAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>The field indicates BALANCE in the account as per SCHEDULES. The balance indicates a FUTURE position assuming a pattern of INFLOW over the period. For Ex:=&gt;A Savings plan with a monthly installment of Rs.1000 is opened on 01.02.02. The schedules ASSUME that every month the installments are received and projects a balance of 2000 as on 01.03.02 3000 as on 01.04.02 4000 as on 01.05.02 and so on and the interest amounts are calculated and capitalized accordingly. But in reality the inflows might not have come for the month of March and April which makes the actual balance as 1000 (while the scheduled balance on that date would be 3000) In case of LOAN accounts the SCHEDULED balance will be diminishing over the periods assuming a fixed pattern of repayment over the periods. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Rule 1:- It is simply a projection of FUTURE cash inflow into the account Rule 2:- Actual balance may differ from the scheduled balance.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRD.RATE.KEY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the Periodic Key linked to AZ deposit .</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.PL.ACCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES CHG. PL. ACCT If the repayment. type is CREDIT-CARD then during repayment if the charges need to be posted to an account or category to setoff the one that was posted online then it needs to be specified here Populated from input in AZ.Account </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> none</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.B</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the "B" schedule amount</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AZ.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES AZ. INT. RATE Implies the interest rate governing the particular loan draw down. Populated to the AZ. Schedules from the AZ.account. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicates the spread or margin of interest, which has to be applied to the Basic interest rate defined in BASIC.INTEREST ( and linked through RATE.KEY ), to arrive at the variable interest. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE (defined already in AZ.ACCOUNT) 1-5 numeric characters of rate type (example 3.25, 99.99); Cannot be greater than 100 A margin, which will result in a negative interest rate is prohibited. Part of a set of multi value fields Allowed only for R type Schedules</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Internal descriptor field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.OPERND</field>
<desc>
        <p>Determines the method by which the basic interest rate is to be adjusted by the RATE.SPREAD to arrive at the Variable interest rate for the loan account under R schedule.. This field specifies whether the Spread Rate is to be added to, subtracted from or multiplied by the basic interest rate to arrive at the final variable interest rate. If Multiply is specified the final rate is (100 + M) percent of the effective interest rate , where M is the Margin Rate percentage. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE. This field is already defined in AZ.ACCOUNT Part of a multi value set of fields under R type schedule.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ANNUITY.ADJUST</field>
<desc>
        <p>Valid in case of ANNUITY contracts. If the REPAY amount calculated from annuity is less than the interest amount, then this field will HOLD the differential interest and the OUTSTANDING balance will be increased by this AMOUNT. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Rule 1: Rule 2</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIXED.RATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicates the annual fixed interest rate applicable for the R schedule defined under the AZ loan account. The fixed interest can be defined for the entire amount outstanding or to a percentage of the outstanding amount. The fixed interest can be defined for the entire period of the loan account or in parts. Example: As per the above R schedule, a rate revision will happen on 22-05-2001, with 60% of the outstanding amount by a variable interest (key1 and spread 6 on Basic Interest) and 40% of the outstanding amount by fixed interest 15% </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input field in AZ.SCHEDULE (defined in AZ.ACCOUNT)</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.INT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the intermediate accrued interest amount. Will be set if there is any B/P/N/R schedule and no "I" schedule</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.I.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the actual interest capitalised amount. Will be updated during online repayment or Interest event date</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDITIONAL.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Refer to helptext of AZ.ACCOUNt</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.DUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>AZ. SCHEDULES AMOUNT. DUE When B schedules for Deposits and P schedules for loan are defined- on the designated dates the system will look for balance in the REPAY a/c for appropriating the above scheduled amounts. In case a lesser balance exists than what is actually needed - the system will appropriate the balance available and write the difference amount in this field AMOUNT. DUE. To illustrate:- If for savings plan an amount of 15000 is defined in B schedule and the amount actually available in the REPAY a/c is only 10000 then the system would appropriate 10000 and puts the balance due for collection in this field i.e. in the present case 5000. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>: Applicable to deposit account with defined B schedules [ only savings plan]</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

