<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>DIR.COL.ALL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXP.START.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exp.Start.Range</p>
            <p>This will be the start range for the unique set of numbers alloted to the customer for export transactions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREFIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is input where an Allotment has an Alpha-numeric range, such as DELL 1 to 100.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>However if one range holds a value, this field becomes mandatory for       every subsequent range.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMP.END.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Imp.End.Range</p>
            <p>This field is mandatory, if the IMPORT.START.RANGE field holds value.</p>
            <p>This is the end range for the unique set of numbers alloted to the customer for import transactions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the start of range of numbers allotted to a customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMP.START.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Imp.Start.Range</p>
            <p>This will be the start range for the unique set of numbers alloted to the customer for import transactions</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REMARKS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This will hold the remarks made on number allotted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />Optional input.    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLECTION.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>COLLECTION.REF</p>
            <p>This field acts as mnemonic or the DIRECT.COLLECTION.ALLOT reference. </p>
            <p>Like the ID, the Mnemonic must be unique across T24.  </p>
            <p>For each Customer, the System will automatically update the internal file "CON.DIR.COL.ALL" which allows the User to display the Customers in Mnemonic sequence instead of Customer number or Customer name</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer number or Mnemonic.</p>
            <p>It is common practice in some parts of the world, where a Collection document is directly sent by the customer to the Drawee or to the Drawee's banker and informs the same to Collecting Bank and hands over the copy of the collection document.</p>
            <p>Although the Drawer' may quote a number of his choice, the same may not be possible with the Collecting Banker. To facilitate the process of nomenclature, the Collecting Banker allots a range of numbers to each customer and informs them of the same. </p>
            <p>The Drawer quotes the same as reference number in his document and informs the Bank. This number is recorded in Collection type LC in the field DIRECT.COLL.NO.</p>
            <p>Say, if DELL were to send a Collection Document for realization and a range allotted to them is COLL 1-100, a document may be registered as COLL24 and dispatched. This COLL24 is recorded by the Collecting Banker in the field DIRECT.COLL.NO and same is fetched when the LC is referred as  DELL.COLL24 or 50040.COLL24 (50024 being the Customer number) or the existing logic of referring as TF....</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Customer number or Mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the End of range of numbers allotted to a customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric input.</p>
            <p>Cannot be less than Start range.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.END.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exp.End.Range</p>
            <p>This field is mandatory, if the EXPORT.START.RANGE field holds value. </p>
            <p>This is the end range for the same unique set of numbers alloted to the customer for export transactions</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

