<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NEW.DISC.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will accept new discount rate for amendments</p>
            <p> This field will be enabled only when New Maturity Date is greater than </p>
            <p>  existing Maturity date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If this field is entered, payment will be made for the DOCUMENT.AMOUNT</p>
            <p> minus the DISCOUNT.AMT+ NEW.DISC.AMOUNT calculated from this rate</p>
            <p> and also minus any load + NEW.LOAD.AMOUNT.</p>
            <p>  The discount amount will be accrued over the life of the drawing at the</p>
            <p>  rate specified in the LC.PARAMETERS file.</p>
            <p>    Either a new discount rate or a new discount amount may be entered. The system</p>
            <p>   will calculate the one not input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(1) Standard rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT202.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-set, this field is used to determine the message type to which the user wishes to amend the delivery and is used exclusively with the fields MSG.CLASS.NO, OVR.CARRIER, ADDRESSEE and SEND.MESSAGE.<p>Validation Rules:</p>      1 - 4 numeric characters. (Optional input). </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the currency of the drawing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) NO INPUT FIELD - The field will be populated from drawings</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.ADV.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.      This field holds the activity number, which is triggered by the latest activity in the life-cycle of the transaction.. The activity is 4 digit number composed of three main parts:First indicates the operationSecond indicates the type of instrumentAnd the last two digit indicate the detail activity related to that operation</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCESS.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is system field  and will contain excess amount to be collected/returned </p>
            <p> to customer with sign.</p>
            <p>If excess amount is less than zero and based on value in RETURN.INTEREST field </p>
            <p>excess amount will be credied to customer or P/L.</p>
            <p>If excess amount is greater then zero then excess amount will be debited from</p>
            <p>customer</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.AMT.AFT.AMD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a System maintained field and displays the value of Payment amount after taking into effect any change that has been made during the current amendment like extension of maturity date or pre-closure or online maturity or backdated, which might affect the discount amount and the Payment amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field  This field contains the tax amount in the currency of the account that the charge is taken from.   When the tax is taken from an account that is in a different currency to the tax currency (TAX.CCY), then this field is used to hold the amount that was actually debited. This will be used for positions update if the charge currency is different to the account currency. The field is automatically updated when the tax is taken from the account using the current mid market spot rates.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will accept new maturity date for amending discounted drawings.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the load  rate of last discounted drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1)NO INPUT FIELD - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Using the conditions specified for the charge code in the FT.CHARGE.TYPE</p>
            <p>   or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables, the system automatically calculates the</p>
            <p>   amount to be charged.  Input of an amount, however, will be accepted to</p>
            <p>   allow the user to override the amount calculated.</p>
            <p>   The amount will be calculated by the system based on the CHARGE.CURRENCY</p>
            <p>   field specified above</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) 14 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters.</p>
            <p>     Associated multivalue field.</p>
            <p> (2) Input is only allowed if a charge/commission code has been entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Using the conditions specified for the charge code in the FT.CHARGE.TYPE</p>
            <p>or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables, the system automatically calculates the</p>
            <p>amount to be charged. Input of an amount, however, will be accepted to</p>
            <p>allow the user to override the amount calculated.</p>
            <p>The amount will be calculated by the system based on the CHARGE.CURRENCY</p>
            <p>field specified above</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) 14 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters.</p>
            <p>Associated multivalue field.</p>
            <p>(2) Input is only allowed if a charge/commission code has been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.SHARE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage of share for each participant in Syndicated LC.The user may however, modify the share provided none of the participant's portion define in Facility tranche is overdrawn.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.LOAD.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participant share in load amount expressed in terms of drawings currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>Noinput field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.AMT.BEF.AMD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the Payment amount of last discounted drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.EXCESS.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participant share in excess amount calculated either due to preclosure of maturity date or reduction in discount rate.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field enables the user to override the defaulted carrier for a particular message type and select a new carrier.   For example : If a specific message is generated by SWIFT, the user is able to override this by choosing other available options from the CARRIER table, eg TELEX or PRINT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.DISC.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will accept new discount amount for discount amendment.</p>
            <p>If entered then NEW.DISC.RATE cannot be entered.</p>
            <p>Total discount amount cannot exceed document amount.</p>
            <p>The new discount amount is calculated as the value added by NEW.DISC.AMOUNT on the date of extension upto the new maturity date and the amount accrued till today i.e.value from DISC.AMRT.TO.DTE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) 1-4 type Amt characters plus a decimal point.</p>
            <p>       Standard Amount Format </p>
            <p>.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.AMRT.TO.DTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Discount amount accrued to date, if the drawing has been discounted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATED.DRAWING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the drawing sequence number and will be mapped to fields CHRG.REL.DRAW, TAX.REL.DRAW of LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES if any charges or taxes involved</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field contains a message class ID, (defined in EB.ADVICES). There may be many classes specified, but only classes, which are related to the operation, will be triggered. For example, the EB.ADVICES   number LC-3801 (L/C Export Sight Drawing) may have the following classes and messages:   Message No. : 1798    EB.MESSAGE.CLASS   :   NOTIFICATION   Message No. : 754 -   EB.MESSAGE.CLASS   :   OPERATIONS   Message No. : 742 -   EB.MESSAGE.CLASS&gt;   :   REIMBURSING   Assume that the EB.MESSAGE.CLASS ID has been mapped to L/C internal class specified in LC.PARAMETERS as follows:      BASIC.MESSAGE   =   OPERATIONS      NOTIFICATION   =   NOTIFICATION      REIMBURSING   =   REIMBURSING   In the L/C Transaction, the system will always populate the OPERATIONS and NOTIFICATION class when the L/C is issued. The REIMBURSING class will only be triggered, when THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO or THIRD.PARTY field (REIMBURSING bank in this case) in LETTER.OF.CREDIT has filled up. In combination with the field (SEND.MESSAGE), you can choose whether you want to produce the messages by flipping the YES/NO flag. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIM.AMT.AFT.AMD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a System maintained field and displays the value of Reimbursement amount after taking into effect any change that has been made during the current amendment like extension of maturity date or pre-closure or online maturity or backdated, which might affect the discount amount and the Reimbursement amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the amount to be drawn under this drawing expressed in the</p>
            <p> currency above (DRAW.CURRENCY).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(1) NOINPUT FIELD - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the delivery keys used for the generation of Drawing advices/ documents/payments from the Electronic Delivery System. <p>Validation Rules:</p> System Generated. Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.CHARGED</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Code to identify the party this charge applies to.</p>
            <p>   This field identifies from whom the charge is to be taken.</p>
            <p>   For all charges within the multivalue set, this can be different.  Some</p>
            <p>   of the charges can be levied against the Opener, others against the</p>
            <p>   Beneficiary.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) (O)pener  (B)eneficiary.</p>
            <p> Associated multivalue field </p>
            <p>.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.DISC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participant share in document amount expressed in terms of drawings currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.TEXT.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format sub-value field for sending advices to participants in Syndicated LC's.This field will be mapped directly to tag 79 of  MT799 message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Accepts Swift characters.</p>
            <p>A sub-value set can hold 35 lines with 50 characters each.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participants share in document amount for drawings under Syndicated LC.</p>
            <p>For confirmed LC's PART.AMOUNT = DOCUMENT.AMOUNT * Participant share defined in LC</p>
            <p>For Partially confirmed LC's PART.AMOUNT= CONFIRMATION.AMOUNT* Participant share defined in LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Acting as part of the delivery multivale set, this field provides the user with the ability to decide whether to send or withhold sending the delivery of any message produced under the contract.   <p>Validation Rules:</p>      Options available are (Y)es - Send Message or (N)o - Do Not Send Message   Default is (Y)es </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies the account where funds are to be paid to under this drawing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) No Input Field - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.LOAD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed if NEW.DISC.RATE or NEW.DISC.AMOUNT is present.  </p>
            <p>When there is a load in drawings this field is mandatory.</p>
            <p>   The load amount will be accrued over the life of the drawing, at the</p>
            <p>   frequency specified in the LC.PARAMETERS file, separately from the</p>
            <p>   discount amount.</p>
            <p>   If the user wishes to enter a load amount rather than a load rate, then</p>
            <p>   this can be performed by entering a value in the LOAD.AMT field below.  If</p>
            <p>   this is the case, then this field will be calculated and updated by the</p>
            <p>   system.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) Standard rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal characters).</p>
            <p>        (Optional input)</p>
            <p>(2) Can only be entered if NEW.DISC.RATE, or NEW.DISC.AMOUNT has been entered.</p>
            <p>(3) If entered, then NEW.LOAD.AMOUNT cannot be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.LOAD.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Optional and only allowed if NEW.DISC.RATE or NEW.DISC.AMOUNT is present.</p>
            <p>   The load amount will be accrued over the life of the drawing, at the</p>
            <p>   frequency specified in the LC.PARAMETERS file, separately from the</p>
            <p>   discount amount.</p>
            <p>If the user wishes to enter a load rate rather than a load amount, then</p>
            <p>   this can be performed by entering a value in the NEW.LOAD.RATE field above.</p>
            <p>   If this is the case, then this field will be calculated and updated by the</p>
            <p>   system.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) 1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal</p>
            <p>      point.</p>
            <p>(2) Can only be entered if  NEW.DISC.RATE, or NEW.DISC.AMOUNT</p>
            <p>       has been entered.</p>
            <p> (3) If entered, then NEW.LOAD.RATE cannot be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.LCCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.   This field contains the local currency equivalent of the tax amount.   If the tax amount is not in local currency, then this amount will be calculated when the charge is debited from an account and credited to the P/L account, using the mid market spot rate's at the time. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.AMRT.TO.DTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Load amount accrued to date, if the drawing has been discounted, and a load amount/rate specified</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.LOAD.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will contain the total recalculated load amount for the drawings after amendment.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> System Generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.DEBIT.TO.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input in this field signifies either that the customer is being debited for a sight bill, which was previously debited to an Internal account or is adjusted to a Loan account. Valid inputs are DEBITED and TRFLOAN. While the former is used to signify that Customer account is debited the latter implies that the payable component has been converted to a Loan.</p>
            <p>When DEBITED is chosen, the discount amount that is yet to be amortized is either credited to the account of the Discount party charged or booked to the P&amp;L account as determined by RETURN.INTEREST.</p>
            <p>If TRFLOAN is chosen, the amount of discount yet to be amortized along with the discount already amortized is credited to the Discount party charged by reversing out the P&amp;L entries as well. Input in this field is allowed only when the contract is matured Online or Backdated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p value="1">Valid inputs are DEBITED/TRFLOAN</p>
                <p value="2">Valid only for Sight Bills.</p>
                <p value="3">Cannot be input for Extension and Pre-closure (where the       NEW.MATURITY.DATE is greater than Today).</p>
                <p value="4">Mandatory input when a Discounted Bill is matured online or Back-dated,       that was earlier set as NOTDEBITED.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.LCCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the local currency equivalent of the charge amount. The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. The value in this field will be the amount that is used to update the charges profit and loss account. If the charge amount is not in local currency, then this amount will be calculated when the charge is debited from an account and credited to the P/L account, using the market mid spot rate at the time</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the load   rate of last discounted drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1)NO INPUT FIELD - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTICIPANT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the Participant who is part of the Syndicated LC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be existing participant of the Tranche.</p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIM.AMT.BEF.AMD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the Reimbursement amount of last discounted drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(1) No Input Field - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates corresponding charge code for tax  defined.</p>
            <p>Validation rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Associated multivalue field associated with fields TAX.CODE through to TAX.DATE</p>
                <p value="2">Noinput field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the discount rate of last discounted drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(1) NOINPUT FIELD - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.XCHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the exchange rate to be used between the charge debit account and the charge currency.</p>
            <p>If no input is made then the mid rate CHARGE.CCY.MARKET set in LC.PARAMETERS will be used.</p>
            <p>If no currency market is set in LC.PARAMETERS then the default market for LC will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Indicates whether charges are to be waived on this Drawing.  If set to 'Y' then no charges will be taken.</p>
            <p>If this field is set to 'Y' then all charges relating to this Drawing will be waived, i.e.. no default charges will be added.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are 'Yes' or 'No'.</p>
            <p>     Defaults to NO.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field. Based on the tax code obtained from the commission and/or charges table, this field displays the automatically calculated tax (if any) which is to be added to the charge</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETURN.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field will accept either 'YES' or 'NO'. If set to 'YES' and excess amount is less than zero then excess amount will be returned to customer if DISC.PARTY.CHRD is B else it will be adjusted in LIVEDB if DISC.PARTY.CHRD is O.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If set to 'NO' excess amount will be retained and credited to P/L in a category specified in LC.PARAMETERS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When DR.DEBIT.TO.CUST is set as TRFLOAN, the system resets the value of this field to YES, thereby crediting the discount party charged with not only the pending amortization amount but also the already amortized amount that has been credited to P&amp;L.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid input is 'YES' / 'NO'</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Enabled except for extension of NEW.MATURITY.DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Defaults to </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.This field contains the code of the tax table which has been used when calculating tax on charges and/or commission.The field does not require any operator input as it is obtained from the relevant commission or charges table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the VALUE.DATE of the drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) NOINPUT FIELD - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USANCE.ACT.SENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.DISC.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will contain total recalculated discount amount for the drawings</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1)Standard amount format.</p>
            <p>(2) No Input Field.</p>
            <p>(3) System Generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies the currency that charges are to be levied in.  This can be</p>
            <p>   different from the DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>  If this field is not entered then a default currency will be selected from</p>
            <p>   the currency  of the drawings.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) CCY (Currency code e.g. GBP must be 3)</p>
            <p>      Associated mulivalue field.</p>
            <p>(2) For all fields within this multivalue set, the currency must be the</p>
            <p>      same.</p>
            <p>(3) Once input, this field cannot be changed.</p>
            <p>(4) Input is only allowed if a charge/commission code has been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the original maturity date before amendment of drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(1) NOINPUT FIELD - This field will be populated from drawings</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.DISC.AGREE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the participant's decision  to participate in the discounting process.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Option field 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>Default value - 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Code to identify the current status of the charge</p>
            <p> Used to identify if the charge has been taken or waived.</p>
			<p>If the status is 15,the charge is waived and will not be processed in the future.It is stored in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES as a charge that has been waived.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.ENTRY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.   This field displays a number generated automatically by the system which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of this Drawing.   The system will automatically insert a number into this field that will refer to a statement entry or a category entry depending on the value contained in the corresponding multivalue fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.SEND.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.   Part of a multi-value set. This field displays the date the related message was sent</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies the types of commission or charges to be levied on the Drawing</p>
            <p>transaction being processed.  The charge or commission code will be</p>
            <p>entered as an eleven-character code as defined on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or</p>
            <p>FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) 2 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>          (Multivalue field)</p>
            <p>(2) The code must be a valid commission or charge code as defined on</p>
            <p>          the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables.</p>
            <p>(3) Input is not allowed if the WAIVE.CHARGES field is set to 'Y'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>202.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for Sender to Receiver (i.e. Sending bank to Receiving bank) Information. Any information entered into this field will appear on a S.W.I.F.T. MT202 message (General Financial Institution Transfer). </p>
            <p>It may be used to provide instructions or additional information for the Receiver, Intermediary, Account with Institution or Beneficiary Institution. </p>
            <p>This field corresponds to field 72 on S.W.I.F.T. messages, and must never be used for information for which another field is intended, or for instructions not required in a message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type SW Multivalue field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain a codeword followed by further information.</p>
            <p>All code words must be valid code words as defined in S.W.I.F.T. documentation and must conform to the rules specified. Use of invalid code words will cause a message rejection when validated by S.W.I.F.T.</p>
            <p>Further code words and information can be entered in subsequent multivalues, but additional information continued on a new line must be preceded by a double slash '//'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESSEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the user to divert a particular message type to another (third) party.   The user has a number of options:      Simple insertion of a name or address. This will re-route the message in PRINT format to the named party.   The code 'TX-' followed by a telex number. This will re-route the message by TELEX to the number detailed.   The code 'SW-' followed by a S.W.I.F.T. code. This will re-route the message by SWIFT to the respective bank.   The code 'C-' followed by a valid customer number or mnemonic. This will re-route the message in PRINT format to the customer indicated. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID to DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS file. DRAWING id appended with field NEXT.AMEND.NO of LC.DISCOUNT.BALANCES. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field displays the charge/commission amount in the currency of the account that the charge/commission is taken from. When the charge/commission is taken from an account that is in a different currency to the charge currency (CHARGE.CURRENCY), then this field is used to hold the amount that was actually debited. This will be used for positions update if the currency is not local. The field is automatically updated when the charge/commission is taken from the account using the current market mid spot rates.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies the account where funds are to be received from under this</p>
            <p> drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1)NO INPUT FIELD - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the discount amount of last discounted drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1)NO INPUT FIELD - This field will be populated from drawings.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Date from which new discount rate or new load rate will be effective.</p>
            <p>This field will be enabled only when NEW.MATURITY.DATE is greater than existing</p>
            <p>MATURITY.DATE.</p>
            <p>(1) Cannot be less than VALUE.DATE of drawings.</p>
            <p>(2) Defaulted to TODAY</p>
            <p>(3) Cannot be less than today.</p>
            <p>(4) Cannot be greater than old maturity of drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(1) Standard date format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIV.SETT.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input in this field denotes the account to be debited when maturing the sight bill. Valid only if DR.DEBIT.TO.CUST is input. Accepts any valid customer account of the same currency as the DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>On committing the amendment with an account in this field, the Internal account is credited and customer account is debited, with discount and charges, if any.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid only for Sight Discounted Bills.</p>
            <p>Input permitted only when DR.DEBIT.TO.CUST is input.</p>
            <p>Accepts any valid Customer account in the same currency as that of the       DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>INST.PORT.NO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
