<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>DR.DISCREPANT.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TICKLER.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts Valid days frequency . If  defined, will be used in the DRAWING which uses this Discrepant type to calculate the Tickler  Date on </p>
            <p>which the Tickler Message  would be sent.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Tickler days should be like +2W or +3C or 5W or 12C  etc.. where  W  stands for Working days and  C  stands for Calendar days.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.PARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Risk party for the Discrepancy type who is held at Risk. If URESERVE.REQ field is set as YES then this field becomes </p>
            <p>mandatory. The value of this field is defaulted in the PAYRES.PARTY field in DRAWINGS whenever a Discrepant type is input in </p>
            <p>DRAWINGS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Allowed Input  PRESENTOR / ISSUING.BANK</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDUCE.LIAB</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts  a value to define the Liability impact when a Collection Drawing is done.</p>
            <p>When the user desires to reduce the Liability of the Letter of Credit, to the extent of a CO Drawing ( or the outstanding Liability of the LC, whichever is less), this  field may be set to YES. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are YES or NO.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.DISCRE.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls the DISCREPANCY field in a DRAWING  which uses this Discrepant type. If set to YES, the DISCREPANCY field in </p>
            <p>a DRAWING becomes mandatory and vice-versa.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1) Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>2) Allowed Input  YES / NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCREPANT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id of DR.DISCREPANT.TYPE. It can be any alpha numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.DISCRE.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls the IN.DISCREPANCY field in a DRAWING which uses this Discrepant type. If set to YES the IN.DISCREPANCY </p>
            <p>field in a DRAWING becomes mandatory and vice-versa.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1) Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>2) Allowed Input  YES / NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTRUMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the type of Instrument (Export/Import) for the Particular Discrepant type. Once authorized this field cannot be changed.</p>
            <p>Eg: If the Letter of Credit is Import, then a Discrepant type with Instrument type set as Import is only allowed and the same for Export. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Mandatory Input</p>
                </p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>      2.  Allowed Input  EXPORT / IMPORT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>URESERVE.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies whether to hold the RISK.PARTY at Risk. This field controls the UNDER.RESERVE field in DRAWINGS whenever a </p>
            <p>Discrepant type is input in a DRAWING (i.e) the value of this field is defaulted in the UNDER.RESERVE field in DRAWINGS. </p>
            <p>Once authorized this field cannot be changed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Allowed Input  YES/NO</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any valid EB.ACTIVITY record can be given. This controls the Basic Activity that is generated in DRAWINGS (i.e) once the Activity code is mentioned here, this is defaulted as the Basic Activity in the DRAWING which uses this Discrepant type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Mandatory Input</p>
                </p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>      2)   Activity code should be like  LC-XXXX</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.MSG.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any valid EB.MESSAGE.CLASS record can be given. This controls the BASIC.MESSAGE.CLASS that is generated in DRAWINGS (i.e)</p>
            <p>once the Message class is mentioned here, this is defaulted as the Basic Message class in the DRAWING which uses this Discrepant </p>
            <p>type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFA.TICKL.TXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-value field. Accepts any free text.. This text is used as the Tickler Message that is generated for a DRAWING with Discrepant type </p>
            <p>set and the TICKLER.MODE set as AUTOMATIC.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1) Mandatory if TICKLER.MODE is 'AUTOMATIC'  otherwise this field cannot be Input.</p>
            <p>2) Accepts 1-50 Alphanumeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the name of the Discrepancy in a brief form and will be used for online enrichments in any field where this Discrepant type is Input. It is a multi  language field and descriptions can be entered in each of the languages defined in the LANGUAGE table.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1) Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>2) Accepts 1  35 Alphanumeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACE.DATE.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls the TRACE.DATE field in a DRAWING which uses this Discrepant type. If set to YES, the TRACE.DATE field in a </p>
            <p>DRAWING becomes mandatory and vice-versa.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1) Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>2) Allowed Input  YES / NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TICKLER.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the mode of the Tickler. If set to 'AUTOMATIC' the  DEFA.TICKL.TXT field becomes mandatory and the DRAWING  which uses </p>
            <p>this Discrepant type generates a Tickler message on the Tickler date calculated before.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid Modes are AUTOMATIC / MANUAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

