<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>DR.INT.CALC.COND</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>In a Discounted Drawing, the method of calculation of Discount component can now be specified using this table. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Specifying the appropriate Id of this table in the Drawing record can do such calculations. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Thus the rate that would be used for computation of the Discount component is now made user definable. Effectively, these can now be computed either on the Draw currency equivalent or its Local currency equivalent. Apart from this the User could also define the Buy/Sell/Mid rate that is to be applied on the currency equivalent.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CALC.CONDITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>  The Id of the record should be a two digit number. 
  E.g. 01, 02...99. 
  This Id is used to input into INT.CALC.COND in the Drawings record. 
 
  Range 01 to 99.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONV.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the rate to be used to calculate Discount amount.</p>
            <p>To see examples on the calculations have a look at the help text of field INT.CALC.CCY</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Accepts     any one of the values BUY / SELL / MID.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory     input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a free text field to describe the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>35 type 'A' alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.CALC.COND.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Id of the record should be a two digit number.</p>
            <p>E.g. 01, 02...99.</p>
            <p>This Id is used to input into INT.CALC.COND in the Drawings record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2 digits N (Numeric)</p>
            <p>Range  01 to 99.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CALC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency for calculating the discount amount with each having a different flow.</p>
            <p> Example:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Let us consider Discount party charged is Beneficiary.</p>
            <p>Assume local currency is USD</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> INT.CALC.CCY     is LCCY, and CONV.RATE is BUY</p>
            <p>    Document amount of GBP 100,000 will be converted using the Buy rate, say 1.45 resulting in USD 145,000.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    On this amount, Interest as defined will be calculated and the interest thus arrived would be (say Interest @7% for 100 days)  USD 2,780.82</p>
            <p />
            <p />   This will be converted to GBP (again at BUY rate) for raising consol entry, 2780.82/1.45 = GBP 1,917.81 <p>    Say the Customer has contracted the Drawing at 1.46. </p><p>    The payment would be for USD 146,000 - 2,780.82 = 143,219.18</p><p /><p /><p /><p /><p>INT.CALC.CCY     is DRAW.CCY, and CONV.RATE is SELL,</p><p>    Assume the GBP interest rate is 5% and the bill period as 100 days.</p><p>    In this instance, the interest amount will be GBP 100,000 @ 5 for 100 days = GBP 1,369.86</p><p>    The local equivalent of GBP 1369.86 @1.48= USD 2027.39 (1.48 being the SELL rate).</p><p>    If the Drawing were contracted at 1.45 and the payment currency is USD (Local),</p><p>    Then the credit amount shall be USD 145,000 - 2,027.39 = USD 142,972.61</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Accepts either DRAW.CCY or LCCY.</p><p>Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

