<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>DRAWINGS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Drawings is an application under the Letter of Credit system that is used to effect the transfer of funds and the acceptance of documents under Letters of Credit and Documentary Collection transaction.  The system is fully integrated within T24 to provide Accounting, Limit Exposure, Position Updating, Control and actual administration of L/C Collection activity together with ensuring efficient delivery of the related Advices, Documents, Covering Letters, and Payments. </p>
            <p>In order to enter a drawing, the Letter of Credit Collection parent contract must first be set up in order to define the types of drawings that can be made. </p>
            <p>The main type of transactions that the system processes are as follows: </p>
            <p />
            <p>Acceptance of Documents (AC) </p>
            <p>After checking that the documents presented comply with the terms and conditions of the LC, the bank will accept a bill of exchange on behalf of the beneficiary, which can then be discounted by the bank.  This is a term or usance type drawing. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Deferred Payment (DP) </p>
            <p>After checking that the documents presented comply with the terms and conditions of the LC, an undertaking is given by the Bank for payment to be made at a future date.  This type can be discounted by the bank in order to effect payment to the beneficiary at an earlier date, although reimbursement will not be received by the bank until the aforementioned future date. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Sight Payment (SP) </p>
            <p>After checking that the documents presented comply with the terms and conditions of the LC, immediate payment is effected to the Beneficiary/ Collecting Bank and reimbursement obtained from applicant/opening bank. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Collections for L/C (CO) </p>
            <p>If there are any discrepancies in the documents presented for payment/ acceptance, they can be handled on a collection basis whereby the Documents are presented to the LC application for their authorisation to pay/accept. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Collection Chase for L/C or D/C (CC) </p>
            <p>Used to chase drawings that have been sent for collection.  Currently this will be performed manually by entering a change to the existing drawing type (from CO to CC), but a facility exists to automate this so that collection chases will be produced on a fixed date specified for the drawing. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Collection rejection for L/C or D/C (CR) </p>
            <p>Used to signify that a drawing sent for collection has been rejected by the applicant or issuing bank.  If payment had been made under reserve, then funds will be claimed back from the Beneficiary. </p>
            <p />           
            <p>Document Checking (DC) </p>
            <p>Registration of Documents (RD) </p>
            <p>The main features of the application can be described as follows: </p>            
            <p />
            <p>1. Input Processing </p>
            <p>A stringent validation process is performed in order to ensure the correctness of any transaction input.  Which includes cross check with the parent L/C contract to enforce any restrictions imposed.  All inputs as applicable, will update limits, positions, accounts, etc. in real time. After authorization of the deal, all the documents, advices, covering letters, and S.W.I.F.T. messages applicable for the deal will be automatically generated by the Electronic Delivery System. </p>
            <p>The account to debit can be in a different currency to that of the LC. In this case the system will automatically calculate the foreign exchange necessary using current mid market buy and sell rates plus customer spread rates.  This exchange rate can be overridden by entering a specific rate to be used. </p>
            <p>The drawings entered will also update statistics held on the parent L/C record to show drawings outstanding, collections outstanding, total amount discounted etc. </p>
            <p>2. Charge Processing </p>
            <p>Default charges for all types of Drawing can be entered via the LC.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file, and will be automatically calculated by the system.  The facility to add extra charges or amend charges is available, together with the facility to waive all charges.  All charge entries are automatically generated, and if specified in a foreign currency, positions will be updated accordingly.  Charges can be amortised over the life of the contract, at frequencies defined by the user. </p>
            <p>Charges can be claimed from a number of parties involved in the Letter of Credit or Documentary Collection.  It is important to note that charges can be denominated in a currency other than the Letter of Credit/ Documentary Collection Currency. </p>
            <p>Whenever a sight drawing is entered that will effect a payment or claim reimbursement, the system will automatically deduct the outstanding charges from the payment amount, or add the total charges to the reimbursement amount, as indicated in the relevant charges fields. </p>
            <p>With regards to Acceptance/Deferred Payment drawings, charges will be taken at the first maturity, which may not necessarily be relative to the first acceptance of documents.  LC requests drafts at 120 days after Bill of Lading date </p>
            <p>e.g.       1st drawing payable 20.12.93            2nd drawing could be payable 18.12.93 </p>
            <p>All outstanding charges will therefore be taken 18.12.93 </p>
            <p>3. Document Processing </p>
            <p>All documents required to be produced by the input of the transaction will be generated by the Electronic Delivery System in order to facilitate easy amendment and customisation of the forms.  Large amounts of text can be entered using the WordPerfect application, and then linked into the L/C documents by simply entering the file name of the WordPerfect ASCII file into the field provided on the screen. </p>
            <p>Frequently used text and clauses can be entered via the LC.ADVICE.TEXT and LC.CLAUSES applications, and then linked into the transaction by entering a short code into the fields provided. </p>
            <p>The word processing system presently used is WordPerfect, but any other package can easily be incorporated into the system. </p>
            <p>4. Inquiries and Reports </p>
            <p>In common with other T24 Applications all data can be enquired upon or selectively analyzed and researched.  The system will also automatically produce reports of Collections Due, Unpaid Charges, etc. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FREE.TEXT.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format sub-value field for sending advices to participants in Syndicated LC's.This field will be mapped directly to tag 79 of  MT799 message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Accepts Swift characters.</p>
            <p>A sub-value set can hold 35 lines with 50 characters each</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES.FOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.COVER.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field details the account to where provision need to be released . Default is the provision debit account in LC. Input of an account will enable the user to release the provision into that newly assigned account. In the event of inputting provision credit account as the DRAW DOWN ACCOUNT in DRAWINGS, This account will be the account where the differential amount will either be debited or credited after accounting for the released provision amount (based on the input in PROV.AMT.REL) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BNK.TO.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to enter any bank to bank information required on the corresponding MT100.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETURN.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether the value date or maturity date or both need to be considered for commission calculation.</p>
            <p>Accepts valid record ID from EB.ACCRUAL.PARAM table.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>Applicable only when COMM.RATE or FIXED.COMM.AMT is defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value computed for the period of GRACE.DAYS in a discounted drawing, at the Discount/Load rate input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GTEE.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The input in this field signifies, that the Drawing is done for the set of Documents, towards which Shipping Guarantee was issued.</p>
            <p>Input in this field cannot be amended once authorized. In this scenario, the Drawdown account of the Drawings should be the same as Credit Provision account of the MD.DEAL.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid MD.DEAL, with outstanding Cash Margin.</p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQUIDATION.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the manner in which overdue payments are handled. The default for all contracts is AUTOMATIC. </p>
            <p>Three options are currently available: AUTOMATIC, SEMI-AUTOMATIC, and MANUAL</p>
            <p>AUTOMATIC indicates that payments will be settled irrespective of whether funds are available in the drawdown account.</p>
            <p>SEMI-AUTOMATIC indicates that a payment will be made only if funds are available, and that a PD end of day process will regularly attempt to make payment by checking whether funds have become available.</p>
            <p>MANUAL indicates that the contract will only settle if funds are available and that any future settlement of outstanding payments must be made manually via the PD module.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>If the PD product is not defined for the current company then the only allowed setting is AUTOMATIC. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDITOR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the code name of the auditor of the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a Numeric field and shall be used to input to indicate the additional number of days for which the interest on the discounted drawing is to be recovered. This amount thus calculated for the number of days input in this field, will be in addition to the Discount and Load amount calculated.</p>
            <p>This field thus represents the cushion that could be made available in the event of the settlement being delayed for a Discounted Drawing. This shall however have no impact on the Maturity Date of the Drawing. Amortization of amount thus collected shall take place only till the MATURITY.REVIEW date or the NEW.MATURITY.DATE as input.</p>
            <p>In the event of such Discounted Drawing being extended using DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS, the amortization shall take place till the NEW.MATURITY.DATE. However, if the same is matured online or back-dated, then the amortization would have taken place only till such date. </p>
            <p>The input in this field is permitted only at the first instance of discounting a Drawing. The field opens up only if the Discount/Load rate is input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.OP.CODE.MT103</field>
<desc>
            <p>SWIFT codes for bank operation (MT103)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid codes are </p>
            <p>CRED,     CRTS, SPAY, SPRI, SSTD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the actual payment amount, less any charges and discount applicable, credited to the payment account. </p>
            <p>This field will be updated by the system when the credit to the payment account is made. On value date for 'SP' and discounted 'AC' or 'DP', or 'CO' Paid Under Reserve drawings, and on the Maturity Review date for non-discounted 'AC' and 'DP' drawings. </p>
            <p>The amount will be the full document or equivalent if a foreign exchange rate has been issued, amount, expressed in the currency of the payment account, minus any charges and discount and load amounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a         decimal point.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.AMT.LOCAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in this field contains the local currency equivalent of the LOAD.AMT, if this amount has been entered.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>When the deal is input, the local currency equivalent of the load amount will be calculated by the system using the mid market spot rate in effect at the time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  1-14 (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INST.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the instalment number to be processed.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to trigger the collection of periodic commission in DRAWINGS.</p>
            <p>Accepts valid code from PERIODIC.COMMISSION table.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>Periodic commission is not supported for,</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Revolving LCs</p>
                <p value="2">LCs issued under syndication</p>
                <p value="3">Pre-advised LCs</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.OPER.CODE.MT103</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.LOAD.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participant share in load amount expressed in terms of drawings currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.SENT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The fields from  ACTIVITY.SENT to field CLASS.SCHED are associated multi-values. They are designed to cater for the USANCE delivery process, whereby some messages will be produced at the time of input, and some will be produce at maturity. Generally, this field will retain the activity, which has already been sent, to avoid message reproduction. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a no-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORMAT.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSNEE.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the revolving period number to which a drawing needs to be applied against a revolving letter of credit..</p>
            <p>The active / current portion of the revolving letter of credit will be defaulted by the system, however the user is able to amend the period number to indiciate that the drawings is against an expired portion. Drawings against a future portion are not permitted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using the conditions specified for the charge code in the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables, the system automatically calculates the amount to be charged. Input of an amount, however, will be accepted to allow the user to override the amount calculated. </p>
            <p>The amount will be calculated by the system based on the CHARGE.CURRENCY field specified above. </p>
            <p>The charge amount can be calculated as a percentage of the Document Amount by specifying a numeric followed by the '%' sign in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>14 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters.         Associated mulivalue field.</p>
            <p>Input is only allowed if a charge/commission code has         been entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARENT.DRAWING</field>
<desc>
            <p>In transferable LCs (exports), DRAWINGs under the transferred LC (CHILD LC) is allowed only when a drawing is done under the parent LC. This field is therefore used to indicate the corresponding DRAWING.NO. already booked under the associated Parent LC. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.CUST.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults to assignment customer number in LC if the ASSIGNMENT.REF matches.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Can be any valid customer ID if ASSIGNMENT.REF is input         as TPPAY or TPRECV.</p>
            <p>Mutually exclusive with ASSN.ADD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIS.PARTY.CHRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the party responsible for paying the discount charges.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.DOC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>TOTAL.DOC.AMT </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSIGNMENT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Assignment release given in LC. On entering the assignment reference it will be checked with the reference given in LC and all related information will be brought to DRAWING record if the reference matches.</p>
            <p>If value 'TPPAY' is input, then it will be understood as multiple settlement to third parties. In such case, updation, verification of LC record is not done.</p>
            <p>If value 'TPRECV' is input, then it will be understood as multiple debits to Applicant/Third parties. In such cases, update, verification  of LC  record is not done.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input if assignment or third party settlement         is to be done.</p>
            <p>Allowed for Import and Export transactions.</p>
            <p>Only the reference used in LC or TPPAY alone will be accepted for the       credit leg.</p>
            <p>Only TPRECV can be used if multiple debits are to be raised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The account where the broker wishes to receive his fee is held in this field. The account is set from the BROKER record for the currency defined in BROKER.CCY. If no account number has been entered on the BROKER record the internal account will be shown here, if such an account exists. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 account number field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENTS.HELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is utilised only for Documentary Collections and is used to identify that when oprocessing a drawing that documents are held at the bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field contains a message class ID, (defined in EB.ADVICES). There may be many classes specified, but only classes, which are related to the operation, will be triggered. For example, the EB.ADVICES </p>
            <p>number LC-3801 (L/C Export Sight Drawing) may have the following classes and messages:</p>
            <p>Message No. : 1798 - </p>
            <p>EB.MESSAGE.CLASS</p> : <p>NOTIFICATION</p><p>Message No. : 754 - </p><p>EB.MESSAGE.CLASS</p> : <p>OPERATIONS</p><p>Message No. : 742 - </p><p>EB.MESSAGE.CLASS </p>: <p>REIMBURSING</p><p>Assume that the EB.MESSAGE.CLASS ID has been mapped to L/C internal class specified in LC.PARAMETERS as follows:</p><p /><p>BASIC.MESSAGE</p> = <p>OPERATIONS</p><p /><p>NOTIFICATION</p> = <p>NOTIFICATION</p><p /><p>REIMBURSING</p> = <p>REIMBURSING</p><p>In the L/C Transaction, the system will always populate the OPERATIONS and NOTIFICATION class when the L/C is issued. The REIMBURSING class will only be triggered, when THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO or THIRD.PARTY field (REIMBURSING bank in this case) in LETTER.OF.CREDIT has filled up. In combination with the field (SEND.MESSAGE), you can choose whether you want to produce the messages by flipping the YES/NO flag.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCREPANCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field specifies the reason(s) for refusal of the documents, for example, discrepancies. It may also hold the type of instruction or information. </p>
            <p>Enter "NO" to prevent the delivery activity LC-3402, which is usually associated with an advice of discrepancy (S.W.I.F.T. MT750).</p>
            <p>Mandatory input for "CO" type of drawing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p><![CDATA[ ]]>Valid SWIFT characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.SHARE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage of Share for each participant in Syndicated LC.The user may however, modify the share provided none of the participant's portion define in Facility tranche is overdrawn.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERMED.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify an intermediary bank through which funds are to be routed. </p>
            <p>If this field is entered, then a payment instruction will be generated to the Nostro payment account, instructing them to route the funds through this account, to the ACCOUNT.WITH bank identified below. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-35 type S (Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Can         be free format name of intermediary bank or a customer id         from the customer file. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If entered, then ACCOUNT.WITH must be entered.</p>
            <p>The Intermediary bank must not be the same as the         advising bank, the issuing bank, the third party bank, or         the advise thru bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INST.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated multi value field of charge multi value set.</p>
            <p>Specifies whether the charge is applicable for current instalment or every instalment.</p>
            <p>Valid options:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">FIXED - Fixed (same) charge amount is applicable for all instalments.</p>
                <p value="2">VARIABLE - Charge is applicable for all instalments but the charge amount will be calculated for each instalment on the instalment amount and conditions defined in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE.</p>
                <p value="3">NULL - Defined charge is applicable for the current instalment only.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the account where charges are to be debited. </p>
            <p>Can be any account including internal account and or nostro. If the account is equal to DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT then the reimburse amount will be added by the charge. CHARGE.STATUS allowed be 8 or 12, depending on whether it is a sight drawing (SP) or acceptance drawing (AC/DP)</p>
            <p>If the account is equal to PAYMENT.ACCOUNT, then the payment amount will be deducted by that amount. CHARGE.STATUS allowed will be 9 or 11, depending on whether it is a sight drawing (SP), or an acceptance drawing (AC/DP)</p>
            <p>If the account is any other account than the two above, CHARGE.STATUS can be null or 2.</p>
            <p>If  PARTY.CHARGED were to be CO or CB, this field would be defaulted with DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT or PAYMENT.ACCOUNT respectively. However in this case, say an Export payment of GBP 100,000 is to be realized from a GBP Nostro to into a Customer's  account in Local currency (other than GBP, say USD) and realization happens for GBP 99,200.00, the PARTY.CHARGED code  would be used as CB and the account defaulted would be Customer's USD  account. But if GBP undergoes a rate change prior to maturity of this Drawing, the settlement amount may not happen for GBP 99,800 but for a small +/- amount depending on the movement of  the rate, creating an inconsistency in the Nostro account.</p>
            <p>In order to eliminate this, when the PARTY.CHARGED  is either CO or CB, the User can manually override the  Defaulted  account, with that of other, i.e.,  for CO with PAYMENT.ACCOUNT and for CB with DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>For further details see help text under field PARTY.CHARGED.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.LAST.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the last date the discount charge amount, if any, was accrued. The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  Type DD Standard date format in range 1000 - 2049.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.DRAW.LC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>BEN.DRAW.LC.CCY :</p>
            <p />
            <p>This represents the amount paid to the Beneficiary, BEN.DRAW.AMT, in terms of the LC Currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWING.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field displays a code to specify what type of drawing this is. </p>
            <p>This code identifies which kind of Drawing is being made under the L/C, and will impact the kind of processing done. The following types can be entered for a new drawing: </p>
            <p>AC - Acceptance (Usance credits) </p>
            <p>DP - Deferred Payment (Usance credits) </p>
            <p>RP - Release Payment </p>
            <p>SP - Sight Payment </p>
            <p>CO - L/C Collection </p>
            <p>The following types can only be entered as a change to an existing drawing: </p>
            <p>CC - Collection Chase </p>
            <p>CR - Collection Rejection </p>
            <p>FR - Final Rejection </p>
            <p>MA - Matured Acceptance </p>
            <p>MD - Matured Deferred Payment. </p>
            <p>RD - Registration of Documents</p>
            <p>DC - Document Checking</p>
            <p>AD-Amendment to drawings (only SP/MA/MD drawings can be amended using AD) </p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">SG - Shipping guarantee is issued under an import Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>Can't be created manually.</p>
            <p>Draw type can be changed to SP, AC or DP only.</p>
            <p>For Drawing types of 'AC' and 'DP', a term or usance credit is established whereby the funds will be debited and paid on the MATURITY.REVIEW date specified later. If the funds are required to be paid before this date, the Drawing can be Discounted, whereby payment is made on the Value date specified, but reimbursement is obtained on the MATURITY.REVIEW date. </p>
            <p>If 'SP' is entered, then both Payment and reimbursement is made on the VALUE.DATE specified. </p>
            <p>For 'AC' and 'DP' type drawings, once the maturity review date is reached and the drawing undergoes maturity processing, then the Drawing type will automatically change to 'MA' (From 'AC'), and 'MD' (From 'DP'), indicating that these deals are now matured. However, it is to be noted that for Export Usance Drawing  to Mature automatically, either the CONFIRM.INST in LC should hold  the value  as CONFIRM or  the Drawing must have been  discounted. In absence of  either of these the Drawing has to be manually matured. In the case of Import Usance Drawing is maturity is always automatic with an  option for the user to manually mature the same. </p>
            <p>If an authorised 'CO' is changed to a 'CC', then the system will perform chasing logic (ie. produce chase advices), and the reset the drawing type back to its original value, once authorised. </p>
            <p>When a drawing type of RP is used for an Export LC, this will generate a message (MT754) acknowledging documents were presented in accordance with the terms and conditions of the underlying credit and also a claim for reimbursement (MT742). Alternatively, an Import LC will generate the release of a payment, to the beneficiary, in the form of a Customer Transfer (MT100). </p>
            <p>A Final Rejection (FR) is normally used when the Sender considers the documents, not to be in accordance with the terms and conditions of the credit, and consequently, refuses them. The difference between drawing type FR and CR is that using type CR will generate a message denoting advice of refusal (MT734) and FR will only ever generate a letter denoting Advice of Refusal/Rejection (1734). Note that this drawing type may only be used following a Collection Rejection (CR). </p>
            <p>Amendment to Drawing (AD) is permitted to facilitate messaging activity by enabling to alter text and/or local fields. </p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">When the field REDUCE.LC.LIAB in MD.PARAMETER is set to 'Yes', 'SG' type of Drawings are created under import LC. </p>
            <p>Can't be created manually.</p>
            <p>Draw type can be changed to SP, AC or DP only.</p>
            <p>Note : Neither a type FR or RP will reduce Drawings limits. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-2 type AAA (Alpha) characters. </p>
            <p>Valid codes are: 'AC'; 'DP'; 'RP'; 'SP'; 'CO'; 'CC'; 'CR'; 'FR'; 'MA'; 'MD';'AD'. (Mandatory Input) </p>
            <p>RP may be used irrespective of the type of the underlying LC. </p>
            <p>If the type of L/C is a sight payment, then the only valid inputs to this field are:- 'SP', 'CO', 'CC', or 'CR'. </p>
            <p>If the type of L/C is a usance or term payment, then the only valid inputs to this field are:- 'AC', 'DP', 'CO', 'CC', or 'CR'. </p>
            <p>'CR' can only be entered if the drawing has been previously authorised as 'CO'. </p>
            <p>'FR' can only be entered if the drawing has previously been authorised as 'CR'. </p>
            <p>Next stage after registering documents "RD" must be "DC".</p>
            <p>Draw type "DC" can be changed to "CR","RP","SP","AC","DP" depending upon the LC type</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.PAYAMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This is the amount paid to the assignee in terms of the account currency when used with TPPAY. </p>
            <p>This is the amount to be collected by way of multiple debits when used with TPRECV.</p>
            <p>This is derived using ASSN.XRATE on ASSN.AMOUNT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically allocated.  First 12 digits made up from the Letter of Credit number input via the LETTER.OF.CREDIT application,  last two digits automatically allocated in the range 1-99. </p>
            <p>The Drawing key is made up of the L/C number plus 2 additional digits uniquely identifying the Drawing.  The format is as follows: </p>
            <p>                [LC NUMBER][NN] </p>
            <p>Where NN is automatically assigned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>14 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the presentor of the documents if they are not a customer of the bank with a valid CUSTOMER.NO.Optionally input, identifies the presentor customer. </p>
            <p>Field is mutually exclusive with PRESENTOR.CUSTNO. </p>
            <P>To generate 59F tag in MT103 and MT202C, address must be defined in following format.</P>
            <P>/1235674              - Account Number</P>
            <p>1/DAVID WARNER        - Beneficiary Name</p>
            <p>2/1000 QUARRY LAKE DR - Beneficiary Address</p>
            <p>3/US/SEATTLE          - Beneficiary Country and Town</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue         field.</p>
            <p>If entered, then PRESENTOR.CUSTNO cannot be entered.</p>
            <p>Optional Input </p>
            <p>Account number should start with '/' for 59F format</p>
            <p>First line should start with '1/' (ie) name of beneficiary for 59F format</p>
            <p>Address is not mandatory. It may or maynot have occurrence with '2/' for 59F format.</p>
            <p>If address is inputted then country code is mandatory (ie)'3/' for 59F format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.CREDIT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Generated Field.</p>
            <p>Identifies the type of Trade Finance Contract from the LC.TYPES file. The type will identify whether this is an Import/Export, Confirmed/Unconfirmed etc... LC. For DRAWINGS, this is automatically defaulted from the Letter of Credit file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input. System Generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONF.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to enter free format text to be placed on the Drawing messages/advices. </p>
            <p>The value entered here will be used in the generation of Drawing covering letters to indicate any special instructions for the receiver, i.e. 'Keep Bill of Exchange for Presentation' </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field.</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>PAY.LCCY</p>
            <p>Presently not in use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.SEND.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Part of a multi-value set. This field displays the date the related message was sent.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMBURSE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field is used to hold the actual reimbursement amount, plus any charges applicable, debited from the Drawdown Account. </p>
            <p>This field will be updated by the system when the debit from the Drawdown Account is made. On value date for 'SP' drawings, and on the Maturity Review date for 'AC' and 'DP' drawings. </p>
            <p>The amount will be the full document amount or equivalent if a foreign exchange rate has been input, expressed in the currency of the Drawdown account, plus any charge amounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a         decimal point.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.FORWARD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the next instalment schedule date to process when instalment due date falls on a holiday.</p>
            <p>Accepted options are C - Calendar , P - Previous working day , N - Next working day.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Applicable only when INST.FQY is defined.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.WITH.REIMB</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the party funds are to be paid to when different from Presentor or Beneficiary. </p>
            <p>Mutually exclusive with PAYPARTY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.').</p>
            <p>If entered, then PAYPARTY cannot be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid customer on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATED.DRAWING</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Contains the last two digits of the drawing ID (LCNUMBER) to uniquely identify the charge for this drawing. If the charge has been taken by deduction from the payment amount or addition to the reimbursement amount, then the digits here will be appended by a '-' and the last two digits of the drawing ID. </p>
            <p>When charges are input or defaulted for a new drawing, the value here will initially contain the last two digits of the Drawing ID. If during validation, the charge entries are made by deducting the charge amount from the payment amount, or by adding the charge amount to the reimbursement amount, then the drawing number here will be appended by a '-' which will indicate that the charge has been taken by this drawing. </p>
            <p>If any charges are outstanding on the LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file, then these will also be taken if a payment or a reimbursement made on this drawing, and the CHRG.REL.DRAW will indicate the above mentioned two digits and '-'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>5 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Associated multivalue         field</p>
            <p>his is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not currently in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVERS.CORR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the correspondent bank for the receiver bank (ie the bank servicing the account held by the receiver bank in the currency of the credit amount).</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNTRF.PORT.CHK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>UNTRF.PORT.CHK </p>
            <p>Presently not in use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT202.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TENOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the tenor to calculate ad-hoc instalment due date from the INST.BASE.DATE viz. 30 days from BL date, etc.</p>
            <p>Associated multi value field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVIS.SCHEDULE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The fields from ACTIVITY.SENT to field CLASS.SCHED are associated multi-values. This field will retain the activity and its schedule. It will also reflect the DRAW.SCHEDULES table, which will be used by End of Day process to trigger off message production. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LD.AMRT.DTE.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Load amount accrued to date, if the drawing has been discounted and a Load amount/rate specified, expressed in local currency. The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>Every time the Load amount is accrued in the end of day, this field is automatically updated to show the total amount accrued to date, converted to local currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  1-14 (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.CHARGED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field displays a code used to identify from whom the charge is to be taken. For all charges within the multivalue set, this can be different. Some of the charges can be levied against the Opener, others against the Beneficiary, and some against the Third Party. </p>
            <p>SIGHT DRAWINGS (SP) </p>
            <p>- If party charges is O, CHARGE.STATUS will be defaulted to 8 if no charge account is input or if the charge account is equal to REIMBURSE.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>- If party charged is B, CHARGE.STATUS will be defaulted to 9, if no charge account is input or if the charge account is equal to PAYMENT.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>- If party charged is CO, only reimburse account is defaulted as charge account, with an option for User to override with that of Payment account and the status should be 10 only.</p>
            <p>- If party charged is CB, only payment account is defaulted as charge account, with an option for User to override with that of Reimburse account and the status should be 10 only.</p>
            <p>ACCEPTANCE, DEFERRED PAYMENT (AC/DP) DRAWINGS</p>
            <p>- If party charged is O, CHARGE.STATUS will be defaulted to 12, if no charge account is input or if the charge account is equal to REIMBURSE.ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>- If party charged is B, CHARGE.STATUS will be defaulted to 11, if no charge account is input or if the charge account is equal to PAYMENT.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>- If party charged is CO, only reimburse account is defaulted as charge account, with an option for User to override with that of the Payment account and and the status should be 13 only.</p>
            <p>- If party charged is CB, only payment account is defaulted as charge account, with an option for User to override with that of the Reimburse account and the status should be only 13 only.</p>
            <p>If the charge account input is an account other than reimburse or pay account, then PARTY.CHARGED WILL BE NULL. and the operator has to input 2 or leave it at null status, depending on the requirement whether to collect the charges now or later.</p>
            <p>NOTE: This signifies the Discount Rate applicable on the Contract for the period mentioned in this associated multi-value set.</p>
            <p>If party charged is (CO), it will be understood as Debit plus charges and pay plus charges. If party charged is CB, it will be understood as Debit less charges and pay less charges.</p>
            <p>If party charged is (T), Then the status can either be null or 2. The third party account in LC needs to be set, if party charged T is to be invoked in DRAWINGS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>(O)pener, (T)hird Party, (B)eneficiary, (CO)rrespondent         charges to the opener or (CB)-Correspondent charges to         the beneficiary. Associated multi-value field. Default         from CHARGES.FROM field above.</p>
            <p>If 'T' is specified, then THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO must be set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether charges are to be waived on this Drawing. If this field is set to 'Y' then all charges relating to this Drawing will be waived, ie. no default charges will be added. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y'es or 'N'o. Default 'N'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during input of the Drawing.  The field will be updated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>During the validation of a Drawing contract, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly, for instance,  that there is no limit set up for the customer. </p>
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the override, the full text of the actual override message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field. </p>
            <p>For example, if the user inputs a deal, then when the Drawing is validated a warning bell will sound and a message will appear at the foot of the screen which reads : </p>
            <p>          'NO LIMIT DEFINED FOR CUSTOMER' </p>
            <p>This will draw the users attention to the override entry(s).  After checking and making any necessary amendments the user then approves the transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated. Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMB.AMT.DOC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>REIMB.AMT.DOC.CCY</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field will hold the equivalent of the document amount in the currency of the reimbursement account. When the document currency and the DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT are of the same currency, this will hold the reimbursement amount.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1  Standard Amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account from which the commission amount has to be collected.  Must be a valid account not necessarily in contract currency.</p>
            <p>Validation:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory when commission code is defined and commission is collected.</p>
                <p value="2">Input not allowed when commission is claimed.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.REL.LC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the local currency equivalent of the amount of provision released against this letter of credit as a result of the drawing. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the tax component for current schedule.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INST.PAY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ad-hoc instalment date to be processed.</p>
            <p>Associated multi value field.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">User can input either INST.BASE.DATE and TENOR or INST.PAY.DATE.</p>
                <p value="2">If INST.BASE.DATE and TENOR are defined, system will calculate and update this field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.NETTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether proportionate provision amount  released is to be netted with Drawings amount at the time of settlement of Drawings.</p>
            <p>Drawings payment entries will be netted only when Drawings and Credit provision account currencies are the same.</p>
            <p>Override message will be generated when these currencies differ and PROV.NETTING field value will be changed to "NO" when override is accepted.</p>
            <p>Example:</p>
            <p>LC Amount USD	              100,000; Provision Percentage     20%; Provision Amount	USD 20,000</p>
            <p>Drawings Amount	USD 50,000; Provision Netting	Yes.</p>
            <table class="TableStyle-Basic" style="mc-table-style: url('../../../Resources/TableStyles/TemenosTables.css');" cellspacing="0">
                <col style="width: 66px;" class="Column-Column1" />
                <col style="width: 177px;" class="Column-Column1" />
                <col style="width: 116px;" class="Column-Column1" />
                <tbody>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1" data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Dr</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Credit Provision Account</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">USD 10,000</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1" data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Dr</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">	Drawdown  Account</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">
                            <p>USD 40,000</p>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1" data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">
                        <td class="BodyB-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: right;">Cr</td>
                        <td class="BodyB-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: right;">Payment Account</td>
                        <td class="BodyA-Column1-Body1">
                            <p style="text-align: right;">USD 50,000</p>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </tbody>
            </table>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Defaulted from PROV.NETTING field in LC.PARAMETERS. User can amend the defaulted value.</p>
            <p>Applicable only for LC's with provision.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTICIPANT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the Participant who is part of the Syndicated LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be existing participant of the Tranche.</p>
            <p>System defaulted field</p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the rate at which the commission is to be calculated.</p>
            <p> If the user inputs a rate in this field then the default commission calculation will be ignored and the commission will be calculated at this rate. User input field.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Not allowed when FIXED.COMM.AMT is INPUT.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used either to hold the broker involved with the deal or will contain the method by which the deal was agreed, hence input to this field must be the key to a valid record on either the BROKER file or the FX.DEAL.METHOD table. </p>
            <p>An agent is a broker or middle man bewteen the import and exporter and earns his fee or commission from the Letter of Credit Drawings amount either as a percentage or flat amount. This flat amount is paid to the agent by the issuing bank at time of drawing. </p>
            <p>When the BROKER.CODE is changed the remaining broker fields are cleared. </p>
            <p>When a FX.DEAL.METHOD is entered the broker fields are cleared and become NOINPUT fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on either the BROKER file or the FX.DEAL.METHOD file.</p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.EXPIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether usance drawings need to be matured manually or automatically on maturity date.</p>
            <p>If AUTO.EXPIRY is set to "YES", Usance Drawings will be automatically matured on MATURITY.REVIEW.DATE.</p>
            <p>If AUTO.EXPIRY is set to "NO", Usance Drawings must be manually matured.</p>
            <p>Validations Rules</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Valid input - YES or NO.</p>
                <p value="2">Allowed only for "AC" or "DP" Drawing types.</p>
                <p value="3">Default value - NO</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the local currency equivalent of the brokerage defined in BROKER.AMOUNT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.LC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>PAY.LC.CCY</p>
            <p>Presently not in use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.MONTHS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate to be applied between commission (contract) currency and commission account currency.  If not input by the user, system to default the appropriate buy/sell rate from the currency table.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional field.</p>
                <p value="2">Not allowed when LC currency and commission account currency are same.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used by Sight drawings where user can specify a different debit value date from the credit value date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
            <p>Optional input field only if DRAWING.TYPE is SP.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MKTG.EXCH.PROFIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not currently in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the delivery keys used for the generation of Drawing advices/ documents/payments from the Electronic Delivery System. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.TERMS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether the settlement is to be made in multiple instalments.</p>
            <p>Valid options - INSTALMENT or NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate used between the document currency (DRAW.CURRENCY) and the Assignment/Multi-Debit account currency. </p>
            <p> User Input.</p>
            <p>Default is the mid rate of the LC market.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.BOOKED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field displays the exchange rate quoted by the treasury department to the trade finance department (ie excluding department spread).</p>
            <p>When the document currency &lt;DRAW.CURRENCY&gt; and debit account currency &lt;DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT.CURRENCY&gt; differ, the user will be able to insert an exchange rate to be applied &lt;DEBIT.CUST.RATE&gt;. This &lt;DEBIT.CUST.RATE&gt; can be derived from the departmental spread indicated in &lt;RATE.SPREAD&gt; and the treasury rate displayed in this &lt;RATE.BOOKED&gt; field.</p>
            <p>Default calculated from currency table, using current mid market spot rate.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal         characters). (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Input to this field is only allowed if the drawdown         account is in a different currency to the draw currency.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.LCCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the local currency equivalent of the tax amount.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>When the deal is input, the local currency equivalent of the document amount will be calculated by the system using the mid market spot rate in effect at the time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  Standard Amount Format.  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is designed to cater for delivery schedules in USANCE payment transactions (AC, or DP). It will allow the user to override number of days before maturity review sending the message based on message class. The default value will be from EB.ACTIVITY if specified. Otherwise, it will default from LC.PARAMETERS. </p>
            <p>In the export usance payment scenario, the user will be able to set different schedule for sending Advice of Payment (MT754) and Reimbursement Claim (MT742), since the system will generate two different activities, whereby each message can be attached to different activity.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.NEGOTIATE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>When a drawing record is created through DRAW.NEGOTIATE application, the ID of the DRAW.NEGOTIATE will be stored here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHGS.CLAIM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the charges claimed by the Sender, if any.</p>
            <p>Any code used in this field must be between slashes and must appear at the beginning of a line.</p>
            <p>Narrative text must not begin with a slash and, if used, must begin on a new line and be the last</p>
            <p>information in the field.</p>
            <p>This can be used as TAG73 of MT734.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid SWIFT.CODE.WORDS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>1-6       lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCREPANT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts all valid Discrepant codes that exists in the DR.DISCREPANT.TYPE table. Once selected, all the definitions of that Discrepant </p>
            <p>type applies to the DRAWING. In an Export LC, this field is used when any discrepancy is found at the time of presentation of documents </p>
            <p>by the Presentor.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Allowed only when Draw type is  CO .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the bank which is the ultimate reeceiver of the funds transferred by the sending bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.WITH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify where the funds, by order of the Beneficiary/Remitting Bank are to be remitted.</p>
            <p>Used when the payment is to be effected to a bank, if defaults are not applicable.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 lines of 1-35 type S (Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Optional     input)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.BANK.REIMB</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the party funds are to be paid to when different from Presentor or Beneficiary. </p>
            <p>Mutually exclusive with PAYPARTY.CUSTNO. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.         Multivalue field.</p>
            <p>If entered then PAYPARTY.CUSTNO cannot be entered.</p>
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the value date for drawing entries. Can be future or back valued. </p>
            <p>The date entered here will be the date that CRF, Statement, and Category entries will be generated for this L/C. If the date specified is in the future, then the end of day batch of this date will generate the required entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date Format. Default to Today.</p>
            <p>Cannot be greater than the Maturity Review date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMB.AMT.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field holds the local currency equivalent of the amount debited to drawdown account using DEBIT.CUST.RATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.ADVICE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used to hold the date maturity advices are produced. </p>
            <p>Maturity advices are produced for drawing types 'AC' and 'DP', the number of working days prior to the maturity review date as specified on the currency file for the country the advices are to be sent to. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Type DD (Standard date format in range 1000 - 2049).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHORISER</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the code name of the authoriser of the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.1ST.COPIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the number of copies of the document, defined in DOCUMENT.CODE above, that are to be sent in the first post to the opening bank/applicant under cover of the Documentary Remittance letter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNDER.RESERVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Applicable for Letter of Credit collection ('CO') drawings, when the documents are sent on a collection basis, because of discrepancies, but the drawing is paid to the benefiary "under reserve". </p>
            <p>This field indicates if payment for the drawing is made under reserve which enables funds paid to the beneficiary to be claimed back by the bank in the event that the documentation is refused by Opening Bank/Applicant due to discrepancies. </p>
            <p>This can only be entered if the drawing type is 'CO' and is an Export L/C, Payment will be effected on the value date of the drawing. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'Y' or 'N'. Default 'N'</p>
            <p>Only allowed for drawing type 'CO', and Export L/C's.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.2ND.COPIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the number of copies of the document, defined in DOCUMENT.CODE above, that are to be sent in the second post. </p>
            <p>For the document identified in DOCUMENT.CODE above, this field, if entered, will specify the number of copies being sent to opening bank/applicant under cover of the Documentary Remittance letter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 type A (Alphanumeric) characters </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the method of payment for the drawing. </p>
            <p>Used to determine which payment method is to be used in order to effect payment to the Beneficiary for Export L/C's, or the Negotiating Bank or Reimbursing bank for Import L/C's. Valid codes are: </p>
            <p />
            <p>N - Pay through a Nostro account</p>
            <p>BP - Issue a Bankers Payment drawn on a Nostro account.</p>
            <p>CH - Issue a Cheque, drawn on a Nostro account</p>
            <p>IT - Pay to an Internal Account </p>
            <p>If the method chosen is 'N', then payment will be made via a Nostro account, entered in the field below PAYMENT.ACCOUNT, with advices. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'N' or 'BP' or 'CH' or 'IT'. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input in this field signifies that Tiered system of calculating Interest rate is needed. Any valid currency can be input and the system uses this currency along with the value in DISC.EFF.DATE field to fetch the rates from the PERIODIC.INTEREST table.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid currency from the CURRENCY table.</p>
            <p>INTEREST.KEY should have been defined in the Parameter.</p>
            <p>Valid only for DRAW.TYPES AC/DP/SP.</p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNCONF.LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>UNCONF.LIMIT.REF: </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.DRAW.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the &lt;BEN.DRAW.AMT&gt; expressed in terms of local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Acting as part of the delivery multivale set, this field provides the user with the ability to decide whether to send or withhold sending the delivery of any message produced under the contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options available are (Y)es - Send Message or (N)o - Do         Not Send Message</p>
            <p>Default is (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.DR.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field</p>
            <p>Same as charges debit account in the charge multivalue set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.AMT.LC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field contains the document amount expressed in the currency of the L/C contract. </p>
            <p>When the deal is input, the L/C currency equivalent of the document amount will be calculated by the system using the mid market spot rate in effect at the time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Generated. 1-14 (Standard Amount Format)         characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the commission code applied for the period band.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Associated multi value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.AMT.LC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participant share in document amount expressed in terms of LC currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECV.CORR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the correspondent bank for the receiver bank (i.e. the bank servicing the account held by the receiver bank in the currency of the credit amount).</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LD.AMORT.TO.DTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Load amount accrued to date, if the drawing has been discounted, and a load amount/rate specified.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>Every time the load amount is accrued in the end of day, this field is automatically updated to show the total amount accrued to date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  1-14 (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>OTHER.CHARGES </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allowed if DISCOUNT.RATE or DISCOUNT.AMOUNT is present. This field together with DISCOUNT.RATE gives the total rate that the Document amount is to be discounted by which should not exceed 100%. </p>
            <p>If this field is entered, then payment will be made to the beneficiary, on the value date of the drawing, for the document amount minus the discount amount calculated from the discount rate entered above, and the load amount calculated from the rate entered here, if the Discount Party Charged is Beneficiary. Any charges for the account of the beneficiary will be deducted the net payment amount (i.e. document amount less discount and  load amounts). </p>
            <p>Similarly, if the reimburse were to be claimed from the Opener, the same is done for the document amount plus the discount amount calculated from the discount rate entered above, and the load amount calculated from the rate entered here, if the Discount Party Charged is Opener. </p>
            <p>The load amount will be accrued over the life of the drawing, at the frequency specified in the LC.PARAMETERS file, separately from the discount amount. </p>
            <p>Drawings can be discounted in respect of Export/Import Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>If the user wishes to enter a load amount rather than a load rate, then this can be performed by entering a value in the LOAD.AMT field below.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal         characters). (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if the DRAWING.TYPE is 'AC', or 'DP' and       DISCOUNT.RATE or         DISCOUNT.AMT has been entered.</p>
            <p>If entered, then LOAD.AMT cannot be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PCT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not currently in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.INTMD.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to specify an intermediary bank through which funds are to be routed.</p>
            <p>If this field is entered, then a payment instruction will be generated to the Nostro payment account, instructing them to route the funds through this account, to the ACCOUNT.WITH bank identified below.</p>
            <p><strong><p>Validation Rules:</p></strong>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-35 type S (Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. -         can be free format name of intermediary bank or a         customer id from the customer file. (Optional Input).</p>
            <p>If entered, then ACCOUNT.WITH must be entered.</p>
            <p>The Intermediary bank must not be the same as the         advising bank, the issuing bank, the third party bank, or         the advise thru bank.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.TAKEOVER</field>
<desc>
            <p>When set to yes then no delivery will be produced.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHGS.DEDUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the charges which have been deducted, by the Sender of the message, from the total amount advised.</p>
            <p>One or more of the following codes may be used, followed by the currency code and amount:</p>
            <p>AGENT Agent's commission</p>
            <p>TELECHAR Teletransmission charges</p>
            <p>COMM Our commission</p>
            <p>CORCOM Our correspondent's commission</p>
            <p>DISC Commercial discount</p>
            <p>INSUR Insurance premium</p>
            <p>POST Our postage</p>
            <p>STAMP Stamp duty</p>
            <p>WAREHOUS Wharfing and warehouse</p>
            <p>Any code used in this field must be between slashes and must appear at the beginning of a line.</p>
            <p>Narrative text must not begin with a slash and, if used, must begin on a new line and be the last</p>
            <p>information in the field.</p>
            <p>This is used to map to Tag 71B of  MT742, MT750, MT752 and MT754.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid SWIFT.CODE.WORDS with MESSAGE.TYPE as 71B.</p>
            <p>1-6 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">Holds message types of all inward messages received.</p>
        <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">For example, if inward MT754 message is received, then value 'MT754' will be stored in this field.</p>
        <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">Associated multi value with INWARD.MSG.REF. System maintained field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDITIONAL.DOCS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to define a free format document name that is to be sent under cover of the Documentary Remittance letter but which has not been pre-defined on the LC.ADVICE.TEXT file (See &lt;DOCUMENT.CODE&gt; above). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field. </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the code name of the inputter of the contract.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FURTHER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field further identifies the purpose of  MT752 and is mapped to Tag 23.</p>
            <p>One of the following codes must be used:</p>
            <p>ACCEPT Conveys an authorization to accept a draft.</p>
            <p>DEBIT Conveys an authorization to debit the account of the issuing bank.</p>
            <p>NEGOTIATE Conveys an authorization to negotiate the documents with discrepancies in those cases where the original credit provides no specific reimbursement instructions or payment provisions.</p>
            <p>REIMBURSE Conveys an authorization to the presenting bank to claim reimbursement.</p>
            <p>REMITTED Is used to pay the presenting bank.</p>
            <p>SEE72 Conveys an authorization and/or payment which is a mixture of the above, or a special version of one of them and the conditions are explained in field 72.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid SWIFT.CODE.WORDS with MESSAGE.TYPE as 23.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13,DOCTYPES.Helptext">This field holds the inward delivery reference for the corresponding message type.</p>
        <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13,DOCTYPES.Helptext">For example, in R20120828160574535800, 'R' identifies an inward message.</p>
        <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13,DOCTYPES.Helptext">Associated multi value with INWARD.MSG.TYPE. System maintained field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value entered here will be spread (number of days from value date to maturity date) used in calculation of a Discount/Load amount.  This value is calculated by the system. </p>
            <p>If a value is entered, then the formula to calculate the discount amount from the discount rate will be calculated as: </p>
            <p>                           Discount Rate       Spread        Discount Amount =  ----------------  *  -------                                  100            Basis </p>
            <p>Where: </p>
            <p>Discount Rate   - Value entered in DISCOUNT.RATE Basis           - Day basis from L/C contract. Spread          - (Maturity Review Date - Value Date) + NO.OF.DAYS, which                   is calculated by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 numeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Value can only be entered if Discount Rate is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TREASURY.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an exchange rate between the document currency and the credit account currency.</p>
            <p>This is the rate quoted by the treasury department to the trade finance department excluding departmental spread.</p>
            <p>The department spread will be accepted in CUSTOMER.SPREAD field. The exchange rate including the rate spread will be customer credit rate and will be shown in CREDIT.CUST.RATE field.</p>
            <p>THE CREDIT.CUST.RATE will be applied between the document currency and the credit account currency (DRAW.CURRENCY and PAYMENT.ACCOUNT.CURRENCY) if they differ.</p>
            <p>Default calculated from currency table, using current mid market spot rate.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal         characters) (Optional Input).</p>
            <p>Input to this field is only allowed if the payment         account is in a different currency to the draw currency.</p>
            <p>Mainly used in export transactions, when the exporter's         credit account is in a different currency to the document         currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field</p>
            <p>Date and Time of input of data.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the corresponding charge code for tax  defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Associated multivalue field associated with fields TAX.CODE through to TAX.DATE</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COVERED.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the portion of the drawing amount for which provision was held. This is system generated and calculated based on the provision percentage displayed in the letter of credit file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the Internal Bank ID number</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.AMT.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field</p>
            <p>This field holds the local currency equivalent of the amount credited to payment account using CREDIT.CUST.RATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the tax amount in the currency of the account that the tax is taken from.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>When the tax is taken from an account that  is in a different currency to the tax currency (TAX.CCY),  then this field is used to hold the amount that was actually debited, and will be used for positions update.  The field is automatically updated when the tax is taken from the account using the current market mid spot rate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  Standard Amount Format.  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINT.CHGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field when set to YES will bring charges with charge status 11,12,13 from LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES to the DRAWINGS record. Only the field CHARGE.XCHG can be amended for the maintained charges.</p>
            <p>The usage is envisaged when charges  are taken in a currency different from that of the Charge Account Currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Charges can be maintained only for 'AC' or 'DP' Drawings.</p>
            <p>Additional charges are not allowed when the value is set to  'YES'.</p>
            <p>Valid inputs are YES or NO (with NULL  representing NO).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERDUE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the contract is overdue, then this field identifies the status of the underlying PAYMENT.DUE contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MKTG.EXCH.PROFIT.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field</p>
            <p>Profit on account of customer spread and or rate spread which is due to the trade finance department. This will be accounted in PL category 53006, as profit or loss.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHASE.REPLY</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHASE.REPLY </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the exchange rate used between the provision debit account and the provision credit account. User input.</p>
            <p>Default is the mid rate of LC.MARKET.</p>
            <p>If debit account and credit account are of the same currency, then the exchange rate is 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>754.CHGS.CLAIM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify any charges which have been added to the amount</p>
            <p>paid/accepted/negotiated.</p>
            <p>One or more of the following codes may be used:</p>
            <p>ACCPTCOM Acceptance commission.</p>
            <p>ADVCOM Advising commission.</p>
            <p>AMNDCOM Amendment commission.</p>
            <p>CONFCOM Confirmation commission.</p>
            <p>CORCOM Correspondent charges.</p>
            <p>DEFCOM Deferred payment commission.</p>
            <p>DSCRPCOM Discrepancies commission.</p>
            <p>HANDLCOM Handling commission.</p>
            <p>INTEREST Any interest including discount charges.</p>
            <p>MISC Miscellaneous.</p>
            <p>NEGCOM Negotiation commission.</p>
            <p>NOTFCOM Notification commission.</p>
            <p>PAYCOM Payment commission.</p>
            <p>POST Postal/Courier charges.</p>
            <p>PREADCOM Preadvice commission.</p>
            <p>SEE72 Additional details are provided in field 72.</p>
            <p>SEE77A Additional details are provided in field 77A.</p>
            <p>STAMP Stamp duty.</p>
            <p>TELECHAR Teletransmission charges.</p>
            <p>Any code used in this field must be between slashes and must appear at the beginning of a line.</p>
            <p>Narrative text must not begin with a slash and, if used, must begin on a new line and be the last</p>
            <p>information in the field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid SWIFT.CODE.WORDS with MESSAGE.TYPE as 754.</p>
            <p>1-6 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.       </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines the frequency at which the commission is to be collected or claimed.  The first scheduled date must be the value date.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency field.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Only monthly frequency allowed (M01, M02, etc.).</p>
                <p value="2">Not allowed when PERIODIC.COMMISSION is defined with 'For every Additional Period'.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYPARTY.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the customer number of the pay party.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.').</p>
            <p>Must be a valid customer on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPTO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of days for which the commission is calculated for the associated period band.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Associated sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.WITH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify where the funds, by order of the Beneficiary/Remitting Bank are to be remitted. </p>
            <p>Used when the payment is to be effected to a bank, if defaults are not applicable. </p>
            <p>For Import L/C's, this will be used to define the either the Reimbursement Banks (THIRD.PARTY.BANK) bank to credit, or the paying/ negotiating bank payment will be made to. </p>
            <p>For Export L/C's, this will be the remitting bank in accordance with the beneficiaries instructions, payment is to be made. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 lines of 1-35 type S (Uppercase alpha or numeric)         characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.AC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Currency of the account where the assignment proceeds are Credited/Debited.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.LC.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be updated with YES when charges are defaulted from LC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHILD.DRAWS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not currently in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANUAL.MATURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where present, this field holds the date on which the Drawing was manually matured, and as such is only applicable to those drawings which have been modified to a drawing type of either MA or MD by the user. </p>
            <p>For all other drawing types, and where the drawing has matured during the end of day processing, this field will be left blank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASS.SCHED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field retains the message class corresponding to ADVIS.SCHEDULE. This field is a copy of MSG.CLASS.NO field. The system will determine which class, or activity and when the messages are going to be generated at the time of input, and update the classes to their corresponding activity from EB.ADV.NO and MSG.CLASS.NO respectively.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a no-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the amount of brokerage to be credit to the broker account specified in the broker currency defined above. </p>
            <p>If a brokerage amount has been entered above, then this field will identify the amount to be credited to the broker account.  If no input is made a defualt will be calculated from the brokerage using the current mid market exchange rates.  If the brokerage is specified in the same currency as the broker currency then the brokeraeg will be copied to this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field, expressed in terms of the BROKER.CCY.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed when a broker code and a broker currency has been defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the charge amount in the currency of the account that the charge is taken from.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>When the charge is taken from an account that  is in a different currency to the charge currency (CHARGE.CURRENCY), then this field is used to hold the amount that was actually debited, and will be used for positions update.  The field is automatically updated when the charge is taken from the account using the current market mid spot rate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System generated.  Standard Amount Format.  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INST.FQY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the frequency between the instalments at regular intervals. </p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Only monthly frequency (M01, M02, etc.) is allowed.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMBURSE.SENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
            <p>This field holds the dates of the reimbursements sent (MT754, MT742).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.CR.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The credit account where the assignment proceeds are to be credited. Must be a valid account on account file.</p>
            <p>When used with  TPRECV this field represents the  multi-debit account.</p>
            <p>Can be NOSTRO, Internal or Customer account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the account where funds are to be paid to under this drawing. </p>
            <p>The account which will be credited on either the value date or maturity review date, depending on drawing type, for the payment in respect of the drawing. </p>
            <p>If the payment method entered above is either 'BP' (Bankers payment) or 'CH' (Cheque), then this field will be automatically updated by the system to indicate the account to be used. This will be set up on the LC.PARAMETERS file as 'B.P.ISSUED.ACC' and 'CHEQUES.ISSUE.ACC'. </p>
            <p>For drawing types 'AC', 'DP', this account will be credited on the Maturity Review date in respect of payment, unless the drawing is being discounted, in which case it will be credited on the value date. </p>
            <p>For drawing type 'SP', this account will be credited on the Value date in respect of payment. </p>
            <p>For drawing type 'CO' with 'UNDER.RESERVE' set to 'YES', then this account will be credited on the value date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-16 Mnemonic characters relating to a Customer Account         or a Nostro Account, or any other account. Default from         Payment Method (see below).</p>
            <p>Mandatory input for Drawing types 'AC', 'DP', 'SP', and         'CO' with UNDER.RESERVE set to 'YES'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the account where funds are to be received from under this drawing. </p>
            <p>The account which will be debited on either the value date or maturity review date, depending on drawing type, in reimbursement of funds paid to the beneficiary of the drawing. </p>
            <p>If this field is not entered, then a default will be found from the parent L/C contract. For Import L/C's, this default will come from the APPLICANT.ACC field of the L/C. For Export L/C's, the default will come from the ISSUING.BANK.ACC field of the L/C. If these fields were not entered, and this drawing involves an actual payment, (i.e. drawing types 'AC', 'D',or 'SP'), then a mandatory input is required. </p>
            <p>For drawing types 'AC', 'DP', this account will be debited on the Maturity Review date in respect of reimbursement. </p>
            <p>For drawing type 'SP', this account will be debited on the Value date in respect of reimbursement. The currency of this account need not be the same as the currency of the drawing. If this is the case, the system will automatically calculate the amount to be debited (see RATE.BOOKED above). </p>
            <p>If the Drawing were linked to Shipping Guarantee, then drawdown account will be consider based on Provision netting field</p>
            <p>If Provision Netting is 'NO' - Irrespective of the account given in Drawdown Account, the Credit Provision Account of the MD is debited to the extent of Provision. For the remaining amount, the Cover Account is debited. The Drawdown account is used only for collecting charges.</p>
            <p>If Provision Netting is'YES' - Credit provision account of the MD is debited to the extent of provision. For the remaining amount, the drawdown account is debited.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-16 Mnemonic characters relating to a Customer Account         or a Nostro Account, or any other account. Default from         L/C (see below). Mandatory input depending upon type.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input for drawing types 'AC', 'DP', or 'SP'.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENTOR.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the presentor's reference; for use on drawing messages/advices. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10 type S (Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Only allowed if PRESENTOR or PRESENTOR.CUSTNO are         present.</p>
            <p>Does not permit SWIFT prohibited characters such as " / ".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the code of the tax table which has been used when calculating tax on charges and/or commission. The field does not require any operator input as it is obtained from the relevant commission or charges table. </p>
            <p>Commission/charges in all instances is charged to the customer on the relevant commission/charge payment dates.  No accrual will be performed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  2 Numeric characters.  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERDRAW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
            <p>The amount that this letter of credit is overdrawn. </p>
            <p>If the letter of credit is not overdrawn then this field will be zero. </p>
            <p>An overdrawn letter of credit is one where the total of drawings exceeds the LC.AMOUNT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input. System generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT796.ANSWER</field>
<desc>
            <p>When MT750 - 'Advice of Discrepancy' is received, rejection of discrepancy must be conveyed via MT796. This field is mapped to 'tag 76' of MT796.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Max characters allowed - 6 lines with 35 characters for each line (6*35).</p>
            <p>Allowed only when inward MT750 is received.</p>
            <p>Allowed only for CR type of drawings.</p>
            <p>Mandatory for CR type of drawings when inward MT750 is received.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the date from which discount will be effective. Discount and load amount will be calculated from this date instead of value date. Applicable only for discounted drawings( SP/AC/DP Drawings only).</p>
            <p>This field accepts input such as 10D or 1M indicating the number of days from the Value date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date Format.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />Defaults to Value     Date.   <p /><p>Cannot     be less than Value Date.</p><p /><p>Cannot     be greater than Maturity Review Date.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESSEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the user to divert a particular message type to another (third) party.</p>
            <p>The user has a number of options:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Simple insertion of a name or address. This will re-route         the message in PRINT format to the named party.</p>
            <p>The code 'TX-' followed by a telex number. This will         re-route the message by TELEX to the number detailed.</p>
            <p>The code 'SW-' followed by a S.W.I.F.T. code. This will         re-route the message by SWIFT to the respective bank.</p>
            <p>The code 'C-' followed by a valid customer number or         mnemonic. This will re-route the message in PRINT format         to the customer indiated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>50 Alphanumeric character field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participants share in document amount for drawings under Syndicated LC.</p>
            <p>For confirmed LC's, PART.AMOUNT = DOCUMENT.AMOUNT * Participant share defined in LC.</p>
            <p> For Partially confirmed LC's, PART.AMOUNT= CONFIRMATION.AMOUNT* Participant share defined in LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPTO.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount on which the 'CSN.RATE' is applied to arrive at the 'CSN.AMT'.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Associated sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.ACCT.WITH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to identify where the funds by order of the Beneficiary/Remitting Bank are to be remitted.</p>
            <p>Used when the payment is to be effected to a bank, if defaults are not applicable.</p>
            <p>For Export/Advising L/C's, this will be the remitting bank in accordance with the beneficiary's instructions, payment is to be made.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 lines of 1-35 type S (Uppercase alpha or numeric)         characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPENING.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the type of commission or charge to be levied on the Drawing transaction being processed. The charge or commission code will be entered as an eleven-character code as defined on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Multivalue field)</p>
            <p>The code must be a valid commission or charge code as         defined on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE         tables.</p>
            <p>Input is not allowed if the WAIVE.CHARGES field is set to         'Y'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the date the tax was raised. </p>
            <p>The date in this field will identify the date the tax was raised, although not necessarily taken. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  Standard Date Format.  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIS.AMORT.TO.DTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Discount amount accrued to date, if the drawing has been discounted.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>Every time the discount amount is accrued in the end of day, this field is automatically updated to show the total amount accrued to date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  1-14 (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.REL.DRG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the last two digits of the drawing ID (LCNUMBER) to uniquely identify the tax for this drawing.  If the tax has been taken by deduction from the payment amount or addition to the reimbursement amount, then the digits here will be appended by a '-' and the last two digits of the drawing ID. </p>
            <p>When charges are input or defaulted for a new drawing, the value here will initially contain the last two digits of the Drawing ID.  If during validation, the charge entries are made by deducting the charge amount from the payment amount, or by adding the charge amount to the reimbursement amount,  then the drawing number here will be appended by a '-' which will indicate that the charge has been taken by this drawing. </p>
            <p>If any charges are outstanding on the LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file, then these will also be taken if a payment or a reimbursement made on this drawing, and the CHRG.REL.DRAW (Field 10.1) will indicate the above mentioned two digits and '-'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  5 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OWN.DOCUMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the share of T24 bank for the drawings under Syndicated LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKERAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the amount of brokerage to be paid to the broker defined above. Expressed in terms of the deal currency. </p>
            <p>Input to this field may be in the form of a flat amount or a percentage. To define a percentage append the % to the rate input, and the system will calculate this percentage of the DOCUMENT.AMOUNT. </p>
            <p>If no value is entered here but a broker code is defined above, then the system will attempt to calculate a default brokerage - firstly using the percentage defined on the underlying Letter of Credit contract, and if not defined using the conditions set up on the BROKER file.  If an amount is calculated succesfully the it will be defaulted in this field, and will be expressed in the deal currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field, expressed in the DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed when a BROKER has been entered in the BROKER.CODE field.</p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Spread applied by the trade finance department on the rate quoted by the treasury department. This will be used together with RATE.BOOKED and DEBIT.CUST.RATE will be determined to debit the customer's drawdown account.</p>
            <p>Input Optional</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in the production of messages/advices. A list of the various types of documents that are commonly required under L/C's are detailed in the LC.ADVICE.TEXT file and recorded by an ID code. This field can therefore be used to display the documents which are being sent under cover of the documentary remittance letter.The full description of the document will be displayed in the field &lt;DOCUMENT.TXT&gt;.</p>
            <p>The field is associated with fields DOC.1ST.COPIES and DOC.2ND.COPIES below which indicate the post the documents will be sent in, and the number of copies. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p>Must exist in LC.ADVICE.TEXT file.</p>
            <p>If documents required under the LC are not recorded in         the LC ADVICE.TEXT file, they can be input separately in         &lt;ADDITIONAL.DOCS&gt;.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.DRAW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the amount payable by the applicant. In respect to multiple debits, the applicant may part part amount from one account and balance from the rest. </p>
            <p>The user may by way of input into this field, identifies the amount to be debited from the DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>When the amount input in this field is less than the DOCUMENT.AMOUNT, the system populates the balance in the field MULTI.DR.AMT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Amount is expressed in DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>Defaults to DOCUMENT.AMOUNT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.RECV.CORR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Correspondent bank of the receiving bank. Through nostro agent, this bank will be paid by MT202 and it will be requested to pay to the receiving bank by means of another MT 100.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the consolidation key which has been generated for this contract.  This field will be updated by the system after its first end of day has been processed.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  The first four parameters will always contain the application ID (i.e. LC), the Currency Market,  the Position Type, and the currency code (DRAW.CURRENCY).  The other parameters will default on the conditions defined in the file CONSOLIDATE.CONDS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLAUSES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the key of a record in the LC.CLAUSES file that is to be included as a clause on the documents/advices for this Drawing. </p>
            <p>Used for the creation of Drawing documents/advices, this value will be used to retrieve a clause narrative from the LC.CLAUSES file to be printed as a clause on the Documentary Remittance letter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NXT.INST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the next instalment date to be processed.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OWN.DISC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the discount share of T24 bank under Syndicated LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement. </p>
            <p>As in the majority of T24 Applications, the user is allowed to define in the Drawings file up to 999 Local elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified.  These local elements should be defined by the user where deemed necessary according to local practice. </p>
            <p>The name(s) of the new element(s), as well as the format and creation of any Drawing transactions. </p>
            <p>As defined by the user within the individual local tables. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters as defined in the local table definition for this local reference field.  Multivalue field.  (Optional or Mandatory input according to definition in LOCAL.TABLE (Ref: Utilities) for this local reference element.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACPT.TM.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Acceptance period mentioned in LC to which the DRAWING should be adjusted to. Applicable for mixed payment LCs.</p>
            <p>When mixed payment LCs are input, the operator shall be giving various time bands with the LC to indicate that each portion belongs to a different time band. As documents are received and DRAWINGS are input, the operator is required to input the time band to which this DRAWING should get appropriated.</p>
            <p>EXAMPLE: - Take a LC record with the following input.</p>
            <p>LC Record</p>
            <p>
                <table border="0" cellspacing="4" width="400">
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">DRAW.TYPE: </td>
                        <td width="20%">SP</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">PAYMENT.PCT:</td>
                        <td width="20%">50</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">PAY.PORTION: </td>
                        <td width="20%">50,000</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">ACPT.TM.BAND:</td>
                        <td width="20%">20000606</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%" />
                        <td width="20%" />
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">DRAW.TYPE</td>
                        <td width="20%">AC</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">PAYMENT.PCT</td>
                        <td width="20%">25</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">PAY.PORTION</td>
                        <td width="20%">25000</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">ACPT.TM.BAND </td>
                        <td width="20%">30</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%" />
                        <td width="20%" />
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">DRAW.TYPE</td>
                        <td width="20%">AC</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">PAYMENT.PCT</td>
                        <td width="20%">25</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">PAY.PORTION</td>
                        <td width="20%">25000</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td width="50%">ACPT.TM.BAND </td>
                        <td width="20%">60</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            </p>
            <p>Let us assume that a particular drawing is to be appropriated to the third multivalue set. In such case the ACPT.TM.BAND in DRAWING should be input as 60. This will be understood that this DRAWING is against the third multivale set in LC.</p>
            <p>For sight and acceptance LCs this will be defaulted to expiry date of the LC</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input for mixed payment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.CUST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained field.</p>
            <p>This is the resultant rate applied between the document currency and the payment account currency.</p>
            <p>Derived from TREASURY.RATE and CUSTOMER.SPREAD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.REL.DOC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the document currency equivalent of the amount of provision released against this letter of credit as a result of the drawing. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>756.BK.TO.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains additional information for the Receiver.</p>
            <p>The following code may be used:</p>
            <p>                RCB Receiver's Correspondent Bank</p>
            <p />
            <p>Any code must be between slashes and must appear at the beginning of a line.</p>
            <p>Narrative text must not begin with a slash and, if used, must begin on a new line and be the last information in the field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-6       lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid       SWIFT.CODE.WORDS with MESSAGE.TYPE  as 756.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUND.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the rounding rule that is to be applied.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULLY.UTILISED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides the user with the ability to indicate that no further drawings will be made under the letter of credit. </p>
            <p>However in the case of a Partially Confirmed Letter of Credit, if the CONF.LIAB.AMT is not reduced to Zero, this field becomes a No input field.</p>
            <p>Input is optional with the only available responses being (Y)es or (N)o.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rate applied on 'UPTO.AMT' to calculate the 'CSN.AMT'.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Associated sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.DRAW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the amount payable to the beneficiary. In respect assignments, beneficiary will receive part payment, instructing balance to be paid to assignees.</p>
            <p>This field will then be changed by the operator, to indicate the amount the beneficiary requires to receive.</p>
            <p>System will automatically calculate the difference and put the balance in TOT.ASSN.AMOUNT, when the BEN.DRAW.AMT is changed by the operator.</p>
            <p>Default is document amount. The amount is expressed in DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYPARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This multivalue field is used to identify the name and  address of the pay party IF they are not a customer of the bank.</p>
            <p>Field is mutually exclusive with PAY.PARTY.NO.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue         field.</p>
            <p>If entered, then PAY.PARTY.NO. cannot be entered.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.LCCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the local currency equivalent of the charge amount. The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>The value in this field will be the amount that is used to update the charges profit and loss account. If the charge amount is not in local currency, then this amount will be calculated when the charge is debited from an account and credited to the P/L account, using the market mid spot rate at the time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Generated. Standard Amount Format. Associated         multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.INSTRUC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables to the user to input any instructions received from the beneficiary and is linked to LC.CLAUSES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.RECV.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Receiving bank of the assignment proceeds. The assignees can have the amount with some other bank and may request the proceeds be remitted to a third bank by SWIFT or by other means. In such cases, the receiving bank is held here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during input of the Drawing. The field will be updated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>During the validation of a Drawing contract, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly, for instance, that there is no limit set up for the customer. </p>
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the override, the full text of the actual override message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field. </p>
            <p>For example, if the user inputs a deal, then when the Drawing is validated a warning bell will sound and a message will appear at the foot of the screen which reads : </p>
            <p>'NO LIMIT DEFINED FOR CUSTOMER' </p>
            <p>This will draw the users attention to the override entry(s). After checking and making any necessary amendments the user then approves the transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24         alphanumeric field. A maximum of 35 characters may be         entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTMD.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify an intermediary bank through which funds are to be routed.</p>
            <p>If this field is entered, then a payment instruction will be generated to the Nostro payment account, instructing them to route the funds through this account, to the ACCOUNT.WITH bank identified below.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-35 type S (Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Can be free format     name of intermediary bank or a customer id from the customer file. (Optional     input)   </p>
            <p>If entered, then ACCOUNT.WITH must be entered.   </p>
            <p>The Intermediary bank must not be the same as the advising bank, the     issuing bank, the third party bank, or the advise thru bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATED.RTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the calculated rate for discount.</p>
            <p>Input optional.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISP.OF.DOCS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains information regarding the disposal of the documents. It may either contain free-format text or the following code words when generating a S.W.I.F.T. MT734 message (Advise of Refusal):- </p>
            <p>        HOLD    -  Documents held at your disposal </p>
            <p>        RETURN  -  Documents being returned to you </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>May be any valid SWIFT character</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NXT.INST.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the next instalment amount to be processed.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.CUST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained field.</p>
            <p>This is the resultant rate applied between the document currency and the drawdown account currency.</p>
            <p>Derived from RATE.BOOKED and RATE.SPREAD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWDOWN.ACCT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.LIAB.RELEASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the total liability released against this letter of credit as a result of the drawing. Amount shown is in the currency of the letter of credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the currency that charges are to be levied in. This can be different from the DRAW.CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>If the field CHARGE.CURRENCY is not entered then a default currency will be selected from Drawing contract. </p>
            <p>If this field is not entered then a default currency will be selected from either the CHARGES.ACCOUNT currency from the Drawing contract, or the currency of the Drawing . If no CHARGES.ACCOUNT is entered, then the DRAW.CURRENCY is used, otherwise the CHARGES.ACCOUNT currency is used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid Currency Code or its  Numeric code. Default from currency of CHARGES.ACCOUNT         from the Drawing contract or DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>Once input, this field cannot be changed when Charges are        Maintained.</p>
            <p>Input is only allowed if a charge/commission code has         been entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not currently in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.DISCREPANCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a free text field and  is used to specify any Internal discrepancy  which the bank finds in a Documentary collection and intends to</p>
            <p> keep it for internal purposes.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Accepts 1  50 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the date the charge was raised. </p>
            <p>The date in this field will identify the date the charge was raised, although not necessarily taken. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  Standard Date format.  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is applicable only to documentary collections and indicate the date the collection should be chased. Accepts Standard date format.  </p>
            <p> Holds the Scheduled date on which a Tracer message has to be sent. If the date is some future date, then an EB.FREE.MESSAGE record is produced on authorization of the DRAWING which holds the Tracer message and relevant details of the particular transaction with the scheduled date on which it has to be sent. If the date is TODAY then the Tracer message is sent during End of Day. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory when Draw Type is 'CO'</p>
            <p />
            <p>Will get cycled only if EB.FREE.PARAMETERS is set up.  </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount assigned to the assignee in terms of document currency (DRAW.CURRENCY). </p>
            <p> The sum total of all assignments should be equal to TOT.ASSN.AMOUNT when used with the reference TPPAY.</p>
            <p>The sum total of all multiple debits should be equal to MULTI.DR.AMT when used with the reference TPRECV.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input for assignment and multiple settlements.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>202.BK.TO.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for Sender to Receiver (i.e. Sending bank to Receiving bank) Information. Any information entered into this field will appear on a S.W.I.F.T. MT202 message (General Financial Institution Transfer). </p>
            <p>It may be used to provide instructions or additional information for the Receiver, Intermediary, Account with Institution or Beneficiary Institution. </p>
            <p>This field corresponds to field 72 on S.W.I.F.T. messages, and must never be used for information for which another field is intended, or for instructions not required in a message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type         SW Multivalue field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35         characters each will be allowed. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain         a codeword followed by further information.</p>
            <p>All code words must be valid code words as defined in         S.W.I.F.T. documentation and must conform to the rules         specified. Use of invalid code words will cause a message         rejection when validated by S.W.I.F.T.</p>
            <p>Further code words and information can be entered in         subsequent multivalues, but additional information         continued on a new line must be preceded by a double         slash '//'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>202.BKBK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to enter any bank to bank information required on the corresponding MT202.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>202.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for Sender to Receiver (i.e. Sending bank to Receiving bank) Information. Any information entered into this field will appear on a S.W.I.F.T. MT202 message (General Financial Institution Transfer). </p>
            <p>It may be used to provide instructions or additional information for the Receiver, Intermediary, Account with Institution or Beneficiary Institution. </p>
            <p>This field corresponds to field 72 on S.W.I.F.T. messages, and must never be used for information for which another field is intended, or for instructions not required in a message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type SW Multivalue field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain a codeword followed by further information.</p>
            <p>All code words must be valid code words as defined in S.W.I.F.T. documentation and must conform to the rules specified. Use of invalid code words will cause a message rejection when validated by S.W.I.F.T.</p>
            <p>Further code words and information can be entered in subsequent multivalues, but additional information continued on a new line must be preceded by a double slash '//'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>742.BK.TO.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains instructions or additional information for the Receiver. Any information entered into this field will appear on a S.W.I.F.T. MT742 message (Reimbursement Claim). </p>
            <p>This field corresponds to field 72 on S.W.I.F.T. messages, and must never be used for information for which another field is intended, or for instructions not required in a message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type         SW Multivalue field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35         characters each will be allowed. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain         a codeword followed by further information.</p>
            <p>All code words must be valid code words as defined in         S.W.I.F.T. documentation and must conform to the rules         specified. Use of invalid code words will cause a message         rejection when validated by S.W.I.F.T.</p>
            <p>Further code words and information can be entered in         subsequent multivalues, but additional information         continued on a new line must be preceded by a double         slash '//'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.AMT.ACC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Imports this field contains the document amount expressed in the currency of the DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT. For Export transactions this will hold the currency equivalent of the PAYMENT.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p> The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated. 1-14 (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INST.PAY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ad-hoc instalment amount to be processed associated with INST.PAY.DATE.</p>
            <p>Associated multi value field.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Sum of all INST.PAY.AMT's must not exceed total Drawings amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code to identify the current status of the charge. Used to identify if the charge has been taken, claimed,waived or not taken. The system will update this field whenever the charge is processed and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>The codes that are used to identify various status of the charge are as follows : </p>
            <p>blank - The charge has not been taken yet </p>
            <p>1 - Charge will be taken in drawing but drawing is not authorised</p>
            <p>2 - The charge has been taken </p>
            <p>3 - The charge has been claimed </p>
            <p>4 - A claimed charge has been settled </p>
            <p>7 - Charge Unpaid Reversed </p>
            <p>8 - Charge has been taken by adding the amount to a reimbursement claim via a drawing. </p>
            <p>9 - Charge has been taken by deducting the amount from a payment via a drawing. </p>
            <p>11 - Charge will be taken by deducting the amount from a payment (status 9) at maturity</p>
            <p>12 - Charge will be taken by adding the amount to a reimbursement claim (status 8) at maturity</p>
			<p>15 - The charge has been waived. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Notes : (i) For status 3, the charge is made by debiting the CRF Claimed bucket and crediting the profit and loss account for the charge (found on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables). A claim advice is sent to the charge party. When the charge is paid the operator will manually access the LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file, where all the charge details are recorded after authorization of the L/C, update the file to indicate that the payment has been received, and the CRF Claimed bucket reimbursed. </p>
            <p>(ii) When a drawing is entered whereby payments are made or reimbursement is required, then the charge amount will be either deducted from the payment amount or added to the reimbursement amount in order to make a profit and loss entry. The charge status that was initially blank will change as applicable to charge status 8 or 9. </p>
			<p>(iii) When the charge status is 15, the related charge is considered waived and written in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES. This charge cannot be collected in the future and the related tax will not be stored in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 or 2 - digit number. Associated multivalue field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.TM.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>NEW.TM.BAND</p>
            <p>Presently not in use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the currency of the drawing. </p>
            <p>However, should the applicant / opening bank / Beneficiary wish to effect reimbursement in a currency different to that of the drawing, the exchange rate input in the field RATE.BOOKED will be used to convert the DRAW.CURRENCY into DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT.CURRENCY. If no input is made in RATE.BOOKED, the market foreign exchange rate will be defaulted and the system will automatically convert the draw currency into that of the reimbursement currency (DRAWDOWN ACCOUNT CURRENCY).</p>
            <p>Also refer help text of field RATE.SPREAD </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>CCY (Currency code e.g. GBP must be 3 characters).         Default to LC.CURRENCY. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>In the event that both the drawdown account and payment         account are different currencies to that of the drawing,         the Foreign exchange rate applicable to the drawdown         account currency and the DRAW.CURRENCY will be entered in         RATE.BOOKED.</p>
            <p>With regards to payment account a separate Foreign         Exchange rate will be entered in TREASURY.RATE field with         TREASURY.SPREAD. The rate entered here will be used         between DRAW.CURRENCY and PAYMENT.ACCOUNT.CURRENCY. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.LINK</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field. Input not permitted.</p>
            <p>This field identifies the CUSTOMER used for accounting and limits processing. </p>
            <p>For import Letters of Credit this will contain the APPLICANT.CUSTNO. </p>
            <p>For export / advising Letters of Credit this will contain the ISSUING.BANK.NO. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, system maintained field.</p>
            <p>Will contain a valid record on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIS.AMRT.DTE.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Discount amount accrued to date, if the drawing has been discounted, expressed in local currency.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>Every time the discount amount is accrued in the end of day, this field is automatically updated to show the total amount accrued to date, converted to local currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  1-14 (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.ONLINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the field is set to 'Yes', system will update the next instalment date to 'TODAY' and process it online provided DR.ONLINE.PAYMENT service is run.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CHG.ST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code to identify the current status of the tax.  Used to identify if the tax has been taken, claimed, or not taken.  The system will update this field whenever the charge is processed and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>The codes that are used to identify various states of the tax are as follows : </p>
            <p>         blank  - The tax has not been taken yet            2    - The tax has been taken            3    - The tax has been claimed            4    - A claimed tax has been settled            7    - Charges Unpaid Reversed            8    - Tax has been taken by adding the amount to a                   reimbursement claim via a drawing.            9    - Tax has been taken by deducting the amount from a                   payment via a drawing. </p>
            <p>Notes : (i) For status 3,  the charge is made by debiting the CRF Claimed             bucket and crediting the profit and loss account for the             charge (found on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE             tables).  A claim advice is sent to the charge party.  When             the charge is paid the operator will manually access the             LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file,  where all the charge details are             recorded after authorization of the L/C, update the file to             indicate that the payment has been received, and the CRF             Claimed bucket reimbursed. </p>
            <p>       (ii) When a drawing is entered whereby payments are made or             reimbursement is required,  then the charge amount will be             either deducted from the payment amount or added to the             reimbursement amount in order to make a profit and loss entry.             The charge status that was initially blank will change as             applicable to charge status 8 or 9. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  1 Digit number.  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For acceptance (AC) or deferred payment (DP) drawings, this field indicates that the deal is being discounted and contains the rate of discount to be applied. </p>
            <p>If this field is entered, payment will be made for the DOCUMENT.AMOUNT minus the DISCOUNT.AMT calculated from this rate and also minus load amount if any, where the Discount Party Charged is the Beneficiary. </p>
            <p>If this field is entered, Reimbursement will be claimed for the DOCUMENT.AMOUNT plus the DISCOUNT.AMT calculated from this rate and also plus load amount if any, where the Discount Party Charged is the Opener. </p>
            <p>The discount amount will be amortized over the life of the Drawing at the frequency specified in the LC.PARAMETERS file. </p>
            <p>Drawings can be discounted on Export or Import Letters of credit. </p>
            <p>Either a discount rate or a discount amount may be entered. The system will calculate amount when rate is input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard rate format.</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if the DRAWING.TYPE is AC or DP.</p>
            <p>Cannot be entered if DISCOUNT.AMT is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.REVIEW</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the date on which Acceptance/Deferred Payment drawings will mature, or Letter of Credit Collection drawings will be due for chasing.  </p>
            <p>For Sight drawings this field is to be used when Discounted, indicating the date up to which interest is to be calculated, when a rate is input. However, this field can be input only when DR.DEBIT.TO.CUST is set to NOTDEBITED for Sight Drawings. </p>
            <p>When a term/usance drawing is entered, the date in this field will be the date that maturity entries will be generated, and limits liquidated. These entries will be generated at the end of day on the date entered. </p>
            <p>For L/C Collection, this date will be used for chasing and following up the fate of the drawing. There will be an end of day report produced which which will list all collection type drawings that have passed their Maturity Review date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date Format.</p>
            <p>Mandatory for drawing types: 'AC', 'DP', 'CO', 'CC'.</p>
            <p>Mandatory when Sight Drawing is discounted.</p>
            <p>No input allowed for drawing type 'SP' when not discounted. If a 'CO' is changed to a 'CC', then the user is requested to change this maturity review date to indicate the date the drawing should next be chased.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This YES/NO flag field controls message production. The DELIVERY module will only process the messages which are attached to the chosen class specified in the In other words, all the message which have the associated </p>
            <p>MSG.CLASS.NO</p> ID specified in EB.ADVICES will be produced after the transaction has been authorized if this flag is set to "Y". <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.AMT.LOCAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in this field contains the local currency equivalent of the DISCOUNT.AMT, if this has been entered.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>When the deal is input, the local currency equivalent of the discount amount will be calculated by the system using the mid market spot rate in effect at the time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  1-14 (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INST.BASE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the base date from which the instalment dates are calculated. For example, 30 days from BL date.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Can be less than or equal to value date of DRAWINGS.</p>
                <p value="2">Cannot be greater than TODAY</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount calculated by applying 'CSN.RATE' on 'UPTO.AMT'.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Associated sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRM.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Acceptance (AC) or Deferred Payment (DP) drawings, this field indicates that the deal is being discounted and is the amount of discount to be applied to the document amount. </p>
            <p>If this field is entered, then payment will be made to the beneficiary, on the value date of the drawing, for the document amount minus the discount amount entered here, and minus load amount if any, if the Discount Party Charged is set as Beneficiary. Any charges for the account of the beneficiary will be deducted from the net payment amount (i.e. document amount less discount and load amounts). </p>
            <p>Similarly, the Reimburse amount will be claimed from the Opener, on the maturity date of the drawing, for the document amount plus the discount amount entered here, and any load amount if any, if  the Discount Party Charged is set as Opener. </p>
            <p>The discount amount will be accrued over the life of the drawing, at the frequency specified in the LC.PARAMETERS file. </p>
            <p>Drawings can be discounted in respect of Export/Import Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>If the user wishes to enter a discount rate rather than a discount amount, then this can be performed by entering a value in the DISCOUNT.RATE field above. If this is the case, then this field will be calculated and updated by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 type Amt characters plus a decimal point. Standard         Amount Format. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if the DRAWING.TYPE is 'AC', or 'DP'.</p>
            <p>If entered, then DISCOUNT.RATE cannot be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INST.PROV.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the proportionate provision amount to be released for next instalment amount.</p>
            <p>System updated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COVER.AMT.DOC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provision amount credited to the Provision Release account when PROV.NETTING is 'Yes', expressed in terms of Drawings currency. System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVOL.PERIOD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAFT.PRINT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether a draft print of the DRAWINGS Message is to be produced on deal input (before the authorization stage). </p>
            <p>If set to 'Y'  a DRAFT print of all the delivery messages that will be produced on authorisation will be produces at the Input stage The Message type used for these messages will be a 9xxx message where xxx is a valid SWIFT MEssage type. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y' or 'N'.  Default from LC.PARAMETERS file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRMED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>CONFIRMED.AMT: </p>
            <p />
            <p>When a Drawing is done under a partially confirmed Letter of Credit, the User has the  option of defining the extent of liquidation under the Confirmed portion, which is input here. </p>
            <p>The input however cannot exceed the total amount confirmed under the Letter of Credit outstanding at that point of time. </p>
            <p>The sum of Confirmed and the Unconfirmed portion should be equal to the Document amount or the Liability amount whichever is lower. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard amount format.</p>
            <p>Mandatory when LC is partially confirmed.</p>
            <p>Automatically populated by the system when Unconfirmed portion is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.ENTRY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays a number generated automatically by the system which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of this Drawing. </p>
            <p>The system will automatically insert a number into this field that will refer to a statement entry or a category entry depending on the value contained in the corresponding multivalue fields. </p>
            <p>Note : User L/C 116.1 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Internal multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.ASSN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field</p>
            <p>Total assignment amount to be paid to different assignees. The amount displayed here is difference between the document amount and the BEN.DRAW.AMT.</p>
            <p>Always expressed in DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SENDER.CORR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where required, this field specifies the account or branch of the Sender or another financial institution through which the Sender will reimburse the Receiver.</p>
            <p>The input may be a valid customer number or  BIC code or 4 lines of Text.</p>
            <p>This  has been mapped to Tag 53a.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Customer number.</p>
            <p>1-4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.       </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.DET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies either the details of the individual transaction or a reference to another</p>
            <p>message containing the details which are to be transmitted to the beneficiary customer.</p>
            <p>One of the following codes may be used:</p>
            <p>INV Invoice (followed by the date, reference and details of the invoice).</p>
            <p>RFB Reference for the beneficiary customer (followed by up to 16 characters).</p>
            <p>ROC Ordering customer's reference.</p>
            <p>The information specified in this field is intended only for the beneficiary customer, i.e., this information only needs to be conveyed by the Receiver.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-4       lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid       SWIFT.CODE.WORDS for Tag 70 of MT103.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The system allows brokerage to be settled in any currency providing it has been set up in the brokerage conditions on the BROKER table. </p>
            <p>If a broker code is present, the system will attempt to default the currency. Firstly, if the DRAW.CURRENCY is specified on the BROKER record then this will be used as the default - if not the first currency defined on the BROKER record will be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed if a broker is not defined in the BROKER.CODE field.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid curreny as defined on the BROKER record.</p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field contains the current status of the L/C contract.</p>
            <p>IHLD for On Hold / INAU for Unauthorized / AU for Authorised / CHLD for Copied file On Hold</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the amount to be drawn under this transaction, expressed in the currency above (DRAW.CURRENCY). </p>
            <p>However, should the applicant/opening bank/Beneficiary wish to effect reimbursement in a currency different to that of the drawing, the market foreign exchange rate will be input and the system will automatically convert the draw currency into that of the reimbursement currency. </p>
            <p>The relevant drawdown account will be in the same currency as that the drawing currency has been converted too. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>16 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters.         (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>This amount will be checked against the L/C liability         amount to ensure this is not exceeded.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYRES.PARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field cannot be input. It defaults to the party mentioned in the RISK.PARTY field of the Discrepant type chosen above.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Eg : If the RISK.PARTY field in the DISCREPANT.TYPE table is PRESENTOR then the Presentor Customer number is defaulted as   </p>
            <p>the PAYRES.PARTY or if the field has ISSUING.BANK as the RISK.PARTY then, the Issuing bank is defaulted as the </p>
            <p>PAYRES.PARTY. </p>
            <p>Explanation : The ultimate purpose of setting this field is to identify the actual Risk party of the particular transaction. Once this field is </p>
            <p>set, a separate Drawing Limit is hit for the party in this field and a contingent entry is raised for the party with type as PAYRES. Once the </p>
            <p>documents under collection are Accepted by the ISSUING.BANK, the Limits are reversed and the Contingent entry raised is also reversed </p>
            <p>and the normal flow continues from there on.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>It is a No input field.</p>
                    <p>Defaults to the value in RISK.PARTY field in the DISCREPANT.TYPE chosen. </p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAL.DISCOUNT.RTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates to the system that a discount should be calculated 'to yield'.</p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Only available responses are (Yes) to indicate a 'to yield' calculation or (N)o to indicate a straight discount calculation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.MLR.MOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input in this field denotes, whether Market lending rate is to be picked up or the Market offer rate, from the PERIODIC.INTEREST table. </p>
            <p>Input in this field is valid only when Tiered system of rate calculation is chosen (when CURRENCY.REF is input). If left blank, defaults to Market lending rate (MLR).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are MLR/MOR.</p>
            <p>INTEREST.KEY should have been defined in the Parameter.</p>
            <p>Defaults to MLR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the tax code obtained from the commission and/or charges table, the system will automatically calculate any tax which is to be added to the charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  Standard Amount Format.  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USANCE.ACT.SENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Assignee's Address. If customer number is input the address is defaulted from the customer file.</p>
            <P>To generate 59F tag in MT103 and MT202C, address must be defined in following format.</P>
            <P>/1235674              - Account Number</P>
            <p>1/DAVID WARNER        - Beneficiary Name</p>
            <p>2/1000 QUARRY LAKE DR - Beneficiary Address</p>
            <p>3/US/SEATTLE          - Beneficiary Country and Town</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Free text field.</p>
            <p>Mutually exclusive with ASSN.CUST.NO.</p>
            <p>Account number should start with '/' for 59F format</p>
            <p>First line should start with '1/' (ie) name of beneficiary for 59F format</p>
            <p>Address is not mandatory. It may or maynot have occurrence with '2/' for 59F format.</p>
            <p>If address is inputted then country code is mandatory (ie)'3/' for 59F format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field enables the user to override the defaulted carrier for a particular message type and select a new carrier.</p>
            <p>For example : If a specific message is generated by SWIFT, the user is able to override this by choosing other available options from the CARRIER table, eg TELEX or PRINT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid record in the CARRIER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.AMT.CLAIM</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows the user to input Additional amount to be claimed, in the currency of the Credit.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This </p>
            <p>being mapped to Tag 33B of MT742, MT750 and MT754.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDIT.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the date and time of the last auditor access.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-set, this field is used to determine the message type to which the user wishes to amend the delivery and is used exclusively with the fields &lt;MSG.CLASS.NO&gt;, &lt;OVR.CARRIER&gt;, &lt;ADDRESSEE&gt; and &lt;SEND.MESSAGE&gt;. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 4 numeric characters. (Optional input). </p>
            <p>The category code must be defined on the DE.MESSAGE         table. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will identify the LIMIT.REFERENCE number to be checked for limit control on L/C transactions. </p>
            <p>Each Drawing transaction will be checked against the LIMIT file to verify the availability of a limit facility. If no input is made at this field, the LIMIT system will provide a default according to the values defined in the LIMIT.PARAMETER file. If required, more details can be found in the LIMIT user guide. </p>
            <p>A Sight drawing / Maturing Acceptance or Deferred Payment will result in the limit availability being increased by the amount of the payment. An Acceptance / Deferred Payment drawing will not impact the limit utilisation until its maturity. </p>
            <p>Note : The customer that limits will be checked against is the customer defined in CON.CUS.LINK (defined on the L/C record). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3-7 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Input to this field must be a valid LIMIT.REFERENCE         number.</p>
            <p>If no limit exists for the customer, a corresponding         error message will be displayed by the system with an         override facility.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERDRAW.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
            <p>This field shows the actual amount that the letter of credit is overdrawn in the local currency. </p>
            <p>If the letter of credit is not overdrawn then this field will be zero. </p>
            <p>An overdrawn letter of credit is one where the total of drawings exceeds the LC.AMOUNT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input. System generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.DISC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participant share in discount amount expressed in terms of drawings currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.XCHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the exchange rate to be used between the charge debit account and the charge currency.</p>
            <p>If no input is made then the mid rate CHARGE.CCY.MARKET set in LC.PARAMETERS will be used.</p>
            <p>If no currency market is set in LC.PARAMETERS then the default market for LC will be used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONF.AMT.LC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>CONF.AMT.LC.CCY: </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field will hold confirmation amount (out of the total Drawings amount) in terms of LC currency. This is useful when a drawing is made in a currency different from the LC currency.  </p>
            <p>Applicable for partly confirmed export LCs only. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional and only allowed if DISCOUNT.RATE or DISCOUNT.AMOUNT is present. This field together with DISCOUNT.AMT gives the total amount that the Document amount is to be discounted by, which should not exceed the document amount. </p>
            <p>If this field is entered, then payment will be made to the beneficiary, on the value date of the drawing, for the document amount minus the discount amount entered above, and the load amount entered here, if the Discount Party Charged is Beneficiary. Any charges for the account of the beneficiary will be deducted the net payment amount (i.e. document amount less discount and  load amounts). </p>
            <p>Similarly, the reimbursement would be claimed for the document amount plus the discount amount entered above, and the load amount entered here, if the Discount Party Charged is Opener. </p>
            <p>The load amount will be accrued over the life of the drawing, at the frequency specified in the LC.PARAMETERS file, separately from the discount amount. </p>
            <p>Drawings can be discounted in respect of Export/Import Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>If the user wishes to enter a load rate rather than a load amount, then this can be performed by entering a value in the LOAD.RATE field above.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a         decimal point.</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if the DRAWING.TYPE is 'AC', or 'DP' and       DISCOUNT.RATE, or         DISCOUNT.AMT has been entered.</p>
            <p>If entered, then LOAD.RATE cannot be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the commission amount for current schedule.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Spread applied by the trade finance department on the rate quoted by the treasury department. This will be used together with TREASURY.RATE and CREDIT.CUST.RATE will be determined to credit the customer's drawdown account.</p>
            <p>Input Optional</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIXED.COMM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the commission amount for the entire tenure of the contract.  Amount expressed in the currency of the contract.</p>
            <p> If the user inputs a value in this field then the default commission calculation will be ignored.</p>
            <p>User input field.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Not allowed when COMM.RATE  is input.</p>
                <p value="2">Fixed commission amount must be less than LC face value.</p>
                <p value="3">Input of value '0' is not allowed.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.DOC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>PAY.DOC.CCY</p>
            <p>Presently not in use.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not currently in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECV.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the bank to whom the payment is to be forwarded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must contain a valid mnemonic of a Bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.INST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of instalments in which the payment has to be settled.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Maximum number of instalments allowed - 24.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENTOR.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the presentor of the documents if they are a customer of the bank with a valid CUSTOMER.NO. </p>
            <p>Field is mutually exclusive with PRESENTOR. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.').</p>
            <p>If entered, then PRESENTOR cannot be entered.</p>
            <p>Must not be the same as: ISSUING.BANK.NO,         ADVISING.BK.CUSTNO, THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO,         ADVISE.THRU.CUSTNO, APPLICANT.CUSTNO, or         BENEFICIARY.CUSTNO.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid customer on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.AMT.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to display the provision amount released on account of this DRAWING. Generally will be defaulted by the system based on the percentage of PROVISION input in LC. This will be in the currency in which the provision is held ( Provision credit account currency in LC contract). The field can also be input by the user as to the amount required to be released on account of this DRAWING. </p>
            <p><strong><p>Validation Rules:</p></strong>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input. </p>
            <p>When input the amount will be checked with the provision         percentage in LC and an error will be returned if the         amount released exceeds the calculated amount. </p>
            <p>For calculation of the credit currency equivalent the         following rules will be used. : The percentage in LC         record is referred and the maximum release amount is         determined. The amount determined is converted to credit         provision currency using the current cross rate or mid         rate. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.DRAW.SET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is defaulted based on the LC type, whenever the user accepts documents under trust. For mixed payment LCs the user needs to input this field with the draw type that will be used to accept the documents.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.DEBIT.TO.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input in this field signifies, whether the customer account is debited or not. Input is allowed only for Sight bills. Valid inputs are NOTDEBITED and DEBITED. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When DEBITED is chosen, the extant flow continues whereas when NOTDEBITED is chosen, an Internal account with Account class CUSDEBIT is debited along with discount charges, if any when Discount Party charged is set as Opener.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are DEBITED/NOTDEBITED</p>
            <p>Input permitted only for Sight Bills.</p>
            <p>Default value is DEBITED.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORT.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines whether charges are to be amortised over the life of the L/C. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to <STRONG>Y</STRONG>es, then this charge will not be taken into the profit and loss account defined for this charge/commission code immediately, but will be amortised over the life of the L/C contract (From issue date to Expiry date). The charge will only be amortised if CHARGE.ACCOUNT field has been entered. If the Maturity date or the Value date of the drawing is to be changed then, the field RECALCULATE.AMORT in LC.PARAMETERS has to be set to YES so that it recalculates the Amortisation amount according to the Value date/New Maturity Date.</p>
            <p>However, when the Drawings are discounted using the DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS application, the Amortisation is carried out only as per the original input maturity period in the Drawings. So if a Drawing is Discounted with Foreclosure or Online maturity, the entries of LCAMORT account move into P&amp;L account according to the original maturity date of the Drawings and not on the new maturity date or online.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y' or 'N'. </p>
            <p>Associated Multi-value field. </p>
            <p>Default from FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE using charge code. </p>
            <p>If the charge is being taken immediately (see CHARGE.STATUS) , then this field must be set to 'N'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTI.DR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained field.</p>
            <p>The field represents the differential component to be paid by an account different  from that of the DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT or even if it is the same account, the amount expressed here may be used to debit at a different exchange rate.</p>
            <p>Always expressed  in DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
            <p>The sum of Multiple debits (ASSN.AMOUNT defined through TPRECV) should       be equal to this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNCONFIRMED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a Drawing is done under a partially confirmed Letter of Credit, the User has the  option of defining the extent of liquidation under the Unconfirmed portion, which is input here.</p>
            <p>The input however cannot exceed the total amount unconfirmed under the Letter of Credit outstanding at that point of time.</p>
            <p>The sum of Confirmed and the Unconfirmed portion should be equal to the Document amount or the Liability amount whichever is lower.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard amount format.</p>
            <p>Mandatory when LC is partially confirmed.</p>
            <p>Automatically populated by the system when confirmed portion is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field contains the number of times the contract has been modified. This is a counter number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the Internal Department ID number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.LIAB.REL.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the total liability released against this letter of credit as a result of the drawing converted into local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.AMT.LOCAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in this field contains the local currency equivalent of the DOCUMENT.AMT.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>When the deal is input, the local currency equivalent of the document amount will be calculated by the system using the mid market spot rate in effect at the time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  1-14 (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDUCE.LIMIT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLAUSES.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is populated automatically from the field CLAUSES, by accessing LC.CLAUSES. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid SWIFT characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.ADV.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field holds the activity number, which is triggered by the latest activity in the life-cycle of the transaction.. The activity is 4 digit number composed of three main parts:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>First indicates the operation</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 - Represents O or     P operation in LETTER.OF.CREDIT</p>
            <p />
            <p>2 - Represents A, C or T operation in         LETTER.OF.CREDIT</p>
            <p />
            <p>3 - Represents Sight Drawing Operation in         DRAWINGS</p>
            <p />
            <p>4 - Represents Usance Drawing Operation in         DRAWINGS</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Second indicates the type of instrument</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 - Represents Outward Collection</p>
            <p />
            <p>2 - Represents Inward Collection</p>
            <p />
            <p>4 - Represents Export Letter of Credit</p>
            <p />
            <p>8 - Represents Import Letter of Credit</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>And the last two digit indicate the detail         activity related to that operation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>For example. : For the L/C Export Sight Payment activity, the first digit will be 3. The second digit will be 4 and the last two digits will be 01; (to indicate basic INPUT/AUTHORIZE operation). Thus the activity for Export Sight Drawing will be LC-3401. For the complete list of activity code, please consult User's Manual.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a no-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVERS.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the bank to whom the payment is to be forwarded or the bank on which the draft is to be drawn.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Accepts a valid customer number.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.TO.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for Sender to Receiver (i.e. Sending bank to Receiving bank) information. It may be used to provide instructions or additional information for the Receiver, Intermediary, Account with Institution or Beneficiary Institution. </p>
            <p>This field corresponds to field 72 on S.W.I.F.T. messages, and must never be used for information for which another field is intended, or for instructions not required in a message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type         SW Multivalue field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35         characters each will be allowed. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain         a codeword followed by further information.</p>
            <p>All code words must be valid code words as defined in         S.W.I.F.T. documentation and must conform to the rules         specified. Use of invalid code words will cause a message         rejection when validated by S.W.I.F.T.</p>
            <p>Further code words and information can be entered in         subsequent multivalues, but additional information         continued on a new line must be preceded by a double         slash '//'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>754.BK.TO.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains additional information for the Receiver or account with bank. Any information entered into this field will appear on a S.W.I.F.T. MT754 message (Advice of Payment/Acceptance/Negotiation) </p>
            <p>This field corresponds to field 72 on S.W.I.F.T. messages, and must never be used for information for which another field is intended, or for instructions not required in a message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type         SW Multivalue field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35         characters each will be allowed. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain         a codeword followed by further information.</p>
            <p>All code words must be valid code words as defined in         S.W.I.F.T. documentation and must conform to the rules         specified. Use of invalid code words will cause a message         rejection when validated by S.W.I.F.T.</p>
            <p>Further code words and information can be entered in         subsequent multivalues, but additional information         continued on a new line must be preceded by a double         slash '//'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINST.PROVIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>REINST.PROVIS </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.AMT.LC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Assignment amount paid/received in terms of LETTER OF CREDIT currency depending on the Assignment reference.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CALC.COND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts Id of DR.INT.CALC.COND as valid input.</p>
            <p> Based on the value in this field, the method of calculation of Discount component is arrived at.</p>
            <p>This effectively could be based on the Drawing Currency or the Local Currency and the rate applicable on that amount, viz., Buy, Sell or Mid.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When DISCOUNT.AMT is input (sans rate), this field accepts only those Id of DR.INT.CALC.COND that have DRAW.CCY as INT.CALC.CCY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input cannot be changed once the Drawing is authorized.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid DR.INT.CALC.COND Id.</p>
            <p />
            <p>2 digits N (Numeric).</p>
            <p>Input permitted only for Discounted Contracts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.PARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code to identify the party this tax applies to. </p>
            <p>This field identifies from whom the tax is to be taken. For all tax within the multivalue set,  these can be different.  Some of the tax can be levied against the Opener, others against the Beneficiary, and some against the Third Party. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'O' or 'T' or 'B'.  Associated multivalue field.  Default from CHARGES.FROM field above.</p>
            <p>If 'T' is specified, then THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO must be set.</p>
            <p>If no input is made this field will default to CHARGES.FROM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRUST.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is activated for CO type drawings under import Letter Of Credits. The valid values accepted are RELEASE, ACCEPT and REJECT. When this field is set to RELEASE, the system updates the trust limit and LC limit will be reversed back for the document amount. The static fields in Letter Of Credit will also be updated. </p>
            <p>The system also creates a contingent entry TRCOLL instead of COLL when the documents are set under REJECT. The system also defaults the draw type to be input by the user when he accepts the documents based on the LC type. In case of mixed payments user has to input the draw type and ACPT.TM.BAND field.</p>
            <p>When the documents are accepted, the user can change the draw type in the Drawing to AC or SP or DP (the value should be in NEW.DRAW.SET) the system automatically updates the TRUST.REL field as ACCEPT. Also the system reverses out the previous limits and contingent entries are creates new limit and contingent entry.</p>
            <p>When the user changes the draw type from CO to CR, this field is automatically set to REJECT thus reversing all the entries and limits created previously.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The valid values accepted are :</p>
            <p>RELEASE, ACCEPT and REJECT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INST.COVER.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the proportionate provision amount which will be credited to Provision Release Account for the next instalment.</p>
            <p>System updated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency that tax is to be levied in.  This can be different from the LC.CURRENCY.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated.  CCY (Currency code e.g. GBP must be 3)  Associated multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.DISC.AGREE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the participant's decision  to participate in the discounting process.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Option field 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>Default value - 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.AMT.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
            <p>Assignment amount paid/received in terms of local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on when Drawings is booked under  LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must not be less than issue date of LC</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENTATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on when document is presented by the beneficiary after shipment.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must not be less than issue date of LC</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHIPMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on when the goods was shipped under Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be less than Presentation Date</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODE.OF.SHIPMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the mode of shipment used to transport goods.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Allowed values are - Air,Sea,Road,Rail,Multi Modal,Other</p>
            <p>Must be 'Sea' when INCO.TERMS is FAS,FOB,CFR and CIF</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TENOR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the tenor of draft for acceptance drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Not applicable for instalment or 'MX' draw type</p>
            <p>Applicable only for Usance Drawings(AC/DP)</p>
            <p>Mandatory If COMM.START.DATE = Tenor</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the base date to calculate maturity review date based on tenor days for Usance drawings.</p>            
            <p>e.g</p>
				<p>BASE.DATE - 01 -Jan- 2014</p>
				<p>TENOR - 90 Days</p>
				<p>Maturity review date will be calculated as 31-Mar-2014</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Not applicable for instalment or 'MX' draw type</p>
            <p>Applicable only for Usance Drawings(AC/DP)</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the document code defined in Letter of Credit</p>
            <p>Defaultes from DOC.CODE field in Letter of Credit</p>
            <p>Associated multivalue field associated with fields DOC.ID  to DOC.DISCREPANCY</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the description of document code.</p>
            <p>Defaulted from DOCUMENT.TXT field in LETTER.OF.CREDIT</p>
            <p>Associated multivalue field associated with fields DOC.ID  to DOC.DISCREPANCY</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the  status of document submitted under LC</p>            
            <p>Associated multivalue field associated with fields DOC.ID  to DOC.DISCREPANCY</p>
            <p>Allowed values are - Clean,Discrepant,Returned,Not Submitted</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.DISCPREANCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the details of discrepancy in documents submitted</p>            
            <p>Associated multivalue field associated with fields DOC.ID  to DOC.DISCREPANCY.</p>
 			<p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory when document status is either Discrepant (or) Not Submitted.</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.DISCREP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the discrepancies  defaulted based on discrepancy check rules defined in LC.DISCPREPANCY.CONDITIONS.</p>                   
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.DISCREPANCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the consolidated discrepancies of user defined discrepancies,document discrepancies and system defaulted discrepancies.</p>
            <p>Associated multivalue field associated with fields CON.DISCREPANCY  to DISCREP.STATUS.</p>                        
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCREP.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the current status of each discrepancies</p>
            <p>Allowed values are Advised Opener,Advised Beneficiary,Advised Issuing Bank,Rejected,Waived,Resolved</p>                        
        </desc>
</t>
<t> 
<field>INWARD.MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds message types of all inward messages received for Drawings</p>
            <p>E.g. if MT752 is received, then value MT752 will be stored in this field.</p>
            <p>Associated multi value with INWARD.MSG.REF. System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the inward delivery reference for the corresponding message type.</p>
            <p>For example, in R20120828160574535800, R identifies an inward message.</p>
         </desc>
</t>      
<t>
<field>MT756.REIMB.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the value date of net amount to be reimbursed or paid.</p>            
            <p>This field will be mapped with date from 33A tag in MT756 inward message.</p>
 			<p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date field.</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT756.REIMB.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the  currency and net amount to be reimbursed or paid.</p>            
            <p>This field will be mapped with currency and amount from 33A tag in MT756 message.</p>
            <p>E.g if reimbursement/paid amount is USD 50000 then this field will hold value as USD50000.</p>
 			<p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Combination of valid currency and amount.</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>732.BK.TO.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the additional information for the receiver and it will be mapped to Tag 72 in MT732 message.</p>            
         	<p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 lines of 35 characters each line.</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Start date for calculation of the acceptance commission. User input field</p>            
            <p>Values are Value Date, Date Accepted, Tenor</p>
            <p>Commission will be calculated from COMM.START.DATE to MATURITY.REVIEW date</p>           
            <p>Default value is Value date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>To define if the subject commission is waived.</p>            
            <p>Values are Yes, Null</p>
            <p>If yes is selected, then the subject commission will not be collected.</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>CHK.DISCREPANCY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DOC.DISCREPANCY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>MT732.BK.TO.BK</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>PAYMENT.TYPE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INST.PORT.NO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INST.DISC.AMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INST.LOAD.AMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INST.TM.BAND</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>IB.EVENT.STATUS</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>IB.ADDL.INFO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>IB.BK.TO.CUST</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>IB.CUST.TO.BK</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>IB.PAY.BY.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DOCS.RECEIVED</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TOT.APPLICANT.CHG</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TOT.BENE.CHG</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>FWD.CONTRACT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>APPL.RESP.DISCREP</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>SUPPORT.DOCS</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DOCUMENT.NAME</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
