<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>DRAW.NEGOTIATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRESENTOR.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the name of the presentor bank of the respective documents received.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWING.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
            <p>This is the counter for the number of drawings made.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is a mandatory input and identifies the Letter of credit number to which a drawing is to apply.Following input of this field the system with download all associated information such as parent LC, LC type etc.</p>
            <p>If the number input is that of a CHILD letter of credit, then the PARENT.LC.NUMBER will be automatically populated in the next field.</p>
            <p>Additionally, following input of the LC.NUMBER, the header should show the current outstanding balance.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid LC record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement. </p>
            <p>As in the majority of T24 Applications, the user is allowed to define in the Drawings file up to 999 Local elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified. These local elements should be defined by the user where deemed necessary according to local practice. </p>
            <p>The name(s) of the new element(s), as well as the format and creation of any Drawing transactions. </p>
            <p>As defined by the user within the individual local tables. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters as defined in the local table definition for this local reference field. Multivalue field. (Optional or Mandatory input according to definition in LOCAL.TABLE (Ref: Utilities) for this local reference element.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCREPANT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to display the current status of the documents. The options available are either SETTLED, RETURNED, HOLD or CHECKED.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>First 2 digits should be start with 'DN' and the next 12 digits should be the Letter of credit ID starts from 3 digit.
         [DN][LC NUMBER starts from 3rd digit]
      (1) 14 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.BK.TO.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to enter any bank to bank information required on the corresponding MT100.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine the message to which the user wishes to amend the delivery and is used exclusively with the fields &lt;MSG.CLASS.NO&gt;, &lt;OVR.CARRIER&gt;, &lt;ADDRESSEE&gt; and &lt;SEND.MESSAGE&gt;.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 - 4 numeric characters. (Optional input). </p>
            <p>The category code must be defined on the DE.MESSAGE table. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.ADDR4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the name and  address of the pay party IF they are not a customer of the bank.</p>
            <p>Field is mutually exclusive with PAY.PARTY.NO.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field.</p>
            <p>If entered, then PAY.PARTY.NO. cannot be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COPY.2ND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the number of copies of the document, defined in DOCUMENT.CODE above, that are to be sent in the second post. </p>
            <p>For the document identified in DOCUMENT.CODE above, this field, if entered, will specify the number of copies being sent to opening bank/applicant under cover of the Documentary Remittance letter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 type A (Alphanumeric) characters (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a key on the LC.ADVICE.TEXT file that is to be used to specify documents which are being sent under cover of the documentary remittance letter. </p>
            <p>The code entered here will be used as the key to locate a record from the LC.ADVICE.TEXT file in order to retrieve the full name of a document (e.g. Bill of Lading), which is to be sent to either the Issuing Bank for Export/Advising L/C's, or the Applicant for Import/Opening L/C's, or the Collecting Bank an outward collection or the Drawee for an inward collection. </p>
            <p>The field is associated with fields COPY.1ST and COPY.2ND which indicate the post the documents will be sent in, and the number of copies. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-5 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalued field associated with fields DOCUMENT.CODE to DOC.2ND.COPIES. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the LC.ADVICE.TEXT file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during input of the Drawing. The field will be updated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>During the validation of a Drawing contract, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly, for instance, that there is no limit set up for the customer. </p>
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the override, the full text of the actual override message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field. </p>
            <p>For example, if the user inputs a deal, then when the Drawing is validated a warning bell will sound and a message will appear at the foot of the screen which reads : </p>
            <p>'NO LIMIT DEFINED FOR CUSTOMER' </p>
            <p>This will draw the users attention to the override entry(s). After checking and making any necessary amendments the user then approves the transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PS.BK.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used in conjunction with field &lt;PRESENTOR.BANK&gt; above and identifies the address of the presentor bank of the respective documents received.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSIGN.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> This field is used as a unique reference number for an assignment of proceeds or multiple payment (TPPAY) transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code specifying what type of drawing this is. </p>
            <p>This code identifies which kind of Drawing is being made under the L/C, and will impact the kind of processing done. The following types can be entered for a new drawing: </p>
            <p>AC - Acceptance (Usance credits) DP - Deferred Payment (Usance credits) SP - Sight Payment </p>
            <p>The following types can only be entered as a change to an existing drawing: </p>
            <p>For Drawing types of 'AC' and 'DP', a term or usance credit is established whereby the funds will be debited and paid on the MATURITY.REVIEW date specified later. If the funds are required to be paid before this date, the Drawing can be Discounted, whereby payment is made on the Value date specified, but reimbursement is obtained on the MATURITY.REVIEW date. </p>
            <p>If 'SP' is entered, then both Payment and reimbursement is made on the VALUE.DATE specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-2 type AAA (Alpha) characters. </p>
            <p>Valid codes are: 'AC'; 'DP'; 'SP'. (Mandatory Input) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.INT.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the Intermediary Bank for the assignment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.BOOKED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an exchange rate field.</p>
            <p>This is the rate quoted by the treasury department to the trade finance department (ie excluding department spread).</p>
            <p>The department spread will be accepted in RATE.SPREAD field. The exchange rate including the rate spread will be customer debit rate and will be shown in DEBIT.CUST.RATE field.</p>
            <p>The DEBIT.CUST.RATE will be applied between the document currency and the debit account currrency (DRAW.CURRENCY and DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT.CURRENCY) if they differ.</p>
            <p>Default calculated from currency table, using current mid market spot rate.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal characters). (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Input to this field is only allowed if the drawdown account is in a different currency to the draw currency.</p>
            <p>Mainly used in import transactions, when the importer's debit account is in a different currency to the document currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Spread applied by the trade finance department on the rate quoted by the treasury department. This will be used together with TREASURY.RATE and CREDIT.CUST.RATE will be determined to credit the customer's drawdown account.</p>
            <p>Input Optional</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.DRAW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the portion of the payment to be paid to the Beneficiary.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-10 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.ADDR3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the name and  address of the pay party IF they are not a customer of the bank.</p>
            <p>Field is mutually exclusive with PAY.PARTY.NO.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field.</p>
            <p>If entered, then PAY.PARTY.NO. cannot be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides the user with the ability to either temporarily or permanantly withhold the delivery of any message produced under the contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Options available are (Y)es or (N)o</p>
            <p>Default is (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHG.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Generated Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COPY.1ST</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies the number of copies of the document, defined in DOCUMENT.CODE above, that are to be sent in the first post. </p>
            <p>For the document identified in DOCUMENT.CODE above, this field, if entered, will specify the number of copies being sent to opening bank/applicant under cover of the Documentary Remittance letter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the message class ID, (defined in EB.ADVICES). There may be many classes specified, but only classes which are related to the operation, will be triggered. For example, the EB.ADVICES number LC-3801 (L/C Export Sight Drawing) may have the following classes and messages:</p>
            <p>Message No. : 1798</p>
            <p />
            <p>EB.MESSAG.CLASS : NOTIFICATION Message No. : 754</p>
            <p />
            <p>EB.MESSAG.CLASS : OPERATIONS Message No. : 742</p>
            <p />
            <p>EB.MESSAG.CLASS : REIMBURSING Assume that the EB.MESSAGE.CLASS ID has been mapped to L/C internal class specified in LC.PARAMETERS as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p>BASIC.MESSAGE = OPERATIONS </p>
            <p>NOTIFICATION = NOTIFICATION </p>
            <p>REIMBURSING = REIMBURSING </p>
            <p>In the L/C Transaction, the system will always populate the OPERATIONS and NOTIFICATION class when the L/C is issued. The REIMBURSING class will only be triggered, when THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO or THIRD.PARTY field (REIMBURSING bank in this case) in LETTER.OF.CREDIT has filled up. In combination with the field (SEND.MESSAGE), you can choose whether you want to produce the messages by flipping the YES/NO flag.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENTATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Generated Field</p>
            <p>This field displays the date of presentation of documents. Only the current day is allowed and the systam automtically defualts to today.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.REC.CORR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the Receiver Bank's correspondent for the assignment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the method of payment for the drawing. </p>
            <p>Used to determine which payment method is to be used in order to effect payment to the Beneficiary for Export/Advising L/C's, or the Advising Bank or Reimbursing bank for Import/Opening L/C's. Valid codes are: </p>
            <p>N - Pay through a Nostro account BP - Issue a Bankers Payment drawn on a Nostro account. CH - Issue a Cheque, drawn on a Nostro account IT - Pay to an Internal Account </p>
            <p>If the method chosen is 'N', then payment will be made via a Nostro account, entered in the field below PAYMENT.ACCOUNT, with advices. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'N' or 'BP' or 'CH' or 'IT'. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.UTILISE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides the user with the ability to indicate that no further drawings will be made under the letter of credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input is optional with the only available responses being (Y)es or (N)o.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.PARTY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the customer number of the pay party.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.').</p>
            <p>Must be a valid customer on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the respective assignment amount</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the account number to where the assignment amount should be paid.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
            <p>Contains current status of the L/C contract.</p>
            <p>IHLD for On Hold / INAU for Unauthorized / AU for Authorised</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARENT.LC.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Generated Field.</p>
            <p>Following input of a Child letter of credit number in field &lt;LC.NUMBER&gt;, this field will automatically beome populated with the corresponding parent letter of credit number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLAUSES.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is populated automatically from the field CLAUSES, by accessing LC.CLAUSES. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid SWIFT characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
            <p>Contains the delivery keys used for the generation of LC advices/ documents/payments from the Electronic Delivery System. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to to allow users to specify a different credit value date to that of the debit value date. If DRAW.TYPE is 'SP' then this date will be mapped to VALUE.DATE in DRAWINGS. For DRAW.TYPE 'AC' or 'DP', this date will be mapped to MATURITY.REVIEW date, in DRAWINGS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
            <p>Optional input field for drawing types: SP, AC, DP. Otherwise, NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.REC.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field is used to identify the Receiver Bank for the assignment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Spread applied by the trade finance department on the rate quoted by the treasury department. This will be used together with RATE.BOOKED and DEBIT.CUST.RATE will be determined to debit the customer's drawdown account.</p>
            <p>Input Optional</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.NEGO.DEAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCPT.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Acceptance period mentioned in LC to which the DRAWING should be adjusted. Applicable for mixed payment LCs.</p>
            <p>When mixed payment LCs are input, permissable acceptance or deferred periods are set up and portions of the total amount allocated. The type and period indicate from which portion the amount should be drawn.</p>
            <p>Where the drawing type is SP then this field defaults to the maturity date in the form yyyymmdd.</p>
            <p>EXAMPLE: - Take a LC record with the following input.</p>
            <p>LC Record</p>
            <p />
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>DRAW.TYPE:</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>SP</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PAYMENT.PCT:</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>50</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PAY.PORTION: </p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>50,000</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>ACPT.TM.BAND</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>20000606</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>DRAW.TYPE</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>AC</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PAYMENT.PCT</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>25</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PAY.PORTION</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>25000</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>ACPT.TM.BAND</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>30</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>DRAW.TYPE</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>AC</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PAYMENT.PCT</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>25</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PAY.PORTION</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>25000</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>ACPT.TM.BAND</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>60</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p>Let us assume that a particular drawing is to be drawn from the third portion. Then the ACCPT.PERIOD should be input as 60. </p>
            <p>For unmixed payment LCs this will be defaulted to expiry date of the LC</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input for mixed payment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This System Generated field contains the activity number triggered by the program. The activity is a 4 digit number, which is composed of three main parts:</p>
            <p />
            <p>First digit stands for Operation</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1  represents O or P operation in LETTER.OF.CREDIT</p>
            <p>2  represents A, C or T operation in LETTER.OF.CREDIT</p>
            <p>3  represents Sight Drawing Operation in DRAWINGS</p>
            <p>4  represents Usance Drawing Operation in DRAWINGS</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Second digit stands for Type of Instruments</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 - represents Outward Collection</p>
            <p>2 - represents Inward Collection</p>
            <p>4 - represents Export Letter of Credit</p>
            <p>8 - represents Import Letter of Credit</p>
            <p>And the last two digit stands for detail activity related to that operation.</p>
            <p>e.g. For the L/C Export Sight Payment activity, the first digit will be 3. The second digit will be 4 and the last two digits will be 01 (to indicate basic INPUT/AUTHORIZE operation). Thus the activity for Export Sight Drawing will be LC-3401. For the complete list of activity code, please consult Users Manual.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a no-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESSEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the user to divert a particular message type via a third party. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>50 Alphanumeric character field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the drawing that is applicable for a particular DRAW.TYPE under the multivalue set. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.ADDR1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the name and  address of the pay party IF they are not a customer of the bank.</p>
            <p>Field is mutually exclusive with PAY.PARTY.NO.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field.</p>
            <p>If entered, then PAY.PARTY.NO. cannot be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the user to override the defaulted carrier for a particular message type and select a new carrier. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid record in the CARRIER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.202.BKBK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to enter any bank to bank information required on the corresponding MT202</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.ADDR2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the name and  address of the pay party IF they are not a customer of the bank.</p>
            <p>Field is mutually exclusive with PAY.PARTY.NO.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field.</p>
            <p>If entered, then PAY.PARTY.NO. cannot be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency of the drawing.</p>
            <p>Should the applicant / Beneficiary wish to effect reimbursement in a currency different to that of the drawing, the exchange rate input in the field RATE.BOOKED will be used to convert the DRAW.CURRENCY into DRAWDOWN.ACCOUNT.CURRENCY. If no input is made in RATE.BOOKED, the foreign market exchange rate will be defaulted and the system will automatically convert the draw currency into that of the reimbursement currency (DRAWDOWN ACCOUNT.CURRENCY).</p>
            <p>Also refer to help text of field RATE.SPREAD.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>CCY (Currency code e.g. GBP must be 3 characters) - Default to LC.CURRENCY </p>
            <p>In the event that both the drawdown account and payment account are different currencies to that of the drawing, the Foreign exchange rate applicable to the drawdown         account currency and the DRAW.CURRENCY will be entered in         RATE.BOOKED.</p>
            <p>With regards to the payment account a seperate Foreign Exchange rate will be entered in TREASURY.RATE field with TREASURY.SPREAD. The rate entered here will be used         between DRAW.CURRENCY and PAYMENT.ACCOUNT.CURRENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the account where funds are to be paid to under this drawing. </p>
            <p>The account which will be credited on either the value date or maturity review date, depending on drawing type, for the payment in respect of the drawing. </p>
            <p>If the payment method entered above is either 'BP' (Bankers payment) or 'CH' (Cheque), then this field will be automatically updated by the system to indicate the account to be used. This will be set up on the LC.PARAMETERS file as 'B.P.ISSUED.ACC' and 'CHEQUES.ISSUE.ACC'. </p>
            <p>For drawing types 'AC', 'DP', this account will be credited on the Maturity Review date in respect of payment, unless the drawing is being discounted, in which case it will be credited on the value date. </p>
            <p>For drawing type 'SP', this account will be credited on the Value date in respect of payment. </p>
            <p>For drawing type 'CO' with 'UNDER.RESERVE' set to 'YES', then this account will be credited on the value date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-16 Mnemonic characters relating to a Customer Account or a Nostro Account, or any other account. Default from Payment Method (see below).</p>
            <p>Mandatory input for Drawing types 'AC', 'DP', 'SP', and 'CO' with UNDER.RESERVE set to 'YES'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field automatically updated with status DELETED , when the drawings created in IHLD is deleted.
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWDOWN.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the account where funds are to be received from under this drawing. </p>
            <p>The account which will be debited on either the value date or maturity review date, depending on drawing type, in reimbursement of funds paid to the beneficiary of the drawing. </p>
            <p>If this field is not entered, then a default will be found from the parent L/C contract. For Import/Opening L/C's, this default will come from the APPLICANT.ACC field of the L/C. For Export/Advising L/C's, the default will come from the ISSUING.BANK.ACC field of the L/C. If these fields were not entered, and this drawing involves an actual payment, (i.e. drawing types 'AC', 'D',or 'SP'), then a mandatory input is required. </p>
            <p>For drawing types 'AC', 'DP', this account will be debited on the Maturity Review date in respect of reimbursement. </p>
            <p>For drawing type 'SP', this account will be debited on the Value date in respect of reimbursement. The currency of this account need not be the same as the currency of the drawing. If this is the case, the system will automatically calculate the amount to be debited (see RATE.BOOKED above). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-16 Mnemonic characters relating to a Customer Account or a Nostro Account, or any other account. Default from L/C (see below). Mandatory input depending upon type.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input for drawing types 'AC', 'DP', or 'SP'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.AC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the account number to where the assignment amount should be paid.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWN.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value date for drawing entries. Can be future or back valued. </p>
            <p>The date entered here will be the date that CRF, Statement, and Category entries will be generated for this L/C. If the date specified is in the future, then the end of day batch of this date will generate the required entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date Format. Default to Today.</p>
            <p>Cannot be greater than the Maturity Review date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the amount to be drawn under this drawing expressed in the currency above (DRAW.CURRENCY). </p>
            <p>Separates the amount of the drawing. </p>
            <p>However, should the applicant/opening bank/Beneficiary wish to effect reimbursement in a currency different to that of the drawing, the market foreign exchange rate will be input and the system will automatically convert the draw currency into that of the reimbursement currency. The relevant drawdown account will be in the same currency as that the drawing currency has been converted too. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>16 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>This amount will be checked against the L/C liability amount to ensure this is not exceeded.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.ASSN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Maintained Field</p>
            <p>This field contains the remaining portion of the drawing amount available to any other assignee(s) or third parties.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TREASURY.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an exchange rate between the document currency and the credit account currency.</p>
            <p>This is the rate quoted by the treasury department to the trade finance department excluding departmental spread.</p>
            <p>The department spread will be accepted in CUSTOMER.SPREAD field. The exchange rate including the rate spread will be customer credit rate and will be shown in CREDIT.CUST.RATE field.</p>
            <p>The CREDIT.CUST.RATE will be applied between the document currency and the credit account currency (DRAW.CURRENCY and PAYMENT.ACCOUNT.CURRENCY) if they differ.</p>
            <p>Default calculated from currency table, using current mid market spot rate.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal characters) (Optional Input).</p>
            <p>Input to this field is only allowed if the payment account is in a different currency to the draw currency.</p>
            <p>Mainly used in export transactions, when the exporter's credit account is in a different currency to the document currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASN.AC.WITH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the Account with Bank for the assignment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

