<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>LC.AMENDMENTS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INC.DEC.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the amount to be added to or deducted from the LC.AMOUNT, which will always be expressed </p>
            <p>in the currency defined in the field LC.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p> Increase amount is unsigned. Decrease amount has minus sign.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) 2-16 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters.</p>
            <p>(2) The decreased amount should neither be less than the LIABILITY amount of the Letter of Credit, nor the DRAWINGS under that Letter of Credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUING.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Name of the Bank that has issued the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the delivery keys used for the generation of Letter of Credit advice/documents/payments from the Electronic Delivery System.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">System generated. </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Acting as part of the delivery multivale set, this field provides the user with the ability to decide whether to send or withhold sending the delivery of any message produced under the contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options available are (Y)es - Send Message or (N)o - Do Not Send Message   </p>
            <p>Default is (Y)es</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>TAX.CODE</p>
            <p>Contains the Tax code used for computing the tax component for the said Charge/Commission. The value is defaulted from the relevant Commission/Charge table.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIABILITY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the actual LIABILITY.AMOUNT of Letter of Credit, at the time of input of Amendment</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field. </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.CURRENCY</p>
            <p>Identifies the currency in which charges are to be levied in. This can be different from that of LC Currency. This field will default currency from that of CHARGES.ACCOUNT if  input in LC else Currency of LC will be defaulted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be valid currency in the Currency Table.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only if Charge/Commission code is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.CODE</p>
            <p>Identifies the type of Commission or Charge to be levied for the transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid code in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE or FT.CHARGE.TYPE</p>
            <p>Associated Multi-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.CHARGED</field>
<desc>
            <p>PARTY.CHARGED</p>
            <p>Code to identify the party this charge applies to, that is from whom this charge must be taken. This could be different for each of the charge multi-value.</p>
            <p>This field can be set against the Opener, Beneficiary or some Third Party.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>O - Opener ; B - Beneficiary ; T - Third Party ( must be specified in       the field THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO.</p>
            <p>If not input then value will default from CHARGES.FROM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.TEXT.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format sub-value field for sending advices to participants in Syndicated LC's.This field will be mapped directly to tag 79 of  MT799 message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Accepts Swift characters.</p>
            <p>A sub-value set can hold 35 lines with 50 characters each</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.PERIOD</p>
            <p>Defines the number of times the charges are required to be taken. This is dependent on the minimum charge period of the CHARGE.CODE and the tenor of the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Default from value in CHARGE.CODE.</p>
            <p>User input will override the default value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPIRY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the current expiry date of Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.LCCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>TAX.LCCY.AMT</p>
            <p>Contains the local currency equivalent of the tax amount. When the tax amount is not in local currency, this amount is calculated on the charges debited at the mid market spot rate, at the appropriate Tax code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>TAX.AMT</p>
            <p>Based on the Tax code obtained from the Commission/Charge table, the system calculates any tax that is to be added to the Charge that is set in Tax code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.AMOUNT</p>
            <p>Using the conditions specified for the charge code in the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables, the system automatically calculates the amount to be charged in the LC currency. Input of an amount here will be in charge currency. This amount will be converted to the charge account currency using the exchange rate in the above field CHARGE.XCHG. </p>
            <p>Input of an amount, however, overrides the amount calculated and charge period will be of no significance.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard AMT field.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when Charge/Commission code is input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.SHARE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage of Share for each participant in Syndicated LC.The user may however, modify the share provided none of the participant's portion define in Facility tranche is overdrawn.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.XCHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.XCHG</p>
            <p>Exchange rate to be used between the charge debit account and the charge currency. If not input, then the mid-rate in the CHARGE.CCY.MARKET set in the LC.PARAMETERS will be used.</p>
            <p>If no currency market for charges is set then the default currency market for the LC will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the details relating to the Beneficiary of the Letter of Credit, such as Name and  Address.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the currency of Letter of Credit</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT FIELD . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE.DR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Debit tolerance percentage of the Letter of Credit at the time of input of Amendment</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.RECV.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Free text for additional information to be sent to the receiver or as captured from from Tag 72 of an Inward message.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>6 lines of 35 A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Text to be attached to the delivery message, Informative Field.</p>
            <p>Multivalue Field of 50 type A (Alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) Multivalue Field of 50 type A (Alphanumeric) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LATEST.SHIPMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the latest date for loading on Board/Dispatch/Taking in charge.</p>
            <p>Used for the production of documents/advice, stipulates the latest date for loading on Board/Dispatch/Taking in charge for goods shipped under the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) 11 Standard date format.</p>
            <p>(2) Date cannot be greater than Expiry date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSPORTATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the final destination of the goods.</p>
            <p>Used for the production of documents and advice stipulated, the final destination of the goods shipped under the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) 32 x 2 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether LIMIT has to be updated when the Amendment is authorized, but prior to use of Operation D in Letter of Credit. Input of value Yes creates a second limit line, after authorization, if there is an upward impact on the LIABILITY, which could happen by way of increase of INC.DEC.AMOUNT or increase of tolerance in INC.CR.AMOUNT. </p>
            <p>This is done by creating a second limit line, when the value YES is entered. It carries the Amendment reference. However, the user has the option to define 'YES' or 'NO' for each of the Amendment. When the value is NO, there is no second limit line, but the limit effect is carried out only when the Operation D is chosen in Letter of Credit and the AMEND.STATUS is APPROVED.</p>
            <p>This value however defaults with YES when the INC.DEC.AMOUNT is input with a positive value. The Letter of Credit, does not move to history, unless a decision on all the authorized Amendments is taken.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>WAIVE.CHARGES</p>
            <p>Decision field on Waiver of Charges under the Letter of Credit. If set to YES, no charges will be calculated, including default charges.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>TAX.ACC.AMT</p>
            <p>Contains the tax amount in the currency of the account from which charge is taken from. When the tax is taken from an account different from local currency, this field holds the amount of tax debited. This is used for position calculation if the charge currency is different from account currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INC.CR.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define the percentage to be added to the Letter of Credit amount (LC.AMOUNT) to calculate the LIABILITY.AMOUNT.</p>
            <p>A rate is specified here, which is used to calculate the LIABILITY.AMOUNT of the Letter of Credit by adding this percentage to the LC.AMOUNT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example: If the LC.AMOUNT = 1,000,000.00 and the percentage entered here = 10, then the LIABILITY.AMOUNT will be equal to 1,100,000.00.</p>
            <p>The value input in this field replaces PERCENTAGE.CR.AMT in Letter of Credit on approval of Amendment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) Standard rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal characters).</p>
            <p>(2) If this Field is entered, then MAXIMUM.CR.AMT must be left blank.</p>
            <p>(3) Holds positive values only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.BASE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.BASE.AMT</p>
            <p>Contains the base amount on which the charges would be calculated. This field should be input if charges are not input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard AMT format</p>
            <p>Mandatory for charge calculation if charge amount is not input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>For Export/Advising Letter of Credit this is the Issuing Bank's/Opener's reference. </p>
            <p>For outward collection it is the Customer Reference Number and for Inward Collection it is the Remitting Banks Reference Number.</p>
            <p>If the Letter of Credit has any value in the field EXTERNAL.REFERENCE, the same would be defaulted. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />1-16 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  <p /><p /><p />Mandatory input.    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-set, this field is used to determine the message type to which the user wishes to amend the delivery and is used exclusively with the fields &lt;MSG.CLASS.NO&gt;, &lt;OVR.CARRIER&gt;, &lt;ADDRESSEE&gt; and &lt;SEND.MESSAGE&gt;.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 4 numeric characters. (Optional input).   </p>
            <p>The category code must be defined on the DE.MESSAGE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the issue date of Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13,DOCTYPES.Helptext">Holds message types of all inward messages received.</p>
        <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13,DOCTYPES.Helptext">For example, if MT707 is received, then the value ‘MT707’ will be stored in this field.</p>
        <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13,DOCTYPES.Helptext">Associated multi value with INWARD.MSG.REF. System maintained field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.EXPIRY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the new date on which the unused liability amount under the letter of credit will be liquidated/reversed by the system.</p>
            <p>If the user doesn’t input any value, system will default the date based on values in the field NEW.ADV.EXP.DATE and EXPIRY.DAYS field of LC.PARAMETERS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date Format or Code.</p>
            <p>Cannot be less than the ISSUE.DATE and must be greater than or equal to NEW.ADV.EXPIRY.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.STATUS</p>
            <p>Code to identify the required status of the Commission/Charge, whether it is to be collected immediately or deferred or waived.</p>
            <p>When the status is NULL, the Commission/Charge amount will be calculated and written in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES. No accounting will take place. This has to be collected later using Operation C in LC, at which time Tax if any will also be collected. </p>
            <p>If the status is 2, Commission/Charge will be collected immediately along with Tax if any.</p>
			<p>If the status is 15, the charge is waived and cannot be collected in the future. If is stored in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES as a charge that has been waived.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input NULL or 2.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.AMEND.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>LC.AMEND.NUMBER is the id of the LC.AMENDMENTS record.Automatically allocated.First 12 digits made up from the Letter of Credit number input via the LETTER.OF.CREDIT application,last two digits automatically allocated in the range 1-99.LC.AMENDMENTS key is made up of the LC record id plus three additional uniquely identifying the LC.AMENDMENTS.The format is [LC.NUMBER]A[NN],where NN is automatically assigned from 01-99.</p>
            <p> 15 ALPHANUMERIC characters.Should be a valid LETTER.OF.CREDIT record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHIP.DESPATCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Multi-value field indicates the place of Dispatch or Taking in charge of the goods or Loading on board.</p>
            <p>Used for the production of documents and advice, stipulates the place of Dispatch or Taking in charge of the goods or Loading on board for shipments made under the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) 4 x 32,  type S alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field enables the user to override the defaulted carrier for a particular message type and select a new carrier.</p>
            <p>For example : If a specific message is generated by SWIFT, the user is able to override this by choosing other available options from the CARRIER table, eg TELEX or PRINT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid record in the CARRIER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.PARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>TAX.PARTY</p>
            <p>Code to identify the party this tax applies to. This field identifies from whom the tax is to be taken. It can be Opener, Beneficiary or Third Party.</p>
            <p>Value is defaulted from PARTY.CHARGED.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
            <p>O - Opener; B - Beneficiary; T - Third Party (as defined in       THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field contains a message class ID, (defined in EB.ADVICES). There may be many classes specified, but only classes, which are related to the operation, will be triggered.</p>
            <p>Similar to MSG.CLASS.NO of LC Application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.DESPATCH.DET</field>
<desc>
            <p>It denotes the Port of Loading/Airport of Departure.populated to 44E tag of 707 message.</p>
            <p>SWIFT related field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.This field displays a number generated automatically by the system which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of LC.AMENDMENTS.The system will automatically insert a number into this field that will refer to a statement entry  or a category entry depending on the value contained in the corresponding multivalue fields.</p>
            <p> Internal multivalue field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the current status of the Amendment (PENDING/APPROVED/REJECTED)</p>
            <p>Default value PENDING.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by system when decision is taken on Amendment in Letter of Credit using Operation 'D'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>(1) NO INPUT field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADV.BK.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains details relating to the ADVISING.BANK of the Letter Of Credit,such as advising bank customer number or name and address.This field automatically populated from Lettre Of Credit record.This field contains the number or mnemonic of the advising bank and will be defaulted from the field ADVISING.BK.CUSTNO from LETTER.OF.CREDIT record.If the field ADVISING.BK is entered in LC record,then the name and address will be defaulted from LC record.</p>
            <p> System maintained field.NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.DATE</p>
            <p>Identifies the date on which charge was raised, although not necessarily taken.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.ACC.AMT</p>
            <p>Contains the Charge/Commission amount in the currency of the account that the Charge/Commission is taken from.</p>
            <p>When the Charge/Commission is taken from an account that is in a different currency to the CHARGE.CURRENCY, then this field is used to hold the amount that was actually debited. This is used for position update if the currency is not local. The field is automatically updated when the Charge/Commission is taken from the account using the mid spot rate at that instance.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard AMT format</p>
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHIPMENT.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies the period of time during which the goods are to be loaded on Board/Dispatched/Taken in charge.</p>
            <p>Used for the production of documents/advice, stipulates the period of time which the goods are to be loaded on Board/Dispatched/Taken in charge.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>6 x 65 type S alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>202.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for Sender to Receiver (i.e. Sending bank to Receiving bank) Information. Any information entered into this field will appear on a S.W.I.F.T. MT202 message (General Financial Institution Transfer). </p>
            <p>It may be used to provide instructions or additional information for the Receiver, Intermediary, Account with Institution or Beneficiary Institution. </p>
            <p>This field corresponds to field 72 on S.W.I.F.T. messages, and must never be used for information for which another field is intended, or for instructions not required in a message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type SW Multivalue field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain a codeword followed by further information.</p>
            <p>All code words must be valid code words as defined in S.W.I.F.T. documentation and must conform to the rules specified. Use of invalid code words will cause a message rejection when validated by S.W.I.F.T.</p>
            <p>Further code words and information can be entered in subsequent multivalues, but additional information continued on a new line must be preceded by a double slash '//'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>747.BNK.TO.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Swift related field.This multivalue free text field allows for additional information to be passed onto the reimbursing bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.AMT.COVERED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is to specify any additional amounts covered by this Letter of Credit, e.g. charges, transportation costs. Used only for the production of Letter of Credit documents and advice, to specify any additional amounts that are covered by this Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) Multi-value Field of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESSEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the user to divert a particular message type to another (third) party.</p>
            <p>The user has a number of options:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Simple insertion of a name or address. This will re-route the message in     PRINT format to the named party.   </p>
            <p>The code 'TX-' followed by a telex number. This will re-route the message     by TELEX to the number detailed.   </p>
            <p>The code 'SW-' followed by a SWIFT. code. This will re-route the message     by SWIFT to the respective bank.   </p>
            <p>The code 'C-' followed by a valid customer number or mnemonic. This will     re-route the message in PRINT format to the customer indiated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>50 Alphanumeric character field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.AMEND.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the number identifying an amendment performed as captured from the inward message.</p>
            <p>The value represents Tag23E of MT707.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Numeric field with a maximum value of 99.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.ADV.EXP.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the new date on which the Letter of Credit expires from the beneficiary’s point of view.</p>
            <p>Mapped to tag 31E of MT707.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
            <p>Optional input Field.</p>
            <p>Must be greater than ISSUE.DATE and less than or equal to NEW.EXPIRY.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE.CR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Credit tolerance percentage of the Letter of Credit at the time of input of Amendment</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PENDING.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the total amount of all the pending Amendments pertaining the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from the field TOT.PEND.MVMT of LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.ADV.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System populated field.</p>
            <p>This field holds the activity number, which is triggered by the latest activity in the life-cycle of the transaction.</p>
            <p>Similar to ACTIVITY.CODE in the LC Application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.ACCT</p>
            <p>The account from which charges are to be collected. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid account.</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORT.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>AMORT.CHARGES</p>
            <p>Defines whether charges are to be amortized over the life of the LC or not.</p>
            <p> If set to YES, the charges collected will be amortized from Issue date to the Advice Expiry date.</p>
            <p>This value will default from that in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE or FT.CHARGE.TYPE but can be overridden.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTICIPANT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the Participant who is part of the Syndicated LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field</p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.AMD.DOC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field holds the new amount of the documentary credit, reflecting the increase or decrease in document amount, obtained from Tag 34B of Inward message.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates Corresponding charge code for tax  defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Associated multivalue field associated with fields TAX.CODE through to TAX.DATE</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT202.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.LCCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHARGE.LCCY.AMT</p>
            <p>Contains the local currency equivalent of the Charge/Commission amount. If the Charge/Commission amount is not in local currency, then this field is populated with the local equivalent using the mid-rate.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard AMT format.</p>
            <p>System maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participants share in LC amendment amount for Syndicated LC.System defaulted field as per participant share defined in LETTER.OF.CREDIT. PART.AMOUNT = AMENDMENT AMOUNT * Participant share defined in LETTER.OF.CREDIT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field.</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.BANK.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used when a message is sent by a Bank other than the Issuing Bank, i.e., it is sent by an Advising Bank.</p>
            <p>This field specifies the reference of the Issuing Bank. If ISS.BANK.REF is input in LC, the value would be defaulted here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>16 Type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.AMEND.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date on which the Issuing Bank considers that the Credit was amended or as captured from the Inward message.</p>
            <p>This represents Tag30 of MT707.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.CR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the maximum amount that can be drawn under this Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>Used to define the maximum credit amount that can be drawn under the LC. The existing value as in Letter of Credit is populated into this field. If the Amendments is done for a change of percentage, INC.CR.AMT, the value in this field has to be deleted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid input terms: MAXIMUM or NOT EXCEEDING.</p>
            <p> Can only be entered if the Field INC.CR.AMT is blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEC.CR.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the negative tolerance relative to the documentary credit amount as a percentage or as captured from an Inward message.</p>
            <p>Example:</p>
            <p>If the LC.AMOUNT = $1,000,000.00 and the percentage entered here = 10, then the minimum drawing expected under this letter of credit is $900,000.00 and the maximum is $1,000,000.00. However, the LIABILITY.AMOUNT will be equal to $1,000,000.00.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field holds the inward delivery reference for the corresponding message type.</p>
        <p>For example, in R20120828160574535800, ‘R’ identifies an inward message.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINAL.DESTINATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>It denotes the Place of Final Destination for the goods when the goods are shipped.In LC.AMENDMENTS this field denotes the amendment in final destination.It will be populated to the tag 44B in 707 message with the maximum of 65 characters.</p>
            <p> SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the actual Document amount of Letter of Credit, at the time of input of Amendment</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO INPUT field . </p>
            <p>This field is automatically populated from LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTH.REIMB.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the date on when the original authorisation to reimburse(MT740) was sent.This field will be mapped from Tag 30 when inward MT747 message is processed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date Field</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.EVENT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to identify the status of the Amendment request initiated through CIB.</p>
			<p>Acceptable values are:</p>
			<p>With Bank - This status will be updated automatically when the amendment request is authorised by Corporate Authoriser </p>
			<p>and it shows the action is pending from Bank User.</p>
			<p>With Customer - This status will be manually selected by the Bank User when the request is to be sent back to </p>
			<p>Corporate User for any queries</p>
			<p>Approved - This status will be manually selected by the Bank User when the request is accepted by the Bank.</p>
			<p>Rejected - This status will be manually selected by the Bank User when the request is rejected by the Bank.</p>         
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.ADDL.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field to input any additional information by the Bank User complimenting the value in the field IB.EVENT.STATUS.</p>        
			<p>Free Text Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.LIMIT.EXCEED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field to input the reason for requesting the amendment when the limit is exceeded.</p>          
			<p>This field must open up only when limit exceeds override is encountered.If Corporate inputter inputs any value </p>
			<p>in this field,the limit override must be suppressed.</p>
			<p>Free Text Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.CUST.TO.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field to input any information that needs to be conveyed to the bank by Corporate User.</p>         
			<p>Free Text Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.BK.TO.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field to input any information that needs to be conveyed to the Corporate User by bank.</p>   
			<p>Free Text Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to identify the date on which the amendment is initiated.</p>
			<p>System updated field and defaults to Today's date</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date Field</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>