<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>LC.DISCOUNT.BALANCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a part of the associated Multi-value set representing the date up to which (last date of the schedule) the Discount Rate/Amount and Load Rate/Amount would be applicable.</p>
            <p>The value is generally the maturity date of the contract. But in the event of the contract being amended through DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS, effecting a Rate or Amount change during the tenor of the contract, specified  through the field EFFECTIVE.DATE, then this field holds the end  date of a schedule.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This signifies the Discount Amount applicable on the Contract for the period mentioned in this associated multi-value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the total Discount component under the Deal and is expressed in terms of the DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>The value is same as  DISCOUNT.AMT in Drawings application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the related DRAWINGS id</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.AMEND.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>A discounted Drawing can be amended only through DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS. The ID of  DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS  is  that of Drawing appended with sequence number. </p>
            <p>The value stored in this field represents the next of the sequence number if the Drawing were to  be amended through DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LD.AMORT.TO.DTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Load component  amortized till  date. The value is the same as that in Drawings Application and is expressed in DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a part of the associated Multi-value set representing the date from which (first date of the schedule) the Discount Rate/Amount and Load Rate/Amount would be applicable.</p>
            <p>The value is generally the DISC.EFF.DATE of Drawings application. But in the event of the contract being amended through DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS, effecting a Rate or Amount change during the tenor of the contract, specified  through the field EFFECTIVE.DATE, then such date is held as the start of a schedule.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency of the Drawing. The value is  defaulted from DRAW.CURRENCY of Drawings application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the Discount rate last applied on the Contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a Numeric field and shall be used to input to indicate the additional number of days for which the interest on the discounted drawing is to be recovered. This amount thus calculated for the number of days input in this field, will be in addition to the Discount and Load amount calculated. This field thus represents the cushion that could be made available in the event of the settlement being delayed for a Discounted Drawing. This shall however have no impact on the Maturity Date of the Drawing. Amortization of amount thus collected shall take place only till the MATURITY.REVIEW date or the NEW.MATURITY.DATE as input. In the event of such Discounted Drawing being extended using DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS, the amortization shall take place till the NEW.MATURITY.DATE. However, if the same is matured online or back-dated, then the amortization would have taken place only till such date.The input in this field is permitted only at the first instance of discounting a Drawing. The field opens up only if the DiscountLoad rate is input. 
  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This signifies the Load Amount applicable on the Contract for the period mentioned in this associated multi-value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This  represents the DOCUMENT.AMOUNT in Drawings application and is expressed in the DRAW.CURRENCY of Drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This signifies the Load Rate applicable on the Contract for the period mentioned in this associated multi-value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIS.AMORT.TO.DTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Discount component  amortized till  date. The value is the same as that in Drawings Application and is expressed in DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIS.AMT.ACR.TDY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.PARTY.CHRG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This  field represents the party by whom Discount Charges are to be borne, viz., O for Opener or B for Beneficiary.</p>
            <p>The value is defaulted from DIS.PARTY.CHRD of Drawings application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This signifies the Discount Rate applicable on the Contract for the period mentioned in this associated multi-value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.AMRT.TODTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Grace Amount component  amortized till  date. The value is expressed in DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the total Load Amount applicable on the Contract. This is  expressed in terms of DRAW.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>The value would be the same as in LOAD.AMOUNT in Drawings application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>  This field holds the value computed for the period of GRACE.DAYS in a discounted drawing, at the Discount/Load rate input. 
  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents  the Load rate last applied on the Drawing contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

