<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>LC.PARTIAL.BALANCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PORT.UNCONF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the Unutilized portion of  the Unconfirmed amount under that Draw set of the Letter of credit. This amount is used to raise accounting for the Unconfirmed portion at the time of revolution, either as a 'MAT' component, if Non-cumulative or as the carry forward component, if cumulative.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.PCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the percentage split for each of the Draw type with the appropriate Time bands as in the Letter of Credit application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This file is maintained by the system. The Id being a valid revolving Export Letter of Credit that is partially confirmed.</p>
            <p>This file is mainly used to keep track of the utilization of the Letter of Credit, when the same is partially confirmed and is of revolving in nature. </p>
            <p>This is mainly so because, in the case of such Letters of Credit, when Drawing is done, the liquidation happens for the Confirmed portion first and then the Unconfirmed portion. So at the time of revolution the system has to pass the requisite entries either for Maturity of the Unutilized portion or Carry forward the same, depending on whether the LC is of Non-Cumulative or Cumulative in nature respectively.</p>
            <p>The values in this file are stored in the Currency of the Letter of credit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.CONF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the Unutilized portion of  the Confirmed amount under that Draw set of the Letter of credit. This amount is used to raise accounting for the confirmed portion at the time of revolution, either as a 'MAT' component, if Non-cumulative or as the carry forward component, if cumulative.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACPT.TM.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the Time Band of the corresponding Draw set as stated in the Letter of credit. This is displayed together with the Payment percentage as in the Letter of Credit application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.CONF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the portion of Drawings done under the Confirmed part of the respective Draw set of the Partially confirmed revolving Letter of credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the DRAW.TYPE as seen in the Letter of credit under which the Drawing is/to be done. The values are stored together with the Time band and the Payment percentage.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.UNCONF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the portion of Drawings done under the Unconfirmed part of the respective Draw set of the Partially confirmed revolving Letter of credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

