<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>LC.PARAMETERS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file contains data and Parameter fields required for L/C processing which are not obtainable from any other File, (there is only one record) and facilitates the addition, amendment and deletion of fields on the record. </p>
            <p>        The purpose of this file is to hold static data that is standard for Letter of Credit and drawings processing, used for: </p>
            <p>               a) Input defaults (Closure Days, Currency, Market, Position Type) </p>
            <p>               b) Entries Generation (Transaction Codes and A/C Numbers) </p>
            <p>               c) End of Day Processing (Pre-Advise Days) </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DIS.RETAIN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category Code where excess interest will be posted if discounted drawings is amended </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when Discounted drawings is</p>
            <p>        Amended and Return Interest field in DR.DISC.AMENDMENTS is set to NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters. (Optional input) The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file. </p>
            <p>        If left blank existing discount category code will be used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEL.WITHNO.DISCREP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Messages of type 750 are only produced for export letters of credit. This field determines whether or not a message will be produced if there are no discrepancies on the drawing contract. </p>
            <p>        Where this field is set to YES, a 750 message is produced regardless of any discrepancies on the drawing. If it is not set to YES then the 750 message will only be produced when the drawing has discrepencies (i.e. the DISCREPANCY field is not set to NO). </p>
            <p>        In addition, where this field is set to YES the production of MT 1750 will also take place. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNDER.RES.TX.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts a valid transaction code for the Debit leg of Payment Under reserve.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.PREV.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.TRAN.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Credit A/C Entries for L/Cs Discounted with Load amounts. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to Discounting an Accepted Drawing with a Load amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on the TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WP.PATH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the full UNIX path name (directory) where the WordPerfect files for free format L/C text reside. </p>
            <p>        Should contain a valid path name where WordPerfect is to be used to enter free format text for L/C Documents. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-50 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.UNCOLL.CATRG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Uncollected Category Code for claimed charges. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when claim charges are made. </p>
            <p>        This field is used if Uncollected.Categ is to be charged and at End of Day this input is moved to Uncollected Catrg. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLECTIONS.DUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the number of days prior to MATURITY.REVIEW.DATE. </p>
            <p>        When the number of days that collections falling due in the period today + COLLECTIONS.DUE days, or already past the due date and not yet actioned will be reported on COLLECTIONS.DUE.REPORT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        2 numeric characters.  (Null defaults to 1)  Valid input is in the range 1-99 number of days prior to MATURITY.REVIEW.DATE, Null input will default to 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.CLASS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>LC.CLASS.TYPE and EB.CLASS.NO are used to formulate the class mapping between L/C internal class and EB.MESSAGE.CLASS. The main driving concept of ACTIVITY and CLASS has lend itself to facilitate the user by automatically trigger only the message related to the operation, which user are currently do. In a sense, the system will try to default a sensible CLASS tiding to corresponding activity, and populate the information on the L/C transaction. Consequently, the user can take control of the class to choose whether he/she wants to produce as per suggestion by the system. </p>
            <p>        The following types are valid types:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        + BASIC.MESSAGE</p>
            <p>        + NOTIFICATION</p>
            <p>        + REIMBURSING</p>
            <p>        + ADVISE.THRU</p>
            <p>        + ADDITIONAL.MSG</p>
            <p>        + PAYMENT.BANK</p>
            <p>        + PAYMENT.CUST</p>
            <p>        + COVER.BANK</p>
            <p>        + RECEIVE.NOTIFY</p>
            <p>        + CREDIT.CUST</p>
            <p>        + DEBIT.CUST</p>
            <p>        + PROVISION.CREDIT</p>
            <p>        + PROVISION.DEBIT</p>
            <p>        + USER.DEFINE1</p>
            <p>        + USER.DEFINE2</p>
            <p>         + USER.DEFINE9</p>
            <p>        + USERDEFINE10</p>
            <p>        It is worth to note that BASIC.MESSAGE, NOTIFICATION and USER.DEFINE1 will always be triggered regardless of operations. The BASIC.MESSAGE has intentionally designed to attach the message class, which are going to send to correspondence bank, i.e. Issuing Bank, Advising Bank, Collecting Bank or Remitting Bank. The NOTIFICATION class is for the advice to Banks client, i.e. Applicant, Beneficiary, Drawer, or Drawee. And USER.DEFINE1 is an additional class for any additional message. For more detail, please consult T24 Users Guide.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Only the following values are allowed : BASIC.MESSAGE, NOTIFICATION, REIMBURSING, ADVISE.THRU, ADDITIONAL.MSG, PAYMENT.BANK, PAYMENT.CUST, COVER.BANK, RECEIVE.NOTIFY, CREDIT.CUST, DEBIT.CUST, PROVISION.CREDIT, PROVISION.DEBIT, USER.DEFINE1, USER.DEFINE2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.CAT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Load Category code for Discounted Drawings with a Load amount. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when Accepted Drawings are Discounted with a Load amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)  The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARAMETER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to the LC.PARAMETERS File and contains the value "SYSTEM" </p>
            <p>        Contains those Data and Parameter fields required for L/C processing which are not obtainable from any other File. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        2 numeric characters (Not input field).  There is only one record on this file and therefore only "SYSTEM" is allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Signifies  the Transaction  code  to be used  when Provision (Cash Margin) debit entries  are passed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>        A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>        The following range is  permitted: 500 to 599</p>
            <p>        Must be the key to a valid entry on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVOL.ADVICE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>In the case of revolving Letter of Credit, this field facilitates control of the number of days prior to generation of advice of the next revolving cycle.</p>
            <p>        Accepts a valid number that determines the number of days prior to revolution the advice is to get triggered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Optional input.</p>
            <p>        Input represents number of Days.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHRG.CAL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserve for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.SWIFT.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future releases. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMBINE.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future releases. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.CAL.BASE</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Decides whether provision needs to be calculated on LC face value or liability amount.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Validation Rules</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Valid Options – LC.AMT and LIABILITY.AMT.</p>
                <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Default value – LIABILITY.AMT..</p>
                <p value="3" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Mandatory field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserve for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts any valid routine. Default routine DR.CALCULATE.INTEREST is attached for fetching the interest rate from the PERIODIC.INTEREST table, when a Drawing is discounted. The routine accepts 4 parameters only, viz.,</p>
            <p>         Incoming Parameters</p>
            <p>        ******************</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Outgoing Value</p>
            <p>        *************</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Client specific routine can be attached in this field to perform interest rate calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Accepts any valid Info-Basic routine.</p>
            <p>        Mandatory if INTEREST.KEY is input.</p>
            <p>        The routine name can be up to 40 characters in length.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSURE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the number of days after the Expiry date when L/Cs will be removed from the system. </p>
            <p>        For L/Cs that are not pre-advised (OPERATION not = P) is the number of days required as a default, to determine the CLOSING.DATE of the L/C. The number of days will be added to EXPIRY.DATE of the L/C to determine the CLOSING.DATE. </p>
            <p>        This field will be used as a default (i.e will only be used if a specific Closing Date has not been input for the L/C). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        3 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>        It must contain numeric data in the range 001-999.</p>
            <p>        If no data is input for this field it must be set to         zeroes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.O.ACCR.CATG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.SUBDIVISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of transaction when an entry is raised for internal account, i.e. payment </p>
            <p>        This is the subdivision to be used whenever an internal A/C number is generated by the system for A/C entries related to L/C payments (it is the equivalent of a G/L sub-ledger number). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        4 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)  Only numeric characters are allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALCULATE.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Indicate here whether amortization of charges has to be reversed and recalculated if a drawing is amended.</p>
            <p>        The recalculation is not done unless this field is set to "YES".</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLL.EXTN.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>In order to prevent the Collection documents from Expiring and its subsequent move to History this field has been introduced. In other words this field keeps the Collection document live as long as it is not fully utilized.</p>
            <p>        It accepts a number, that represents number of Days, and on the Original Expiry Date, the system rolls over the Expiry date by this many number of days. This reset is also carried out on the Closing Date and on the Limit line. </p>
            <p>        This is an End of Day activity and such a roll-over would take place only if the LC has any liability outstanding.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Numeric input.</p>
            <p>        Applicable only for Collection Documents.</p>
            <p>        Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.TRANS.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the transaction code to be used on Debit A/C entries for payment under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to payments made under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = DEBIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAFTS.ISSUED.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the A/C to be credited for Drafts issued in making payments for Drawings under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>        The account in this field will be used when the PAYMENT.METHOD field for L/C = code "D" (Draft) and the L/C amount is not in Local Currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        2-14 numeric characters relating to a Nostro Account or  3-10 type MNE mnemonic characters (will be converted to      Account.Number)</p>
            <p>        The account number must not be in a Local Currency.</p>
            <p>        The A/C number input must be present on ACCOUNT File.</p>
            <p>        (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.PREV.YEAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMB.SUBDIVISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of transaction when an entry is raised for an internal account. </p>
            <p>        This is the subdivision to be used whenever an internal A/C number is generated by the system for A/C entries related to L/C Reimbursement (it is the equivalent of a G/L sub-ledger number). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-4 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)  Only numeric characters are allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WRITE.OFF.TR.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Credit A/C Entries for charges written off under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to written off charges made under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMB.TRANS.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Credit A/C Entries for L/C Reimbursement. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to reimbursement. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNCOLLECTED.CATRG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Uncollected Category Code for claimed charges. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when claim charges are made. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters. (Mandatory Input)  The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUES.ISSUED.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the account number to be credited when a payment under a drawing is made by cheque. </p>
            <p>        The account in this field will be used when the PAYMENT.METHOD field for L/C = code "CH" (cheque) and the L/C amount is in Local Currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        6-12 type A (alphanumeric) characters         or  3-10 type A (alphanumeric) account mnemonic  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>        The account number must be in a Local Currency.</p>
            <p>        The A/C number input must be present on ACCOUNT File.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.ACCR.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this  field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDUCE.LIMIT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not currently used.  Needed for future releases. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.TRAN.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Debit leg of Accounting entries when Multiple debits are raised from Drawings using the Assignment related fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>        Must be a valid TRANSACTION code with DEBIT.CREDIT.IND set as DEBIT.</p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500 - 599.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.ACCR.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEL.CHARGES.ADV</field>
<desc>
            <p>Y = charges acc. ben. taken from the CRF and credited to P/L. charges then claimed from the beneficiary. after payment manually entered on LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES - </p>
            <p>        NO = ben charges only taken at time of payment</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>        The values are permitted are Y or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.LD.CAT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Load Category code for Discounted Drawings with a Load amount. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when Accepted Drawings are Discounted with a Load amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>        The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>        This field is used if LOAD.CAT.CODE is to be changed and at end of day this input is moved to LOAD.CAT.CODE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field decides whether to hit the limit at the stage of 'IO'(Initial operation while opening LC through ARC) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> It can accept accepts two values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p> Default value is 'NO' </p>
            <p> 'YES' will hit the limit at 'IO' stage </p>
            <p> 'NO' will not hit the limit at 'IO' stage </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.WR.OFF.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Write off Category Code for claimed charges. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when claim charges are written off. </p>
            <p>        This field is used if WRITE.OFF.PL is to be changed and at End of Day this input is moved to WRITE.OFF.PL. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters.  The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.CLASS.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used in conjunction with the previous field to populate the class on the L/C transaction. Without this field set, the user will not be able to control the delivery message. This message class should be used in EB.ADVICES, which are associated to LC activity.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>      Cannot use the same EB.CLASS.NO for several LC.CLASS.TYPE (only 1 to 1 mapping is allowed).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.ACCR.TRCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.TRANS.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Credit A/C Entries for Payments under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to payments made under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHG.TOLERANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>EXCHG.TOLERANCE allows input between 1 and 100% and sets a tolerance by which the provision and limit amounts may differ where Foreign Exchange calculations are involved </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        A percentage</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROK.CAL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.AMORT.FQY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the accrual cycle period for posting commission accruals.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Standard T24 frequency field.</p>
                <p value="2">Only monthly or daily frequency is allowed.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIS.CYCLE.F.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the frequency with which interest relating to Discounted Drawings will be accrued under L/C deals in foreign currency. </p>
            <p>        The system allows the user to define different accrual frequencies for local and foreign currencies. </p>
            <p>        Input at this field specifies the frequency with which interest is to be accrued in foreign currency.  The user has the choice of either daily or monthly accruals and the following examples define the various options: </p>
            <p>                  (i)  12 DEC 1985 D - this input specifies that the first accrual                shall be on 12th Dec 1985 and thereafter at daily (D)                intervals. </p>
            <p>                 (ii) 31 JAN 1985 M0131 - this input specifies that the first               accrual will be on 31st Jan 1985 and thereafter at monthly               (M01) intervals on the last day (31) of each month. </p>
            <p>                (iii) 31 JAN 1985 M0115 - this input specifies that the first               accrual will be on 31st Jan 1985 and thereafter at monthly               (M01) intervals on the fifteenth day (15) of each month. </p>
            <p>        This field is updated automatically whenever the accrual process has taken place and so unless the accrual cycle is to be changed, the only time attention needs to be paid to this field is when the first 'off-line' is to be run.  Prior to the first 'off-line' of the system, the date entered here must be equal to or greater than the 'NEXT.RUN.DATE' field in the appropriate BATCH job (LC.END.OF.DAY).  If it is greater than the date specified on the batch record then the update of the batch job NEXT.RUN.DATE must coincide with the date entered here at some point in the future. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        Standard frequency format. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>        Must be a valid date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPIRY.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p> Contains the number of days to be added after the advice date inorder to default EXPIRY.DATE of LC </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 3 numeric characters </p>
            <p> It must contain numeric data in the range 001-999.</p>
            <p> If no data is input for this field it must be set to zero.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Transaction code to be used when Provision (Cash Margin) credit entries are passed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. </p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The following range is permitted:       500...599</p>
            <p>        Must be the key to a valid entry on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Input in this field determines the key to be used for fetching interest rates from the PERIODIC.INTEREST table in a discounted drawing contract which uses Tiered system of rate calculation. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Accepts any 2-digit number. This key along with the date and currency determined in the Drawings application is used to fetch the rate from PERIODIC.INTEREST table.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Accepts any 2 digit number</p>
            <p>        Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAFT.PRINT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the default DRAFT.PRINT field for L/C transactions if this is not entered on the deal. </p>
            <p>        If this field is set to yes then a Draft print of the L/C documents will be printed when the deal is entered into the system (before Authorization),  so that all details can be vetted before authorization. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        'Y' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the default Position Type for L/C transactions if the field is not entered on the L/C. </p>
            <p>        Indicates the position the transaction will be recorded under, e.g. Trading, Investment, Reserve, etc. </p>
            <p>        LC is restricted to allow TR gaap alone (Mandatory input). This type must be present on the FX.POS.TYPE File</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        Only gaap type TR is allowed </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.ADVISE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the number of days after ISSUE.DATE that PRE-ADVISED L/Cs will be removed from the file if no action is taken. </p>
            <p>        For pre-advised L/Cs the number of days in this field is added to ISSUED.DATE to produce the CLOSING.DATE if CLOSING.DATE is not entered, i.e ISSUE.DATE + PRE.ADVISE.DAYS = CLOSING.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-3 numeric characters.  It must contain numeric data in the range 1-366.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.C.ACCR.CATG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACKWARD.DELIVERY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Delivery process in LETTER.OF.CREDIT and DRAWINGS module has been revised to allow you to produce additional message/advice other than standard ones provided by the system. Through the new soft-delivery mechanism, the user can attach any additional message send via delivery.</p>
            <p>        If this field is left blank or has value YES in it, the system will go through the old mapping process. The existing mapping record will be maintained. In other words, if you have used the L/C Application before G10.1.02, you still can use the existing advice or swift without any changes. And you can instantly make use of this new flexibile mechanism.</p>
            <p>        If this field is set to NO, the system will entirely skip the old mapping process. In other word, the mapping records, i.e. mostly 700 and 400 ranges, which has been defined before G10.1.02 have to be changed to correspond to the new HANDOFF information. This option is only advised for a new implementation. For further information, please consult T24 User's Manual.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.PRFT.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The category for FX P and  L arising from LC activities.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Is an existing CATEGORY.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.CALC.BASE</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Decides whether provision needs to be calculated on LC face value or liability amount.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Validation Rules</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Valid Options – LC.AMT and LIABILITY.AMT.</p>
                <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Default value – LIABILITY.AMT..</p>
                <p value="3" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Mandatory field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.TRAN.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Credit A/C Entries for L/Cs Discounted. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to Discounting an accepted Drawing. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on the TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = CREDIT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.USANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the number of days prior to MATURITY.REVIEW.DATE. </p>
            <p>        The number of days that usance drawings maturing in the period today + MATURITY.USANCE days, or already past maturity and not yet matured will be reported on MATURING.USANCE.PAYMENTS.REPORT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        2 numeric characters - (Null Defaults to 1).  Valid data is in the range 1-99 number of days prior to MATURITY.REVIEW.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CCY.MKT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        For Charges within LC and Drawings application, a separate currency market can be defined and the same can be invoked from this filed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        : </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETURN.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether the excess commission amount calculated on account of principal decrease has to be returned to the customer or not.</p>
            <p>Acceptable values are YES or No</p>
            <p>Defaulted at the LC input level.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>        This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLAIM.ENTRIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies whether charge claim entries are to be made whereby any charges due from the beneficiary are debited from the CRF and credit to P/L, and then claimed from the Beneficiary in order to credit the CRF. </p>
            <p>        If this field is set to 'Y' then if any charges are for the account of the Beneficiary they are initially taken from the CRF 'CLM' bucket and credited to the charge P/L account.  The charges are then claimed from the Beneficiary.  When the Beneficiary pays the charge, this is to be entered manually on the LC/ACCOUNT.BALANCES application,  so that the CRF 'CLM' bucket can be reimbursed.  If the field is set to 'NO' then Beneficiary charges are not taken until a payment is made via a Drawing when the charges will be deducted from the payment amount and credited to the charge P/L account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        'Y' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>B.P.ISSUED.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the A/C to be credited for all Banker's Payments issued in making payments for Drawings under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>        The account in this field will be used when the PAYMENT.METHOD field for L/C = code "BP" (Bankers Payment) and the L/C amount is in Local Currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        2-14 numeric characters relating to a Nostro Account or 3-10 type MNE mnemonic characters (will be converted to      Account.Number)</p>
            <p>        The account number must be in a Local Currency.</p>
            <p>        The A/C number input must be present on ACCOUNT File.</p>
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNCONFIRMED.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>        In an unconfirmed LETTER.OF.CREDIT  the limit line in the absence of a specific LIMIT.PARAMETER, is set against the information limit line as defaulted from the LIMIT.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        When a LETTER.OF.CREDIT is partially confirmed, the limit line is split and one is set against the confirmed portion and the other against the unconfirmed. When this information limit line is considered redundant in a partially confirmed Letter of Credit, this may be suppressed by assigning 'NO' to this field. If set to 'YES' the information limit line appears.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        For Example:</p>
            <p>         If an unconfirmed Letter of Credit is issued for GBP 100,000, the limit line would look like this:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        CREDIT.LINE.NO.... 100054.0009700.01.100054 BOE:Lett Cred:BOE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        1 TXN.DATA.......... TF0115200001\GBP\-100000\20010803\BNK\-100000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        This when partially confirmed for GBP 40,000, would appear in two lines:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        CREDIT.LINE.NO.... 100054.0002000.01.100054 BOE:Lett Cred:BOE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        1 TXN.DATA.......... TF0115200001\GBP\-40000\20010803\BNK\-40000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        CREDIT.LINE.NO.... 100054.0009700.01.100054 BOE:Lett Cred:BOE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        1 TXN.DATA.......... TF0115200001\GBP\-60000\20010803\BNK\-60000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        In the above case, the second limit line is only for information purposes. This can now be suppressed by setting the value "NO" to this field. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        The resultant display would be:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        CREDIT.LINE.NO.... 100054.0002000.01.100054 BOE:Lett Cred:BOE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        1 TXN.DATA.......... TF0115200001\GBP\-40000\20010803\BNK\-40000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Suppression of Information limit line is done only if the Letter of Credit is partially confirmed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Valid inputs are 'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
            <p>        One time input and cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIS.CYCLE.L.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the frequency with which interest relating to Discounted Drawings will be accrued under L/C deals in local currency. </p>
            <p>        The system allows the user to define different accrual frequencies for local and foreign currencies. </p>
            <p>        Input at this field specifies the frequency with which interest is to be accrued in local currency.  The user has the choice of either daily or monthly accruals and the following examples define the various options: </p>
            <p>                 (i)  12 DEC 1985 D - this input specifies that the first accrual               shall be on 12th Dec 1985 and thereafter at daily (D)               intervals. </p>
            <p>                (ii) 31 JAN 1985 M0131 - this input specifies that the first              accrual will be on 31st Jan 1985 and thereafter at monthly              (M01) intervals on the last day (31) of each month. </p>
            <p>               (iii) 31 JAN 1985 M0115 - this input specifies that the first              accrual will be on 31st Jan 1985 and thereafter at monthly              (M01) intervals on the fifteenth day (15) of each month. </p>
            <p>        This field is updated automatically whenever the accrual process has taken place and so unless the accrual cycle is to be changed, the only time attention needs to be paid to this field is when the first 'off-line' is to be run.  Prior to the first 'off-line' of the system, the date entered here must be equal to or greater than the 'NEXT.RUN.DATE' field in the appropriate BATCH job (LC.END.OF.DAY).  If it is greater than the date specified on the batch record then the update of the batch job NEXT.RUN.DATE must coincide with the date entered here at some point in the future. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        Standard frequency format. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>        Must be a valid date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNDER.RES.TX.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts a valid transaction code for Credit leg of the Payment Under reserve. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.PREV.YEAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.TRAN.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Debit A/C Entries for L/Cs Discounted </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to Discounting an Accepted Drawing. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on the TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = DEBIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.PREV.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WRITE.OFF.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Write off Category Code for claimed charges. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when claim charges are written off. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)  The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.TRAN.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Debit A/C Entries for L/Cs Discounted with Load amounts. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to Discounting an Accepted Drawing with a Load amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on the TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = DEBIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYND.CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid charge or commission codes that needs to be syndicated among participants for Synidcated LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge codes defined in FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.NETTING</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">Decides whether the provision amount is to be netted with Drawings amount at the time of settlement of Drawings.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">Value defined gets defaulted at the Drawings level. Acceptable values ‘Yes’ or ‘No’.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">Validation Rules:</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext,FROMRELEASE.R13">Default Value - No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.D.CAT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Discount Category Code for Accepted Drawings Discounted. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when Accepted Drawings are Discounted. </p>
            <p>        This field is used if DISC.CAT.CODE is to be changed and at end of day this input is moved to DISC.CAT.CODE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.ACCR.TRCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.CAL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>         Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRO.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used by the system to default the Credit Provision account in the absence of User input. The system uses this category to credit the Cash Margin amount. The currency of this account would be that of Debit Provision account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>        Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>        Must be in the Internal Category range (10000 to 19999).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFUND.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>PL category to be debited for the refund of realized portion of commission/charge.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">No change field.</p>
                <p value="2">Must be a PL category in the range 50000 - 59999.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNCOLLECTED.TR.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the transaction code to be used on Credit A/C entries for uncollected charges under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to charges under L/Cs that are uncollected. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNCOLLECTED.TR.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the transaction code to be used on Debit A/C entries for uncollected charges under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to charges under L/Cs that are uncollected. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = DEBIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency Market relative to the L/C transaction. </p>
            <p>        Indicates the market that exchange rates apply, e.g. Money Market, Notes etc. This field is the default if CURRENCY.MARKET is not entered on the L/C. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1 numeric digit Currency Market code. (Mandatory input)  Must be a valid code on the CURRENCY.MARKET table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMB.TRANS.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Debit A/C Entries for L/C Reimbursement. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative to be used when entries have been created relating to reimbursement. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = DEBIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.BY.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is mainly used in Delivery to  signify the sender of the Message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>        Standard T24 customer field.</p>
            <p>        A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>        Must be the key to a valid entry on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMBURSE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the number of days before Maturity when the Reimbursement message should be sent in the case of Usance Drawing. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.CAT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Discount Category Code for Accepted Drawings Discounted. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field identifies the P/L category code to be used when Accepted Drawings are Discounted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        1-6 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)  The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUND.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the rounding rule that is to be applied</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.WITH.PROV</field>
<desc>
            <p>When Provision (Cash Margin) is taken in LC, the Limit line is impacted with net of Provision. However, where the LC limit line is to be impacted for the entire Liability amount irrespective of the Provision taken, this field may be utilized.</p>
            <p>        Setting this field to YES, would ensure the existing flow of Limit being impacted net of Provision.</p>
            <p>        Setting this to NO, would ensure that irrespective of the Provision taken the limit would be impacted for the entire Liability.</p>
            <p>        The value input here is defaulted into the LC record where the user has the option of setting such condition singularly.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>        Valid inputs are 'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAKEOVER.PROCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is designed for implementers in the change over process, where the data have been taken over from the old system to T24. If it is set to YES, no delivery will be produced. This field should always be set to NO during the real transaction inputting. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AT.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently this field is not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORT.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Credit A/C entries for Amortisations under L/Cs. </p>
            <p>        The code in this field contains the Narrative used when entries have been created in the Amortisation of changes at End of Day. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        3-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500-599.</p>
            <p>        It must be present on TRANSACTION.CODE file, with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMR.CYCLE.F.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the frequency at which the charges will be amortised. When the amortisation is set to monthly, user can define the day of the month on which the amortisation process will run. </p>
            <p>        Input at this field specifies the frequency with which charges are to be amortised for foreign currency charges. </p>
            <p>                  (i) 31 JAN 1995 M0131 -Specifies the first               amortisation as 31st Jan 1995 and thereafter at               monthly (M01) intervals on the last day (31) of each month. </p>
            <p>                 (ii) 31 JAN 1995 M0115 -Specifies the first               amortisation as 31st Jan 1995 and thereafter               at monthly (M01) intervals on the fifteenth day (15) of each               month. </p>
            <p>        This field is updated to the next frequency date when the current frequency is processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        Standard frequency format. </p>
            <p>        Can be monthly or daily frequency.</p>
            <p>        Mandatory Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMR.CYCLE.L.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the frequency at which the charges will be amortised. When the amortisation is set to monthly, the user can define day of the month on which the amortisation process is to be run. </p>
            <p>                  (i) 31 JAN 1995 M0131 - Specifies the first               amortisation date as 31st Jan 1995 and thereafter at               monthly (M01) intervals on the last day (31) of each month. </p>
            <p>                 (ii) 31 JAN 1995 M0115 - Specifies the first               charge amortisation date as 31st Jan 1995 and thereafter               at monthly (M01) intervals on the fifteenth day (15) of each               month. </p>
            <p>        This field is updated to the next frequency date when the current frequency is processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>        Standard frequency format. </p>
            <p>        Can be monthly or daily frequency.</p>
            <p>        Mandatory Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.TRAN.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction code to be used on Credit leg of Accounting entries when assigned under Drawings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>        Must be a valid TRANSACTION code with DEBIT.CREDIT.IND set as CREDIT.</p>
            <p>        1-10(Max Value) numeric characters TRANSACTION Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>        The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>        The code entered must be in the range 500 - 599.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>IB.RESPOND.BY.DAYS</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
