<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>LC.TYPES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file controls the maintenance of the LC.TYPES, which contains the Letter of Credit types allowed in the system with their narrative descriptions. </p>
            <p>The records in this file can be defined by the user in order to set up customised types of Letters of Credit and Documentary Collections. </p>
            <p>The table is used during the input and validation for L/C's to verify the credit types and details, and also to setup the default CATEGORY.CODE. </p>
            <p>It is also used for the maintenance of L/C statistics in the form of a counter which is updated whenever a L/C is Pre-Advised, Opened, Expired and Closed. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DUPLICATE.CHECK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field must be a valid record id from the EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE file.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE file allows for the definition of a criterion to check against for the occurrence of any duplicate contracts that then match this.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When more than one Id is input for validation, for a given LC.TYPE, override is generated even if the condition is satisfied for one of them. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Multi-value field.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Id in the EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE file, whose application is       set as LC.</p>
            <p>Accepts u</p>
            <p>p       to 35 alpha-numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPENED</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Field not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRMED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the LC.TYPE is a Confirmed or an Unconfirmed credit. </p>
            <p>This field will have an impact on the Limits and CRF processing relevant to L/Cs. </p>
            <p>If any LC transactions are existing with this LC.TYPES in the live file or unauthorised file ,this field cannot be modified, because modifying this field leads to conflict in ASSET.TYPE in CRF entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'YES' or 'NO'. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSFERABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies if the LC.TYPE is able to be transferred. </p>
            <p>This field is used during the creation of L/C documents and advices and determines whether Transferable is to be printed on the documents. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Inputs - 'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains narrative description for the L/C type. </p>
            <p>This field enables the user to input (in a choice of language) the description for each LC.TYPE.  The description is used for enrichment purposes when completing an L/C. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPIRED.NOT.CLOSED</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Field not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies by which method the LC.TYPE is to be paid. </p>
            <p>Identifies the payment method for the credit where: </p>
            <p>'P' - By Payment </p>
            <p>'A' - By Acceptance </p>
            <p>'N' - By Negotiation </p>
            <p>'M' - Mixed payment</p>
            <p>'D' - By Direct credit Reimbursement </p>
            <p>'NS' - Negotiate Sight </p>
            <p>'NA' - Negotiate Acceptance </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'P' , 'A' , 'M' , 'N' , 'D' ,'NS' or 'NA'.  (Mandatory input) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.TYPE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>The user should only input the types that are to be used. </p>
            <p>Can be any meaningful name to the user. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAN.COLLECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Documentary Collection type Credits, determines whether the LC.TYPE is a Clean collection. </p>
            <p>Field is used during the creation of Collection documents and advi. </p>
            <p>If any LC transactions are existing with this LC.TYPES in the live file or unauthorised file ,this field cannot be modified, because modifying this field leads to conflict in ASSET.TYPE in CRF entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.COLLECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies if the LC.TYPE is a Documentary Collection type, not a Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>If set to 'YES' then the LC.TYPE is used for Documentary Collections only.  If an L/C is input using this type, then all processing is carried out for Documentary Collections. </p>
            <p>If any LC transactions are existing with this LC.TYPES in the live file or unauthorised file ,this field cannot be modified, because modifying this field leads to conflict in ASSET.TYPE in CRF entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'YES' or 'NO'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UCPDC.DEFAULT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the fields on the file LETTER.OF.CREDIT in which defaulting is to be suppressed on cross validation. </p>
            <p>Field level default is not affected by this. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input field. (No default)</p>
            <p>Input must be valid field names on the file LETTER.OF.CREDIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.ADVISED</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Field Not in Use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STANDBY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies if the LC TYPE supports Standby L/C or not. </p>
            <p>This field is mapped to the appropriate L/C documents and advices. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid inputs - YES or NO (Default NO)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAN.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Letter of Credit type credits, determines whether the LC.TYPE is a clean credit. </p>
            <p>Field is used during the creation of L/C documents and Advices. </p>
            <p>If any LC transactions are existing with this LC.TYPES in the live file or unauthorised file ,this field cannot be modified, because modifying this field leads to conflict in ASSET.TYPE in CRF entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMPORT.EXPORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the LC.TYPE is an Import (Issuance) or Export (Advising) type credit. </p>
            <p>Depending on whether this field contains 'I' or 'E' the processing will treat the L/C as an Import or Export credit. </p>
            <p>If any LC transactions are existing with this LC.TYPES in the live file or unauthorised file ,this field cannot be modified, because modifying this field leads to conflict in ASSET.TYPE in CRF entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'I' or 'E'. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.LC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for transferrable LC initiated through Internet Banking.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to specify the application format which will be used instead of the default value. </p>
            <p>This allows the format of advices to be defined at the LC type level. When input is valid in this field, appropriate records should be created on the DE.FORMAT.PRINT file. Input in this field will form the second part </p>
            <p>The value in this field will form the second part of the key to the file DE.FORMAT.PRINT. The key will be derived appending the value in this field to the literal 'LC'. For example, input of a '2' in this field will mean that the key to DE.FORMAT.PRINT will be 700.LC2.1.GB instead of the default 700.1.1.GB. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Optional input. Default is 1 if left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.LC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Back-to-back letters of credit are related to each other usually with one acting as security for the other.  T24 can help with the preparation of details by using one as the basis for generating the other. </p>
            <p>This field indicates the type of LC which will be used in the generated back-to-back transaction. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.TO.BACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies if the LC.TYPE can be used in Back to Back processing. </p>
            <p>This field is used during the input of Back to Back documents and indicates whether a further Back to Back document should be created. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the category code under which each LC.TYPE should be reported. </p>
            <p>This field is used as the default when the CATEGORY.CODE is not entered as part of the L/C input data. </p>
            <p>If any LC transactions are existing with this LC.TYPES in the live file or unauthorised file ,this field cannot be modified, because modifying this field leads to conflict in ASSET.TYPE in CRF entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>The value entered must be in the range 23000-23999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

