<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>LC.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to set up the default charges for all Letter of Credit/ Documentary Collections and Drawing types.  Each input into the Letter of Credit system will have a set of default charges in this file set up. </p>
            <p>The defaulting mechanism works by defining in this file a record corresponding to each type of L/C (LC.TYPE), together with the operations that can be performed. </p>
            <p>The key used to extract records from this file for Letter of Credit input will be the LC.TYPE input and the OPERATION input. </p>
            <p>The key used to pick default charges for Drawings input under a Letter of Credit will be the LC.TYPE and the Drawing type. </p>
            <p>For example, if there is an LC TYPE record with key as 'BILL', then the user should define here the following four records for default charges to the Letter of Credit file: </p>
            <p>           BILL-O   For operation 'O'            BILL-P   For operation 'P'            BILL-A   For operation 'A'            BILL-T   For operation 'T' </p>
            <p>However, whilst it is beneficial to have a default facility, Letter of Credit especially are not stereotype with regards to their terms and conditions.  Subsequently commissions/charges (as recorded in the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE and FT.CHARGE.TYPE files) can be input if need be, separately to override the default and match the requirements. </p>
            <p>And for drawings under the LC.TYPE, the following records could be set up: </p>
            <p>           BILL-AC  For Acceptance            BILL-DP  For Deferred Payment            BILL-DC  For Documentary Collections            BILL-SP  For Sight Payments            BILL-CO  For Collections            BILL-CC  For Collection Chases            BILL-CR  For Collection Rejection </p>
            <p>Note : For Drawings, not all possible drawing types will need to be set up        for each lc type since under one type a 'SP' and 'AC' cannot be        input. </p>
            <p>With the above records defined here, then each type an L/C is input with type equal to 'BILL' and Operation equal to 'O', then the default charges will be picked up from the fields for commission and charges defined in the record 'BILL-O'. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FLAT.CONFIRM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLAT.OPENING.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This  field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPENING.COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the file, the value here will be defined as the LC.TYPE followed by either the LC.OPERATION for Letters of Credit, or the DRAWING.TYPE for Drawings. </p>
            <p>Whenever a transaction is input via the Letter of Credit/Documentary Collections or Drawings applications, a key is built up of the current LC.TYPE and the current operation (For L/Cs), or the Drawing type (for drawings).  This key is then used to retrieve a record from this file in order to set up all the default charges for the current transaction. </p>
            <p>For Letters of Credit, the key is defined as: </p>
            <p>           [LC.TYPE]'-'[OPERATION] </p>
            <p>For Drawings, the key is defined as: </p>
            <p>           [LC.TYPE]'-'[DRAWING.TYPE] </p>
            <p>Where LC.TYPE is from the parent Letter of Credit record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input for new records.</p>
            <p>Should relate to a valid L/C type and Operation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains a free format description of the default charges. </p>
            <p>This field provides a description of the Charge Type and is used for the enrichment in T24 applications. </p>
            <p>It can be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Charge Type in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table, and will indicate to the user the language in which the Description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.  Multivalue, multilanguage field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the charge type in an abbreviated format which can be used for reporting where space is limited. </p>
            <p>This multivalue field is used to enter a Short Description for the Charge Type code in various languages.  Each expansion will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language Table and will indicate to the user the language in which the short description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-15 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.  (Mandatory input)  Multivalue, Multilanguage field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field moved to FT.Charge Type/FT.Commission.Type </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field moved to FT.Charge Type/FT.Commission.Type </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.TYPES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains records in the FT.CHARGE.TYPE file that are to be used as default charges for this record. </p>
            <p>All the entries here will relate to the Charge types that are to be defaulted whenever a Letter of Credit or Drawing, depending on transaction type above, is input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-11 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.  Multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must keys to valid records on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TYPES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the record id on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file that are to be used as default charges for this record. </p>
            <p>All the entries here will relate to the Commission types that are to be defaulted whenever a Letter of Credit or Drawing, depending on transaction type above, is input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-11 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.  Multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record ID on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIR.COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRD.COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Periodic commission code to be defaulted in LC or Drawings.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only for operation O or A for LC</p>
            <p>Input allowed only for draw type DC or AP for Drawings.</p>
            <p>Should be a valid ID in PERIODIC.COMMISSION table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

