<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LC</product>
<table>LETTER.OF.CREDIT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Letter of Credit controls the administration and processing of both Letters of Credit and Documentary Collections. It is fully integrated within T24. </p>
            <p>It automates accounting, limit exposure, position updating, control and administration of trading activity and ensures efficient delivery of the related advices, documents, and payments. </p>
            <p>The Letter of Credit types processed by the system can be customised using the LC.TYPES application, where combinations of the major features of an LC can be set up. (e.g. import/export, sight/usance (term), confirmed/unconfirmed, etc.) </p>
            <p>It is important to note that the details set up on the Letter of Credit application do not make any payments or reimbursements.  In order to achieve this, a Drawing must be entered via the DRAWINGS application. This will be linked to the LETTER.OF.CREDIT contract. </p>
            <p>A history of each LETTER.OF.CREDIT contract. and in particular the charges processed for the contract, is held on the LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES application. </p>
            <p>Many events occur within the life of a LETTER.OF.CREDIT contract. Each event is recorded on the contract by (I)nputting to the contract and usually the OPERATION field on the contract will control the event being entered. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The main transactions that the system can process are: </p>
            <p />
            <p>ISSUANCE OF A LETTER OF CREDIT </p>
            <p>Used when the Bank opens a Letter of Credit on behalf of its client (applicant) which will be advised to the beneficiary, via the Bank's correspondent.  Usually in the country that the beneficiary resides. </p>
            <p />
            <p>ADVISING/CONFIRMING A LETTER OF CREDIT </p>
            <p>Used when the Bank receives a Letter of Credit that has been issued by another Bank and is requested to forward it.  (Sometimes via a third party Bank) to the beneficiary with or without adding confirmation. </p>
            <p />
            <p>PRE-ADVISE A LETTER OF CREDIT </p>
            <p>At the request of the applicant, a pre-advice is sent by the issuing Bank, prior to their issuance of the operative credit instrument, to provide the beneficiary, via the advising bank, with brief details of the LC which is in the process of being opened. </p>
            <p />
            <p>AMENDMENT OF A LETTER OF CREDIT </p>
            <p>This facility will allow the user to insert any changes which will produce an amendment to the original terms and conditions of an LC and automatically generate all relevant accounting entries for commissions, increase or decrease of the principal amounts, and advices and documents to the Electronic delivery system. </p>
            <p />
            <p>OPEN A REMITTANCE DOCUMENTARY COLLECTION (EXPORT) </p>
            <p>Used when the Bank (acting as Remitting Bank) receives a Documentary Collection from its client (the drawer) in respect of goods/services they have sold to their customer (the drawee).  The bank forwards the documents to their Correspondent (The Collecting Bank) in the country of residency of the drawer for presentation to the drawee against payment/acceptance. </p>
            <p />
            <p>OPEN A COLLECTING DOCUMENTARY COLLECTION (IMPORT) </p>
            <p>Used when the Bank (acting as Collecting Bank) receives a Documentary Collection from another Bank (The Remitting Bank) for  presentation to the Bank's client (the drawee) against payment/acceptance. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>MAIN FEATURES OF THE APPLICATION -------------------------------- </p>
            <p />
            <p>The main features of the module can be described as follows: </p>
            <p />
            <p>1. INPUT PROCESSING </p>
            <p>Validation is performed to ensure the correctness of any transaction input.  All inputs will update limits, positions, accounts, etc.. in real time.  After authorization of the transaction, all the documents, advices, and SWIFT messages applicable for the L/C will be automatically generated by the Electronic Delivery System. </p>
            <p>All L/C types can be entered in local or foreign currencies, i.e. contracts can be denominated in any currency. </p>
            <p />
            <p>2. CHARGE PROCESSING </p>
            <p>Default charges for all types of Letters of Credit and Documentatary Collections can be entered via the LC.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION application, and will be automatically calculated by the system.  The facility to add extra charges or amend charges is available, together with the facility to waive all charges.  All charge entries are automatically generated, and if specified in a foreign currency, positions will be updated accordingly.  Charges can be amortised over the life of the contract, frequencies defined by the user. </p>
            <p>Charges can be claimed from a number of parties involved in the Letter of Credit or Documentary Collection.  It is important to note that charges can be denominated in a currency other than the Letter of Credit /Documentary Collection Currency. </p>
            <p>Once an LC is authorised, all charges are recorded in the LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file. Should further charges be input the file will automatically be updated. </p>
            <p />
            <p>3. DOCUMENT PROCESSING </p>
            <p>All documents required to be produced by the input of the transaction will be generated by the Delivery application in order to facilitate easy amendment and customisation of the forms. The T24 Graphical User Interface provides a simple way of entering large volumes of text. </p>
            <p>Frequently used text and clauses can be entered via the LC.ADVICE.TEXT and LC.CLAUSES applications, and then linked into the transaction by entering a short code into the fields provided. </p>
            <p />
            <p>4. ENQUIRIES AND REPORTS </p>
            <p>In common with other T24 Applications, all data can be enquired upon or selectively analyzed and researched.  The system will also automatically produce reports of Collections Due, Unpaid Charges, etc. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CONF.LIAB.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>CONF.LIAB.AMT:  </p>
            <p />Identifies the total confirmed liability amount in respect of partially confirmed Letters of Credit. It represents the running total of the remaining confirmed portion of the liability amount, as the drawings are being made under this Letter of Credit. <p>The amount will be expressed in terms of LC currency. This field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p> System Generated.</p><p /><p> Standard Amount format.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACER.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Accepts Standard date format. Holds the date on which a tracer message will be sent. Once input and authorized, this will produce an EB.FREE.MESSAGE record which will contain relevant details of the particular transaction and the date on which the Tracer message has to be sent. Further tracers may be sent on an automatic cycle which can be specified in TRACER.DAYS. </p>
            <p>The EB.ACTIVITY which will be triggered is defined in the application LCs Company record in EB.FREE.PARAMETERS. If this is not defined then no message will be sent.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid date, which is not       less than Today.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input allowed only when       Operation is  O,  T or  A .</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.BASE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>CHARGE.BASE.AMT:</p>
            <p>While amending a Letter of Credit, when charges are allowed to default the same is calculated for the entire amount of the LC and not for the amended amount. </p>
            <p>The value input into this field enables the user to identify a portion of the Letter of Credit for which the charges are to be applied. This facility is available for operation "O" and "A" only. </p>
            <p>For Example: </p>
            <p>When a Letter of Credit is input for GBP 100,000 and then amended to GBP 150,000, the user has the option to recover charges only to the extent of the enhanced amount, which is GBP 50,000 in this case. This enhanced amount is treated as the CHARGE.BASE.AMT.</p>
            <p>If left blank, LC.AMOUNT will be used for calculating default charges, which is the existing flow.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard amount format.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input is only allowed if valid Charge/Commission code has been entered</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUING.BANK.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Export Letters of Credit, this field identifies the Issuing Bank. </p>
            <p>For Outward Documentary Collections, this field identifies the Collecting bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.').</p>
            <p>The customer code must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>No input allowed for Inward Documentary Collections /         Import Letters of Credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.LC.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the banks former or current l/c number (or reference of the L/C on another computer system).</p>
            <p><strong><p>Validation Rules:</p></strong>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LCY.PORT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the local currency equivalent of the liability portion stored in LIAB.PORT.AMT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVOLVING.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input in this field is applicable only for <strong>Revolving Letters of Credit.</strong></p>
            <p>This field is used to identify the type of Revolving Letter of Credit applicable.</p>
            <p>Options available are (CM) Cumulative or (NC) Non-Cumulative.</p>
            <p>T24 fully support the internationally recognized understanding of cumulative and non-cumulative revolving letters of credit.</p>
            <p><strong>Example:</strong>
            </p>
            <p>A revolving letter of credit is issued for $10,000 revolving on the 15th day of every month with 3 revolutions. An initial drawing of $6000 is made and no further drawings were made by the 15th of the month (i.e. the time the first revolution is set to take place).</p>
            <p />
            <p>For a <strong>Cumulative</strong> letter of credit, on         the 15th, the unutilized amount of $4000 will be carried         over by the system to the next revolution period. i.e. the system will provide for the first revolution to be drawn         for an increased amount of $14,000 (being $10,000 +         $4000)</p>
            <p>For a <strong>Non-</strong><strong>Cumulative</strong> letter of credit,         on the 15th, the untilled portion of $4000 is now         unavailable for drawing and the system will provide for         the fist revolution to be drawn for $10000 only..</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options available are (CM) Cumulative or (NC) Non-Cumulative. </p>
            <p>Default will be null, which indicates that the letter of         credit is not revolving.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Letter of credit this field identifies the Reimbursing bank. For Collections this file identifies the Account with bank </p>
            <p>This field is optional. </p>
            <p><strong>LETTER OF CREDIT </strong>
            </p>
            <p>This THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO must be a customer of the bank and identifies the reimbursing third party bank through whom reimbursement will be made to the paying/negotiating bank for a letter of credit. </p>
            <p>For import letters of credit this will identify where funds are to be remitted whenever payments are made. </p>
            <p>For export letters of credit this will identify where funds are to be received from whenever reimbursement is required after effecting payment to the beneficiary. </p>
            <p>If this field is not set then the default channel of payment and reimbursement is from the Opening Bank to the Negotiating Bank. </p>
            <p><strong>COLLECTION </strong>
            </p>
            <p>For a collection this is the account with bank field used when ordering party requests that the beneficiary be paid at a bank other than the receive bank. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.').</p>
            <p>For Import LCs must not be the same as the         ADVISING.BK.CUSTNO or the ADVISE.THRU.CUSTNO.</p>
            <p>For Export LCs must not be the same as the         ISSUING.BANK.NO or the ADVISE.THRU.CUSTNO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the lastest date and time of input of data to the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.ACCEPTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is valid for Documentary Collections Only. It records the maturity date as advised by the Collecting Bank of a usance draft accepted payable by the Drawee. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date format only.</p>
            <p>Documentary Collection input only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES.DET</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will be mapped against Tag 71B of Outward and Inward MT730 messages.</p>
            <p />
            <p>or of MT740</p>
            <p>When set to MT730, the valid codes are:    </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />AGENT Agent's commission <p>                TELECHAR Teletransmission charges</p><p>                COMM Our commission</p><p>                CORCOM Our correspondent's commission</p><p>                DISC Commercial discount</p><p>                INSUR Insurance premium</p><p>                POST Our postage</p><p>                STAMP Stamp duty</p><p>                WAREHOUS Wharfing and warehouse</p><p>When set to MT740, the valid codes are:</p><p>                DISCCHGS Discount Charges.</p><p>                ACCECHGS Acceptance Charges.</p><p>Any code used in this field must be between slashes and must appear at the beginning of a line.</p><p>These codes must have been defined  in the SWIFT.CODE.WORDS.</p><p>Narrative text must not begin with a slash and, if used, must begin on a new line and be the last</p><p>information in the field.</p><p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p>1-6       lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters</p><p>Valid  SWIFT.CODE.WORDS with MESSAGE.TYPE as 740 when reimbursing       is set else 71B.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMB.BK.CHGS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows to specify by which party the reimbursing bank's charges are to be borne.</p>
            <p>The absence of this field implies that charges will be borne by the Sender of this message.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The value present in this field is populated in Tag 71A of MT740.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are OUR or CLM.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.SHIPMENTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies if part shipments are allowed under the terms of the Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>Part shipments is used in the production of messages/advices to specify whether part shipments are allowed under the terms of the Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'Y'- Partshipments Allowed or 'N' - Partshipments Not         Allowed. Default to 'N'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>RESERVE7 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.TRAN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field.  This field will maintain the child Liability amount if the SHARE.PARN.LIM in LC.PARAMETERS is set to NO.   Alternatively, it would always be zero if the SHARE.PARN.LIM is set Y. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>System Generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AWAITING.MT701</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Used in conjunction with the incoming interface to indicate if any MT701's are still needed to complete the transaction .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REL.PROVIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field is used to release the outstanding provision amount. The release will be done on line. The provision credit account will be debited for the outstanding amount and the provision debit account will be credited in this operation. This cannot be set to Y when no provision amount is outstanding in the credit account. When set to Y, no other amendment to the amount etc are allowed. When releasing provision, PROV.EXCH.RATE will act as provision release exchange rate.</p>
            <p>LC will not be allowed to be reversed unless the outstanding provision amount is released through operation REL.PROVIS equal to Y.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRM.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE8</field>
<desc>
            <p>RESERVE8 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.CR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the users preferred choice to indicate that the l/c amount indicated in field &lt;LC.AMOUNT&gt; is a maximum. This field reflects the options available under S.W.I.F.T. specifications.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>13 type Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if the field         &lt;PERCENTAGE.CR.AMT&gt; is blank. </p>
            <p>Validate input terms are: UP.TO, MAXIMUM, or NOT         EXCEEDING.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where present, the value in this field is used to calculate the default brokerage on all Letter of Credit Drawings for which this contract is the underlying Letter of Credit. The default brokerage amount is set to the percentage defined here of the document amount on the DRAWINGS application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 rate field.</p>
            <p>Input cannot be greater than 100%.</p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICANT.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional input. Defines the default account to be used for reimbursement from the Applicant in the case of an Import Letter of Credit and the Drawee in the event of an Inward Collection. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Account Format. </p>
            <p>Only allowed for Import Letters of Credit and  Inward         Documentary Collections.</p>
            <p>Account must belong to the Applicant.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This system maintained field is a copy of LC.AMOUNT to retain the original L/C amount before transferring. It is the case where the SHARE.PARNT.LIM is set to NO (non-sharable). The LC.AMOUNT will be reduced automatically every time the L/C is transferred. </p>
            <p>If the SHARE.PARNT.LIM is set to YES (sharable), this field will always be equal to LC.AMOUNT, because each subsequent transfer does not reduce the original LC.AMOUNT (parent L/C amount).</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The amount can not be less than the amount in LC.AMOUNT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BWD.FWD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies to which day the scheduled frequency date is to be cycled, when the scheduled date is not a working day.</p>
            <p>Options:</p>
            <p>C - Calendar, P  - Previous working day, N - Next working day.</p>
            <p>Validation:</p>
            <p>Applicable only when COMM.FREQUENCY is defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMBURSE.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field displays a code to identify from whom reimbursement will be received from under the letter of credit.</p>
            <p>Valid codes are: </p>
            <p><strong>O</strong>(pener) - <strong>T</strong>(hird Party Bank (Reimbursing bank)) or <strong>W</strong>(aiting for further instructions)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'O', 'T', or 'W'.</p>
            <p>If 'T' is specified then THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO or         THIRD.PARTY must be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.PARTY.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.TERMS</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field is used to decide the pay type for LC when LC initiated through Internet Banking.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory when LC initiated through Internet Banking </p>
            <p> Allowed Values are </p>
            <p> Sight </p>
            <p> Deffered </p>
            <p> Acceptance </p>
            <p> Nego.Sight </p>
            <p> Nego.Acceptance </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICANT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the name and address of the Applicant / Drawee / Drawer.</p>
            <p>LETTERS OF CREDIT</p>
            <p>For Letters of Credit, this field identifies the applicant's name and address on whose behalf of a Letter of Credit is issued. Although the initial values are defaulted from the Customer file, yet they may be altered with an alternate address that the Bank may think is apt.</p>
            <p> In the case of Transferred Letter of Credit, this field holds the value of the Original Beneficiary of the Parent Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>DOCUMENTARY COLLECTIONS</p>
            <p>For Documentary Collections, this field identifies the bank's customer's name and address i.e. Drawee (inward collection) or drawer (outward collection).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Only allowed if APPLICANT.CUSTNO is not entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.LCCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field will display the local currency amount that is used to update the charges/commission profit and loss account. If the charge/commission amount is not in local currency, then this amount will be calculated when the charge is debited from an account and credited to the P/L account, using the mid-market spot rates at the time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
            <p>Standard Amount Format. Associated mulivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAILABLE.WITH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of letter of credit messages/advices, this field identifies the bank authorised to pay, accept, or negotiate documents presented under the L/C if it is not a customer of the bank with a valid CUSTOMER.NO. This field is not required for collections.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>If this field is entered, then AVAIL.WITH.CUSTNO must be         blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.PROV.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field displays the provision amount in terms of the debit account. This will be prefixed by a minus sign to indicate the debit. As debit account and credit account can be of any two currencies, this field will indicate the amount debited in the currency of the debit account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT202.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.2ND.COPIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in the production of messages/advices, this field in conjunction with &lt;DOCUMENT.CODE&gt; is used to identify the number of each document being sent in the first mailing to the respective party.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field displays a code to identify from whom the bank is to claim it's charges. </p>
            <p>Valid codes are: </p>
            <p><strong>O</strong>(pener), <strong>B</strong>(eneficiary) or <strong>T</strong>(hird Party)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'O', 'B', or 'T'. Default is 'O'.</p>
            <p>If 'T' is entered, then THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO or THIRD.PARTY         must be present.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.SHIP.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the details of Part Shipment. </p>
            <p>If input, this field takes priority over PART.SHIPMENTS for the purpose of delivery messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>35 Type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHIPMENT.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of messages/advices, this free text field stipulates the period of time which the goods are to be loaded on board/dispatched/taken in charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>6 x 65 type A alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Input to this field is not permitted if the field         &lt;LATEST.SHIPMENT&gt; has been used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMB.BK.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows input of reference number, assigned by the Receiver of the message MT747.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The value present in this field is populated in Tag 21 of MT747</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-16       type A (Alphanumeric) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.1ST.COPIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in the production of messages/advices, this field in conjunction with &lt;DOCUMENT.CODE&gt; is used to identify the number of each document being sent in the first mailing to the respective party. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.TXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This free text multi valued field provides the user with the ability to either generate or amended pre-coded documents derived from field &lt;DOCUMENT.CODE&gt;.. </p>
            <p>Used in the production of messages/advices, this field in conjunction with &lt;DOCUMENT.CODE&gt; is used to identify the number of each document being sent in the first mailing to the respective party.. </p>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 50 Alphanumeric characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using the conditions specified for the charge code in the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables, the system automatically calculates the amount to be charged in LC currency. Input of an amount here will be the amount in charge currency. This amount will be converted to charge account currency using the exchange rate in the above field CHARGE.XCHG. Input of an amount, however, when accepted to allow the user to override the amount calculated, the charge period will be of no significance and will be overridden.. </p>
            <p>Input of a Numeric followed by the percent (%) sign will cause the system to calculate the percentage amount of the LC.AMOUNT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>14 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters.         Associated multivalue field.</p>
            <p>Input is only allowed if a charge/commission code has         been entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate to be applied between commission(contract) currency and commission account currency. </p>
            <p> If not input by the user, system to default the appropriate buy/sell rate from the currency table.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional field.</p>
                <p value="2">Not allowed when LC currency and commission account currency are same.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.COVERED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides the user to input an amount that will be added to the liability amount of the LC and the limit will be updated accordingly. </p>
            <p>Examples of the use of this field could be to book additonal amounts which have been described in the field &lt;ADD.AMOUNT.COVERED.&gt;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVIS.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine the account from which the provision should be debited when such a transaction is deemed to require provision. The account will be re-credited when either a Sight Drawing is processed or on maturity of an acceptance Drawing by default. However, user can define a different account in DRAWINGS so that the provision amount is released into that account.</p>
            <p>For release of provision, this shall be the credit account and no change will be allowed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Field PROVISION must be set to 'YES'.</p>
            <p>The account can be any account including a nostro or an         internal account.</p>
            <p>If the account is not an account of the opener an         override will be raised to alert the user.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the date that the LC is due to be closed, and written to the history files. If any drawings are outstanding on this date for the LC, then the LC will not be closed. </p>
            <p>The date entered here will be the date on which the LC will be closed from the books and written to the history files. This will not happen if there are outstanding drawings sent for collection, authority to Pay/Access oand Requested, term/usance deals with maturity review dates greater than this date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date Format. (Default from EXPIRY.DATE +         CLOSING.DAYS from LC.PARAMETERS file). </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Acting as part of the delivery multivale set, this field provides the user with the ability to decide whether to send or withhold sending the delivery of any message produced under the contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options available are (Y)es - Send Message or (N)o - Do         Not Send Message</p>
            <p>Default is (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVOLVING.FQY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the frequency at which the letter of credit is to revolve.</p>
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input of 'WEEK3' indicates that the letter of credit         needs to be revolved every three weeks from the issue         date.</p>
            <p>Input of 'M02' indicates that the letter of credit needs         to be revolved every 2 months from the issue date.</p>
            <p>In the case of export revolving letters of credit which have been transferred, the frequency cannot be changed by amendment.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory for all revolving letters of credit..</p>
            <p>An override will be required if the date as defined on         the HOLIDAY table is a non working day.</p>
            <p>Input prohibited for a date prior to the system date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLAUSES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the key of a record in the LC.CLAUSES file that is to be included as a clause on the documents/advices for this L/C/Documentary Collection. </p>
            <p>Used for the creation of L/C Collection documents/advices.  Will be used to retrieve a clause narrative from the LC.CLAUSES file and will be stored in the field CLAUSES.TEXT in the LC file. This can then be used in the printing of Advices, Documents, etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> It accepts either Text or Customer Number-Text, If both exists priority is given to Customer Number-Text </p>
            <p> Customer Number should exists in CUSTOMER table. </p>
            <p> Text can be maximum of  6 Alphanumeric Characters </p>
            <p> Must exist on the LC.CLAUSES file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.DRAWING</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the number of the next drawing that will be made under the letter of credit. 01 is defaulted if there are no drawings against the L/C. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the rate at which the commission has to be calculated. </p>
            <p>If the user inputs a rate in this field, then the default commission calculation will be ignored and the commission will be calculated at this rate.</p>
            <p>User input field.</p>
            <p>Validation:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Not allowed when FIXED.COMM.AMT is INPUT.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.PEND.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the total amount from all pending amendments for the LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">(1) System maintained field.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">(2) The value in this field will reflect the net principal(LC.AMOUNT) movements inclusive of tolerance done through LC.AMENDMENTS for which decision is pending.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLAUSES.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This multi-value field is used to select a pre-defined clause(s) which are required for the specific letter of credit. The pre-defined clauses should be set up in LC.CLAUSES and these can easily be retrieved by inserting the respective code and hitting &lt;F5&gt;. Only one clause may be inserted at a time. Once retrieved, the now expanded clause description can be modified, if necessary, prior to validation. </p>
            <p>This description will be included as a clause on the documents / advices for this L/C / Documentary Collection. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>50 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.TO.BACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Back-to-back letters of credit are related to each other usually with one acting as security for the other. T24 can help with the preparation of details by using one as the basis for generating the other. </p>
            <p>This field indicates whether a back-to-back LC is to be generated. Input is allowed in this field only if the BACK.TO.BACK field is set to YES in the LC.TYPES record of an export letter of credit. The type of the generated LC is taken from the BACK.LC.TYPE field in the LC.TYPES record. The associated import letter of credit will be generated in the IHOLD status when the record is authorised. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds message types of all inward messages received.</p>
            <p>E.g. if MT700 is received, then value 'MT700' will be stored in this field.</p>
            <p>Associated multi value with INWARD.MSG.REF. System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>RESERVE6 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is valid for <strong>Documentary Collections and LC.</strong> only. It is used in conjunction with the previous field 'TENOR' to indicate the tenor of the drafts under the collection and is used in the production of corresponding documentary collection messages. </p>
            <p>However, this field in order to support Option K of Tag 32a, accepts "D" or "M" followed by number representing Number of Days or Number of Months.</p>
            <p>Eg. To input a draft of '120 days from the bill of lading date', the number 'D120' would be inserted in this field. The descriptive text i.e. 'days from the bill of lading date' would be inserted in the field 'TENOR'. COLL.MAT.CODE may also be input with BE in this case.</p>
            <p>COLL.MAT.CODE in conjuction with DAYS field will be defaulted for deferred and acceptance LC's in DEFERRED.PAY and DRAFTS.AT fields.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum length of 4.</p>
            <p>First Character can either be D or M followed by number such as 120 or       012.</p>
            <p>Documentary Collection input only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE.DR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the negative tolerance relative to the documentary credit amount as a percentage. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>If the LC.AMOUNT = $1,000,000.00 and the percentage entered here = 10, then the minimum drawing expected under this letter of credit is $900,000.00 and the maximum is $1,000,000.00. The LIABILITY.AMOUNT will be equal to $1,000,000.00. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal         characters).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVOCABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate whether the letter of credit is Revocable or Irrevocable. </p>
            <p>If 'Y' is input then the LC is Revocable, If 'N' is input LC is Irrevocable. Default is 'N'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'Y' or 'N'. Default 'N'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAFTS.AT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in the production of messages/advices, this field indicates the tenor of the draft to be presented under the Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>Example: when a letter of credit has a tenor of 120 days sight, '120 days sight' will be entered in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>If this field is used then the Tenor field must be blank         and either DRAWEE.CUST.NO or DRAWEE must have a value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When AVAILABLE.BY is "BY ACCEPTANCE or BY NEGOTIATION"(Negotiation Acceptance), standard text will be defaulted based on values defined in COLL.MAT.CODE and DAYS field for import LC</p>
            <p />
            <p>E.g 120 DAYS AFTER BILL OF EXCHANGE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the amount of discount made against the letter of credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.PARTY.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETURN.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether the excess commission amount calculated on account of principal decrease is to be returned to the customer or not.</p>
            <p>Acceptable values are YES or No. Value gets defaulted from LC.PARAMETERS which can be amended by the user.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.RULE.MT740</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the rules the reimbursement is subject to. Following values can be input 
URR LATEST VERSION,                                                                                                 NOTURR
. This field can be input only if field THIRD.PARTY or THIRD.PARTY.CUST.NO is input   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUR.REVOL.LIAB</field>
<desc>
            <p>This displays the liability in terms of the LC currency for the Current revolution.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained  field.</p>
            <p>Value is populated only if the LC is  revolving and        non-cumulative.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRM.INST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains confirmation instructions for the Receiver. </p>
            <p>Only three Swift key words can be entered into this field (see <p>Validation Rules:</p>) The default from the LC.TYPE file can be overwritten. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>7 Alphanumeric characters as specified in the Validation         Rules. Defaults from the LC.TYPE parameter file.</p>
            <p>Valid codes are as follows: CONFIRM The Receiver is         requested to confirm the credit. MAY ADD The Receiver may         add its confirmation to the credit. WITHOUT The Receiver         is not requested to confirm the credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVISE.THRU.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional input. Identifies the account of the advise-thru bank, if there is an account relationship. </p>
            <p>For Export/Advising LC'/Collections, if an account relationship exists between the bank and the advise thru bank, and this account is to be used to route payments to the beneficiary of the LC, then the account is entered here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Account Format.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid account that belongs to the         ADVISE.THRU.CUSTNO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency that charges are to be levied in.  This can be different from the LC.CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>If this field is not entered then a default currency will be selected from either the CHARGES.ACCOUNT currency, or the currency of the L/C.  If no CHARGES.ACCOUNT is entered, then the LC.CURRENCY is used, otherwise the CHARGES.ACCOUNT currency is used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>CCY (Currency code e.g. GBP must be 3 characters).  Associated mulivalue field.  Default from currency of CHARGES.ACCOUNT or LC.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>For all fields within this multivalue set, the currency must be the same.</p>
            <p>Once input, this field cannot be changed.</p>
            <p>Input is only allowed if a charge/commission code has been entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.EXPIRY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the date that a letter of credit expires from the beneficiary's point of view. This will usually be a number of working days before the EXPIRY.DATE. </p>
            <p>Charge calculation and customer advices will be using this field whereas accounting, limit updates will still be taking place on EXPIRY.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
            <p>Optional input field. (Default EXPIRY.DATE)</p>
            <p>Must be less than or equal to EXPIRY.DATE.</p>
            <p>If Presentation days and Lastest shipment date is defined, advice expiry date will be calculated based on Lastest shipment date plus Presentation Days for import LC's.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the type of commission or charge to be levied on the L/C / Documentary Collection transaction being processed. The charge or commission code will be entered as a eleven-character code as defined on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Associated multivalue         field.</p>
            <p>The code must be a valid commission or charge code as         defined on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE         tables.</p>
            <p>Input is not allowed if the WAIVE.CHARGES field is set to         'Y'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rate applied on the 'UPTO.AMT' to calculate the 'CSN.AMT'.</p>
            <p>System maintained field. Associated sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIMB.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows to input amendments of a reimbursement (Narrative of MT747) that has been included in the message.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The value present in this field is populated in Tag 77A of MT747.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 20 lines of 35 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PEND.DEC.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the total of all negative amount from all pending Amendments for the LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) NO INPUT Field . </p>
            <p>(2) This Field is automatically updated by adding up the decrease of Liability Amount on decision of each Amendment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTH.REIMB.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field displays the date on which MT740 (Authorization to Reimburse) was sent</p>. <p>The value present in this field is populated in Tag 30 of MT747.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>NO INPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The valid values are SP, AC, DP and MX. This field is drived by PAY.TYPE field in LC.TYPES where</p>
            <p />
            <p>'P' will default 'SP'</p>
            <p>'A' will default 'AC'</p>
            <p>'D' will default 'DP'</p>
            <p>'N' will default 'MX'</p>
            <p>If 'M', this field will become mandatory, and input is         required.</p>
            <p>Only mixed payment, the user will be allowed to input combination of 'SP', 'AC' or 'DP', whereby</p>
            <p />
            <p>Only one 'SP', if input</p>
            <p>Any number of 'AC' or 'DP' , nevertheless any repeating         type, if input, ACPT.TM.BAND has to be different.</p>
            <p>For example:</p>
            <table border="0" cellspacing="4">
                <tr>
                    <td>DRAW.TYPE</td>
                    <td>SP</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>ACPT.TM.BAND</td>
                    <td>20001231</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>DRAW.TYPE</td>
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>ACPT.TM.BAND</td>
                    <td>90</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>DRAW.TYPE</td>
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>ACPT.TM.BAND</td>
                    <td>180</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>DRAW.TYPE</td>
                    <td>DP</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>ACPT.TM.BAND</td>
                    <td>180</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input for mixed payment LC's.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account from which the commission amount is to be collected.  Must be a valid account not necessarily in contract currency.</p>
            <p>Validation:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory when commission code is defined and commission is collected.</p>
                <p value="2">Input is not allowed when commission is claimed.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSFERABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to decide whether LC is tranferrable or not when LC initiated through Internet Banking.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed Values are YES or NO</p>
            <p> Default value is 'NO' </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the departmental ID number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the commission amount for current schedule.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.XCHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the exchange rate to be used between the charge debit account and the charge currency.</p>
            <p>If no input is made then the mid rate CHARGE.CCY.MARKET set in LC.PARAMETERS will be used.</p>
            <p>If no currency market is set in LC.PARAMETERS then the default market for LC will be used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAFT.PRINT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This fielkd is used to indicate whether a draft print of the Letter of Credit / Documentary Collection document created is to be produced on deal input (i.e. before the authorization stage). </p>
            <p />
            <p>If set to 'Y' and the Letter of Credit is an IMPORT credit then a draft print of the letter of credit MT700 will be produced after validation. The message type used for this delivery transaction is MT9700. This preview will not be available at the authorisation stage</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>'Y' or 'N'. Default from         LC.PARAMETERS file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDIT.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays that date and time of the last auditor access to the file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is no longer used. Its function is replaced by the multi-value PORT.LIM.REF</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.MT740</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Decides whether MT740 needs to be sent at LC issuance or Drawings stage. If MT740 is not sent at LC level, MT740 will be sent at Drawings level on the acceptance date.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">If MT740 was not sent at LC level, then MT747 will not be triggered at LC amendment stage.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Field options are YES or NO.</p>
                <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Default value is 'YES'.</p>
                <p value="3" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Allowed only for Import LC's.</p>
                <p value="4" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Allowed only when THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO is specified.</p>
                <p value="5" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Must be 'YES' for Sight or Mixed LC's.</p>
                <p value="6" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Override message "MT740 message will be sent from Drawings" is generated when value is set to 'NO'.</p>
                <p value="7" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">No change field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.CHARGED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to input a code to determine the identity of the party from whom the charge is to be taken. For all charges within the multivalue set, this can be different. Some of the charges can be levied against the Opener, others against the Beneficiary, and some against the Third Party. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p><strong>O</strong>(pener) or <strong>T</strong>(hird         Party) or <strong>B</strong>(eneficiary). </p>
            <p>If 'T' is specified, then THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO must be set.</p>
            <p>If no input is made this field will default to         CHARGES.FROM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYNDICATE.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field decides whether charges need to syndicated or not.Only charges defined in LC.PARAMETERS can be syndicated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Allowed values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>No change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WP.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>From G10.2.02, the charge account will be part of the charge input set. Therefore this field will be no longer use.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field identifies the account from which related charges will be taken, if any.Any valid account number can be entered in this field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>If this is entered and the credit is an IMPORT contract , then all charges relating to this L/C will automatically be taken from this account whenever a charge arises during the life of the L/C. All charges for drawings under this L/C will taken from this account, on the day the charge is raised, unless value dating charges is set to yes (From the LC.PARAMETERS file), when they will be taken on the Issue date for L/Cs and the value date for drawings under this L/C. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Account Format.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Override messages acknowleged at the latest input </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to display the Issuing Bank/Handling Bank/Customer reference for use on messages and advices. </p>
            <p>For Export LCs this is the Issuing Bank's reference. </p>
            <p>For outward collections this is the Customer's reference number and for inward collections this the Remitting Bank's reference number. </p>
            <p>For Inward MT730 the field will be populated with the value in Tag20</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-16 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Input only allowed         for Collections and Export Letters of Credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMENDMENT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field for Import Letter of Credit and Input field for Exports.</p>
            <p>This field displays the number of <strong>external</strong> amendments made to this letter of credit. </p>
            <p>Amendments (OPERATION.CODE of A) are classified as internal or external depending on the value input in the AMENDMENT.DEL field. </p>
            <p>Third parties are informed of external amendments. </p>
            <p>For each external amendment made, this field will be automatically incremented by 1. In the case of Export Letter of Credit, the user has the option to input the same. It can then be used in advices and documents sent to third parties to ensure that all are aware of each modification made to the LC. </p>
            <p>This field is used in SWIFT message MT707 field 26 Number of Amendment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a NO-INPUT, system maintained field for Import Letters of       Credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIXED.PAYMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This free text field will specify the payment dates, amounts and/or method for the determination in an LC, which is available by mixed payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters for free format text - Type A.         (Multivalue field (Maximum of 4 lines)) </p>
            <p>Optional input, no default.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIM.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.RULE.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the rules the credit is subject to. Accepts 35 alphanumeric characters. Input to the field is mandatory only if OTHR is specified in APPL.RULE.CODES field. For the remaining values of APPLR.ULE.CODE field, This field remains NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the number of times the contract has been modified. This is a counter number with the initial entry of the contract being 1. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts the Amendment Number, on which the decision has received. The order of input need not be sequential or in any pattern. The number is the amendment number of the LC Amendment. Once input and committed, until the Amendment is authorised, the field does not open up. </p>
            <p>Input, only during Operation 'D'.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) MANDATORY INPUT, when Operation is 'D'.</p>
            <p>(2) Input must be the number after the alphabet A of the LC.AMENDMENTS ID.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: If LC.AMENDMENTS ID is TF0007500001A01 , then AMEND.NO must 01.</p>
            <p>(3) The Amendment must have status as PENDING.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>RESERVE5 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULLY.UTILISED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate whether this transaction is fully utilised. </p>
            <p>YES - fully utilised NO - not fully utilised </p>
            <p>If this field is set to YES then any drawings will require the override of a warning message. </p>
            <p>This field will default to NO. It may be set to YES in the following circumstances. </p>
            <p>- Manually during an amendment to the LC. </p>
            <p>- If a drawing has its FULLY.UTILISED field set to YES. </p>
            <p>- Automatically if the total of all drawings exceed the LC amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Must be YES or NO.</p>
            <p>Default is NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWING.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Thid field displays the amount of DRAWING processed under the related DRAW.TYPE multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LMT.FOR.REVOLVING</field>
<desc>
            <p>In the case of Revolving Non-Cumulative Letters of Credit, the limit can be impacted only for the current revolution, by setting this field to SINGLE. The consol entry also would be raised for the current cycle's liability.</p>
            <p>The default would be NULL, retaining the extant flow.</p>
            <p>If  an LC were to be issued for USD 150,000 for  2 revolutions, the limit would be impacted  for USD 450,000 and consol entry would be raised for USD 450,000. By setting this to  SINGLE, the limit would be impacted for USD 150,000 and this would also be the amount  of consol entry. </p>
            <p>During the roll-over the new limit line and the consol entry would be raised as a part of End of Day processing.</p>
            <p>However, if Cash Margin (Provision) were to be taken under this LC, the same would be calculated on the entire Liability of the LC and not just for the Current cycle's  liability as populated in CUR.REVOL.LIAB.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input is SINGLE.</p>
            <p>Input permitted only if the LC is  revolving and        non-cumulative in nature.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVOLVE.FQY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRO.OUT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field represents the provision amount outstanding for the transaction.</p>
            <p>When a sight DRAWING is processed, the provision released will be deducted from the outstanding provision amount.</p>
            <p>When an acceptance DRAWING is processed, this field will not be affected. However, PRO.AWAIT.REL will be stored with the released amount, pending to be released on maturity date of the acceptance DRAWING.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the mid rate between the LC CURRENCY and the PROVISION CREDIT ACCOUNT CURRENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATED.DRAWING</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Currently, the only value of this field will be '00'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUE.BK.KEYED</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Flag set when issuing banks name and address has been input.</p>
            <p>This means that if this flag has been set then only print output is produced.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.ENTRY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays either a statement entry number or a category entry number depending on the value contained in the corresponding multivalue fields of the contract. </p>
            <p>Note : The only statement and category entries raised on this deal will relate to charge entries. All other entries are CRF contingent entries. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.LIM.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field displays the limit reference number to be checked for limit control on LC transactions. A check will be done on the limit parameter to update the correct reference. In case of mixed payment this will refer to the limit reference to be updated for the portion concerned. </p>
            <p>Each LC transaction will be checked against the LIMIT file to verify the availability of a limit facility.</p>
            <p>This information was formerly held in LIMIT.REFERENCE. (G10.2)</p>
            <p>If no input is made in this field, the LIMIT system will provide a default according to the values defined in the LIMIT.PARAMETER file. If required, more details can be found in the LIMIT user guide.</p>
            <p>Note: The customer that limits will be checked against is the customer defined in CON.CUS.LINK.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3-7 numeric characters</p>
            <p>Input to this field must be a valid LIMIT.REFERENCE         number</p>
            <p>If no limit exists for the customer, a corresponding         error message will be displayed by the system with an         override facility.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the customer portfolio number to which this LC record will be associated with. This will be used for the portfolio valuation for that BENEFICIARY.CUSTNO. </p>
            <p>No input will result in this deal to be excluded from the portfolio valuation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 characters numeric. (Optional input )</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate the number of times the charges are required to be taken on the default charges.</p>
            <p>-----</p>
            <p>Example</p>
            <p>An LC is opened for 6 months and a charge set in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE, is invoked by default. Let us assume the amount invoked by default calculation is USD100. - If the user wants to collect USD 400 then charge period will be set to 4 by the user. </p>
            <p>------</p>
            <p>This is applicable only when the charge is defaulted from FT.COMMISSION.TYPE or FT.CHARGE.TYPE.</p>
            <p>Note that the expiry date may be have been extended to ensure it occurs on a working day. You may have to adjust this field because the calculation of the default for the number of times the charge is applied depends on the number of calendar months and is rounded up.</p>
            <p>If charge currency and amount is input, CHARGE.PERIOD input will be overridden.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.AMOUNT.LOCAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>The value in this field contains the local currency equivalent of the liability amount mentioned in field &lt;LIABILITY.AMT.&gt;.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.CUM.TRF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.NOTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides the user with a free text field to make any internal notes regarding the assignment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field identifies the currency that tax is to be levied in. This can be different from the LC.CURRENCY. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Based on the tax code obtained from the commission and/or charges table, this field displays the automatically calculated tax (if any) which is to be added to the charge. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Indicates the calculation method to be used to generate the Discount and Load amounts on the Drawing contracts related to this L/C and also for charge amortisations. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The following types are acceptable:</p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p><strong>Key</strong>
                        </p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p><strong>Days/Denominator</strong>
                        </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>A</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>360/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>B</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>366/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>C</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>366/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>D</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>360/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>E</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>366/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>F</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>360/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>S</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>Special</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>W</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>252/252</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>W1</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>21/252</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p>For illustrations of all supported </p>
            <p>INTEREST.BASIS</p>
            <p> types see: </p><a href="INTEREST.BASIS_data.htm"><p>INTEREST.BASIS</p></a>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 type A (alphanumeric) character. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are A, B, C, D,E, F, S,W,W1 or blank. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Default Value = Interest Day Basis    as specified on the Currency record for the currency of         the Letter of Credit / Documentary Collection. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THIRD.PARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>For letters of credit, this field identifies the reimbursing third party bank, through whom reimbursement will be made to the negotiating bank, if this is not a customer of the bank. For collection this field is used to identify the Name &amp; Address of the Account with Bank. </p>
            <p>If the third party reimbursing bank is not one of the banks customers (i.e. not on the customer file), then this field allows the input of a name and address of the reimbursing bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>No input allowed if THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO is set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECT.COLL.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Direct Export Collection Reference. One of a series of references pre-issued for use by a customer.</p>
            <p>It is a reference which can be used with the customer ID as an alternative key to access the collection record..</p>
            <p>The reference must be in a series assigned to the customer in the DIR.COL.ALL application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The reference must be in a series assigned to the         customer in the DIR.COL.ALL application.</p>
            <p>The reference must not have been used in another         collection by this customer.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REIM.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDITOR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field dispalys the code name of auditor of the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement. </p>
            <p>As in the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to define in the LC file up to 999 Local Elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified. These Local Elements should be defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice. </p>
            <p>The name(s) of the new element(s), as well as the Format and <p>Validation Rules:</p>, must be defined in the LOCAL.TABLE, prior to the creation of any LETTER.OF.CREDIT records. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the reference number to uniquely identify a particular contract. </p>
            <p>Every new Letter of Credit will automatically be assigned a unique number.  The system maintains a central indicator on the company record, which determines whether new contract numbers are to be automatically generated by the system or input by the user. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The Letters of Credit number is a 10 digit number, prefixed with 'TF' based upon the following format:           TF YY DDD 99999   where:           TF    = Trade Finance (Letter of Credit)          YY    = Current Year          DDD   = Julian Day          99999 = Sequence Number</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIXED.COMM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the commission amount for each commission schedule.  Amount expressed in the currency of the contract. If the user inputs a value in this field, then the default commission calculation will be ignored.</p>
            <p>User input field.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Not allowed when COMM.RATE  is input.</p>
                <p value="2">Fixed commission amount must be less than LC face value.</p>
                <p value="3">Input of value zero is not allowed.</p>
                <p value="4">If user doesnt input any value in this field, system will default PERIODIC.COMM.AMT field of LC.GROUP.CONDITION defined for the periodic commission code in COMM.CODE field</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFERRED.PAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This free text field will specify the payment date or method for its determination for which deferred payment drawings will be made under the LC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 x 35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>If the LC type is DP (Deferred Payment) this field is         mandatory input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When AVAILABLE.BY is "BY DEF PAYMENT", standard text will be defaulted based on values defined in COLL.MAT.CODE and DAYS field for import LC.</p>
            <p />
            <p>E.g 120 DAYS AFTER BILL OF EXCHANGE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSSHIPMENTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies if transhipments are allowed under the terms of the LC. </p>
            <p>Transhipments is used in the production of documents and advices to specify whether transhipments are allowed under the terms and conditions of the Letter of Credit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'Y' - Transhipments Permitted or 'N' -Transhipments not         permitted. Default is 'N'.</p>
            <p>Also permits a maximum of 35 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSFERRED.LC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This is the T24 transaction reference of Child L/C(s) and associated with Field &lt;TRAN.PORT.AMT&gt;. It is used for maintaining the serial control between Parent and Child L/C(s) in transferable L/C process. Details please refer to the example of the help text in Field &lt;PARENT.LC.NO&gt;.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>RESERVE2 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the internal bank identity number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNCONF.LIAB.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>UNCONF.LIAB.AMT: </p>
            <p>                                  Identifies the total unconfirmed liability amount in respect of partially confirmed Letters of Credit. This is used as a running total of the remaining unconfirmed liability amount, after drawings have been made under this Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p> The amount will be expressed in terms of LC currency. This field will be calculated by the system as the difference between LIABILITY.AMT and CONF.LIAB.AMT. No operator input will be allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>System Generated</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard amount format </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.TEXT.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format sub-value field for sending advices to participants in Syndicated LC's.This field will be mapped directly to tag 79 of  MT799 message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Accepts Swift characters.</p>
            <p>A sub-value set can hold 35 lines with 50 characters each.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates corresponding charge code for tax  defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Associated multivalue field associated with fields TAX.CODE through to TAX.DATE.</p>
            <p>Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.TRACE.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays last trace information relating to the previous field &lt;LAST.DATE.INFO&gt;.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMENDMENTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This free format field is used to describe amendments to the transaction, other than Amount/CCY/Maturity date, which can be amended in their specific fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>6 x 35 type S (Swift Standard Format).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the amount of the Letter of Credit / Documentary Collection which will always be expressed in the currency defined in the previous field (LC.CURRENCY). </p>
            <p>In order to facilitate the efficient entry of the amount, an input feature has been provided which allows for the suppression of trailing zeros. In english language text this is accomplished by using a 'T' to denote thousands, and an 'M' to denote millions. Other languages will require the provision of translation values. </p>
            <p>e.g. INPUT VALUE </p>
            <p>1T = 1,000.00, 1M = 1,000,000.00, 1B = 1,000,000,000.00</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2-16 type AMT (Standard amount format) characters.         (Mandatory input) The amount must be greater than zero.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GTEE.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Specifies the Shipping Guarantee (SG) reference linked to the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">System updated field in case SG is issued under LC and User updated field in case SG is issued under import documentary collection.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Validation Rules:</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">User input allowed only when,</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">LC and SG currency are the same</p>
                <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">LC and SG amount are the same</p>
                <p value="3" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">SG is (must be) a live record</p>
                <p value="4" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">SG is not (must not have been) attached to any other LC</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEG.DEALER.REFNO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.REIM.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the position the transaction will be recorded under. </p>
            <p>Any positions updated as a result of the Letter of Credit / Documentary Collection contract willl be recorded under the position type entered here e.g. Trading, Investment etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2 SSS (Uppercase alpha) characters. </p>
            <p>Default from LC.PARAMETERS.</p>
            <p>Must be present on the FX.POS.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACK.ACPT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field holds the amount Acknowledged/Accepted, when an inward MT410/MT412 (as held in Tag32) is processed.</p>
            <p>The value held here is for information purpose only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a system maintained field.</p>
            <p>Standard amount field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UCP.IND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define whether the letter of credit is subject to the Uniform Customs and Practices or not. </p>
            <p>If 'Y' is input then this LC is subject to the Uniform Customs and Practices Rules, otherwise it is not. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'Y' or 'N'. Default 'Y'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLL.MAT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>In support of Option K of Tag 32a in 4** series of SWIFT for collection and to default text in DEFERRED.PAY and DRAFTS.AT for acceptence and deferred LC's.</p>
            <p>This works in conjunction with the DAYS field and accepts the following values.</p>
            <p>will get triggered if DAYS field has a value and DATE.ACCEPTED is left blank.</p>
            <p>The default values are ST in the case of Sight Document and BE in the case of Usance documents.</p>
            <p>The value here along with DAYS shall form the basis for  field 32 of MT 400 generated from DRAWINGS under this collection. In case DATE.ACCEPTED is input, then that will be taken to form F32 of MT 400.</p>
            <p>COLL.MAT.CODE in conjuction with DAYS field will be defaulted for deferred and acceptance LC's in DEFERRED.PAY and DRAFTS.AT fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory for Option K of Tag 32a in 4** series.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRO.AWAIT.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the Provision amount awaiting to be released. This is the provision amount that is pending to be released on the maturity date of the ACCEPTANCE DRAWINGS.</p>
            <p>This is the sum total of all provision amounts awaiting release.</p>
            <p>When an acceptance drawing is matured from AC to MA or a DP is matured to MD manually, the provision amount awaiting release will be released on line. If AC or DP is not changed to MA or MD manually, then the EOD (End Of Day) operation will change the status and release the provision amount. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATED.LC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field is used for displaying the corresponding import letter of credit number when a back to back transaction is generated.</p>
            <p>See the BACK.TO.BACK field for further information. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>16 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>This is a NO INPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field holds the activity number, which is triggered by the latest activity in the life-cycle of the transaction. The activity is 4 digit number composed of three main parts:</p>
            <p />
            <p>First indicates the operation</p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - Represents O or P; operation         in LETTER.OF.CREDIT</p>
            <p>2 - Represents A, C or      T; operation in LETTER.OF.CREDIT</p>
            <p>3 - Represents Sight Drawing Operation in DRAWINGS</p>
            <p>4 - Represents Usance Drawing Operation in DRAWINGS</p>
            <p />
            <p>Second indicates the type of instrument</p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - Represents Outward Collection</p>
            <p>2 - Represents Inward Collection</p>
            <p>4 - Represents Export Letter of Credit</p>
            <p>8 - Represents Import Letter of Credit</p>
            <p />
            <p>And the last two digit indicate the detail activity         related to that operation.</p>
            <p>For example : For the L/C Import Issuing activity, the first digit will be 1. The second digit will be 8 and the last two digits will be 01 (to indicate basic INPUT/AUTHORIZE operation). Thus, the activity for L/C import issuing will be LC-1801. The complete list of activity codes can be found in User's Manual.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.DR.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field will be equivalent to the charge account in the respective multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.NO.BEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the customer portfolio number with which this letter of credit record will be associated. This will be used for the portfolio valuation for that BENEFICIARY.CUSTNO. </p>
            <p>No input will result in this deal being excluded from the portfolio valuation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 3 characters numeric. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field contains the code of the tax table which has been used when calculating tax on charges and/or commission. </p>
            <p>The field does not require any operator input as it is obtained from the relevant commission or charges table. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the charge/commission amount in the currency of the account that the charge/commission is taken from. </p>
            <p>When the charge/commission is taken from an account that is in a different currency to the charge currency (CHARGE.CURRENCY), then this field is used to hold the amount that was actually debited. This will be used for positions update if the currency is not local. The field is automatically updated when the charge/commission is taken from the account using the current market mid spot rates. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
            <p>Standard Amount Format. Associated mulivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the account to which charges are to be debited when the charge is to be collected immediately. Not allowed if the status is input as 3. Allowed only when the status is set to null or 2. Can be any account including nostro or internal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.PORTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of LC that is available for a particular DRAW.TYPE under the multivalue set. This field, when input will automatically calculate and update the PAYMENT.PCT. Not allowed if PAYMENT.PCT is input. For amendment of mixed payment LC under operation "A", the increase or decrease of amount for each DRAW.TYPE is to be entered by the operator.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SL.REF.TRANCHE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts Facility reference plus tranche number when LETTER.OF CREDIT is issued under SL facility.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid facility reference plus tranche id with product type in Facility defined as either LCI or LCE.</p>
            <p>Input not allowed for Revolving LC's.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWINGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field is used to display a running total of the amount of drawings/payments made under the contract to date. The amount will be expressed in the currency of the Letter of contract (LC.CURRENCY). </p>
            <p>When a new Letter of Credit/Documentary Collection is input, this field will contain 0. Whenever a new drawing is entered, this field will be updated by the amount of the drawing. A drawing on a 'collection' basis (Drawing Type CO) under a letter of credit will not be included in the total. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the code name of the latest inputter to the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNCONF.LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>UNCONF.LIMIT.REF: </p>
            <p>                                 In a partially confirmed Letter of Credit, the user may prefer to assign a valid LIMIT.REFERENCE number for the unconfirmed portion. The value into this field enables to update the limit accordingly.</p>
            <p>If left blank, the information limit line is defaulted from the LIMIT.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field must be a valid LIMIT.REFERENCE number.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USANCE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.TO.BK740</field>
<desc>
            <p>Applicable only to import letters of credit when a reimbursement bank has been nominated. This multivalue free text field allows for additional information to be passed onto the reimbursing bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.REVOLVING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the number of times the letter of credit will revolve.</p>
            <p><strong>Example:</strong>
            </p>
            <p>A letter of credit is issued for US$50,000.00 and the NO.OF.REVOLVING field shows an input of '3'. This indicates that the letter of credit will be revolved three times. The liability will show an outstanding of USD200,000 (i.e. the initial US$50,000 plus US$150,000 [US$50,000 revolved 3 times]).</p>
            <p>In the case of an export revolving letter of credit which has been transferred; any amendment (operation 'A') to the field NO.OF.REVOLVING will be checked against that of the transferred letter of credit. If the proposed number change does not support the transfer already effected then it will not be allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 alphanumeric characters. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>For <strong>Letters of Credit</strong> this field identifies the Beneficiary's name and address.</p>
            <p>For<strong> Documentary Collections</strong> this field identifies the name and address of the bank's customer's counterparty i.e. Drawer (Inward Collections), Drawee (Outward Collections).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>This file is mandatory if the BENEFICIARY.CUSTNO. has not         been input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIAB.PORT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>In mixed payment letters of credit, the liability relating to each portion such as sight, acceptance or deferred payment is stored here.</p>
            <p>In revolving letters of credit this field will contain the lc amount which is to be revolved or expired each time it crosses the expiry date mentioned in ACPT.TM.BAND of that particular portion.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUING.BANK.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional input. </p>
            <p>Input to this field sets up the default account to be used for reimbursement from the Issuing Bank (in the case of a Export Letter of Credit) and the Collecting Bank (in the case of an Outward Documentary Collection). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Account Format. Should belong to the Issuing /         Collecting Bank.</p>
            <p>Only allowed for Export Letters of Credit / Outward         Documentary Collections.</p>
            <p>No input allowed for Inward Documentary Collections /         Import Letters of Credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTION.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This will be the number of multivalue sets used in serial order. If three multivalue sets are input originally and authorised and subsequently, if a set is deleted and another one is input the number will be 4 though there will be only three sets appearing in the record. It is a serial count.</p>
            <p>For revolving letters of credit this field will display the revolution number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMENDMENT.DEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate whether the amendment is internal of external.</p>
            <p>'Yes' indicates that this amendment is external and will be communicated to third parties using messages and documents sent via the Delivery application. </p>
            <p>'No' indicates that this amendment is internal and will not be communicated to the third parties to the contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Following values allowed: Yes - send delivery messages.         This is an external amendment. No - do not send delivery         messages. This is an internal amendment.</p>
            <p>Input only permitted if OPERATION.CODE is A for         amendment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVIS.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field details the provision percentage to be used to calculate the provision amount. Input into this field is only permitted if the field &lt;PROVIS.AMOUNT&gt; is left blank. They cannot co-exist.</p>
            <p>However, as this field is also used for Partial Confirmation, whenever a value is input in the  &lt;CONFIRMATION.AMT&gt; and the provision is calculated only on that value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAND.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field is used to decide whether LC is STANBY or not when LC initiated  through Internet Banking.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed Values are YES or NO</p>
            <p> Default value is 'NO' </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.ORIG.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the rate between LC.CURRENCY and local currency. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field decides whether to hit the limit at the stage of 'IO' for this LC </p>
            <p> Defaulted from IB.LIMT field of LC.PARAMETERS, user can overwrite the default value.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed Values are YES or NO</p>
            <p> Value 'YES' will hit the limit at 'IO' stage in Internet Banking </p>
            <p> Value 'NO' will not hit the limit at 'IO' stage in Internet Banking</p>
            <p> Default value is 'NO' </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides the user with the ability to produce free format narrative for particular types of delivery messages. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERDRAWN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the amount that this letter of credit is overdrawn. If the letter of credit is not overdrawn then this field will be zero. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.TRACE.DTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the date of last tracer of a documentary collection.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE.CR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define the percentage to be added to the letter of credit amount (LC.AMOUNT) to calculate the full liability amount or maximum amount that can be drawn. </p>
            <p>If a rate is specified here, then it is used to calculate the liability amount of the letter of credit by adding the percentage of the LC.AMOUNT to the LC.AMOUNT. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>If the LC.AMOUNT = 1,000,000.00 and the percentage entered here = 10, then the LIABILITY.AMOUNT will be equal to 1,100,000.00. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard rate format (Only up to 6 integer and decimal         characters).</p>
            <p>If this field is entered, then MAXIMUM.CR.AMT must be         left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TENOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is valid for <strong>Documentary Collections </strong>only. It is used in conjunction with the following field 'DAYS' to indicate the TENOR of the drafts under the collection and is used in the production of corresponding Collection messages. Only the descriptive text is input in this field.</p>
            <p>eg. To input a draft of '120 days from the bill of lading date', the words 'days from the bill of lading date' would be inserted in this field. The actual number of days i.e. '120' would be inserted in the field 'DAYS'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>35 S (Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.</p>
            <p>For usance collection, free format text.</p>
            <p>Defaults to "at Sight".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field determines the exchange rate to be used between the provision debit account and the provision credit account, when the currencies differ.</p>
            <p>Default is the mid rate of LC.MARKET.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE.CHRGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This free text field is used to specify charges to be borne by the beneficiary.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>1-6 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Defaults standard text - All charges outside (Applicant's Country) are for the account of Beneficiary' for import LC's.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.AMT.COVERED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to specify any additional amounts covered by this LC, i.e. charges, transportation costs, etc. </p>
            <p>Used only for the production of LC documents and advices, to specify any additional amounts that are covered by this LC (as described in S.W.I.F.T. MT700 field no. 39c) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Multivalue field of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OSUSANCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the total number of term or usance drawings made under this letter of credit. </p>
            <p>When a new deal is input, this field will contain 0. Whenever a new term or usance drawing (drawing with type 'AC', or 'DP') is entered via the DRAWINGS application, then this field will be increased by 1. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENTS.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the description of the documents to be presented by under the letter of credit. It will be included in messages/advices generated by the application. </p>
            <p>The descriptions input to this field will be used in addition to the predefined documents input in the DOCUMENT.CODE field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Multivalue field of 50 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.PCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the percentage amount of LC that is available for a particular DRAW.TYPE. </p>
            <p>For LC.TYPES with P &amp; A defined in PAY.TYPE (within LC.TYPES) this shall be defaulted to 100 by the system.</p>
            <p>For MIXED PAYMENT, the user shall input the appropriate percentage and also the DRAW.TYPE. This is mutually exclusive to the field "PAY.PORTION". As the percentage is input the PAY.PORTION amount is calculated and stored.</p>
            <p>For revolving letters of credit this field is system generated and will hold a value in proportion to the total liability. For example, if a revolving letter of credit is opened for US$100,000 with number or revolutions 3, then this field will hold a value of 25% ($100,000*4 = $400,000, which is equal to 100%, so the lc amount will be shown as 25%)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTICIPANT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the Participant who is part of the Syndicated LC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid participant in Facility tranche.</p>
            <p>No change field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVISE.THUR.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the Advise thru bank's reference number.</p>
            <p><strong><p>Validation Rules:</p></strong>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in the production of messages/advices. A list of the various types of documents that are commonly required under L/C's are detailed in the LC.ADVICE.TEXT file and recorded by an ID code. This field can therefore be used to display the documents required for presentation under a letter of credit, or in the case of collections to display the actual documents presented.The full description of the document will be displayed in the field &lt;DOCUMENT.TXT&gt;.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> It accepts either Text or Customer Number-Text, If both exists priority is given to Customer Number-Text </p>
            <p> Customer Number should exists in CUSTOMER table. </p>
            <p> Text can be maximum of  10 Alphanumeric Characters </p>
            <p> Must exist in LC.ADVICE.TEXT file </p>
            <p> If documents required under the LC are not recorded in         the LC ADVICE.TEXT file, they can be input separately in         DOCUMENTS.REQ.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRO.AWAIT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>When an acceptance LC with provision is opened, the provision is opened, the provision needs to be released on the maturity date of the DRAWING. This field represents the related provision to be released subsequently on maturity date of DRAWING.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.TRF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>In case of transferable export LCs, this will contain the amount transferred to various transferees. </p>
            <p>In case of mixed payment LC (export), this will contain the transferred amount under the the respective DRAW.TYPE.</p>
            <p>For transferred child LCs, this will contain the LC amount transferred to the beneficiary.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to trigger the collection of periodic commission in LETTER.OF.CREDIT for an issuance and also for an amendment.</p>
            <p>Separate amendment commission code can be defined for the LC either through operation A or D.</p>
            <p>Accepts valid code from PERIODIC.COMMISSION table.</p>
            <p>If any code is defined for the LC type (with operation O, A or D) in LC.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION, then the same is defaulted in this field. However, user input takes precedence.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>Periodic commission is not supported for,</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Revolving LCs</p>
                <p value="2">LCs issued under syndication</p>
                <p value="3">Pre-advised LCs</p>
            </p>
            <p value="1">If no issuance commission has been taken, then amendment commission cannot be taken.</p>
            <p value="2">If separate amendment commission code is not input, then the existing issuance commission will be recalculated.</p>
            <p value="3">Only one amendment commission can be taken (either through operation A or D). For subsequent amendments, the same amendment commission will be recalculated. LC issuance commission accruals will remain unchanged.</p>
            <p value="4">If frequency is defined for LC issuance commission, then separate amendment commission code cannot be input in the amendment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GTEE.MARGIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value held by this field represents the portion of LC Cash Margin used up by the MD.DEAL when linked to Shipping Guarantee.</p>
            <p>The amount is represented in the currency of the Credit Provision account of the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWEE.CUST.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of messages/advices, this field identifies the name of the drawee of Bills of Exchange to be presented under the LC, if the drawee is a customer of the bank with a valid CUSTOMER.NO.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z Uppercase alpha or '.').</p>
            <p>If DRAFTS.AT is used, either this field or DRAWEEmust         have a value.</p>
            <p>If this field is used, then DRAWEE must be left blank.</p>
            <p>The Customer code must be on CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>If the LC type is DP (Deferred Payment) this field must         be left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.CONFIRM.INST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the previous asset type(i.e. Previous value in CONFIRM.INST field). </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPIRY.PLACE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is relevant to <strong>Letters of Credit </strong>only and identifies the location at which the Letter of Credit expires. </p>
            <p>Can be a 2 digit country code eg. GB or US or up to 26 free format characters identifying the place of Letter of Credit expiry. If a 2 digit code is entered, then this is checked against the COUNTRY file for enrichment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2-26 S (Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.</p>
            <p>If 2 digits are entered then this must be a valid country         code from the COUNTRY file.</p>
            <p>If more than 2 digits are entered then any location can         be specified.</p>
            <p>No input required for Collection.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LATEST.SHIPMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of messages/advices, this field stipulates the latest date for loading on board/dispatch/taking in charge for goods shipped under the LC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format.</p>
            <p>Date cannot be greater than Expiry date.</p>
            <p>Input to this field is not allowed if field         &lt;SHIPMENT.PERIOD&gt; has been used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Contains the delivery keys used for the generation of LC advices / documents / payments from the Electronic Delivery System. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field turns on the <strong>Provision</strong> processing for import Letters of Credit and export confirmed LCs.. When this field is set to 'YES' , an account/percentage provision can be entered. The system will then calculate (using the percentage entered) a provision amount, which will be passed to the Provision.amount field. This amount is in the currency of the provision account. Provision processing is also known as Margin processing. </p>
            <p>For a customer with a standard provision account and percentage you can set-up the LC.CUSTOMER.CONDITION file with the defaults for the provision account/percentage by Letter of Credit type. </p>
            <p>Note : Throughout the Trade Finance module this processing will be referenced as Provision processing. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Default is 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUING.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the Issuing Bank for an Export Letter of Credit and the Collecting Bank for an Outward Documentary Collection.</p>
            <p>Input is mandatory if the Bank in question is not a customer on the CUSTOMER file and the respective customer no. has not been inserted in the field ISSUING.BANK.NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>No input allowed for Inward Documentation Collections /         Import Letters of Credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.TO.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provide the user with the ability to input free format information for the receiver bank, to be reproduced on L/C messages/advices. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>6x35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVISE.THRU.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the bank who is designated to act as an intermediary between the advising bank of a letter of credit and the beneficiary or the collecting bank of a documentary collection and the drawee. Input into this field is conditional upon the party in question holding a valid customer.no with the bank.</p>
            <p>This field is required for letters of credit and collections if the advising/collecting bank does not have a direct relationship with the beneficiary/drawee. It identifies the bank through which documents/advices are to be routed for advice/presentation to the beneficiary/drawee. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.').</p>
            <p>For Import/Opening LCs/Outward Collection, cannot be the         same as the ADVISING.BK.CUSTNO or the THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO.</p>
            <p>For Export/Advising LCs/Inward Collection, cannot be the         same as the ISSUING.BANK.NO or the THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the total number of term or usance drawings made under the letter of credit which have been discounted. </p>
            <p>When a new deal is input, this field will contain 0. Whenever a new term or usance drawing (drawing with type 'AC', or 'DP') that is discounted, is entered via the DRAWINGS application for this Letter of credit then this field will be incremented by 1. This provides the user with an easy reference to identify the total number of discounted drawings made against this letter of credit. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVOLVING.OS.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the inward delivery reference for the corresponding message type.</p>
            <p>For example, in R20120828160574535800, 'R' identifies an  inward message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the SWIFT currency code to denote the currency of the Letter of Credit / Documentary Collection. Will be used on all related correspondence. CRF entries are generated in this currency. </p>
            <p>Defaults to local currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT Currency code e.g. United States Dollars must be         USD. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>Once the deal has been authorised, this field cannot be         changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESSEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the user to divert a particular message type to another (third) party. </p>
            <p>The user has a number of options:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Simple insertion of a name or address. This will re-route         the message in PRINT format to the named party.</p>
            <p>The code 'TX-' followed by a telex number. This will         re-route the message by TELEX to the number detailed.</p>
            <p>The code 'SW-' followed by a S.W.I.F.T. code. This will         re-route the message by SWIFT to the respective bank.</p>
            <p>The code 'C-' followed by a valid customer number or         mnemonic. This will re-route the message in PRINT format         to the customer indiated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>50 Alphanumeric character field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the commission code applied for the period band.</p>
            <p>System maintained field. Associated multi value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This free text field is used to identify the assignee's name and  address if they are not a customer of the bank and their customer number has not been input in field &lt;ASSN.CUSTNO&gt;.</p>
            <p>.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.OS.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the assignment amount outstanding under each assignment reference. Multivalue set. Any overdrawing of an allotted (assigned) amount will be displayed with a negative sign.</p>
            <p>Updated from DRAWINGS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether Letters of Credit/Documentary Collection default charges are to be waived. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to 'Y' then all charges relating to this LC will be waived, i.e. no default charges will be added. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options available are - <strong>Y</strong>(es) or <strong>N</strong>(o).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.RULE.CODES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the rules the credit is subject to.Following values can be input 
UCP LATEST VERSION,  
EUCP LATEST VERSION, 
UCPURR LATEST VERSION, 
EUCPURR LATEST VERSION, 
ISP LATEST VERSION, 
OTHR                                                                                                                                      If OTHR is input then, the rule under which credit is subject to must be input in APPL.RULE.DESC field. For the other values, APPL.RULE.DESC will remain a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>RESERVE1 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OSUSANCE.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the total value of any outstanding term or usance drawings made under this letter of credit. The amount will be expressed in the currency of the letter of credit (LC.CURRENCY). </p>
            <p>When a new deal is input, this field will contain 0. Whenever a new term or usance drawing (drawing with type 'AC', or 'DP'), is entered via the DRAWINGS application for this LC, then this field will be increased by the amount of the drawing. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHORISER</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the code name of the authoriser of contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCO.TERMS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the terms of LC contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Allowed Values are </p>
            <p> CIF stands for COST,INSURANCE AND FREIGHT </p>
            <p> CFR stands for COST AND FREIGHT </p>
            <p> FOB stands for FREE ON BOARD </p>
            <p> FCA stands for FREE CARRIER </p>
            <p> FAS stands for FREE ALONGSIDE SHIP</p>
            <p> CPT stands for CARRIAGE PAID TO </p>
            <p> CIP stands for CARRIAGE AND INSURANCE PAID TO </p>
            <p> DAF stands for DELEIVERED AT FRONTIER </p>
            <p> DDP stands for DELIEVERED DUTY PAID </p>
            <p> DDU stands for DELIVERED DUTY UNPAID </p>
            <p> DES stands for DELIVERED EX SHIP </p>
            <p> DEQ stands for DELIVERED EX QUAY </p>
            <p> EXW stands for EX WORKS </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLIENT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free text field to hold Client Reference Number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 10 Alpha numeric characters characters </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field contains the tax amount in the currency of the account that the charge is taken from. </p>
            <p>When the tax is taken from an account that is in a different currency to the tax currency (TAX.CCY), then this field is used to hold the amount that was actually debited. This will be used for positions update if the charge currency is different to the account currency. The field is automatically updated when the tax is taken from the account using the current mid market spot rates. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OSCOLLECT.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field identifies the total value of documents sent for 'collection' under a letter of credit which remain outstanding. The amount will be expressed in the currency of the letter of credit (LC.CURRENCY). </p>
            <p>When a new deal is input, this field will contain 0. Whenever a set of documents are sent for collection (drawing type of 'CO' is entered via the DRAWINGS application), then this field will be increased by the amount of the drawing. </p>
            <p>Note: When a drawing that has been sent for 'collection' is subsequently changed to a 'SP', 'AC', or 'DP', then this field is reduced by the amount of the drawing. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.REL.DRG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently, the only value of this field will be '00'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 digits.  Associated mulivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACER.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts valid number of days. The days mentioned here get defaulted in the respective EB.FREE.MESSAGE record.  </p>
            <p> During the EOD process, the tracer date is cycled so as to produce the tracer message again after the above said number of days. If the days are not entered, it is either defaulted from the COUNTRY file or from the EB.FREE.PARAMETERS file for that Application. </p>
            <p>E.g. : +1W or 20W or +9W etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Accepts valid days format  - +NW or NNW where  N  stands for Number of days and  W  stands for Working days.  </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPTO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of days for which the commission is calculated for the associated period band.</p>
            <p>System maintained field. Associated sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDITIONL.CONDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to provide a description of additional conditions that are not detailed elsewhere. The contents of this field may be printed on messages and advices generated by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Multivalue field of 50 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify an easily recognisable reference for each assignment portion. This reference cannot be duplicated within the letter of credit record and should be unique.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORWARD.CONTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds FX forward contract IDs booked against the current Letter Of Credit Contract</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a multi value field </p>
            <p> Holds only valid FX contract reference</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SL.LINK.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents  the date when LETTER.OF.CREDIT was linked to Facility.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Default value - Today</p>
            <p>No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTACT.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p> Free text field to hold telephone numbers or email address for applicant bankers to contact when LC initiated through Internet Banking.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHIP.DESPATCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of messages/advices, this field stipulates the place of dispatch or taking in charge of the goods or loading on board for shipments made under the LC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Marked to Tag 44A.</p>
            <p>One line of 65 characters for SWIFT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THIRD.PARTY.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional input, this field defines the account to be used when payment to or payment from the third party reimbursement bank is to be made. </p>
            <p>The account entered in this field will be used as the default payment to or reimbursement from account for this Letter of credit. </p>
            <p>For Export LCs, this account will be used for claiming funds from the reimbursement bank. </p>
            <p>For Import LCs, this account will be used to pay funds to the reimbursement bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard account format.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid account that belongs to the         THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional input. This multi-value field contains the code(s) to identify other Account Officer(s) involved with the transaction. </p>
            <p>Validation is the same as ACCOUNT.OFFICER above. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mulivalue field of 1-4 digit numeric.</p>
            <p>Must not be the same as ACCOUNT.OFFICER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the date the charge was raised, although not necessarily taken. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REV.OS.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.LCCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field contains the local currency equivalent of the tax amount. </p>
            <p>If the tax amount is not in local currency, then this amount will be calculated when the charge is debited from an account and credited to the P/L account, using the mid market spot rate's at the time. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADV.BK.CONFIRM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for export LC during 'IO' stage in Internet Banking for LC </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether the value date or maturity date or both need to be considered for commission calculation.</p>
            <p>Accepts valid record ID from EB.ACCRUAL.PARAM table.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Applicable only when COMM.RATE or FIXED.COMM.AMT is defined.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.WITH.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of letter of credit messages/advices, this field identifies the bank authorised to pay, accept, or negotiate document presented under the letter of credit if such a bank is a customer with a valid CUSTOMER.NO. This field is not required for collections.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.').         (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>If this field is entered then AVAIL.WITH cannot be         entered.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid CUSTOMER.NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRO.OS.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the provision amount outstanding. This is calculated based on the provision percentage and/or the PROVISION.AMOUNT input by the user. For mixed payment LCs, PAYMENT.PCT will be taken into account in addition to provision percentage or provision amount and the respective provision outstanding amount will be calculated.</p>
            <p>EXAMPLE</p>
            <p>Let us assume a mixed payment for LC for GBP 100,000.</p>
            <table border="0" width="100">
                <tr>
                    <td>DRAW.TYPE </td>
                    <td>SP</td>
                    <td>50%</td>
                    <td>50,000 </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>DRAW.TYPE </td>
                    <td>AC30 </td>
                    <td>50% </td>
                    <td>50,000</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>Let us assume a provision percentage of 50% with provision credit account equal to GBP account. Then PRO.OS.AMT will be 25,000 each under DRAW.TYPE SP and AC30.</p>
            <p>If provision amount is entered instead of %, say 40,000 then this will be divided into two parts of 50% each and 20,000 will be stored in each DRAW.TYPES namely SP and AC30.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the initial date of the contract i.e. the date the Letter of Credit is Issued/Advised/Confirmed. Can be prior to or after the deal input date. </p>
            <p>Should an unconfirmed export Letter of Credit subsequently be confirmed, this initial date will not change. All entries for contingent accounting/charges will be produced effective from this date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date Format. </p>
            <p>Mandatory Input (Default to Today).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVIS.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is used to register any changes in the amount of provision held, as displayed in field &lt;PRO.OUT.AMOUNT&gt; and can be either System Generated or User Input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>As this field is also used for Partial Confirmation, when a value is input in the field &lt;CONFIRMATION.AMT&gt;  the provision is taken only on that value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>By inputting a percentage in the field &lt;PROVIS.PERCENT&gt; the system will automatically calculate a new Provision Amount based on the L/c amount, provision percentage, provision exchange rate and the provision debit account.. Alternatively the user can input an amount directly to indicate an increase in provision. A minus (-) sign inserted before the amount indicating a reduction in the provision amount. The amount is stored in the currency of the provision credit account. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If an amount is input then the         PROVIS.PERCENTAGE will be ignored and the amount entered         will override the calculated %amount. For mixed payment         LCs the amount entered in this field will be split         according to the DRAW.TYPE percentage given in the         multivalue set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The amount here will be converted         to LC.CURRENCY and the Limit will be hit for an amount         LIABILITY minus provision amount, initially when the LC         is input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to input the Decision text, on the Amendment with number entered in the previous field AMEND.NO. This signifies the Beneficiary consent on the Amendment. When the value input is APPROVED and LIMIT.UPDATE holds the value YES the second limit line is appended to the first. The decision APPROVED is irrevocable even at the INAU status. The opposite is possible</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are APPROVED or REJECTED.</p>
            <p>Once APPROVED cannot be REJECTED even at INAU.</p>
            <p>If there is an AMEND.NO this is MANDATORY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.CCY.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts User input exchange rate at which Facility is to be impacted when the LC currency is different from that of the Facility. Commitment available amount in Facility  and Facility limit line will be updated at the rate input in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>Default value  - Mid Reval Rate</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Export Letters of Credit Only. This field identifies the Beneficiary's default account for crediting proceeds to. </p>
            <p>If this field is entered then this account will be credited with the proceeds from the Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Account Format.</p>
            <p>Only allowed for Export/Advising LC's.</p>
            <p>Must belong to Beneficiary.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the 2 digit number to be appended to the key of this L/C/Documentary Collection in order to create the key of the next drawing under this L/C.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>When a new L/C/Documentary Collection is Opened with operation code as 'O',   then this field will contain '01',  identifying the next drawing number as the key of this L/C appended with '01'. When subsequent drawings are entered, this the value of this field will be incremented by 1. so that all drawings made under this L/C/Documentary Collection will have a unique key identifying them. </p>
            <p>Note: For Pre-Advised L/C's  the value in this field will be blank, since no drawings can be made under this type of L/C.  If the Pre- Advised L/C is subsequently changed to Opened,  then this field will be changed to '01' indicating drawings can now be made. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated. 2 Digit number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the payment amount of the last DRAWING made under this letter of credit in the currency of the drawing. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPIRY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For <strong>Letters of Credit</strong>, this field details the 'Expiry Date' of the Letter of Credit in the bank's book and is not necessarily the actual Expiry Date of the Letter of Credit. <strong>On this date all CRF contingent entries and Limits will be liquidated. </strong>After this date no further drawings can be made. For term/usance drawings made under an LC, the maturity review date can be greater than this date. </p>
            <p>Care should be taken not to confuse this field with ADVICE.EXPIRY.DAT which is the actual expiry date advised to the beneficiary in the letter of credit, if different to this EXPIRY.DATE field..</p>
            <p>For <strong>Documentary Collections</strong>, this field details the 'TRACE' date. On this date the item will be included in the 'TRACE' report, which in respect of all Collections whose fate has not been notified by the Collecting Bank. This date can be amended to meet the user's requirements. </p>
            <p>To facilitate easy input of this field, the user can enter a code indicating the number of weeks or months forward of the issue date to be used as the expiry date. This can be entered in the form of a number followed by the letter 'W' for weeks and 'M' for 'months'. For example if '3M' is entered here and the issue date entered above is '15 June 2000' then the expiry date will be calculated as '15 September 2000'. </p>
            <p>Note that if you enter "6M" and a 3-monthly charge is applied then the number of charge periods may default to 3 if the expiry date is adjusted to a working day. If this happens then you should override the number of charge periods manually.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date Format or Code (see above). </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>If the expiry date of a Letter of Credit exceeds the         issue date by more than one year, then an override will         be needed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENT.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of messages/advices this field specifies the number of days after the date of issuance of the transports document(s) within which the documents must be presented for payment, acceptance or negotiation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>35 type Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Optional input (if left blank UCP rules apply)</p>
            <P />
            <P>When presentation days is defined for import LC, system will default standard text 'Documents must be present within (Presentation Days) from the date of shipment but before the expiry of credit'.</P>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the customer number of the assignee if they are a customer of the bank. Should be a valid customer number. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field contains a message class ID, (defined in EB.ADVICES). There may be many classes specified, but only classes, which are related to the operation, will be triggered. For example, the EB.ADVICES number LC-1801 (L/C Import Issuing) may have the following classes and messages:</p>
            <p>Message No. : 700</p>
            <p>EB.MESSAG.CLASS : OPERATIONS</p>
            <p>Message No. : 1700</p>
            <p>EB.MESSAG.CLASS : NOTIFICATION</p>
            <p>Message No. : 740</p>
            <p>EB.MESSAG.CLASS : REIMBUSING</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>And let us assume that the EB.MESSAGE.CLASS ID has been mapped to L/C internal class specified in LC.PARAMETERS as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p>BASIC.MESSAGE</p> = OPERATIONS  <p /><p>NOTIFICATION </p>= NOTIFICATION  <p /><p>REIMBURSING </p>= REIMBURSING  <p /><p>In the L/C Transaction, the system will always populate the OPERATIONS and NOTIFICATION class when the L/C is issued. The REIMBURSING class will only be triggered, when </p><p>THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO</p> or <p>THIRD.PARTY</p> field (REIMBURSING bank in this case) has been completed. You can choose whether you want to produce the messages by flipping the YES/NO flag - <p>SEND.NOTICE</p>.  <p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.PARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the party from whom the tax is to be taken.</p>
            <p>For all tax within the multivalue set, these can be different. Some of the tax can be levied against the Opener, other against the Beneficiary, and some against the Third Party. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p><strong>O</strong>(pener) or <strong>T</strong>(hird         Party) or <strong>B</strong>(eneficiary). Associated         mulivalue field. Default from CHARGES.FROM field above.</p>
            <p>If 'T' is specified, then THIRD.PARTY.CUSTNO must be set.</p>
            <p>If no input is made then this field will default to         CHARGES.FROM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPENING.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.WITH.PROV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This value is defaulted from the Parameter. </p>
            <p>When set to YES, the Limit is impacted net of the Provision taken if any and when set to NO, irrespective of the Provision taken the limit is impacted for the Liability amount.</p>
            <p>E.g. When a Letter of Credit is opened for USD 100,000.00 and a Provision of USD 50,000 is taken, the impact of the limit line would be for: </p>
            <p />
            <p>USD 50,000  when LIMIT.WITH.PROV is set to YES</p>
            <p>USD 100,000 when LIMIT.WITH.PROV is set to NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input is YES or NO.</p>
            <p>Input cannot be changed even at INAU.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARENT.LC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is applicable to transferred child L/C(s) input only. The &lt;PARENT.LC.NO&gt; is the T24 transaction reference for parent L/C. When inputting the child L/C(s) record, the parent L/C number has to be put in this field. so that the serial updating control can be maintained in the parent L/C record. The details of the parent L/C can be retrieved for use in the child L/C record(s). For example:</p>
            <p>Example - The parent L/C is a sight credit and partial shipments allowed (i.e. in which case, multi-transfer under this L/C can be effected.). It has been input in T24 under reference TF0005200001 with following extract:</p>
            <p>Date of Issue:</p>
            <p>06-Mar-00</p>
            <p>Expiry Date:</p>
            <p>06-Jun-00</p>
            <p>Place of Expiry:</p>
            <p>Germany</p>
            <p>Applicant:</p>
            <p>PO Box 888, Bangkok, Thailand</p>
            <p>Beneficiary:</p>
            <p>German Mechanical Ltd.,</p>
            <p>PO Box 999, Hamburg, Germany.</p>
            <p>Amount:</p>
            <p>USD600,000</p>
            <p>Available With:</p>
            <p>Any Bank</p>
            <p>By Payment</p>
            <p>Draft At:</p>
            <p>Sight</p>
            <p>Shipment Latest:</p>
            <p>16-May-00</p>
            <p>Shipment:</p>
            <p>1,000 sets of washing machine and         accessories.</p>
            <p>FOB Singapore</p>
            <p>Against presentation of the following         documents:</p>
            <p>+Signed Commercial Invoice in five-fold</p>
            <p>+Full set clean on board Ocean Bills of         Lading made out to the order and blank endorsed marked         "Freight Collect" evidencing shipment of the         above merchandise.</p>
            <p>+Packing List in five-fold</p>
            <p>Documents are to be presented within 21 days         after the date of issuance of the shipping documents.</p>
            <p>The advising bank may add its confirmation         to the credit.</p>
            <p>Shipment will be from Singapore to Bangkok,         Thailand</p>
            <p>Transshipment is allowed</p>
            <p>Partial shipment is allowed</p>
            <p />
            <p>Against presentation of the following documents:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>+Signed Commercial Invoice in five-fold</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>+Full set clean on board Ocean                                 Bills of Lading made out to the                                 order and blank endorsed marked                                 "Freight Collect"                                 evidencing shipment of the above                                 merchandise.</p>
            <p>+Packing List in                                 five-fold</p>
            <p>Documents are to be presented                                 within 21 days after the date of                                 issuance of the shipping                                 documents.</p>
            <p>The advising bank may add its                                 confirmation to the credit.</p>
            <p>Shipment will be from                                 Singapore to Bangkok, Thailand</p>
            <p>Transshipment is allowed</p>
            <p>Partial shipment is allowed</p>
            <p>Now, the 1<sup>st</sup> beneficiary requests to transfer above L/C to A Co. and B Co. for USD250,000 and USD200,000 respectively. When input the Child L/C(s), TF0005200001 has to be input in &lt;Field 34&gt;, then the details in above extract would be retrieved in the child L/C records, except the Applicant of which it would be replaced by the 1<sup>st</sup> beneficiary automatically. As usual, the expiry date, shipment date and days of presentation may be reduced according to 1<sup>st</sup> beneficiary's request.</p>
            <p>After committing the Child L/C(s), let us say TF0005300001 and TF0005300002, the fields &lt;TRANSFERRED.LC&gt; and &lt;TRAN.PORT.AMT&gt; in the parent L/C record will be updated accordingly as below:</p>
            <p>TRANSFERRED.LC TF0005300001 </p>
            <p>TRAN.PORT.AMT.. 250,000</p>
            <p>TRANSFERRED.LC. TF0005300002 </p>
            <p>TRAN.PORT.AMT.. 200,000</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only valid Letter of Credit record allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICANT.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the descriptive details or the SWIFT address of the Applicant's Bank if different from Issuing Bank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>35 Type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVISING.BK.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional input for <strong>Import Letters of Credit</strong>. Identifies the account number of the Advising bank to be used as the default payment account. </p>
            <p>Input is allowed only if the ADVISING.BK.CUSTNO is set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Account Format.</p>
            <p>Not allowed for Export/Advising LCs.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the total amount of discount in respect of terms of usance drawings discounted under this L/C. expressed in local currency.  The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>When a new deal is input, this field will contain 0. Whenever a new term or usance drawing (drawing with type 'AC', or 'DP') that is discounted, is entered via the DRAWINGS application for this L/C,  then this field will be incremented by the amount of the discount converted to local currency.  So at any stage the user can identify the total amount of discount relevant to this L/C in local currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Generated. Standard Amount Format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINAL.DESTINATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the final destination or place of delivery to be indicated in the transport document</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.PROVIS.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the account where the provision needs to be credited. In can be in any currency.</p>
            <p>If not input, default will be from the LC.PARAMETERS and the credit will be in the same currency as that of the debit currency.</p>
            <p>NOTES:</p>
            <p>The provision credit account can be changed to any other         account provided the currencies are the same.         During change of credit provision account (in same         currency), no additional amounts can be debited.</p>
            <p>If provision credit account currency needs to be changed         to an account of another currency, then first the         existing provision needs to be released by setting         REL.PROV to "Y" under operation "A".         Once the existing provision is released, the operator can         take a revised provision to the debit and credit accounts         of different choice. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input if Field PROVISION set to 'YES'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.ADV.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value of Tag23 of MT700, which is an additional reference to the Documentary Credit, which has been Pre-advised.</p>
            <p>This is an input field for Operation 'O'.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>16 Type A (Alphanumeric) Characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.NO.APP.ISS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the customer portfolio number to which this letter of contract will be associated with. This will be used for the portfolio valuation either for the APPLICANT.CUSTNO or the ISSUING.BANK.NO fields. </p>
            <p>On Import LCs the APPLICANT.CUSTNO field will be used here and for Export LCs the ISSUING.BANK.NO field will be used in the Portfolio Valuation. </p>
            <p>The amount of the letter of credit less the drawings will be used to update the Portfolio as a NEGATIVE amount, i.e. will be treated similar to a Loan. </p>
            <p>No input will result in this deal being excluded from the portfolio valuation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 3 characters numeric. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code to identify the required status of the charge. Used to identify if the charge has been taken, claimed, or to be deferred or waived.User defined field. </p>
            <p>The codes that are used to identify various states of the charge are as follows: </p>
            <p>blank - The charge has not been taken yet </p>
            <p>2 - The charge has to be taken immediately to the debit of the charge account given above </p>
            <p>3 - The charge has been claimed. If status 3 is input then the charge will be debited to CRF (claimed bucket) and profit and loss will be credited. At this stage tax if any associated with the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE or the FT.CHARGE.TYPE will not be debited to the CRF bucket. </p>
            <p>4 - A claimed charge has been settled. This will be allowed to be input only in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES. </p>
            <p>5 - A claimed charge has been written off to the debit of profit or loss. Input allowed only in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file. </p>
            <p>15 - The charge has been waived. </p>
            <p>Notes:</p>
            <p>(i) A claim advice is sent to the charge party when charge status is input as 3.</p>
            <p>(ii) When the charge is paid the operator will manually access the LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file, where all the charge details are presented after authorization of the L/C, update the file from 3 to 4 to indicate that the payment has been received, and the CRF Claimed bucket reimbursed. </p>
            <p>(iii) When claimed charge is not paid, the operator will manually access the LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES file and change the charge status from 3 to 5. This will reverse the profit and loss and credit to CRF bucket.</p>
            <p>(iv) When the charge status is null, only the charge amount will be calculated and written in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES. The related tax will be calculated at the applicable rate on the day the charge status is set to 2.</p>
            <p>(v) When the charge status is 15, the related charge is considered waived and written in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES. This charge cannot be
            collected in the future and the related tax will not be stored in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>User Input. 1 digit. Associated mulivalue field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OSCOLLECT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field identifies the total number of outstanding drawings sent for 'collection' under the letter of credit. </p>
            <p>When a new deal is input, this field will contain 0. </p>
            <p>Whenever a new drawing sent for 'collection' (drawing type of 'CO' is entered via the DRAWINGS application for this LC), the field will be increased by 1. </p>
            <p>Note: When a drawing that has been sent for collection is subsequently changed to a 'SP', 'AC', or 'DP', then this field is decreased by 1. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>RESERVE3 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the contents of various system generated warning messages related to the contract at the time of data input and confirmation (F5) by the inputter.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRAN.PORT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained Field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is applicable to Transferred Letters of Credit Only and displays the corresponding transferred amount for the child L/C(s) in Field &lt;TRANSFERRED.LC&gt;. It is used for maintaining the serial control between Parent and Child L/C(s) in the transferable L/C process. For further details please refer to the example of the help text in Field &lt;PARENT.LC.NO&gt;.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.CUS.LINK</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field. </p>
            <p>This field identifies the CUSTOMER used for accounting and limits processing. </p>
            <p>For import Letters of Credit this will contain the APPLICANT.CUSTNO. </p>
            <p>For export Letters of Credit this will contain the ISSUING.BANK.NO. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a NO INPUT, system maintained field.</p>
            <p>Will contain a valid record on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the value updated from the LC.AMENDMENTS application. </p>
            <p>It is based on this field, the second Limit line for the LC.AMENDMENT is hit or reversed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(1) System maintained. Updated from LC.AMENDMENT application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTION.PCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will retain all the transferred L/C number associated to this L/C.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid L/C record ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount calculated by applying 'CSN.RATE' on 'UPTO.AMT'.</p>
            <p>System maintained field. Associated sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency market applicable to Letter of Credit and  Documentary Collection contracts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>One numeric digit Currency Market code. </p>
            <p>Default from LC.PARAMETERS file.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the CURRENCY.MARKET table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISS.BANK.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used when a message is sent by a Bank other than the Issuing Bank, i.e., it is sent by an Advising Bank. The value held here represents the Issuing Bank's reference of the Documentary Credit.</p>
            <p>This is used as Tag23 of MT707.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>16 Type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the date when the Documentary Collection or Letter of Credit accounting was charged to the account or CRF entries produced. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>11 Date Format. </p>
            <p>This is a NO INPUT field (system maintained).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field displays the current status of the contract.</p>
            <p><strong>IHLD</strong> for on hold / <strong>INAU</strong> for unauthorized / <strong>AU</strong> for authorised / <strong>CHLD</strong> for copied transaction on hold.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESC.GOODS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the creation of messages/advices, this free text field is used to identify the description of the goods covered by the transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Multivalue field of 50 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSN.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify the total amount of the letter of credit which has been assigned to the assignee under the specific assignee reference/multi value set. This amount cannot exceed the liability amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACK.CHG.CLAIM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows input of currency and amount of charges to be claimed by the Sender.</p>
            <p>The field will be mapped against the Tag 32a for Outward and Inward MT730 messages.</p>
            <p>If EUR 120 were to be claimed as charges, the input may either be EUR120 or 100.120, where 100 represents the ID of EUR in the NUMERIC.CURRENCY table.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 character (uppercase alpha) - type SSS, or 1-3     numeric character for a valid currency code. </p>
            <p>When Numeric code  is used for the currency, the     '.' delimiter is mandatory. </p>
            <p>1-14 characters plus a decimal point (standard amount     format) - type AMT to represent the amount.</p>
            <p>The Numeric Currency Code must be an existing code on     the NUMERIC.CURRENCY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>RESERVE4 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.SHARE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage of Share in LC amount for each participant in Syndicated LC.The user may however, modify the share provided none of the participant's portion define in Facility tranche is overdrawn.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field as per participant share defined in FACILITY but user can modify the share.</p>
            <p>Overall Share percentage cannot exceed 100%.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Participants share in LC amount in Syndicated LC.The user may however, modify the share amount provided none of the participant's portion define in Facility tranche is overdrawn.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System defaulted field as per participant share defined in FACILITY.</p>
            <p>For confirmed LC's PART.AMOUNT = LC.AMOUNT * Participant share defined in Facility.</p>
            <p>For Partially confirmed LC's PART.AMOUNT= CONFIRMATION.AMOUNT* Participant share defined in Facility.</p>
            <p>Overall Share amount cannot exceed total LC amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSPORTATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of messages/advices, this field identifies the final destination of the goods shipped under the LC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Marked to Tag 44B.</p>
            <p>One line of 65 characters for SWIFT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.EXPIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether LC is to be liquidated manually or automatically on EXPIRY.DATE.</p>
            <p>When set to "YES", LC will be automatically expired on EXPIRY.DATE of LC.</p>
            <p>When set to "NO", LC will be in live status even after crossing the EXPIRY.DATE and has to be manually liquidated.</p>
            <p>Validations Rules</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Valid input- YES or NO</p>
                <p value="2">Default value - YES</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the tax component for current schedule.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.OVERDRAW</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field represents the amount overdrawn for a particular portion in a mixed payment transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines the frequency at which the commission is to be collected or claimed.  The first scheduled date must be the value date.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency field.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Only monthly frequency allowed (M01, M02, etc.)</p>
                <p value="2">Not allowed when PERIODIC.COMMISSION is defined with 'For every Additional Period'.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPTO.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount on which the 'CSN.RATE' is applied to arrive at the 'CSN.AMT'.</p>
            <p>System maintained field. Associated sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONF.ADDL.INST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to mark against Tag 40B of MT710/720.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Accepts a maximum of 24 characters.</p>
            <p>Valid inputs are: Adding our Confirmation / Without our Confirmation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.REIMB.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMENDMENT.DTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field for Import Letter of Credit and Input field for Exports.</p>
            <p>This field displays the date of the last external amendment. </p>
            <p>Amendments to Letters of Credit (OPERATION CODE A) are classified as internal or external depending on the value input to the field AMENDMENT.DEL. </p>
            <p>This field will contain the date of the last external amendment. In the case of Exports the User has the option to register the Amendment Date as seen in MT707. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a NO-INPUT, system maintained field for Import Letter of Credit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVISING.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>For <strong>Import Letters of Credit </strong>this field identifies the name and address of the advising bank.</p>
            <p>For <strong>Inward Documentary Collections </strong>this field identifies the name and address of the Remitting Bank.</p>
            <p>This field is mandatory if the ADVISING.BK.CUSTNO. has not been input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field enables the user to override the defaulted carrier for a particular message type and select a new carrier.</p>
            <p>For example : If a specific message is generated by SWIFT, the user is able to override this by choosing other available options from the CARRIER table, eg TELEX or PRINT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid record in the CARRIER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for the production of messages/advices, this free text field is used to identify the drawee of Bills of Exchange to be presented under the LC, if the drawee is not a customer of the bank with a valid CUSTOMER.NO. Drawees Name and Address may be manually input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 lines of 35 type A Alphanumeric characters..</p>
            <p>If DRAFTS.AT is used, either this field or DRAWEE.CUST.NO         must have a value.</p>
            <p>If this field is used, then DRAWEE.CUST.NO must be left         blank.</p>
            <p>If the LC type is DP (Deferred Payment) this field must         be left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIABILITY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field identifies the total liability amount in respect of each individual issued or confirmed letters of credit. Used as a running total of the remaining credit amount available after all current drawings (if any) have been made under the letter of credit. The amount will be expressed in the currency of the letter of credit (LC.CURRENCY). </p>
            <p>When the letter of credit/documentary collection is input this field will contain either the LC.AMOUNT, or the MAXIMUM.CR.AMT, or the LC amount plus any tolerance indicated in field &lt;PERCENTAGE.CR.AMT&gt;.and any amount entered in the field &lt;ADD.COVERED.AMOUNT&gt;. Whenever drawings are entered, this amount is reduced by the amount of the drawing, so at any stage the total credit amount remaining will be shown by this field. </p>
            <p>This field also represents the undrawn balance of an unconfirmed letter of credit and the unpaid balance of a documentary collection. </p>
            <p>The contingent CRF entry will be updated by this field for all live letters of credit, to show the total liability amount. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.CLAIMED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies whether the commission is to be collected from the customer's account or claimed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.PARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates a liability number to be used instead of that of the Issuing Bank's. However, it defaults to the Issuing Bank. This may be entered at any time until DRAWINGS are made under that Letter of Credit.</p>
            <p>Normally, once the <STRONG>Export</STRONG> LETTER.OF.CREDIT is established, the amounts are applied against the limits of the Issuing Bank taking the value from ISSUING.BANK.NO. In cases where the Reimbursing bank is not the Issuing bank, functionally, setting up the limit against the Issuing Bank may not be required but the contract has to reduce the limit of the Reimbursing Bank/Guaranteeing Bank/Confirming Bank. If input at the time of opening the Letter of Credit, then the limits are set against the Reimbursing Bank. But if it is done as an amendment, then the limit usage of the Issuing Bank is reversed and the amount applied against the Reimbursing Bank. This also generates two APP entries for CRF to reverse the old entry and set up the new one.</p>
            <p>The contents of this field are used to indicate the liability and Consolidated Reporting (CRF).</p>
            <p>Replaces the value in the CON.CUS.LINK field, because of which, in an Export Letter of Credit, all the delivery messages, which were hitherto being sent to Issuing Bank, which had defaulted to the CON.CUS.LINK, will now be addressed to the value in this field. Therefore this would warrant a review of mapping of fields in relation to the Delivery messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Default value is Issuing Bank Customer Number.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid Customer number or Mnemonic.</p>
                <p>This field cannot be changed when a Drawing exists under the LC.</p>
                <p>Input allowed only for Export LC.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVISE.THRU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to identify the bank (which is not a customer of the bank) which is assigned to act as the intermediary between the advising bank of a Letter of Credit/ Collecting Bank or a Documentary Collection and the beneficiary/drawee. </p>
            <p>If an intermediary between the advising bank/collecting bank and the beneficiary is required, but the intermediary chosen is not a customer of the bank, then this field allows the input of a free format name and address of the chosen bank. It will be used to route all documents/advices for advising/presenting to the beneficiary/drawee. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>No input allowed if ADVISE.THRU.CUSTNO is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PCT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.CALC.BASE</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Determines whether provision has to be calculated on LC face value or liability amount. For example,</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Example 1 <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">LC Amount       100,000; Provision Percentage    20%; Credit Tolerance  5%; </p><p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Provision  Calc Base    LC.AMT; Liability Amount 105,000;</p><p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13"> Provision Amount  = (100,000 * 20%/100) </p><p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;= 20,000.</p></p>
                <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Example 2<p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">LC Amount    100,000; Provision Percentage     20%; Credit Tolerance  5%;</p><p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Provision  Calc Base  LIABILITY.AMT; Liability Amount   105,000;</p><p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Provision Amount  = (105,000 * 20%/100) </p><p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;= 21,000.</p></p>
            </p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Valid options are LC.AMT and LIABILITY.AMT.</p>
                <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Allowed only for LC's with provision.</p>
                <p value="3" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Defaulted from PROV.CALC.BASE field in LC.PARAMETERS.  Defaulted value can be amended by the user.</p>
                <p value="4" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">No change field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the required operation to be executed for a Trade Finance contract. The following codes are valid: </p>
            <p>O - Open new Letter of Credit / Documentary Collection contract, P - Preadvise new Letter of Credit contract, A - Amend an existing Letter of Credit / Documentary Collection contract, C - Direct charge processing for an existing contract, T - Trace existing Documentary Collection contract, D - Decision on an Amendment.</p>
            <p>Operation 'C' provides the operator with the ability to either record a new charge or amend (not cancel or write-off) a previously input charge. Operation 'C' also displays all uncollected charges (having null status) in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES, which are available to the operator to amend. However, keeping the status unchanged at null will enable the system to rewrite the charges back in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES.</p>
            <p>To ensure that no fee/charges are accidentally deleted or 'lost' from the system, once a charge set has been input, it cannot be deleted. However such a charge can be written off in LC.ACCOUNT.BALANCES.</p>
            <p>When accessed the contract will be shown with all relevant fields in their amended state, except charges set. </p>
            <p>When using 'T' trace, an MT420 will be produced and the next process date will have to be modified. </p>
            <p>Operation D is used when a decision on a Pending Amendment is to be taken as either Approved or Rejected. Use of this option opens up AMEND.NO and AMEND.STATUS. to use this the Letter of Credit has to be previously authorised in its O status.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Mandatory input. </p>
                <p>For a new contract the following are valid: O - open, P - pre-advise </p>
                <p>For an existing contract the following are valid: A - amend, C - direct charge, T - trace (collections only), D  decision.</p>
                <p>For D operation, the Letter of Credit must be previously authorised as O, should not be of a Mixed payment or Revolving type or a Collection Document.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the category code to which the deal will be accounted. This information will be used for CRF and MIS reporting and will identify the product being processed. </p>
            <p>A default category code may be specified for each L/C type on the LC.TYPES file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>5 numeric characters. (Optional input, default value, see         details below).</p>
            <p>The category code must be defined on the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p>The category code must relate to the LC application.         Valid range is 23000-23999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Indicates the consolidation key which has been generated for this contract. This field will be updated by the system after its first end of day has been processed. The field will be calculated by the system and no operator input will be allowed. </p>
            <p>The first four parameters will always contain the application ID (i.e. LC), the Currency Market, the Position Type, and the currency code (LC.CURRENCY). The other parameters will default on the conditions defined in the file CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRUST.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is activated for Import Collections.  The values accepted are RELEASE,ACCEPT and REJECT and can also be left blank. </p>
            <p>On opening of a LC the valid value accepted in this field is RELEASE. This denotes that the documents have been accepted under TRUST. The user can accept  or reject the documents at a later stage and accordingly update the TRUST.REL field.</p>
            <p>Whenever documents are accepted under trust, the system will hit the trust limit set up in LIMIT.PARAMETER. Also instead of the normal COLL contingent entry,  system will create a contingent entry with TRCOLL.</p>
            <p>Subsequently when the documents are accepted, the previous limit and contingent entries will be reversed and the normal collection limit and contingent entry will be created.</p>
            <p>When the documents are rejected, the previous limits and contingent entries will be reversed out and the LC liability will become zero.</p>
            <p>When this field is kept as null, the system processes like a normal collection.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The valid sequences allowed are:</p>
            <p>
                <p>RELEASE  REJECT</p>
                <p>RELEASE  ACCEPT</p>
            </p>
            <p>If a document has been released under trust and it is neither accepted nor rejected before the expiry date, the system will expire the LC and will update this field as EXPIRED.  No drawings are allowed in the system unless the documents released under trust are accepted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENTATION.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OWN.PART.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the share of T24 bank in the Syndicated LC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts product type 'LCE' or 'LCI' depending upon the LETTER.OF.CREDIT type(Import or Export).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>For Import LC - Product type should be 'LCI'.</p>
            <p>For Export LC - Product type should be 'LCE'.</p>
            <p>Product type LCI or LCE should be defined in Facility.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>This field identifies the date the tax was raised, although not necessarily taken. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of Trade Finance contract from the LC.TYPES file. The type will identify whether this is an Import/Export, Confirmed/Unconfirmed/Revolving/Transferrable lc etc... If the type input is a Documentary Collection, then this will impact on the processing performed, and some of the other input fields' meanings. </p>
            <p>The value entered must be a valid record on the LC.TYPES file and will be used to determine which kind of processing is required for the various combinations of Import/Confirmed/Usance etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>For any parent transferred LC, which has already been         transferred the LC.TYPE cannot be changed. (L/C         transaction has already had the child L/C number         associated to). </p>
            <p>A child is not be allowed to transfer to another child         l/c and therefore the child LC.TYPE cannot be         transferrable.. </p>
            <p>3-4 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input) </p>
            <p>Must be present on the LC.TYPES file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTRUCTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in the generation of messages/advices, this field can be used to stiputate any special or additional instructions to the Paying/Accepting/Negotiating Bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>50 x 12 type S (Standard format).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICANT.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>For <strong>Letters of Credit </strong>this field identifies the applicant on whose behalf the Letter of Credit is issued, if the applicant is held on the CUSTOMER file. Either this field or APPLICANT field (a text description of the applicant) must be entered. </p>
            <p>For <strong>Documentary Collections</strong> this field identifies the banks customer i.e. drawee (inward collection) or drawer (outward collection). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Number of mnemonic of customer on CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>Either this field or APPLICANT is mandatory.</p>
            <p>10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.')</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-set, this field is used to determine the message type to which the user wishes to amend the delivery and is used exclusively with the fields &lt;MSG.CLASS.NO&gt;, &lt;OVR.CARRIER&gt;, &lt;ADDRESSEE&gt; and &lt;SEND.MESSAGE&gt;.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 4 numeric characters. (Optional input). </p>
            <p>The category code must be defined on the DE.MESSAGE         table. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVISING.BK.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is mandatory for <strong>Import Letter of Credits </strong>and contains the customer number or mnemonic of the advising bank. </p>
            <p>For <strong>Inward Documentary Collections </strong>this field contains the customer number or mnemonic of the Remitting Bank. </p>
            <p>When a child LC is created from an Export transfer type of Letter of Credit, this field identifies the name and address of the bank that receives the outward MT720. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.')</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>Not allowed for Export Letters of Credit except those opened through Inward MT710 or Outward         Documentary Collections.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.DESPATCH.DET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the place of taking in charge(in case of multimodal transport document), the place of receipt(in case of a road, rail or inland waterway transport document or a courier expedited delivery service document), the place of dispatch  or the place of shipment to be indicated on the transport document</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEG.WITH.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows input of drawer of the drafts, to be drawn on the reimbursing bank, when the drawer is the negotiating bank.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The value present in this field is populated in Tag 58a of MT740</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Customer number or BIC Code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4       lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREADV.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to decide if the limit is to be impacted for Operation 'P'. </p>
            <p>This is an input field only for operation 'P'. The value cannot be amended once the record is authorized.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are either YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACPT.TM.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate the number of days applicable to an Acceptance or Deferred Payment period under a letter of credit. This field will indicate the expiry date for a sight letter of credit and will be updated by the system. If not input, default is the expiry date. For mixed payment LCs if the DRAW.TYPE is AC and/or DP then input is mandatory.</p>
            <p>For revolving letters of credit this field is system generated and will indicate the date on which the revolution concerned will expire.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.BROKEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>when a CRITICAL limit override message is received. Additional information may be added here for the Credit Officer of the account .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRMATION.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>CONFIRMATION.AMT</p>
            <p>In a partially Confirmed Letter of Credit this field can be input with a value that represents the portion of the Letter of Credit that has been confirmed. </p>
            <p>This can be expressed in terms of percentage or amount.</p>
            <p>When input as a percentage, the CONFIRMATION.AMT will be calculated only on the LC amount without taking into account the credit tolerance or Add Covered amount if any. </p>
            <p> If a provision amount is input without CONFIRMATION.AMT, then to input the confirmation amount the provision has to be released first. But the provision and the CONFIRMATION.AMT may be input concurrently, or the provision may be taken after inputting the confirmation amount. Either way when a provision is input with a CONFIRMATION.AMT then the provision is calculated only for this value and not the LC amount.</p>
            <p> If a Drawing is done prior to inputting a value into this field, then no partial confirmation can be done for that Letter of Credit. Likewise if the LC is of a Transferable type then no partial confirmation can be done.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> It cannot be greater than liability amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />Enabled only for export Letter of Credits.    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.REIM.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.REASON</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field holds the reason for change in IB.STATUS field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory when there is any change in IB.STATUS field in Internet Banking</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>For <strong>Letters of Credit</strong> this field identifies the Beneficiary. </p>
            <p>For <strong>Documentary Collections</strong> this field identifies the bank's customer's counterparty i.e. Drawer (Inwards Collections) and Drawee (Outward Collection).</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>10 type MNE (0-9, or A-Z uppercase alpha or '.'). The         customer code must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CHG.ST</field>
<desc>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p>This field displays the code used to identify the current status of the tax. (ie - if the tax has to be taken now or deferred).</p>
            <p>The codes that are used to identify the various states of the tax are as follows: </p>
            <p>blank - The tax has been deferred. 2 - The tax has been taken now.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to indicate the status of LC request through internet banking.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Below are the allowed Values </p>
            <p> Pending - Status which will be updated when client initially submits the LC issue request through Internet Banking </p>
            <p> Modification Requested - Status which will be manually changed on the bank side if the LC contract needs any corrections to be made by client </p>
            <p> Modified - Status will be manually changed on the client side after modification requested by the bank is over</p>
            <p> Approved - Status will be manually changed on the bank-side if they approve the issue request by client through Internet Banking.</p>
            <p> Reject - Status will be manually changed on the bank-side if they reject the issue requested by client through Internet Banking.</p>
            <p> Accept - Reserved for future use </p>
            <p> Advised - Reserved for future use </p>
            <p> Accepted - Reserved for future use </p>
            <p> Advising Bk Ack - Reserved for future use </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORT.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define whether charges are to be amortised over the life of the LC. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to YES, then this charge will not be taken into the profit and loss account defined for this charge/commission code immediately, but will be amortised over the life of the LC contract (From issue date to Expiry date). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'Y' or 'N'. Associated mulivalue field. Default from         FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE for charge code.</p>
            <p>Unless the charge is taken immediately (see         CHARGE.STATUS) below, then this field must be set to 'N'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>202.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for Sender to Receiver (i.e. Sending bank to Receiving bank) Information. Any information entered into this field will appear on a S.W.I.F.T. MT202 message (General Financial Institution Transfer). </p>
            <p>It may be used to provide instructions or additional information for the Receiver, Intermediary, Account with Institution or Beneficiary Institution. </p>
            <p>This field corresponds to field 72 on S.W.I.F.T. messages, and must never be used for information for which another field is intended, or for instructions not required in a message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type SW Multivalue field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain a codeword followed by further information.</p>
            <p>All code words must be valid code words as defined in S.W.I.F.T. documentation and must conform to the rules specified. Use of invalid code words will cause a message rejection when validated by S.W.I.F.T.</p>
            <p>Further code words and information can be entered in subsequent multivalues, but additional information continued on a new line must be preceded by a double slash '//'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>730.ACC.WITH.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the bank to which the amount of charges is to be remitted in favor of the sender. </p>
            <p>The field will be mapped against Tag 57a of Outward and Inward MT730 messages.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Customer number.</p>
            <p>BIC Code prefixed  with SW-.</p>
            <p>1-4 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>730.SND.RCV.INF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies additional information for the Receiver. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The field will be mapped against Tag 72 of Outward and Inward MT730 messages.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Permitted Codes are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />BENACC The beneficiary has accepted the amendment of the credit. <p>                       BENREJ The beneficiary has rejected the amendment of the credit.</p><p>When this message is used to advise of acceptance or rejection of an amendment of a credit, the</p><p>confirmation of the beneficiary must be indicated in this field.</p><p>Any code must be between slashes and must appear at the beginning of a line.</p><p>Narrative text must not begin with a slash and, if used, must begin on a new line and be the last</p><p>information in the field.</p><p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Valid SWIFT.CODE.WORDS with MESSAGE.TYPE as 72.</p><p>1-6 lines of 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters       </p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the account officer responsible for the relationship with the client for whom the transaction has been opened/confirmed/advised. This information will be used by the Management Information System (MIS) for the determination of the Customer Profitability Analysis. </p>
            <p>This field has been provided to enable the user to override at transaction level the client default account officer defined in the CUSTOMER file. </p>
            <p>For Import L/C's the client is defined as the Applicant of the L/C. </p>
            <p>For Export L/C's the client is defined as the Issuing/Opening bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 digit numeric field. (Optional input; Default value =         Account Officer specified on the clients CUSTOMER file.)</p>
            <p>The Account Officer code must appear on the         DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.PARTY.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to identify whether the commission is claimed from opener or beneficiary. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No change field.</p>
            <p>Option field. Options - O(Opener) or B(Beneficiary)</p>
            <p>Allowed only when commission is claimed.</p>
            <p>When commission claimed is "Yes", system defaults this field as "O".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODE.OF.SHIPMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the mode of shipment used to transport goods.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be 'Sea' when INCO.TERMS is FAS,FOB,CFR and CIF</p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p />
            <p>Air</p>
            <p>Sea</p>
            <p>Road</p>
            <p>Rail</p>
            <p>Multi Modal</p>
            <p>Other</p>
         </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAILABLE.BY</field>
<desc>
             <p>This field identifies the how the credit is available under Letter of Credit.</p>
             <p>
                 <p>Validation Rules:</p>
             </p>
             <p />
             <p>Defaults based on PAY.TYPE in LC.TYPES</p>
             <p />
             <p>Allowed Values are</p>
             <p />
             <p>BY ACCEPTANCE</p>
             <p>BY DEF PAYMENT</p>
             <p>BY MIXED PAYMENT</p>
             <p>BY NEGOTIATION</p>
             <p>BY PAYMENT</p>
          </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOCUMENT.ID</field>
<desc>
              <p>This field is used to default list of documents defined in  LC.ADVICE.TEXT.</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>Applicable only for Import Letter of Credit</p>
              <p />
              <p>Default will be based on the following combinations and order from LC.ADVICE.TEXT</p>
              <p />
              <p>Applicant customer - Inco Terms - Mode of Shipment</p>
              <p>Inco Terms - Mode ot Shipment</p>
              <p>Applicant customer - Free Text</p>
              <p>Applicant customer</p>
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.BK.TO.BK</field>
<desc>
              <p>This field is used to capture the additional information in Tag 72 of incoming swift message.</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>Applicable for MT420, MT430 and MT422.</p>
              <p>1-6 lines of 35 characters each line.</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.COLL.MSG</field>
<desc>
              <p>This field is used to generate MT422 or MT416 as adhoc messages for Collections.</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>Options as MT422 and MT416.</p>
              <p>Allowed only for Collections.</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOPAY.REASON</field>
<desc>
              <p>This field is used to map 77A tag in MT416 message (Inward as well as outward).</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>Allowed to input only when MT416 is set in SEND.COLL.MSG field.</p>
              <p>Allowed to input only during amendment of LC record.</p>
              <p>Not allowed to input if drawings are present under the Collection.</p>
              <p>Not allowed if LC is already fully utilised.</p>
              <p>Should not be more than 20 lines.</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAL.REQ</field>
<desc>
              <p>Specifies whether avalization request has been received.</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>a) Allowed Values - "YES"/"NO"</p>
              <p>b) Allowed only for Usance collection with DOC.COLLECTION = "YES" and PAY.TYPE = "A" in LC.TYPES.</p>
              <p>c) Not allowed to modify if avalization has been accepted by defining AVAL.DATE..</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAL.BY</field>
<desc>
              <p>Specifies the party who has avalized the inward collection bill.It can be avalized either by own bank or third party.</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>a) Allowed Values  "OWN"/"OTHERS".</p>
              <p>b) Allowed only when avalization is requested.</p>
              <p>c) Allowed only for inward collections.</p>
              <p>d) Not allowed to modify if avalization has been accepted by defining AVAL.DATE.</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAL.CUST.NO</field>
<desc>
              <p>Specifies the customer number who has avalised the collection bill.</p>
              <p>Must be valid customer number.</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>a)Either AVAL.CUST.NO (or) AVAL.CUST is mandatory when AVAL.REQ = "YES".</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>XX.AVAL.CUST</field>
<desc>
              <p>Specifies the customer who has avalised the collection bill.</p>
              <p>Free text field  to record name and address of third party who has avalized the bill.</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>a)Either AVAL.CUST.NO (or) AVAL.CUST is mandatory when AVAL.REQ = "YES".</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
              <p>This field holds the date of avalisation. A valid date present in this field indicates that the collection bill is avalized.</p>
              <p>Valid Date field.</p>
              <p>
                  <p>Validation Rules</p>
              </p>
              <p />
              <p>a) Allowed only when avalization is requested.</p>
              <p>c) Cannot be less than Today.</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
              <p>Start date for calculation of the LC commission.</p>
              <p>Values are Advising Date, Confirmation Date, Issue Date, Aval Date.</p>
              <p>Default value for Import LC is Issue Date.</p>
              <p>Allowed value for Import LC is Issue Date only</p>
              <p>Allowed value for Import Collections is Aval Date only</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVISING.DATE</field>
<desc>
              <p>Date of advising of the export LC.</p>
              <p>Field applicable only for export LCs.</p>
              <p>Defaulted to the current date.</p>
              <p>System maintained field</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRMATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
              <p>Date of adding confirmation to the export LC.</p>
              <p>Field applicable only for export LCs.</p>
              <p>Defaulted to the current date, when LC gets confirmed</p>
              <p>System maintained field</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.COMM</field>
<desc>
              <p>To define if the subject commission is waived.</p>
              <p>Values are Yes, Null</p>
              <p>If yes is selected, then the subject commission will not be collected.</p>
              <p />
           </desc>
</t>
<t><field>AVAL.CUST</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
