<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BR</product>
<table>BR.BRANCH</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used for the settings for each branch using BR. It is used mainly at the branch itself but would be created and maintained at the Head office.</p>
            <p />
            <p> The settings are used for the import services and the toolbox console.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MONITOR.PORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The port number used by toolbox to monitor the branch server.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMP.ACC.BAL.LOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The directory where the import service(s) will check for the account balance update records sent across from head office. The directory does not need to be in the .run directory but the location given is in relation to the .run directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example</p>
            <p>  ../ACCBALS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  would indicate that the file is located one level higher thatn the .run directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If not an existing directory then it will be created at authorisation along with it's VOC record. Both of these are required before the import service can be run successfully.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRANCH.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the Branch</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVER.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>IP address allocated to the branch server.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRANCH.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Status to note whether the branch database is open for Offline Transactions.  The branch status is set in the T24 Toolbox using services provided by the browser infrastructure.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  ONLINE - the branch users connect to the head office server when communications are fine.</p>
            <p>  OFFLINE - the Head Office server is unreachable and the branch users logto the branch backup instead.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Valid values are balnk ONLINE or OFFLINE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMP.OFS.SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to identify the OFS.SOURCE record associated with the import of static data. The record is used for the generic inputter and the log file directories.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The OFS.SOURCE should be a source type of T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMP.STA.APP.LOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The directory where the import service(s) will check for the  static update records sent across from head office. The directory does not need to be in the .run directory but the location given is in relation to the .run directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example</p>
            <p>  ../STATAPPS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  would indicate that the file is located one level higher thatn the .run directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If not an existing directory then it will be created at authorisation along with it's VOC record. Both of these are required before the import service can be run successfully.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.ENTRY.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the record id of the AC.ENTRY.PARAM which is used by BR to create accounting entries from the account balance updates. The update service compares the balances of the accounts from the head office and if the local branch balance is not the same then an accounting entry will be created at the branch to bring the balance back into alignment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used at present</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTE.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used at present</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.BRANCH.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of the branch, used to identify the branch in browser and toolbox definition files as well as the identifier on the SPF record in the branch itself.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVER.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name allocated to the branch server.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

