<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BR</product>
<table>BR.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The main settings for the creation of the branch database and the running of the online/offline systems using the BR module.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The main purpose of BR and hence this file is the creation and maintenance of a backup system for the branch to use if the communications to the Central Server breakdown.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OFFLN.APS.UPLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The applications listed here are currently hard-coded and restricted to TELLER, TELLER.ID &amp; PASSWORD.RESET. When online the deals wil be sent by browser to both the head office server and the branch server to keep the systems in synch. When offline the deals will be written to the branch server with a copy created on the SFQ file for later replication to the Head Office.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MONITOR.PORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The port number used by T24 Toolbox to monitor the Central Server</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.STA.APP.LOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The directory where the system creates the static update records to be sent across to the branch. The directory does not need to be in the .run directory but the location given is in relation to the .run directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Example</p>
            <p />
            <p> ../STATAPPS</p>
            <p />
            <p> would indicate that the file is located one level higher thatn the .run directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p> If not an existing directory then it will be created at authorisation along with it's VOC record. Both of these are required before the export service can be run successfully.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SFQ.OFS.SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The SFQ updates sent across from the branch (created whilst the branch was offline) use an OFS.SOURCE record to get the genric user and log file locations. The OFS.SOURCE record used is indicated here and should be a T24 type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.INC.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where only selected records of a particular file are required then the filename is listed here and the records to copy across in the associated filed REC.INC.ID</p>
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATION</p>
            <p>  Presently restricted to the TSA.SERVICE file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.INC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where only selected records of a particular file are required then the records are listed here and only they will be copied across to the branch.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATION</p>
            <p>  Presently restricted to the TSA.SERVICE records</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFLN.APS.ALLWD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Only these applications will be allowed while the Branch Server is offline.</p>
            <p>  All other applications will only be allowed in functions:  S, P or L.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  NO-INPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.ACC.BAL.LOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The directory where the export service(s) will create the account balance update records to be sent across to the branch. The directory does not need to be in the .run directory but the location given is in relation to the .run directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Example</p>
            <p />
            <p> ../ACCBALS</p>
            <p />
            <p> would indicate that the file is located one level higher thatn the .run directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p> If not an existing directory then it will be created at authorisation along with it's VOC record. Both of these are required before the export service can be run successfully.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID to be keyed in as SYSTEM as this table should contain only one single record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.FILES</field>
<desc>
            <p>The files to be excluded while creating the branch database. Once excluded all physical files out of this application will be excluded during the branch database creation process.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  A valid key in FILE.CONTROL.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.ENT.PER.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximim number of accounts to be included in a single record when the export service is run, provides for a better performance when importing the updates at the branch.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATIC.APPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any transactions done for these application on the Central server will be written to the export drectory in field EXP.STA.APP.LOC. They will e transferred later to the branch and replayed back onto the Branch Server during the update process.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Should be a valid entry in FILE.CONTROL</p>
            <p>  Cannot be a Financial file type.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.DB.LOCATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The physical path where the branch database will to be created under. This wil be the top level directory under which all branch files will be created during the database process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CENTRAL.SER.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The IP Address of the Central Server</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CENTRAL.SER.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name given to the Central Server in the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.FILES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Files which require only the physical presence in the branch but the records from the central server need not be copied across.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

