<t24help>
  <header>
    <product>FINEXT</product>
	<title>Credit Bureau Reporting Parameter</title>
	<table>CBR.PARAMETER</table>
  </header>
  <overview>
    <ovdesc>
      <p>The table is used to parameterize the condition necessary for creating credit bureau information. Also, this table is used to parameterise values which are essential to create Header information of Metro2 format Credit bureau reporting</</p>
      <p>APPLICATION - USBTCH.CBR.PARAMETER</p>
      <p>@ID - The ID must be Valid Company Id</p>
    </ovdesc>
    <ovimage>
    </ovimage>
  </overview>
  <menu>
    <t>
      <field>CBR.DESCRIPTION</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Free text field to key in the record description</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>CBR.ID.NUMBER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>The field should be keyed in with a unique identifier.</p>
		<p>This unique identifier is to identify each branch, office, or credit central where information is verified</>
	  </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>REC.DESC.WORD</field>
      <desc>
        <p>The field Contains a value equal to the length of the physical record.</p>
		<p>example the value should be 426 for fixed length format</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>REC.IDENTIFIER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field identifies the header segment of the file.</p>
		<p>The value should be defined as HEADER</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>CYCLE.NUMBER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field should configured with internal cycle code for reporting.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>INNOVIS.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field holds the Credit agency Innovis Programme identifier</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	<t>
      <field>EQUIFAX.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field holds the Credit agency Equifax Programme identifier.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	<t>
      <field>EXPERIAN.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field holds the Credit agency Experian Programme identifier.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	<t>
      <field>TRANS.UNION.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field holds the Credit agency Trans Union Programme identifier.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
  <t>
      <field>PROGRAM.DATE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Reports the configured date in the header segment in metro 2 file in format MMDDYYYY</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
   <t>
      <field>REPORTER.NAME</field>
      <desc>
        
        <p>Report the name of the company name sending the data.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>REPORTER.ADDR</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Report address of the company sending the data.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>

	<t>
      <field>REPORTER.TEL.NO</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Reporters telephone number should be mapped in this field.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	<t>
      <field>VENDOR.NAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field should updated with the vendor name and details to update in the header segment.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>

	<t>
      <field>SOFTWARE.VER.NO</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field should updated with software version name.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>INNOVIS.PRBC</field>
      <desc>
        <p>The field should updated with a unique identification number assigned by this consumer reporting agency.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>EQUIFAX.PRBC</field>
      <desc>
        <p>The field should updated with a unique identification number assigned by this consumer reporting agency.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>TRANS.UNION.PRBC</field>
      <desc>
        <p>The field should updated with a unique identification number assigned by this consumer reporting agency.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>EXPERIAN.PRBC</field>
      <desc>
        <p>The field should updated with a unique identification number assigned by this consumer reporting agency.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>PORTFOLIO.CATEG</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field should keyed in with valid T24 Category code.</p>
		<p>  Validation Rules</p>
        <p>  Valid Category.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
		<t>
      <field>PORTFOLIO.TYPE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is a associated field with PORTFOLIO.CATEG</p>
		<p>The field should keyed in with portfolio type related to category defined above.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>ACCT.TYPE.CATEG</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field should keyed in with valid T24 Category code.</p>
		<p>  Validation Rules</p>
        <p>  Valid Category.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>ACOUNT.TYPE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is a associated field with ACCT.TYPE.CATEG</p>
		<p>The field should keyed in with account type related to category defined above.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>JSEGMENT</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field specifies whether the Metro 2 file J1 / J2 segments required for delinquent loans or for all loans.</p>
		<p>  Validation Rules</p>
        <p>  Values should be ALL_DELINQ.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>

	<t>
      <field>PRODUCTS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field should updated with AA products that to be included in the CBR extract.</p>
		<p>  Validation Rules</p>
        <p>  Valid AA product.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>DELINQ.AMT.LIMIT</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is a associated field with the product defined above</p>
		<p>This field should keyed in with the threshold limit for considering delinquency amount limit.</p>	
      </desc>
    </t>
		
    <t>
      <field>FROM.DAYS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is an associated multi-value field that holds the range of days which is the deciding factor for account status update.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>

	<t>  
	<field>TO.DAYS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is an associated multi-value field that holds the range of days which is the deciding factor for account status update.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>ACCT.STATUS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Holds the parametrized value for the different day ranges, the alphanumeric code to be marked for each loan when determining the payment rating of the loan.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>PAYMENT.RATING</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Holds the parametrized value for the different day ranges, the alphanumeric code to be marked for each loan when determining the payment rating of the loan.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>LEGACY.ID.TYPE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This should be the alternate id type to get the legacy loan number.</p>
        
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>CLOSURE.DAYS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This will hold the number of months after which closed loans will not to be reported.</p>
        
      </desc>
    </t>

	<t>
      <field>TERM.AMOUNT.CONV</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is a conditional field to convert the actual schedule amount is converted as per metro 2 format if its set as YES.</p>
        
      </desc>
    </t>

	</menu>
</t24help>