<t24help>
  <header>
    <product>FINEXT</product>
    <title>CBR CONSUMER DETAILS</title>
    <table>CBR.CONSUMER.DETAILS</table>
  </header>
  <overview>
    <ovdesc>
      <p>This table updated with fields required for CBR extract by the service CBR.UPDATE.DETAILS</p>
      <p>APPLICATION - CBR.UPDATE.DETAILS</p>
      <p>@ID - The ID will be a valid AA account number</p>
    </ovdesc>
    <ovimage>
    </ovimage>
  </overview>
  <menu>
    <t>
      <field>PRIMARY.CUSTOMER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with the AA customer ID which is called base customer reference number for selected arrangement records.</p>
        
      </desc>
    </t>
   
   <t>
      <field>SURNAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's family from the field FAMILY.NAME.</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
    
	<t>
      <field>FIRST.NAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's first name from the field GIVEN.NAME.</p>
		
      </desc>
    </t>
    
	<t>
      <field>MIDDLE.NAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's middle name from the field  MIDDLE.NAME.</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
	
	
	<t>
      <field>SUFFIX.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's suffix title from the field SUFFIX.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>SSN</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's social security number from the field TAX.ID</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>DATE.OF.BIRTH</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's Date.of.Birth</p>
	</desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>TELEPHONE.NUMBER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's telephone number from the field PHONE.</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
	
	
	<t>
      <field>ECOA.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's relation code.</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
	
	
	<t>
      <field>CI.INDICATOR</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Contains a value that indicates a special condition of the account that applies to the primary consumer.</p>
		
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's country code from the field COUNTRY.</p>
		
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>FIRST.ADDRESS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's first line address from the field NAME.2.</p>
		
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	
	<t>
      <field>SECOND.ADDRESS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's second line address from the field STREET.</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
		
	<t>
      <field>BASE.CITY</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's city from the field TOWN.COUNTRY</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>BASE.STATE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's  state from the field state.</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>BASE.ZIP.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with base or primary customer's  postal / zip code from the field This field updated with base or primary customer's .</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>ADDR.IND</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This will be the blank field.</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
	
		
	
  <t>
      <field>J1.CUSTOMER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>The field updates with relative customer for the base customer extracted from the AA OWNER field.</p>
        <p>this is a associated set fields updated with the joint customer details who located in same address of base customer</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    
		
    <t>
      <field>J1.CUS.SURNAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's family name from the field FAMILY.NAME.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    
	<t>
      <field>J1.FIRST.NAME</field>
      <desc>
		<p>This field updated with joint customer's first name from the field GIVEN.NAME.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    
	<t>
      <field>J1.CUS.MID.NAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's middle name from the field  MIDDLE.NAME.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    
	<t>
      <field>J1.SUFFIX.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's suffix title from the field SUFFIX.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>

	<t>
      <field>J1.CUS.SSN</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's social security number from the field TAX.ID</p>
      </desc>
    </t>

	<t>
      <field>J1.CUS.DOB</field>
      <desc>
		 <p>This field updated with joint customer's Date.of.Birth</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>J1.TELE.NUMBER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's telephone number from the field PHONE.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>J1.ECOA</field>
      <desc>
		<p>This field updated with joint customer's relation code.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
  <t>
      <field>J1.CONS.IND</field>
      <desc>
       <p>Contains a value that indicates a special condition of the account that applies to the primary consumer.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    
	<t>
      <field>J2.CUSTOMER</field>
      <desc>
      <p>The field updates with relative customer for the base customer extracted from the AA OWNER field.</p>
      <p>this is a associated set fields updated with the joint customer details who located in different address of base customer</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
 
	
    <t>
      <field>J2.CUS.SURNAME</field>
      <desc>
		<p>This field updated with joint customer's family from the field FAMILY.NAME.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>J2.FIRST.NAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's first name from the field GIVEN.NAME.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>J2.CUS.MID.NAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's middle name from the field  MIDDLE.NAME.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>J2.SUFFIX.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's suffix title from the field SUFFIX.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>J2.CUS.SSN</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's social security number from the field TAX.ID</p>
      </desc>
    </t>

	<t>
      <field>J2.CUS.DOB</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's Date.of.Birth</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>J2.TELE.NUMBER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's telephone number from the field PHONE.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	<t>
      <field>J2.ECOA</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's relation code.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	
	<t>
      <field>J2.CONS.IND</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Contains a value that indicates a special condition of the account that applies to the primary consumer.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
		<t>
      <field>J2.COUNTRY</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint customer's country code from the field COUNTRY.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
		<t>
      <field>J2.FIRST.ADDRESS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field updated with joint first line address from the field NAME.2.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
		<t>
      <field>J2.SECOND.ADDRESS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Update the address of joint customer.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
		<t>
      <field>J2.CUS.CITY</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Update the city of joint customer.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	<t>
      <field>J2.CUS.STATE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Update the state of joint customer from the field US.STATE.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
		<t>
      <field>J2.CUS.ZIP.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Update the postal code of joint customer form the field POST.CODE.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
	
	</menu>
</t24help>