<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IM</product>
<table>IM.DOCUMENT.IMAGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

 
 IM
 DOCUMENT IMAGE
 IM.DOCUMENT.IMAGE
 
 
 <p>
 This application is used to define and store individual images. 
 The key is a standard T24 contract key, i.e. Application ID, Julian Date, Sequence Number. 
 The image is identified by: 
 IMAGE.TYPE - as defined on IM.IMAGE.TYPE 
 IMAGE.APPLICATION - Relates to the IMAGE.REFERENCE if relevant 
 COMPANY.MNEMONIC - Relating to the IMAGE.REFERENCE if relevant 
 IMAGE.REFERENCE - A value relating to the stored image, can be a record key referred to by the IMAGE.APPLICATION or any valid field reference. 
 IMAGE - The file name of the image stored in the PC directory for the IMAGE.TYPE 
 The filename does not need to reflect the actual image stored. 
 This application allows great flexibility in defining images as there is no restriction on the type of application or field to which the stored image is related. 
 When the user is in input mode, clicking on the image toolbar button will result in either the existing image being displayed on a separate form. This form contains a menu allowing the existing image to be modifed or replaced by a new image (which can either be loaded from an existing image or scanned using any TWAIN compliant scanning device). The resultant image can be stored in a variety of formats. If no existing image is held one can be scanned in or a pre-scanned image loaded. 
 If the user is in authorise mode the current and previous image (if present) can be displayed by clicking the image toolbar button. 
 A stored image can be displayed from any T24 application in any function mode (except this application whilst in input mode) by clicking the image toolbar button. 
</p> 

 
 
 
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Identifies the type of image to be stored and its location. Typical usage would be to segregate images by criteria such as PASSPORTS, PHOTOGRAPHS, SIGNATURES and DOCUMENTS. Image types can be used to assist selection of records in Enquiries as well as the physical distribution of files. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 Must be a valid record on IM.IMAGE.TYPE.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 The Key is in the standard T24 contract ID format, 
 IMYYDDDNNNN where: 
 IM identifies the IM product YY is the year DDD is the Julian day number in the year when the record was input NNNNN is the daily sequence number 
 To access a record input today then only the sequence number needs to be entered. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 10 numeric characters prefixed by IM. Once input this field can never be changed.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Provides a short description from 3 to 35 characters of this stored image. 
 The short description is displayed in the title bar of the image form when it is presented to the user. It should therefore contain a meaningful, concise description of the image. It could for example be the signature authorities or the details of whose signature is being displayed. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 3 to 35 alphanumeric characters.
 

</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is reserved for future expansion. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMAGE.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field can be used as a reference to the image being stored. The reference can be free format, but if input is made in IMAGE.APPLICATION and/or COMPANY.MNEMONIC the value will be checked as a valid record of that application. 
 Examples of values related to an application are: 
 ACCOUNT NUMBER where the application is ACCOUNT CUSTOMER ID where the application is CUSTOMER 
 Examples of unrelated values are: 
 DOCUMENT 1634562 PASSPORT PHOTO OF MR ALWYN P JONES 
 The value from this field is used to provides the key for the IM.REFERENCE cross reference file. This is used to link all related images so that they can be accessed speedily by other T24 applications. 
 Where a related IMAGE.APPLICATION has been entered, it records instances of image records related to that application/reference combination. 
 For example there may be several image records for one specific ACCOUNT. 
 When in any application, except IM.DOCUMENT.IMAGE, the request for an image will use the application field content or the application id to search for related images. If only one is found it is displayed immediately, if more than one exists an Enquiry display will show the records for the user to choose the appropriate image. If none are found a message will advise the user of the search criteria used. 
 It is therefore possible to check for images related to an ACCOUNT when you are in any valid field containing that ACCOUNT number. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 Up to 18 alphanumeric characters. Values will be checked against the T24 application specified in IMAGE.APPLICATION. ACCOUNT &amp; CUSTOMER mnemonics may be entered as well as the numeric equivalents.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This is an optional input field, but if entered the value must be a valid company id on the MNEMONIC.COMPANY file. 
 In a single company environment this field will not be used however, if is used to identify the IMAGE.REFERENCE within a specified company. 
 For example, if an image was related to a specific contract record in a multi-company site then the IMAGE.APPLICATION would contain the application relating to the contract, the COMPANY.MNEMONIC would contain the relevant company mnemonic and the IMAGE.REFERENCE would contain the contract id. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 If input the value entered must exist on MNEMONIC.COMPANY
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is used to record the details of the image, and is for internal purposes. It can contain details of the image or document format, such as the reason the image is held, or any free format text the bank requires. 
 This is a multi-valued; multi-language field and can be expanded to allow the user to enter the description in various languages. 
 Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table. (Ref: GENERAL TABLES) which will indicate the language in which the description must be entered. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 Multivalued Language type field. 3 to 35 characters.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMAGE.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field is used to link an image to a T24 application or file. Typical usage would be to input CUSTOMER as an application in this field with the CUSTOMER number or mnemonic being entered in the IMAGE.REFERENCE field. 
 The application must be a valid T24 application. 
 If the value in IMAGE.REFERENCE is not related to a T24 application then this field should be left blank. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 Optional input. Must be a valid T24 application with an associated file.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMAGE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This system updated field identifies the image stored on the client PC or on a PC network file system. 
 The name is derived to be compatible with MS DOS, i.e. 8 character name with a 3-character extension. The extension indicates the version number of the image. 
 The image will be stored in the location relevant to the IMAGE.TYPE defined.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This is a NOINPUT field. This field is only updated by the system.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>

 Standard T24 local reference field. 
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTI.MEDIA.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
        </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.
 This is a NOCHANGE field.
 The following values are permitted: IMAGE SOUND VIDEO
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

