<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IM</product>
<table>IM.IMAGE.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

 
 IM
 TYPE OF IMAGE
 IM.IMAGE.TYPE
 
 
 
 <p>
 This Application is used to define and identify the location of groups of related images. 
 For example customer photographs could be defined as one type and passport scans as another. 
 All images of a particular type should be stored in the same directory on the PC or Network as defined by a combination of the default drive and path fields. 
 The individual images are defined by the IM.DOCUMENT.IMAGE Application which is linked to this application via the IMAGE.TYPE field. 
 </p>
 
 
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PATH</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 The path of the directory where the images of this type are stored. 
 
 
 Used with/without the default drive to identify the location of images of the type defined in this record. 
 For example \GLOBUS\IMAGES\CUSTOMER\PHOTO\ 
 The path must be entered in MSDOS, MS WINDOWS Format.
 A full path can be entered withou a default drive as long is this can be evaluated by T24 as a valid location. The path can alos be prefixed with Unix type indicators './' or '../.' etc which makes the path a relative one. Relative to the web browser root directory (Windows or Unix). Full Unix patsh can be entered but may need networking software installed so they can be accessed by browser/explorer.
 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 1-35 alphanumeric characters. The first and Last character must be \.
 

</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.DRIVE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Identifies the PC or Network drive where images related to this type are stored. 
 The Drive should be defined in MSDOS/WINDOWS format eg. C: D: etc. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 Two-character alphanumeric. Drive should be entered in the following format. Character 1 = A to Z Character 2 = :
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Describes the types of image being stored using this IM.IMAGE.TYPE. 
 Can be expanded to allow the user to enter the description in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspand to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES) which will indicate the language in which the descrption must be entered. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 Multivalued Language type field. 3 to 35 Alphanumeric characters.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.LOCATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>The physical location (SERVER/LOCAL) of files to be uploaded/retrieved. Location could be either SERVER or LOCAL.</p>
        <p>DEFAULT.DRIVE and PATH field values will be combined as path to proceed file process based on the type of location. For SERVER location DEFAULT.DRIVE field should be empty, since T24 server's run directory will be taken as default drive.  <![CDATA[
 ]]></p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>It's a mandatory,list box field and cannot provide any inputs by manual process.  <![CDATA[ 
]]></p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMAGE.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Identifies the type of image stored. This can be used to segregate images that are used for different purposes or to spread the files across physical devices. 
 For example ACCOUNT mandates can be stored on drive D: in a directory called MANDATES whilst signatures could be in directories SIG1 to SIG99 on drive E: i.e 
 D:\MANDATES E:\SIG1 E:\SIG2 E:\SIG3 and so on. 
 All images which have an identical IM.IMAGE.TYPE will be stored in the same directory on the PC or PC Network. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 Maximum 15 characters Minumum 1. First Character must be A...Z . 0...9 and ' '()+,-.' also allowed.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLD.MAX.SIZE</field>
<desc>
        <p> This field holds maximum size of file to be uploaded. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 Optional field. If set, then specifies a maximum size (in bytes) to be uploaded. If not set, then the system will not place any artificial limits on the upload file size.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

