<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>ASSET.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Simple table type file used to define and categorise an individual security or product within a recognised group for reporting and information purposes. It need not be restricted to a security as is used to describe foreign exchange transactions, money market transactions etc. which need to be picked up and displayed along with a clients portfolio instruments such as equities, precious metals, etc. </p>
            <p>A separate ID is attributed to each individual group of investment articles. For example all Ordinary share capital type issues traded on the open market could be called Asset type 1 and given a heading of "Equities". </p>
            <p>This table is user defined and maintained. Records can be altered as the need may arise. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Abbreviated description of the ASSET.TYPE. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the ASSET.TYPE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multi-language field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INCL.ACCR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may have a value of 'YES' to indicate that the accrued interest will be included into the calculation of the CG P&amp;L</p>
            <p>Or a value of 'NO' to indicate that the accrued interest will not be included into the CG P&amp;L calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>Nulls treated like 'NO'</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies which valuation category under which you wish this particular ASSET.TYPE to be located. </p>
            <p>This facility therefore enables you to group together one or more asset types of a similar nature so that they are combined within a single reporting section. </p>
            <p>You should use this field to point the particular ASSET.TYPE to a report format field as should be contained within the SC.VAL.FORMAT file. </p>
            <p>For example, you might have a report format category called "BONDS" and several various asset types all of which could be reported under bonds. If you require these reported collectively in this way, you should ensure that the asset types all point to a common report format. </p>
            <p>Asset types for which this field is NULL will NOT be included in the valuation reports. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 Alpha and/or numeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must already exist on the SC.VAL.FORMAT file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WCG.INCL.ACCR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may have a value of 'YES' to indicate that the accrued interest will be included into the calculation of the CG P&amp;L withheld tax</p>
            <p>Or a value of 'NO' to indicate that the accrued interest will not be included into the CG P&amp;L withheld tax calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>Nulls treated like 'NO'</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the percentage of the asset/liability as defined by the ASSET.TYPE to be used in portfolio valuations. </p>
            <p>This is the third level of checking when Securities programs value other (non securities) assets.  If a value is not found on the ASSET.BY.CATEG or SUB.ASSET.TYPE file then this percentage rate is applied to the value of the asset involved. </p>
            <p>Depending upon whether a valuation should include/exclude liabilities, either this field or LOSS.MARGIN.RATE will be used to calculate the margin value. The method of calculation is defined in the field MARGIN.VALUE in SC.PARAMETER </p>
            <p>If no value is found on either file then a margin rate of 0% is assumed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 - 9 numeric characters. (Optional input where there is a value in the INTERFACE field, otherwise no input allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Single Value field that stores the risk level of the particular combination of Managed Account and Investment Strategy . Must validate against the EB.LOOKUP options for 'RISK.LEVEL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency for which margin rate is to be specified. Will hold the valid CURRENCY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.SEC.MGN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Asset margin rate of the currency. This is of numeric type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOSS.MARGIN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the percentage of the asset/liability as defined by the ASSET.TYPE to be used in portfolio valuations. </p>
            <p>This is the third level of checking when Securities programs value other (non securities) assets.  If a value is not found on the ASSET.BY.CATEG or SUB.ASSET.TYPE file then this percentage rate is applied to the value of the asset involved. </p>
            <p>Depending upon whether a valuation should include/exclude liabilities, either this field or MARGIN.RATE will be used to calculate the margin value. The method of calculation is defined in the field MARGIN.VALUE in SC.PARAMETER </p>
            <p>If no value is found on either file then a margin rate of 0% is assumed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 - 9 numeric characters. (Optional input where there is a value in the INTERFACE field, otherwise no input allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.OUT.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate for calculating sell-out margin amount</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum of 9 numeric characters is allowed </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.SUB.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the sub total group for use in valuation reports. </p>
            <p>Links groups of ASSET.TYPE together to allow more meaningful presentation in valuation reports. </p>
            <p>No estimation for ACCOUNT balances will be shown on valuation reports if this field is left blank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 numeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>No default value.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the SC.VAL.REP.SUB.TOTAL file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INCL.EXPENSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may have a value of 'YES' to indicate that the expenses will be included into the calculation of the CG P&amp;L</p>
            <p>Or a value of 'NO' to indicate that the expenses will not be included into the CG P&amp;L calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>Nulls treated like 'NO'</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.LOSS.MGN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Loss margin rate of the currency . This is of numeric type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WCG.INCL.EXPENSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may have a value of 'YES' to indicate that the expenses will be included into the calculation of the CG P&amp;L withheld tax</p>
            <p>Or a value of 'NO' to indicate that the expenses will not be included into the CG P&amp;L withheld tax calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>Nulls treated like 'NO'</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.BASE.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the percentage of the CGT Base amount that will be included in the tax calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>Must be a percentage</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.UP.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate for calculating top-up margin amount</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum of 9 numeric characters is allowed </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERFACE.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies and is used to link with the other T24 modules for valuation purposes. </p>
            <p>This is a indicator which is used to inform the system to look for and pick up any foreign exchange,money market transactions for any requested report or valuation. </p>
            <p>Note: It is VERY IMPORTANT that an ASSET.TYPE for Foreign Exchange,       Accounting, Money Market, etc. be set up at this stage.  Failure to       do so will mean that the system will not be able to interface with       those modules to extract and display the information at "Enquiry       Level" where a clients' whole financial position is amalgamated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 alpha character "Module Code".  Input must be one of the following:      AC,  FD,  FI,  FR,  FU,  FX,  LD,  LQ,  MD,  ME,  MM,     LCE (Export) or LCI (Import) Letters of Credit,     RP (Repo), RS (Reverse Repo),   SW(Swap).  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the Adjusted margin rate for calculating ADJ.MARGIN.AMT in SC.POS.ASSET.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALERT.PRICE.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts two numeric values. When the percentage of price change, for the security is greater than ALERT.PRICE.PERC, then an alert will be sent to the portfolio owner, if the portfolio has subscribed for price movement alert. A check will be made to this field, only when ALERT.PRICE.PERC is not defined in SECURITY.MASTER and SUB.ASSET.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the ASSET.TYPE. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the ASSET.TYPE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters. Multi-language field. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.TYPE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the ASSET.TYPE. </p>
            <p>User defined description of a group of similar investment instruments for reporting and information extraction purposes.  All similar securities under this particular asset type would be totalled under one heading on a clients' valuation. </p>
            <p>Examples: All issued share capital could be given an ID of 123 with a           formal description of, say, EQUITIES. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

