<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>BROKER.COMM.EARNT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Used for information purposes only to illustrate precisely how much business, in the form of commission earned is being passed on to individual brokers. </p>
            <p>It has the additional facility of being able to record those commissions in the actual currency of trade. </p>
            <p>There is also a multi value field which allows the user to store various levels of commission earned at which related discounts should be paid. Once a retrocession has been received the running total can be adjusted by a simple input to either a 0.00 position or a lower amount accordingly. </p>
            <p>It must be pointed out however that this application does not pass any financial entries.  Any money received from brokers as a result of this must utilise the DATA.CAPTURE facility. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RUNNING.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically updated with the brokerage charged by a broker in the currency as specified in TRADE.CCY. </p>
            <p>Whenever a retrocession is received from a broker based on the nominal amounts stored within the AMOUNT and the percentage stored in the PERC.DISC this field should be reset to "0.00". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters (plus up to 3 decimal places dependant on TRADE.CCY entered).  (Multivalue field).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency in which the trade is settled (i.e. the broker currency). </p>
            <p>This is a multi value field so that any number of currencies may be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 characters (uppercase alpha) - type SSS         or 1-3 numeric characters. (Multivalue field). (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid code on the CURRENCY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERC.DISC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the percentage discount payable on the AMOUNT as stored in the related field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 5 numeric characters.  Multivalue field with subvalue.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date from which any accrued commissions relate.  Each time the running total is cleared the date should be reset to illustrate the new period. </p>
            <p>Each date corresponds to the previous TRADE.CCY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format (type D). (Multivalue field) (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines a predetermined brokerage amount at which a discount (retrocession) should be received.  Multivalue for different amounts and related percentages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters (Plus up to 3 decimal places dependant on the TRADE.CCY entered).  Multivalue field with subvalue.  (Optional input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Broker. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric character customer id             or 3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".") character mnemonic customer id.  (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Must be a valid customer for whom the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file record (CUSTOMER.TYPE) equals "BROKER".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.ONLY</field>
<desc>
            <p>An indicator to the user that any commission earned by the broker is of a 'Net' nature, i.e. no retrocession will be repaid. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Y)es or (N)o allowed only. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

