<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>CAPTL.INCREASE.DET</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to maintain all relevant details applicable to a particular Capital Increase Transaction. </p>
            <p>Within the various fields are stored the number of new shares for old; the number of rights to which the holder is entitled, again based on a ratio type input; the cost of the New Security; the average cost of the Rights and details of the Rights and New Shares. </p>
            <p>The User can enter the Rights Security Number and/or the New Share Security Number where for example it does not rank along with the Old Issue. </p>
            <p>These then are the conditions applicable to this Capital Increase and the system will utilise these when reckoning entitlement, allotment and costs to each holder of the Base Security. </p>
            <p>The Delivery System within T24 will create advises for the customer advising him of the various options available to him. </p>
            <p>After receipt of the clients instructions Rights will be bought and sold before the Subscription date for application for the New Shares. </p>
            <p>On take-up of the New Shares again the Client will be advised of the transaction again via T24 Delivery. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SUBSCRIPTION.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the currency in which the new shares are to be issued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard currency format.</p>
            <p>Must exist on Currency File.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATIO.NEW.SHARES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in conjunction with RATIO.OLD.SHARES to illustrate the Ratio of New Shares for old within a Capital Increase. </p>
            <p>The Capital Increase Module will utilise this ratio in calculating entitlement of holder to new shares. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>Capital Increase where existing shareholders are offered 1 New Share for every 10 Old Shares held. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric type input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RERUN.CANCEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>User may rerun a Capital Increase Detail record or cancel a whole run. </p>
            <p>An End of Day Batch recreates all the Customer records where a Detail record has the rerun flag set at 'R'.  This gives the User the opportunity to alter and amend positions. </p>
            <p>The Cancel facility will cancel all customer records created by the detail record.  Again this is done as an End of Day type job. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only values 'R', 'C' or blank allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUBSCRIPTION.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Details the price at which the new shares are to be issued. </p>
            <p>The price is in the currency as detailed in SUBSCRIPTION.CCY. </p>
            <p>The price is normally detailed in the offer document. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format.</p>
            <p>Must exist on Currency File.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in conjunction with NUMBER.OLD.SHARES to calculate the number of rights per old shares to which an existing shareholder is entitled. </p>
            <p>Normally rights are issued on a 1 for 1 basis and the number of rights then entitles the shareholder to apply for new shares on a new for old ratio basis. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>Client A has a holding of 1000 shares in Co.A.  On a 1 for 1 rights issue the client has 1000 rights which entitle him on a 1 for 3 basis to apply for 333 new shares. The Client can take up his allotment of new shares or even sell the rights to those shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric type input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.PORTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>As with CAPITAL.PORTION, the Premium portion represents a nominal sum payable within the subscription price of a Capital Reorganisation where additional shares are being offered to existing shareholders. </p>
            <p>For Information and display purposes CAPITAL.PORTION and PREMIUM.PORTION store details within a Capital Reorganisation of a Companies' Share Issue and relate to the Capital and Premium portion of the Subscription Price. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note : It is not envisaged that this facility will be of much use to        European or Domestic Style Capital Reorganisations. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Price type format.  Maximum 14 characters length.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.SUBS.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>All subscriptions for this particular Capital Increase transaction must be received and transmitted to the Issuer by the Subscription date entered. </p>
            <p>This date is the effective last date to pass on information relating to a subscription for a Capital Increase to the Issuer concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date Format           or Default = User date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OLD.SHARES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in conjunction with NUMBER.RIGHTS to calculate the number of rights per old shares to which an existing shareholder is entitled. </p>
            <p>Normally rights are issued on a 1 for 1 basis and the number of rights then entitles the shareholder to apply for new shares on a new for old ratio basis. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>Client A has a holding of 1000 shares in Co.A.  On a 1 for 1 rights issue the client has 1000 rights which entitle him on a 1 for 3 basis to apply for 333 new shares. The Client can take up his allotment of new shares or even sell the rights to those shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric type input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.1.RIGHT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Combined with VALUE.1.RIGHT.PRC, VALUE.1.RIGHT.CCY contains details of the approximate price and currency of 1 right. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard currency type format.</p>
            <p>Must exist on CCY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security involved in the transaction.  This is taken from the SHORT.NAME field within the Security Master file. </p>
            <p>This information is extracted from the Detail Key and enriched from the Security Master record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.SECURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a New Security is being issued or allotted from the Base Security this field will be used to store that Security ID Ref. No. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Security Master format: 6 prefix numbers separated by '-' from 3 suffix numbers.   Examples:  A Capital Increase where existing shareholders are entitled to subscribe for 1 New Share for every 10 Old Shares held.  When the New Shares are Nil Paid or partly paid and are a separate asset.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to record details of a Capital Increase, where Nil Paid or Partly paid stock is being issued.  Multivalue for more than one call. </p>
            <p>Nominal value of stock may be 1.00 where the initial payment is for example 0.25 at a particular date and the balance of 0.75 at a later date. </p>
            <p>Used in conjunction with PAYMENT.DATE to record details of how much is payable for each call and when it is payable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format.  Multi value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the Capital Increase is of a 'Rights Issue' type this Standard Security Master ID. Ref. No will identify the Rights allotted (A separate Security from the Base Security). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Security Master format: 6 prefix security ID separated by '-' from 3 suffix numbers.   Examples:  A Customer holding 1000 shares would be allotted 1000 Rights to New shares.  He may buy &amp;/or Sell part or all of those rights which exist as a separate asset from the Base Security.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.RIGHT.OF.DEV</field>
<desc>
            <p>Dividend date of right. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format (Optional Input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Along with QUOTE.CCY, QUOTE.PRICE is used to record the Quoted price and currency of that price for either the Rights or New Shares involved in the Capital Increase. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format.</p>
            <p>If QUOTE.CCY is input, QUOTE.PRICE becomes mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TRADING.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Signifies the date from which trading either in the rights or new shares is allowed to take place. </p>
            <p>Trading in rights occurs within a particular period and the subscription period for new shares will take place during a specific period afterwards. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format           or Default = User date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.1.RIGHT.PRC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Combined with VALUE.1.RIGHT.CCY, VALUE.1.RIGHT.PRC contains details of the approximate price and currency of 1 right. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard currency type format.</p>
            <p>Must exist on CCY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TRADING.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Trading in Rights or New Shares happens between the DATE.TRADING.FROM and the DATE.TRADING.TO. </p>
            <p>Trading in rights occurs within a particular period and the subscription period for new shares will take place during a specific period afterwards. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format          or Default = User date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in conjunction with PAYMENT to store the payment dates of the part payments of a new issue. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format          or Default = User Date   Examples:  B. P. ord 1 stock. Capital Increase of 1 for 3 New Part Paid shares 25p payable on the 1st April and the Balance on 1st September the next year.</p>
            <p>Where PAYMENT is entered, PAYMENT.DATE is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies uniquely each CAPTL.INCREASE.DET transaction which uses Security ID, Optional Depository number, Capital Increase Type and the Extraction Date. </p>
            <p>Which Security Master record is to be used within this particular Capital Increase Detail record.  Which Depository holding is to be taken.  The type of Capital Increase to be transacted.  Extraction Date - used to Determine Clients' Holdings at a particular date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The request key is made up of the following format:  A - 6 numeric character Security Master Number B - Depository (Optional) C - 1 - 5 Alpha numeric (Types) Capital Increase Type number D - Extraction Date for establishing security positions</p>
            <p>Must be valid Depository.</p>
            <p>Must be valid Capital Increase Type existing in Capital Increase Type table.</p>
            <p>Must be valid Security Master Record ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date at which the QUOTE.PRICE was effective. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format        or Default = User date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPLY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Having provided the Customer with the details of the Capital Increase and the options available to him.  The reply date signifies the date by which 'his' reply must be received in order to subscribe for the new shares. This date will be formatted on the clients' advice. </p>
            <p>Trading in rights occurs within a particular period and the subscription period for new shares will take place during a specific period afterwards. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid date type entry.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATIO.OLD.SHARES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in conjunction with RATION.NEW.SHARES to illustrate the Ratio of New Shares for Old within a Capital Increase. </p>
            <p>The Capital Increase Module will utilise this ratio in calculating entitlement of holder to new shares. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>Capital Increase where existing shareholders are offered 1 New Share for every 10 Old Shares held. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric type input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Along with QUOTE.PRICE, QUOT.CCY is used to record the Quoted price and currency of that price for either the Rights or New Shares involved in the Capital Increase. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type CCY (currency code) characters.  Optional input.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the Currency file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPITAL.PORTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>For display and information purposes this field stores details of the "Capital" portion of the New Share(s) paid. </p>
            <p>The price of the New Shares as indicated in SUBSCRIPTION.PRICE may be further explained as being either a Capital payment or as in a PREMIUM.PORTION of the share being issued within this Capital Increase type transaction. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>A share being issued at say GBP 10.00 could comprise a Capital portion payment of say GBP 5.00 and a premium payment of say GBP5.00. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Price type input. Maximum 14 characters length.</p>
            <p>Both the totals of the Capital and Premium portions cannot be greater than the price input at SUBSCRIPTION.PRICE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUPON.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not used at present. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUS.SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 customer field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional Input used to identify the Depository Holding being affected by the Transaction. </p>
            <p>Where no Depositary entered System assumes all Depositary Holdings are affected by the transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input Internally generated by the key used.</p>
            <p>If entered must be a valid Depositary Number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

