<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>CAPTL.INCREASE.TYP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used within the Capital Reorganisation area of the Securities Module to identify the type of 'Capital Increase' being used within any particular transaction. </p>
            <p>It therefore indicates whether the transaction involves the issuing of rights, the trading of rights or perhaps a straightforward new shares for old shares type transaction. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the CAPITAL.INCREASE.TYPE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>Rights Issue </p>
            <p>Bonus Issue </p>
            <p>etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATE.RIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether rights are to be calculated within the Capital Increase Detail record or not. </p>
            <p>This field specifies whether the Capital Increase is of the sort which issues Rights. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes or N/NO = No only.  (Mandatory input).  Default Value = NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.TO.SEC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether any Capital Increase transaction is to update the Original Security used or not. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Y = Yes or N/NO = No only.  (Mandatory input.)  Default Value = NO.</p>
            <p>Fields WITH.RIGTHS and DEFAULT.TO.SEC.NO cannot be Y at the same time. For   rights process, 2 transactions have to be entered, one for rights issue and   another one for rights takeup. For rights issue, WITH.RIGHTS should be Y and   DEFAULT.TO.SEC.NO should be NO. For rights takeup, WITH.RIGHTS should be NO,   and DEFAULT.TO.SEC.NO should be Y.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the CAPTL.INCREASE.TYP record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.  (Mandatory input).   Examples:  RIGHTS  -  Rights Issue  SCRIP   -  Scrip Issue</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.REQ.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to store details of Original Capital Increase Type used within any particular Transaction. </p>
            <p>Used for comparison lists of positions before and after. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the CAPITAL. INCREASE.TYPE in various languages. </p>
            <p>Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-15 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.SHORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       Y      NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WITH.RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether rights are involved with a particular Capital Increase Transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Y = Yes or N/NO = No only.  (Mandatory input.)  Default Value = NO.</p>
            <p>Fields WITH.RIGTHS and DEFAULT.TO.SEC.NO cannot be Y at the same time. For   rights process, 2 transactions have to be entered, one for rights issue and   another one for rights takeup. For rights issue, WITH.RIGHTS should be Y and   DEFAULT.TO.SEC.NO should be NO. For rights takeup, WITH.RIGHTS should be NO,   and DEFAULT.TO.SEC.NO should be Y.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether Securities are to be posted to safecustody accounts or not. </p>
            <p>The Capital Increase Type may be such that no actual postings are to be made to a client's safecustody Account.  Merely a reference or a calculation facility. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes or N/NO = No only.  (Mandatory input.)  Default Value = NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether a Safecustody Account is to be credited or debited with a Capital Increase Type Transaction. </p>
            <p>Used to inform the System of any Reverse Splits where it may need to debit the safecustody Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes or N/NO = No only.  (Mandatory input.)  Default Value = NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether a Safecustody Account is to be Debited or not with any particular Capital Increase type Transaction. </p>
            <p>ACCOUNT.CREDIT and ACCOUNT.DEBIT can be utilised to cater for any different Capital Increase Type Transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes or N/NO = No only.  (Mandatory input.)  Default Value = NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies which format print is to be used to print the advices. </p>
            <p>The value you specify should point to a particular record on the DE.FORMAT.PRINT file for those advice types which relate to capital restructuring activities. These are located under advice type 1510. </p>
            <p>The key to the DE.FORMAT.PRINT records is similar to the following: </p>
            <p>            1510.1.1.GB             1510.2.1.GB </p>
            <p>Where 1510 relates to Captial Increases generally and the second part of the key defines the format. </p>
            <p>You should ensure that the format you wish to use exists as this cannot be validated at this point. For example, if the above two records only existed and version 3 was selected then NO advice would be created by the delivery system. </p>
            <p>This field will be defaulted into field ADVICE.PRINT.FLAG on the CAPTL.INCREASE.CUS record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 numeric characters. (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.SUBS.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the System is to calculate the subscription details or not for any particular Capital Increase Transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes or N/NO = No only.  (Mandatory input.)  Default Value = NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

