<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>CAPTL.INCREASE.CUS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The Capital Increase Customer records are automatically generated by the System utilising the information stored within the Capital Increase Detail Application. </p>
            <p>A separate record will be created for each customer position within a specified security and this file will contain all the relevant details applicable to that holding given the criteria specified within the Capital Increase Detail record. </p>
            <p>The System  will calculate the number of rights to which a customer is entitled and will illustrate the number of underlying new shares which those rights represent. Additionally, it will calculate the "rounded up" and "rounded down" number of shares to which a client is entitled with the various options available to him. Whether to buy additional rights enabling him to subscribe for the rounded up number or to sell the extra rights and merely subscribe to the rounded down number of shares. </p>
            <p>The System allows the user to post any increases owing to a Capital Increase to either the existing security number or to a new security position again depending entirely on the information as set up in the "Detail" record. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency of this particular capital increase. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field which is updated from the CAPTL.INCREASE.DET.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Balance of clients holding (client signified in SECURITIES.ACCOUNT) in this particular Security which is to be used in calculating the number of new shares and rights to which the Customer is entitled. </p>
            <p>One customer record per depository holding is created form the Detail Key input. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>If 6 customers hold the particular security concerned then 6 customer records will be created by the system.  Where one customer holds a security at two depositories two records will be created for that client. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.  Numeric type display.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatic system ID which identifies uniquely each customer record. </p>
            <p>Automatically created reference number using the module mnemonic, plus Julian date and next sequential reference number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using the ratio of rights to old shares as detailed in CAPTL.INCREASE.DET this field will display the number of rights to which the Customer in SECURITIES.ACCOUNT is entitled. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field. Numeric type display.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUBSCRIBE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using the ratio of new shares to old as detailed in the Capital Increase Details this calculated number represents the number of new shares to which the client may apply or subscribe. </p>
            <p>Client A has 100 old shares and in the event of a Capital Increase with a ratio of 1 new share for 2 old the client would be entitled to apply for 50 new shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.  Numeric type display.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security involved in the transaction.  This is taken from the SHORT.NAME field within the Security Master file. </p>
            <p>Security short name enrichment read from the security master file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REF.BASE.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange Rate between Security Currency and Base Rate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Rate format.  Examples: Local Currency is . Security being transacted is in NLG Rate is NLG to .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Illustrates the no of rights which a client may sell if he takes the rounded down no as the basis of his Capital Increase subscription. </p>
            <p>Where Client A has 100 old shares and there is a Rights Issue of 1 for 3. The client has 100 rights which entitle him to subscribe for 33 new shares. </p>
            <p>This then allows him to sell 1 right for cash as 33 x 3 = 99 Rights. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.  Numeric type display.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDED.DOWN.NUMB.</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using the ratios supplied with the C.I. detail record this automatically updated field will specify the no. of new shares to which a client is entitled rounded down to the next whole no. F12 will then be used in conjunction to illustrate how many rights may be sold. </p>
            <p>Where Client A has 100 old shares and there is a Rights Issue of 1 for 3.  The client has 100 rights which entitle him to subscribe for 33 new shares. </p>
            <p>This then allows him to sell 1 right for cash as 33 x 3 = 99 Rights. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Numeric type display</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESS.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>If entered, it is used to check the format of the override delivery address entered, depending on the value of the carrier from the message control message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters. (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>Must be the id of a valid Message Control record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITIES.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customers Securities Account involved in this particular Capital Increase. An existing shareholder who is entitled to this particular Capital Increase. </p>
            <p>Capital Increase Details will create an individual record for each client who is eligible for this particular Capital Increase as at the date which formed part of the Capital Increase Detail key. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVE.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provides the address where the Advices relating to this trade are to be sent. </p>
            <p>If entered, will be used by the delivery system in place of any addresses stored elsewhere in the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multivalue fields available to enable the full address to be input.  Optional input. Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPO.SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 customer field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PURCHASE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>To entitle the client to an extra share to (the customer) will have to buy additional rights to entitle him to an extra share where the calculation is not exactly pro rata. </p>
            <p>This field will be used in conjunction with PURCHASE.NUMBER. </p>
            <p>Where client A has 100 old shares and there is a Rights Issue of 1 for 3. The client has 100 rights which entitle him to subscribe for 34 new shares. </p>
            <p>To enable him to apply for 34 new shares the PURCHASE.NUMBER of rights is 2, i.e. 102 rights = 34 new shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.  Numeric type display.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDED.UP.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using the ratios supplied within CAPTL.INCREASE.DET this automatically updated field will specify the number of new shares (rounded up) to which the client is eligible. ROUNDED.UP.NUMBER will then indicate how many additional rights the customer will have to buy to enable him to subscribe for the rounded up number. </p>
            <p>Where client A has 100 old shares and there is a Rights Issue of 1 for 3. The client has 100 rights which entitle him to subscribe for 34 new shares. </p>
            <p>To enable him to apply for 34 new shares the PURCHASE.NUMBER of rights is 2, i.e. 102 rights = 34 new shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.  Numeric type display.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.INDICATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Informs the system if excess rights are to be sold by the Custodian Bank on behalf of its clients. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Y)es or (N)o allowed only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Capital Increase Details automatically generated by the Criteria Selected in the detail record. Identifies uniquely each Capital Increase. Customer transaction. </p>
            <p>Once the Capital Increase details key has been input and authorised the user will be able to access the customer records to enable an increase. </p>
            <p>Examples: 123456-000.100104.CAP.20010327.100099-1.100.111 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />The Detail key is made up of the following format: NNNNNN-NNN - 6 numeric character Security Master number XXXXXX - 1-6 Numeric depository number NNN - 1-3 numeric Capital Increase Type number YYYYMMDD - Standard Date format NNNNNN-NNN - 1-6 numeric character Security Account Master number (Mandatory input) -<p /><p /><p>ZZZZZ 1-5 characters Nominee code (Optional) &amp;#8211; SSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS 1-16 CHARACTERS</p><p /><p>Sub Account</p><p> (Optional).</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Depository ID as specified within the Capital Increase Detail record. </p>
            <p>Where no depository used within the Capital Increase Detail, the System assumes all Customer Depository holdings are eligible for the Capital Increase transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Default value is 'nil' where no Depository ID entered at Capital Increase Detail.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.PRINT.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the default advice format required in respect of this particular capital increase request as has been defined on the CAPTL.INCREASE.TYP file. </p>
            <p>The delivery system uses the value in this field to decide which format 1510 advice type to print in respect of the capital increase type. </p>
            <p>The value in this field defaults from the ADVICE field in the CAPTL.INCREASE.TYP file. Provided that the required format exists then delivery will attempt to create the advice. </p>
            <p>You may change the value in this field prior to final authorisation (Null included). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1- 5 numeric characters. Default see below.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVERAGE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculated average price for valuation profit and loss calculations. Net proceeds divided by Nominal balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the reference number of the advices, delivery instructions and payment/receipt messages related to this transaction. </p>
            <p>This field is generated by the delivery system when the messages are created. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>External field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPO.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Depository at which the Capital Increase is taking place.  When omitted the Application will assume all Depositories for purpose of calculation. </p>
            <p>Check at Input level of Capital Increase Details that no. is a valid Depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field which is picked up from the key generated in Captl. Increase Det.</p>
            <p>Can only be a valid Depository number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

