<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>CG.BASE.BUILDER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This will be a new work file that may be used to specify the CG Transaction Base build requirements. </p>
            <p>This application will be used to specify the portfolio &amp; security master id combinations for which the build process will be carried out. </p>
            <p>The application will create a concat file CG.BASE.BUILD.TODAY that will be processed by an end of day process (EOD.BUILD.CG.TXN.BASE)</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the condition to be used when selecting the field in FIELD.NO .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be any of 'EQ', 'NE', 'LT', 'GT', 'LE', 'GE', 'RG',         'NR', 'LK', 'UL'.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if FIELD.NO is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESULT.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can indicate the portfolio number for which the CG transaction base needs to be built.</p>
            <p>This field will be used in conjunction with the SM.ID field to select portfolio and security master combinations for which the CG transaction base will be built.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>If this field is entered then the fields FIELD.NO,         OPERAND &amp; FIELD.CONTENT must be left empty.</p>
            <p>If entered the field must contain an existing portfolio         id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can indicate the security number for which the CG transaction base needs to be built.</p>
            <p>This field will be used in conjunction with the SAM.ID field to select portfolio and security master combinations for which the CG transaction base will be built.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>If this field is entered then the fields FIELD.NO,         OPERAND &amp; FIELD.CONTENT must be left empty.</p>
            <p>If entered the field must contain an existing security         master id</p>
            <p>The field can also contain the value 'ALL' to indicate         all securities</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.CONTENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the value to be matched according to the OPERAND and FIELD.NO fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be entered as either a field number or field name on the CUSTOMER file. The field name will be displayed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>If entered must be a valid field on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the ID field of the file. It will comprise of the application indicator 'CG' concatenated to a julian date and a sequence number of 5 digits.</p>
            <p>Eg: CG9502000001</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The record can be input and changed only on the day it         was initially input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 local reference field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>User defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTED.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain a list of the Customer id's, portfolio group name &amp; security master id combinations for which the CG Transaction base will be built.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

