<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>CG.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file will contain parameters pertaining to the Capital Gains Processing provided within T24.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DATE.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to set-up the end dates for which each CGT tax method (LIFO, FIFO or AVG) is to apply.</p>
            <p> The current and historical bases must be set-up in descending order (i.e. oldest date in the lowest value sub-field). To acknowledge the fact that the highest value sub-field will relate to the current base, you won't be able to populate that field with a date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> The latest field cannot be populated as it relates to the current period</p>
            <p> Dates must be in descending order</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WCG.INCL.ACCR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may have a value of 'YES' to indicate that the accrued interest will be included into the calculation of the capital gains withheld tax profit and loss.</p>
            <p> A value of 'NO' or blank will indicate that the accrued interest will not be included into the CG P&amp;L withheld tax calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p> Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REACQ.PRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate the period of time which must have elapsed between a sale and a subsequent purchase so that the purchase is not regarded as a RE-PURCHASE of the said sale (so called "bed and breakfasting").</p>
            <p> Provided that the next field, REACQ.DROP.LOSS, has been set to "Y"es, any re-purchases taking place before the specified time has elapsed will cause the "dropping" of any loss that the original sale may have incurred.</p>
            <p> Normal periodic method are permitted in the form "nn" to specify the number coupled with either "D", "B", "W", "M" or "Y".</p>
            <p> For example : "10D" indicating 10 calendar days, "10B" indicating 10 business days and "1M" indicating 1 month.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be alpha/numeric in the format "NNNA"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.INFL.INDX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the specification of whether inflation indexation is to be applied to the specified capital gains. If blank then no inflation indexation will be applied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input</p>
            <p> Either YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WCG.INCL.EXPENSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may have a value of 'YES' to indicate that the expenses will be included into the calculation of the Capital gain withheld tax profit and loss.</p>
            <p> A value of 'NO' or blank will indicate that the expenses will not be included into the CG P&amp;L withheld tax calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p> Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WHT.TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the tax type record that is to be used as the CGT tax code mnemonic.</p>
            <p> This feature allows the system to default a tax code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> If entered must be a valid TAX.TYPE record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REACQ.DROP.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify whether it is a requirement to drop any loss associated with a sale and the System detects a reacquisition of the same security within the period specified in the previous field REACQ.PRD.</p>
            <p> Enter "Y"es if this is a requirement, otherwise enter "N"o or leave blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only "Y"es, "N"o or blank permitted</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Company to which this particular parameter file belongs.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Must exist on the COMPANY file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALC.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field RECALC.BASIS determines the value on which the tax due is to be</p>
            <p> calculated when a re-calculation is performed as the result of inserting or</p>
            <p> deleting a transaction from the transaction history.</p>
            <p> Null indicates that any recalculation of tax will be based on recalculated gain considering all</p>
            <p> transactions afresh,</p>
            <p> TRANSACTION indicates that the value entered on the</p>
            <p> transaction itself will be used, CGT.BASE.AMT. Initial tax calculations will</p>
            <p> always use the value determined from considering all transactions afresh.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INCL.ACCR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may have a value of 'YES' to indicate that the accrued interest will be included into the calculation of the captial gain profit and loss.</p>
            <p> A value of 'NO' or blank will indicate that the accrued interest will not be included into the CG P&amp;L calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p> Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INCL.EXPENSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may have a value of 'YES' to indicate that the expenses will be included into the calculation of the Capital gains profit and loss.</p>
            <p> A value of 'NO' or blank will indicate that the expenses will not be included into the CG P&amp;L calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p> Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The purpose of this field is to indicate the particular basis applicable up to the DATE.TO field content. Note that the last DATE.TO field may be blank therefore indicating that it is the current period.</p>
            <p> Only FIFO (First in, first out), LIFO (Last in, first out) and AVG (Pool rate) are valid and may be selected from the "pick" list provided.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only FIFO, LIFO or AVG are allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.TAPER.RELIEF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to CG.TAPER.RELIEF record from which the taper relief on gains is defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

