<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>CG.TXN.BASE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is a financial level live file that holds the relevant information required for the Capital Gains Calculations.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>WHT.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain, if any, the resultant Profit or Loss for the transaction on which Witholding Tax is calculated.</p>
            <p>The amount is always recorded in the security currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates, for example, whether the underlying transaction is a PURCHASE, SALE or REDEMPTION etc.</p>
            <p>Example: 'SSL' - Sale ; 'SPR' - Purchase, as set up in SC.TRANS.NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the currency code indicating the security currency as recorded on the underlying SECURITY.MASTER file. All monetary values in the base record will be expressed in terms of this currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.PL.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains, if any, the cumulative Profit or Loss in the security on which Capital Gains Tax has been calculated.</p>
            <p>This amount is always recorded in the security currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUR.TXN.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the trade date and time of the individual matched transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Format will be YYYYMMDDHHMM, where YYYY specifies the         year, MM specifies the month, DD specifies the day, HH         specifies the hour and MM specifies the minutes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPENSES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the total of any transaction charges such as brokerage, fees and commission.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>I-descriptor allowing access to the first element of the record key, the customer code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRD.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field illustrates the NOMINAL amount or NUMBER of the security in the underlying transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUR.TXN.RED.</field>
<desc>
            <p>The taper relief percentage applied to any gain calculated against the individual transaction before the calculation of withholding tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WHT.PL.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains, if any, the cumulative Profit or Loss in the security on which Witholding Tax has been calculated.</p>
            <p>This amount is always recorded in the security currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAM.SM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the id of the CG.TXN.BASE record.</p>
            <p>The id is in three parts separated by a dot character ".". The first part contains the underlying CUSTOMER id, the second part contains the group to which the portfolio belongs, as defined in PORTFOLIO.GROUPING, therefore indicating the id of the portfolio to which the security belongs. If portfolio groups are not defined then the system will automatically set them up with each portfolio belonging to a unique group with the same id as the portfolio.</p>
            <p>The third part identifies the security itself.</p>
            <p>For example: 12435.12435-1.000123-000</p>
            <p />
            <p>Where 12435 is the CUSTOMER id, 12435-1 indicates the portfolio group and 000123-000 indicates the security held by the customer.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORP.TXN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction name (from SECURITY.TRANS field TRANS.TYPE) of any corporate actions that affected the individual transactions, for example a bonus issue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRD.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will show the cost of the security as contained in the underlying transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.TRD.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the residual nominal cost should any transaction have been partially netted against one or more other transactions.</p>
            <p>For example, using the FIFO (First in, first out) basis :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Purchase 100,000 @ 101, CG.TRD.COST would equal 40,400</p>
            <p>Purchase         100,000 @ 102, CG.TRD.COST would equal 102,000</p>
            <p>Sale 60,000, CG.TRD.COST would equal 0.</p>
            <p>In the above example, the sale of 60,000 has resulted in the first transaction being partially sold, the CG.NOMINAL has been reduced from the original 100,000 to 40,000, in line with this the original TRD.VALUE of 101,000 has been reduced to 40,400 (40000/100000 * 101000). Subsequent sales are compared against the initial purchase cost until it is exhausted and then the next candidate purchase is located.</p>
            <p>Suppose a further sale of 80,000 took place, then the following CG.NOMINAL balances will exist :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Purchase 100,000 @ 101 CG.TRD.COST would equal 0</p>
            <p>Purchase         100,000 @ 102 CG.TRD.COST would equal 61,200</p>
            <p>Sale 60,000, CG.TRD.COST would equal 0.</p>
            <p>Sale 80,000, CG.TRD.COST would equal 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.SAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The portfolio under which the transaction was enacted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the method which has been used in the calculation of capital gains tax or withholding tax.</p>
            <p>Will be either :-</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>FIFO - First in, first out.</p>
            <p>LIFO - Last in, first out.</p>
            <p>AVERAGE, Average.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUR.TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will be the list of credit transactions against which a debit transaction has been matched or partially matched.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRD.NOMINAL.ADJ</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a manual amendment is made to a tranaction detail using CG.MANUAL.INPUT then the changes to TRD.NOMINAL will be stored in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the residual nominal should any transaction have been partially netted against one or more other transactions.</p>
            <p>For example, using the FIFO (First in, first out) basis :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>In the above example, the sale of 60,000 has resulted in the first transaction being partially sold, the CG.NOMINAL has thus been reduced from the original 100,000 to 40,000. Subsequent sales are compared against these purchase values until it is exhausted and then the next candidate purchase is located.</p>
            <p>Suppose a further sale of 80,000 took place, then the following CG.NOMINAL balances will exist :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUR.TXN.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will contain the amount of nominal of the matched credit transactions against which a debit transaction has been matched.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The statement numbers corresponding to any tax postings that have been made. The format is the standard for T24 STMT.ENTRY ids.</p>
            <p>For example,</p>
            <p>110160001847230.00</p>
            <p>1-2</p>
            <p>indicates that the keys 110160001847230.000001 &amp; 110160001847230.000002 are the tax postings for a particular transaction.</p>
            <p>110160001847230.00</p>
            <p>1.4</p>
            <p>indicates that the keys 110160001847230.000001 &amp; 110160001847230.000004 are the tax postings for a particular transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TRANS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the transaction reference of the underlying SECURITY.TRANS record.</p>
            <p>The format of the transaction reference is typically as shown under:</p>
            <p>SCTRSC9933000001.4 (The '.4' indicates that this security transaction record pertains to the 4</p>
            <p>The sequence number will always be "1" in respect to SECURITY.TRANSFER transactions. However, for SEC.TRADE transactions as indicated above it will increment to identify a location within a bulk transaction. Since a bulk security trade may update many different CG.TXN.BASE records, the sequence number 7, for example, means that this particular customer/security record relates to the 7</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME.CGUPDT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the date and time of the last update to the base record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Format will be YYYYMMDDHHMM, where YYYY specifies the         year, MM specifies the month, DD specifies the day, HH         specifies the hour and MM specifies the minutes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.POSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the current CG position in the security. This is the total of all unsold amounts (CG.NOMINAL) upto and including the current transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The original value of TRD.NOMINAL when the transaction was made. The value of TRD.NOMINAL may change throughout the life cycle of a holding depending on any corporate actions that affect the holding. This figure will remain unaffected by any corporate actions.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>I-descriptor allowing access to the second element of the record key, the customer group to which the portfolio belongs.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain, if any, the resultant Profit or Loss for the transaction on which Capital Gains tax is to be paid.</p>
            <p>The amount is always recorded in security currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>I-descriptor allowing access to the third element of the record key, the security number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORP.TXN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction date of any corporate actions that affected the individual transactions, for example a bonus issue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.EXPENSES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the residual amount of any expensesshould any credit transaction be partially matched against one or more debit transaction.</p>
            <p>For example,</p>
            <p>If a purchase of 10,000 of a bond was made with expenses of $100.00 and a subsequent sale of 6,000 was made the CG.EXPENSES would be $40.00 (4000/10000 * 100).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUR.AC.CG.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual gain, after the taper relief has been applied, on the individual transaction against which withholding tax has been calculated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The original value of TRD.VALUE when the transaction was made. The value of TRD.VALUE may change throughout the life cycle of a holding depending on any corporate actions that affect the holding. This figure will remain unaffected by any corporate actions.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the trade date and time of the underlying transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Format will be YYYYMMDDHHMM, where YYYY specifies the         year, MM specifies the month, DD specifies the day, HH         specifies the hour and MM specifies the minutes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARAM.CONDITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The CG.PARAM.CONDITION that applies to this transaction base.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INT.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the current total of CG accrued interest position. It is the total accrued interest (CG.ACCRUED.INT) of all unsold transactions upto and including the current transaction. Only present for interest bearing stocks (Bonds).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.INDEX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The index at which the transaction is based. This will be used when calculating indexation coefficients for adjusting trade costs before calculating any gains or losses.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SRC.LCL.CGT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This indicates whether the tax was to be deducted by the bank or the depository.</p>
            <p>Will be either :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>SOURCE - Tax deducted at source (depository)</p>
            <p>LOCAL - Tax deducted by the bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORP.TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction id of any corporate actions that affected the individual transactions, for example a bonus issue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether tax has already been calculated for this transaction or is awaiting posting in the end of day batch.</p>
            <p>Will be either :-</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NONE - No tax to be calculated.</p>
            <p>POSTED - Tax has been calculated.</p>
            <p>TO_BE_CALC - Tax to be calculated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUR.TX.INDEX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The index at which the matched transaction is based. This will be used when calculating indexation coefficients for adjusting trade costs before calculating any gains or losses.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.GRP.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the id of the CG.TXN.BASE record.</p>
            <p>The id is in three parts separated by a dot character ".". The first part contains the underlying CUSTOMER file id, therefore indicating the id of the customer to which the transactions belong. The second part identifies the group to which the portfolios in this base record belong. The third part identifies the security itself.</p>
            <p>For example: 12435.GBPSEC.000123-000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Where 12345 indicates the owning customer, GBPSEC         indicates the group to which the portfolios in this base         record belong and 000123-000 indicates the security held         by the portfolios.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUR.TX.CG.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will contain the withholding tax profit or loss calculated against the individual matched transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUED.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the underlying security is interest bearing then this field will contain the accrued interest, if any, on the underlying transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.ACCRUED.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the residual amount of any accrued interest should any credit transaction be partially matched against one or more debit transaction. Only used for interest bearing stocks (Bonds).</p>
            <p>For example,</p>
            <p>If a purchase of 10,000 of a bond was made with accrued interest of $100.00 and a subsequent sale of 6,000 was made the CG.ACCRUED.INT would be $40.00 (4000/10000 * 100).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.COST.OF.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the current cost of CG position (excluding ad hoc items such as charges and commission). It is the total cost (CG.TRD.COST) of all unsold transactions upto and including the current transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.EXP.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the current total of CG expenses position. It is the total expenses (CG.EXPENSES) of all unsold transactions upto and including the current transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

