<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>CG.TAPER.RELIEF</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Provides details of how taper relief is to be applied when calculating withholding tax due on securities transactions.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REDUCT.PCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of taper relief to be applied, will be a percentage between 0 and 100.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 local reference field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>User defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPER.RELIEF.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id for the Taper relief records is a numeric element and a date element. For example, 100.19990101. The date element allows transactions with different trade dates to use the same taper relief id.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Numeric element must to 1 to 3 characters</p>
            <p>Date element must be a valid date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>I-descriptor allows access to the first part of the id, the taper relief id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUR.QUAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date before which purchases must have been made inorder to qualify for taper relief.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPER.QUAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>I-descriptor allows access to the second part of the id, the date from which the taper relief is active.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELD.PERIOD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The period for which the holding must be held, can be either MONTH or YEAR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SALE.QUAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date after which purchases must have been made inorder to qualify for taper relief.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The description for the taper relief record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELD.PERIOD.CUTOFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>If entered it will affect the holding period calculation as follows,</p>
            <p>If the purchase date is less than the cut off date and the sale date is greater than the cutoff date the holding period will be the diference between the purchase date and the cut off date.</p>
            <p>If both dates are before the cut off date the the held period will be the difference between the purchase date and the sale date.</p>
            <p>Otherwise the held period will be the difference between the purchase and sale dates.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELD.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>A number indicating the period for which the security must be held before taper relief can be applied.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELD.PERIOD.ROUND</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of rounding to be applied when calculating the holding period. Will round the decimal portion with UP or DOWN.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

