<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>DIARY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to define actual DIARY events.</p>
            <p>  Basic parameters for the type of the event will have to be defined in DIARY.TYPE application. Using this event type, details of the forthcoming actual event are entered in this application. The EVENT.TYPE field in this application controls the input/update of various fields.</p>
            <p>  DIARY record can be created both manually and by an Extel Financials data feed.</p>
            <p>  DIARY record will record the actual details of the event, event type, number of new shares for old, amount of dividend etc.</p>
            <p>  Once the DIARY record has been authorised, user will be able to choose an option of creating ENTITLEMENT record online or during End Of Day process. Entitlement records are created for each portfolio of the Security the DIARY record has been raised for.</p>
            <p>  Any modifications to an existing DIARY record is only possible before authorisation of ENTITLEMENT records.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to the delivery message(s) generated by the DIARY transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for information only.</p>
            <p>  This field is used to record the market price of any new shares or rights that are created as part of the event.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input of 0-16 numeric characters in Standard T24 format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.ADVICE.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether pre confirmation advices are generated when entitlements are created via this Diary record.</p>
            <p>  The value will be defaulted from the relevant DIARY.TYPE record.</p>
            <p>  The actual message types are determined via the relevant EB.ADVICES records, which will be either SC-0100-EVENT.TYPE, for entitlement creation or SC-0101-EVENT.TYPE, for entitlement amendment or deletion.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Input can be set to YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.MKT.PRC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only used for capital gain purposes. If the event type specified in CG.TXN.RULES is a merger with fiscal effect then this field may be used, dependent on settings, to calculate the capital gain for each ENTITLEMENT record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Will default to the value in SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT2.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT2.DEPOT to OPT2.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHT.TO.NEW</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used in conjunction with the NEW.RATIO field to produce the ratio with which securites will be received by a portfolio as a result of talking up the right to the securities.  For example if a portfolio holds 300 of a particular right for which there is a rights issue then if:</p>
            <p>  NEW.RATIO = 1     RIGHT.TO.NEW = 3</p>
            <p>  Then the portfolio will receive 100 new securities.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input only allowed for Diary records where the associated DIARY.TYPE record has the RIGHTS field set to Y.</p>
            <p>  Only numeric input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.POSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the Security Position updated by the execution of the Corporate Action will be blocked.</p>
            <p>  If the position is to be blocked it can take place at the authorisation of the DIARY record (value DIARY) when the entitlements are created unauthorised, or when individual entitlements are authorised (value ENTITLEMENT). The default value for this field is contained in the DIARY.TYPE record. The blocked amount is always the QUALIFY.HOLDING on the ENTITLEMENT record. Blocks are created in the SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS application automatically when a block is required, similarly they are unblocked using the same application automatically. A block / unblock is created under the following circumstances:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  A value of NONE can be entered to suppress any default option if required.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Input</p>
            <p>  Values DIARY or ENTITLEMENT or NONE allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT1.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT1.DEPOT to OPT1.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION2</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.OR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field should be used to generate Entitlements based on Value Date. For a Value Date based Entitlement, all Security movements that have a Value Date before the EX.DIV date of the DIARY will be included. All positions were the EX.DIV Date is lesser than the Value Date will be ignored.</p>
            <p>  If this field is left blank, the System will default to the TRADE.OR.VALUE field of the SECURITY.MASTER of the Security processed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Input.</p>
            <p>  Input can be TRADE or VALUE or left Blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.EVENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only used for capital gain purposes. This allows different rules, using CG.TXN.RULES, to be specified for each option within the corporate action.</p>
            <p>  It can only be used for DIARY records with options, and where the DEF.OPT.EVT is set to Y in DIARY.TYPE for the field EVENT.TYPE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid DIARY.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION3</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT4.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT4.DEPOT to OPT4.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for information only.</p>
            <p>  Date at which the quoted price in the previous field was in effect.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input in Standard T24 Date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOREIGN.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Data entered in this field relates to the input in the FOREIGN.CHARGES field.</p>
            <p>  If the FOREIGN.CHARGES field is set to CASH then the amount entered will be used as a percentage for use in the calculation that produces the value of the FGN.CHARGES.AMT field in ENTITLEMENT.</p>
            <p>  If the FOREIGN.CHARGES field is set to NOMINAL then enter the rate per nominal unit to be used in the calculation that produces the value of the FGN.CHARGES.AMT field in ENTITLEMENT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Either enter an amount or a rate per nominal unit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT1.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT1.DEPOT to OPT1.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT4.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT4.DEPOT to OPT4.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES.INDICATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether Foreign Charges entered in the previous field is a Percentage value of the Gross Amount (CASH) or rate per nominal unit of stock (NOMINAL).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of CASH or NOMINAL allowed.  Mandatory input if an amount is present in the FOREIGN.CHARGES field otherwise input not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TRANS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>System generated field showing the number of Security Transactions records created.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the old factor associated with the bond for which the corporate action has been initiated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            <p>  Automatically updated by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT4.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT4.DEPOT to OPT4.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.NEW.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether to Sell New securities which are being offered or not.</p>
            <p>  If this field is set to Y then the securities received by the portfolio in the associated NEW.SEC.NO, NEW.RATIO and OLD.RATIO fields will be sold by the corporate action at the price input in the NEW.PRICE field. This will result in two securities movements (and hence two SECURITY.TRANS records) being generated for the portfolio by the corporate action; one crediting the portfolio with the new securities and one debiting the portfolio with the securities it has received being sold.</p>
            <p>  Effectively this field allows Enhanced Scrip Dividends to be processed as a single event.</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if NEW.SECURITIES field in DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>  Input only allowed if the NEW.SECURITIES field is set to Y on the DIARY.TYPE record that defines this event.</p>
            <p>  Will default to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default Commission Code to be used in calculation of commission for the entitlements generated by this event if the portfolio has not had a charging structure set-up for this type of Corporate Action.</p>
            <p>  This field will defaults to the Commission Type setup in CUSTOMER.SECURITY file for the DIARY.TYPE. If this is blank it will defaults to the Commission Type defined in the DIARY.TYPE record.</p>
            <p>  This code is validated against the  FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>  This code will only be used if there is no commission code defined in the SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION charging structure.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Must exist in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>  11 characters alphanumeric input.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT3.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT3.DEPOT to OPT3.DEBIT form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold value DEPOSITORY or BROKER. No input, system updated field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.PROC.CONTRA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the automatic settlement of the Contra settlement record generated for closing out</p>
            <p>  the stock position in the old security while processing corporate events where one security</p>
            <p>  is being converted to another.The settlement records are generated after authorisation of the entitlement.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input allowed only when field SEC.HOLD.SETTLE in DIARY is set to YES</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input allowed only for Stock Conversion Events.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed values are YES, NO or Null. A Null is equivalent to NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.PRE.DIARY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field maintains the cross reference to the id of the corresponding record in SC.PRE.DIARY that was used to create the DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  An EXTERNAL field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows which options have been taken by the user.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is related to the previous field (TOTAL.CASH) and shows the Currency to which TOTAL.CASH belongs to.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 Currency format and updated by the system.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date the portfolios (SEC.ACC.MASTER and related cash accounts) are to be updated by the event.</p>
            <p>  This is the value date of the corporate action event in respect of updating the ACCOUNT and SECURITY.POSITION files as a result of the corporate action. In some cases, it may be found necessary to delay the value date for which customers accounts receive value. Such instances may, for example, include those cases where the dividend is received by cheque and, should this be in a foreign currency, will require sending for collection.</p>
            <p>  If no date is entered then this field will default to the same date as that entered into the PAY.DATE field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input of Standard T24 Date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CASH.XCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multivalued field associated with the DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  It contains the exchange rate used in calculating the local currency equivalent of the amount payable to or receivable from the Depository. Thus it is the exchange rate used in calculating the TOTAL.CASH.LCCY field from the TOTAL.CASH field, i.e. the exchange rate between the currency in the associated TOTAL.CASH.CCY field and the local currency of the system.</p>
            <p>  This field will default to the midrate between the currency in the associated TOTAL.CASH.CCY field and the local currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This field will default to the midrate between the Corporate Action currency and the local currency of the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODD.LOT.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field containing the security number of the Odd Lot Security. Must exist on the SECURITY.MASTER application.</p>
            <p>  This field can be the same or it can be different that the main security on which the transaction takes place.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid Security Number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-value field. Optional field. If left blank then the diary events will  occur for all holdings of the security across all portfolios in the specified depository. If portfolios are entered then diary events will only occur across those portfolios.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Optional field. Numeric nnnnnn-n format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price that will be apply on the SEC.TRADE or SEC.OPEN.ORDER generated for dividend reinvestment.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input only allowed if REINV.PARAM field of the related DIARY.TYPE is not empty</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rate of tax levied by the Local government. This will default to rate in the LOCAL fields of the COUPON.TAX.CODE record for the country of which the security in question is domiciled.</p>
            <p>  The field is multi-valued to show all the percentages associated with any linked taxes entered in LOCAL.TAX.CODE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.RATIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field showing the number of new shares for the number of old shares input in the previous field to build up an new for old entitlement ratio.</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if SECURITY.UPDATE field in DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>  Mandatory input if the associated NEW.SEC.NO field has been populated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Security number of the security that the Diary record relates to. Must exist on the SECURITY.MASTER record. While input can be the Security mnemonic (as defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record) or the alternate security index (as defined on the SC.PARAMETER file) the security will be held as the ID of the SECURITY.MASTER record.</p>
            <p>  It will be enriched by the short description of the Security from Security Master.</p>
            <p>  All DIARY records are controlled by a particular security as they generate ENTITLEMENT record according to which portfolios hold that security on the EX.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>  Input can be a valid SECURITY.MASTER ID, a Security Mnemonic or a Security Alternative Index.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is related to the previous field (TOT.SECURITY) and shows the total number of the corresponding securities that have been credited to holdings as a result of the DIARY event which is being defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will indicate whether the Rate is quoted as a net or gross figure - with respect to tax. The Corporate Actions suite of programs allows rates to be entered before tax  or charges (Gross) or after tax  or charges (Net).</p>
            <p>  Only input of GROSS or NET allowed.</p>
            <p>  The system will default to NET.</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if CASH field on DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Only input of GROSS or NET allowed.</p>
            <p>  Mandatory input if the CASH field on the DIARY.TYPE record that defines the corporate action is set to Y other wise input is not allowed.</p>
            <p>  GROSS type is not allowed when ACCUM.INCOME field in DIARY.TYPE is set   to Y.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INS.STOCK.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default instruction to be applied on the related ENTITLEMENT records.</p>
            <p>  This field is populated from the STOCK.CASH field of the DEFAULT record of</p>
            <p>  the SC.ENT.INSTR file for the concerned security number.</p>
            <p>  It indicates the action to be taken when STOCK or CASH option are present.</p>
            <p>  The RECOMMEND option means the system will apply the instruction stored in the</p>
            <p>  RECOMMEND field of the SECURITY.MASTER file for the current SECURITY.NUMBER.</p>
            <p>  It can be amended or left blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid inputs are : Empty string, STOCK, CASH or RECOMMEND</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT2.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT2.DEPOT to OPT2.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for information only.</p>
            <p>  Currency of price in the QUOTE.PRICE field. If entered, validated in CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input of 0-3 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price of the New Security entered. This field will defaults to the current market price read from the SECURITY.MASTER file if the DIARY.TYPE record defining the DIARY indicates that:</p>
            <p>  NEW.SECURITIES = Y     FREE.SECURITIES = NO          and RIGHTS = NO</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input mandatory if securities are being updated that are not free and this is not a Rights issue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RP.TOT.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is automatically updated with the total cash amount to be debited from the Repo Nostro account in security currency.</p>
            <p>  The detail of this total can be viewed in the RP.ALT.NOSTRO record keyed on the DIARY id.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  No-input multi-valued field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field used in the calculation of consideration using the Columbian Yield Method.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTL.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  This field contains the number of ENTITLEMENT records that have been settled for this DIARY record for the Depository contained in the associated DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  This field will be updated when the ENTITLEMENT records are settled using SC.SETTLEMENT.  It will decrease by one whenever an Entitlement is settled that is associated with this DIARY/ Depository combination.</p>
            <p>  Only applicable if actual settlement has been used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify a reallowance amount which is effectively a commission for the Bank for processing the dividend request. Input into this field will automatically populate the contents of the field REALLOW.XRATE with the mid rate between the local currency of the system and the currency of the corporate action. This field is the reallowance amount in the Corporate Action currency.</p>
            <p>  This field can only be updated if the UPDATE.NOSTRO field on the DIARY.TYPE record associated with this field is set to YES. The ID of the DIARY.TYPE record associated with this corporate action is given in the EVENT.TYPE field.</p>
            <p>  This amount will be withheld from the amount that would otherwise be posted to the NOSTRO Account specified in the associated DEP.ACCOUNT.NO field and will be posted insted to the Category identified in the REALLOWANCE.PL.CAT field on the DIARY.TYPE record. If the REALLOWANCE.PL.CAT field has not been populated then this field will be a no-input field even if the UPDATE.NOSTRO field is set to YES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field, 19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>  Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the new factor associated with the bond for which the corporate action has been initiated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            <p>  Automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.ENT.AUTH.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Cross references to the transaction id in SC.ENT.AUTHORISE that were used to authorise the ENTITLEMENT records associated with this DIARY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.HOLD.SETTLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>CASH.HOLD.SETTLE will be used to control whether cash will update the SC.SETTLEMENT application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  CASH.HOLD.SETTLE will allow input of #145;YES#146; or #145;NO#146; only.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the ACTUAL.SETTLEMENT field on the SC.PARAMETER record is #145;NO#146; then CASH.HOLD.SETTLE will be no-input field that will default to #145;NO#146;.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the CASH.HOLD.SETTLE field is #145;YES#146; then the cash accounting will use actual settlement.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If DIARY transaction is authorised with CASH.HOLD.SETTLE field set to #145;YES#146; then the system will create a SC.SETTLEMENT record from the transaction.SC.SETTLEMENT         records will be created with an unauthorised status.The         cash settlement can be recorded using the AMT.RECD.PAID         field In SC.SETTLEMENT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RP.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is automatically updated in case of REPO entries if the SPLIT.DEBIT.CPN field is set to YES in the REPO.PARAMETER. This field is defaulted from the ACCOUNT field in the NOSTRO.ACCOUNT record keyed on the security currency if the APPLICATION field is set up to RP.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  No-input multi-valued field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the user to input details of any future payments for part paid securities. This field will record the date the payment is to be made.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional Date field in Standard T24 format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date of the Event is paid/issued.</p>
            <p>  This is the date that the company initiating the corporate action performs the corporate action. For example if the corporate action is a dividend then this will be the date the dividend is paid out, if it is a Takeover then this will be the date of the Takeover.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory input of Standard T24 Date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RCVBL.TAX.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tax percentage of the associated RCVBL.TAX.CODE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPLY.BY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Advises the date that instructions must be with the registrar or custodian.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input of Standard T24 Date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT3.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT3.DEPOT to OPT3.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Security Number of the Rights Security which is being issued as a result of the corporate action.</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if RIGHTS flag on the DIARY.TYPE record that defines this event is set to Y.</p>
            <p>  The value entered is validated in SECURITY.MASTER file and if it is a valid security it is enriched by the short description of the security.</p>
            <p>  Any security input into this field must have the RIGHTS.FLAG field set to Y on the SECURITY.MASTER record that defines it.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory input if Rights are issued as part of the Corporate Action, otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p>  Must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>  Input can be a valid SECURITY.MASTER ID, a Security Mnemonic or a Security Alternative Index.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RERUN</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO field allowing a user to regenerate the ENTITLEMENT records for a DIARY.</p>
            <p>  If this field is set to YES then the ENTITLEMENT records for the DIARY will be regenerated to reflect the changes made to the DIARY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input is only allowed to DIARY records that have been previously authorised.</p>
            <p>  Input can only be YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP2.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate should represent the so called </p>
            <p>  The distributions from this rate will be posted to the clients income account if this process has been defined on the customers SEC.ACC.MASTER (portfolio) accounts using the AC.DEF.SYS.CODE fields therein for the purpose of posting particular entry types to specific accounts. If not, then normal defaulting rules will be applied to locate an appropriate account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1 - 16 numeric characters</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only when EQUALISATION field on DIARY.TYPE record the DIARY is linked to is YES, in which case this field is mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.TAX.CALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether stamp tax calculations are due for this event type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Source Tax Code used for Source Tax.</p>
            <p>  Automatically updated by the system from COUPON.TAX.CODE file.</p>
            <p>  The field contains either the key of a TAX record or the key of TAX.TYPE.CONDITION record prefixed by an *.</p>
            <p>  If APPL.GEN.CONDITION application has a record with id DIARY, then CONTRACT.GRP is identified based on the conditions defined in the fields from DECIS.FIELD to DECISION.TO in APPL.GEN.CONDITION.</p>
            <p>  In TAX.TYPE.CONDITION, the tax codes that are assigned to particular groups of contract (CONTRACT.GRP) are populated in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This is an INPUT field.</p>
            <p>  2 numeric characters allowed for a TAX code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT2.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT2.DEPOT to OPT2.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CONVERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the automatic settlement of unsettled transactions in the original security,</p>
            <p>  while processing corporate events where one security is being converted to another.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input allowed only if field ACTUAL.SETTLEMENT is set to YES in SC.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input allowed only for Stock Conversion Events.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed values are Yes,NO and Null. NO and Null are treated differently.</p>
            <p>  NO indicates Auto Conversion is not required.Null indicates,the system should look for a</p>
            <p>  parameter at a higher level i.e AUTO.CONVERSION field in CUSTOMER.SECURITY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the book cost with which the new securities will update the SECURITY.POSITION file. It is different from the price of the securities as in Corporate Actions such as Call Payments the the cost to the portfolio of the resultant securities will not be solely the price paid in the Corporate Action but will also include the cost of the partly paid securities the portfolio already holds.</p>
            <p>  This field should also be used for events such as Scrip Dividends where the shares are free though they do have a cost assciated with them as they are received in lieu of cash.</p>
            <p>  If an amount in entered in both the BOOK.COST and PRICE fields then this field will take precedence when updating the cost of the securities to the portfolio.</p>
            <p>  Any amount input into this field will not effect the accounting. If accounting entries are required then an amount should be entered into the PRICE field.</p>
            <p>  The field will only allow input when security positions are being updated by the Corporate Action.</p>
            <p>  If input is allowed it will be optional.</p>
            <p>  The cost is in the security of the Diary record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input, numeric field.</p>
            <p>  Input only allowed if the associated NEW.SEC.NO field is populated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RCVBL.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field displays the Recoverable Tax  or Tax type condition applicable for the Corporate Action event. If the Rate.Type is GROSS and the event is Taxable, this field is updated with the Tax Code.</p>
            <p>  It is an input field and can be changed at the DIARY level if needed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  The code should should exsist either on the Tax or Tax Type Condition tables.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rate of Source Tax levied. This field will defaults to the system from SOURCE.TAX.CODE field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field will only be updated if the TAXABLE field on the DIARY.TYPE record that defines this corporate action is set to YES.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INS.SELL.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default instruction to be applied on the related ENTITLEMENT records.</p>
            <p>  This field is populated from the SELL.ODD.LOTS field of the DEFAULT record of</p>
            <p>  the SC.ENT.INSTR file for the concerned security number.</p>
            <p>  It indicates if the ODD.LOTS should be sold or not.</p>
            <p>  It can be amended or left blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid inputs are : Empty string, YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT3.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT3.DEPOT to OPT3.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.PORTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for information only. It allows the user to input the premium portion of the price paid for the new security.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input of 0-16 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT3.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT3.DEPOT to OPT3.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION1</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.DIST.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Interest distribution factor for this event. Applicable to shares only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Depository number to which the DIARY event is related to.  User has option of entering a specific depository OR ALL can be entered. In the later case, processing will be done for all the depositories that have been flagged on the Customer Security file as being a depository that carries out Corporate Actions. If a depository has been entered it is validated against the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file and enriched with the customer short name.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory input of 1-10 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>  Must exist in CUSTOMER.SECURITY file as a DEPOSITORY if depository code is entered else only ALL is allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>A brief description of the Option which is being recorded.</p>
            <p>  If the corporate action has only one option then this field will default from the description of the corprate action on the DIARY.TYPE field that defines the corporate action.</p>
            <p>  If this field is equal to LAPSE then this option result in nothing happening.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  35 characters long free format text.</p>
            <p>  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start of the Equalisation period for the stock.</p>
            <p>  Normally, this field will contain the previous equalisation (dividend) date if it is recorded on the SECURITY.SUPP file relating to the security. If not, you will be prompted to supply this date before you can successfully commit the transaction. On acceptance, the date you enter here will be stored in the SECURITY.SUPP file for use on the next dividend payment date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date format</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only when EQUALISATION field on DIARY.TYPE record the DIARY is linked to is YES, in which case this field is mandatory</p>
            <p>  Must be earlier than EX.DATE</p>
            <p>  Defaults to previous distribution date from the SECURITY.SUPP file for the security</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.MKT.PRC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only used for capital gain purposes. If the event type specified in CG.TXN.RULES is a merger with fiscal effect then this field may be used, dependent on settings, to calculate the capital gain for each ENTITLEMENT record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Will default to the value in SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>A number generated automatically by the system which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of the postings made to the Nostro account identified in the associated DE.ACCOUNT.NO field.</p>
            <p>  The system will automatically insert a number into this field and this number may refer to a statement entry or a category entry depending on the value contained in the corresponding sub-valued fields.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Currency of the Event which is being defined.</p>
            <p>  This field will default to the SECURITY.CURRENCY as defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record of the Security entered into the SECURITY.NO field. However the user does have the option of changing this field.</p>
            <p>  If a new currency is entered then the input is validated against the CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory input of 3 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>  Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO flag indicating whether update from an external source is allowed. If set to NO then automatic update from an external source is blocked. It will be automatically set to YES when the DIARY record is first updated by an external feed. This field will automatically be set to NO once manual input has been made to the DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Allowed values are YES/NO only. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT3.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT3.DEPOT to OPT3.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local Tax Code user for Local Tax.</p>
            <p>  Automatically updated by the system from COUPON.TAX.CODE file.</p>
            <p>  This field could be populated with a TAX ID or a TAX.TYPE.CONDITION ID.</p>
            <p>  If a TAX Id is used and the TAX record has the field LINK.TAX populated then all taxes linked to the Id entered will be displayed using the multi-values as required, the associated percentages will be displayed in the field LOCAL.TAX.PERC.</p>
            <p>  If APPL.GEN.CONDITION application has a record with id DIARY, then CONTRACT.GRP is identified based on the conditions defined in the fields from DECIS.FIELD to DECISION.TO in APPL.GEN.CONDITION. In TAX.TYPE.CONDITION, the tax codes that are assigned to particular groups of contract (CONTRACT.GRP) are populated in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Either a valid TAX</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Or a Valid TAX.TYPE.CONDITION</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Only multi-value 1 may be used for entry</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INS.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the option to be choosed by default if not standing instruction have been found or no instructions</p>
            <p>  have been given by the customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Option number (multi-value number of the OPTION.DESC field)</p>
            <p>  Input only allowed if the current DIARY record contains more than one option</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique identifier for the DIARY record.</p>
            <p>  The format of the Diary record ID is as follows : DY YY DDD 99999 where DY represents the DIARY application, YY the year the DIARY record was set-up, DDD the Julian date the DIARY record was first set-up and 99999 is a sequence number which is generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields DEP.NO to RIGHTS.COST form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.OR.LOCAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether tax has been deducted at source or not.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether the DIARY record was updated by an external source or manually.</p>
            <p>  System generated field containing EXTERNAL or MANUAL.</p>
            <p>  This field will be automatically be set to EXTERNAL when the DIARY record is created by an external feed and set to MANUAL when input has been made to it by a user.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTL.AUTHORISED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  This field contains the number of ENTITLEMENT records that have been authorised for this DIARY record for the Depository contained in the associated DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  This field will be updated when the ENTITLEMENT records are authorised using SC.ENT.AUTHORISE or ENTITLEMENT.  It will decrease by one whenever an authorised Entitlement is reversed that is associated with this DIARY/ Depository combination.</p>
            <p>  If the UPDATE.NOSTRO flag is set to YES on the DIARY.TYPE record associated with the DIARY then when this field equals the associated ENTL.CREATED field then the Nostro Account in the associated DEP.ACCOUNT.NO field will be updated wil the amount to be credited to or debited from the depository.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field -  automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A brief description of the DIARY event which is being defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  35 characters long free format.</p>
            <p>  Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.AUTO.AUTH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the Start of Day process will automatically authorise the ENTITLEMENT record.</p>
            <p>  This field is automatically populated from the parameters entered in the related DIARY.TYPE</p>
            <p>  record (fields ENT.AUTO.AUTHORISE, ENT.AUT.NB.OF.DAYS, ENT.AUT.PRI.AFT and</p>
            <p>  ENT.AUT.SEL.DATE).</p>
            <p>  This field can be amended.</p>
            <p>  The user will be prompted to bypass the date when authorising the DIARY record manually.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 Date format</p>
            <p>  The date must be greater than the DIA.AUTO.AUTH.DATE field but lower than the DEF.INST.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT3.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT3.DEPOT to OPT3.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT1.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT1.DEPOT to OPT1.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOND.SHARE.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag indicating whether the originating security is of type Bond or Share. Automatically updated by the system from SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT1.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT1.DEPOT to OPT1.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accrual Start Date for Corporate Action event</p>
            <p>  This is the date from which the calculation will commence. For example, if the corporate actions is a dividend then this will be the date from which the dividend calculation will start. Like the PAY.DATE this field will be defaulted from the SECURITY.MASTER, and may be amended by the user.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 Date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUST.SOO.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id of SEC.OPEN.ORDER record created to allocate the shares remaining. These are calculated in case of Adjustment on the broker (Actual Settlement).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  No-input field</p>
            <p>  Field updated only for the Actual Settlement mode with the ROUNDING.LEVEL field equal to DEPOSITORY and ROUNDING field equal to DOWN       in DIARY.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTL.CREATED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associeated with the DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  This field contains the number of ENTITLEMENT records that have been created by this DIARY record for the Depository contained in the associated DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  This field will be updated when the ENTITLEMENT records are created following authorisation of the DIARY record, either online or during the end of day. It will also be incremented whenever an Entitlement record is input directly for this Depository.  It will decrease by one whenever an Entitlement is deleted or reversed that is associated with this DIARY/ Depository combination.</p>
            <p>  If the UPDATE.NOSTRO flag is set to YES on the DIARY.TYPE record associated with the DIARY then when this field equals the associated ENTL.AUTHORISED field then the Nostro Account in the associated DEP.ACCOUNT.NO field will be updated wil the amount to be credited to or debited from the depository.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field - automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTL.REVERSED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  This field is updated when an ENTITLEMENT record is reversed for this depository. The ENTL.AUTHORISED field is debited and this field credited. When a new ENTITLEMENT record is created to replace the old one then this field is debited and the ENTL.AUTHORISED credited.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Noinput field</p>
            <p>  this field is automatically updated by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Ex.Div date of the DIARY. All holders in the Security specified as of this date are entitled to the event.</p>
            <p>  When calculating the holding of a particular security position that qualifies for the Corporate Action event the system calculates the balance of the security position on this date. All security movements that have a trade date before this date are included, all security movements with a trade date equal to or after this date are ignored when calculating the qualifying balnce.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory input of Standard T24 Date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT4.DEPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT4.DEPOT to OPT4.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 customer field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field containing a list of all the depositories where portfolios that will be updated by this corporate action hold the relevent stock.</p>
            <p>  This field and its associated fields give details of the amount of cash received/paid to the depository any stock movements associated with the depository, reallowance amounts received by the bank from the depository for processing the Corporate Action etc.  In addition to this if the UPDATE.NOSTRO flag on the DIARY.TYPE record associated with the DIARY is set to YES then these fields will give details of the nostro account to which postings for the depository are made and the details of the entries of the postings made to the Nostro Account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INS.REINVEST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default instruction to be applied on the related ENTITLEMENT records.</p>
            <p>  This field is populated from the REINVEST field of the DEFAULT record of</p>
            <p>  the SC.ENT.INSTR file for the concerned security number.</p>
            <p>  It indicates if the cash income should be reinvested or not.</p>
            <p>  It can be amended or left blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid inputs are : Empty string, YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.SEC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Security Number of the New security to be allocated. This field is a sub-valued field so as to allow more than one security to be offered in response to holding in a particular security.</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if SECURITY.UPDATE field on the DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>  Entered value is validated against the SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input depending on the type of Corporate Action.</p>
            <p>  Must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>  Input can be a valid SECURITY.MASTER ID, a Security Mnemonic or a Security Alternative Index.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether the event is net (free) of charges. This field will dictate the way in which the foreign charges  tax on foreign charges affects the TOTAL.CASH field on the depositories. This flag does not in any way alter the amount due to the customer. Whether or not the foreign charges  tax on the foreign charges are to be deducted from the customer amount is decided by the RATE.TYPE field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of Y or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>  If the field is set to Y foreign charges  tax on foreign charges will be included in the TOTAL.CASH figure associated with the depository.</p>
            <p>  If the field is set to NO foreign charges  tax on foreign charges will not be included in the TOTAL.CASH field associated with the depository.</p>
            <p>  Will default to NO if no input is made.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the total amount of Cash payable to or receivable from the Depository identified in the associated DEP.NO field as a result of the corporate action. This is the amount in the Corporate Action currency and is the total of all the Entitlement records linked to the depository after any options have been taken.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This field is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EARLY.DEADLINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be updated from SC.PRE.DIARY and will hold the deadline date of the event.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rate at which the dividend/coupon is paying. Input allowed only if CASH field in DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>  The system will take this as a gross or net figure depending on the value of the RATE.TYPE field.</p>
            <p>  Should this particular dividend relate to a unit trust type security on which equalisation is granted, then this rate should be the all income gross rate. The breakdown of group2 and equalisation rates should be made in the GROUP2.RATE and EQUALISE.RATE fields respectively.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
				<p>Input to this field is not allowed when either EVENT.AMOUNT or EVENT.NOMINAL is present and viceversa</p>				
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input of 1-15 numeric characters in Standard T24 Amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT1.DEPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT1.DEPOT to OPT1.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 customer field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INS.RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default instruction to be applied on the related ENTITLEMENT records.</p>
            <p>  This field is populated from the RIGHT field of the DEFAULT record of</p>
            <p>  the SC.ENT.INSTR file for the concerned security number.</p>
            <p>  It indicates the action to be taken for RIGHTS processing.</p>
            <p>  It can be amended or left blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid inputs are : Empty string, BUY.MORE, SELL or TAKE.UP</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is related to TOT.SECURITY and shows the total number of the corresponding securities that have been debited from holdings as a result of this event.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.SECURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the SEDOL numbers of any security holdings that have changed as a result of the DIARY event which is being defined.</p>
            <p>  System updated field and enriched by Short Description of the Security from Security Master file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.RATIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field showing the number of old shares for the number of new shares entered in the next field to build up an new for old ratio.</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if SECURITY.UPDATE in DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>  Mandatory input if the associated NEW.SEC.NO has been entered otherwise input not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RP.TOT.CASH.XCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is automatically updated with the exchange rate used between the security currency and the local currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  No-input multi-valued field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional date field that can be before, after or equal to EX.DATE. The Record Date of a Corporate Event does not affect the beneficial entitlement to the event, but does affect the way the event is processed with regard to who will receive the outcome of an event directly and where the outcome is due to/from.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input of Standard T24 Date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the holdings nominal used for each option by the user.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRM.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether confirmation advices are generated when entitlements are created via this Diary record.</p>
            <p>  The value will be defaulted from the relevant DIARY.TYPE record.</p>
            <p>  The actual message types are determined via the relevant EB.ADVICES records, which will be either SC-0102-EVENT.TYPE, for entitlement creation or SC-0104-EVENT.TYPE, for entitlement reversal.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Input can be set to YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SRC.TAX.DEDUCTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field should be used to specify whether the Depository account should be debited with the Gross amount or the Gross amount less Source Tax. In the former case, the Source Tax will be shown as a separate accounting entry in the Depositoty account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Input.</p>
            <p>  Input can be YES, No or left Blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT2.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT2.DEPOT to OPT2.DEBIT form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Type of the Event this DIARY record is for. This event type must exist in DIARY.TYPE file. This field controls the input/update OR noinput/noupdate attributes of various fields of the DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory input of 1-15 alpha numeric characters.</p>
            <p>  Must be a valid DIARY.TYPE in DIARY.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT4.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT4.DEPOT to OPT4.DEBIT form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.TO.RIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used in conjunction with the OLD.RATIO field to produce the ratio with which Rights will be issued to a portfolio.</p>
            <p>  For example if a portfolio hold 900 of a particular security for which there is a rights issue then if:</p>
            <p>  OLD.RATIO = 3   OLD.TO.RIGHT = 1</p>
            <p>  Then the portfolio will receive 300 rights.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input only allowed for Diary records where the associated DIARY.TYPE record has the RIGHTS field set to Y.</p>
            <p>  Only numeric input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the DEP.NO field.</p>
            <p>  This field contains the Nostro Account field that will be updated with any postings for the depository if the UPDATE.NOSTRO field on the DIARY.TYPE record identified in the EVENT.TYPE is set to YES. The ID of the STMT.ENTRY and CATEG.ENTRY records will be contained in the associated STATEMENT.NOS field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This field will be automatically populated with the Nostro Account for the relevent currency.</p>
            <p>  Input is allowed and the account can be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPITAL.PORTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for information only. It allows the user to input the capital portion of the price paid for the new security.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input of 0-16 numeric characters in Standard T24 Amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INSTR.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the Start of Day process will apply default instructions to the ENTITLEMENT records</p>
            <p>  generated from the current DIARY.</p>
            <p>  This field is automatically populated from the parameters entered in the related DIARY.TYPE</p>
            <p>  record (fields DEF.INSTR.APPLY, DEF.NB.OF.DAYS, DEF.PRI.AFT and DEF.INSTR.SEL.DATE).</p>
            <p>  This field can be amended.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 Date format</p>
            <p>  The date must be greater than the DIA.AUTO.AUTH.DATE field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDEM.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will specify the redemption percentage upto which nominal will be redeemed based on trading units.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CASH.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the total amount of Cash payable to or receivable from the Depository identified in the associated DEP.NO field as a result of the corporate action.  This is the amount in the local currency of the system and is the local currency equivalent of the amount in the TOTAL.CASH field at the exchange rate input in the associated TOTAL.CASH.XCH field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This field is a NOINPUT field and updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOW.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the reallowance in local currency is held in this field and is calculated from the values in the fields REALLOW.AMT and REALLOW.XRATE. If one of these fields is modified then the contents of this field are updated automatically.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field, 19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>See PERCENTAGE field, this is a synonym field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate should represent the so called </p>
            <p>  The payments from this rate will be posted to the clients capital account if this process has been defined on the customers; SEC.ACC.MASTER (portfolio) accounts using the AC.DEF.SYS.CODE fields therein for the purpose of posting particular entry types to specific accounts. If not, then normal defaulting rules will be applied to locate an appropriate account.</p>
            <p>  Equalisation is a capital repayment and therefore not liable to taxation. However, the amount of equalisation must be deducted from the cost of the underlying security for Capital Gains Tax purposes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1 - 16 numeric characters</p>
            <p>  Input allowed only when EQUALISATION field on DIARY.TYPE record the DIARY is linked to is YES, in which case this field is mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Interest counter for this event. Applicable to shares only. Defaulted from the associated SECURITY.MASTER record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT3.DEPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT3.DEPOT to OPT3.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 customer field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The associated tax code for this event type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.HOLD.SETTLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>SEC.HOLD.SETTLE will be used to control whether stock will update the SC.SETTLEMENT application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  SEC.HOLD.SETTLE will allow input of #145;YES#146; or #145;NO#146; only.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the ACTUAL.SETTLEMENT field on the SC.PARAMETER record is #145;NO#146; then SEC.HOLD.SETTLE will be no-input field that will default to #145;NO#146;.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If DIARY transaction is authorised with SEC.HOLD.SETTLE field set to #145;YES#146; then the system will create a SC.SETTLEMENT record from the transaction.SC.SETTLEMENT         records will be created with an unauthorised status.The         stock settlement can be recorded using the NOM.RECD.DEL         field in SC.SETTLEMENT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the user has input #145;YES#146; in the SEC.HOLD.SETTLE field of a transaction and consequently is processing the stock nominal through actual settlement then the system         will update UNSETTLE.NOMINAL field on the SECURITY.POSITION         file with the nominal of the transaction when the SC.SETTLEMENT         record is created. Where the security position is being         added to (a purchase for example) this field will be         credited with the stock. Where the security position is         being debited (a sell for example) this field will be         debited with the nominal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAULT.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO flag controlling whether a VAULT.EXPECT record will be generated by the Corporate ACtion. Defaults to YES. If the Vault is switched off or the depository is not on VAULT.PARAMETER as being one that updates VAULT.CONTROL then no VAULT.EXPECT record will be produced even if this field has a value of YES.</p>
            <p>  Will be NO if no Securities are updated by the Corporate Action.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Allowed values are YES/NO only.  Mandatory input.  Defaulting dependant on the VAULT.PARAMETER file and the DIARY.TYPE record linked to the DIARY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The associated tax type for this event type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT2.DEPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT2.DEPOT to OPT2.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 customer field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT2.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT2.DEPOT to OPT2.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT4.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT4.DEPOT to OPT4.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT4.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT4.DEPOT to OPT4.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to allow a user to input which ADVICE.TYPE will be handed off to delivery for formatting.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Will default to one of the values 1, 2 or 3 depending on whether the Security is local and the value of the RATE.TYPE field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used by the system in the update of the STATEMENT.NO field.</p>
            <p>  As the STATEMENT.NO field is sub.valued and contain more than one set of entries - as there may be more than one depository - this field is used in the call to Accounting to hold the STMT.ENTRY and CATEG.ENTRY IDs used in the postings of the Nostro amount and Reallowance amount. The system automatically moves the contents of this field form this field to the relevent position in the STATEMENT.NOS field and is then cleared and therefore will normally be blank.</p>
            <p>  Technical note : this is done in the program SC.ENT.ACCOUNTING.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field, for internal system use only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AFC.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Coupon Reference Number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional Input of 8 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RP.TOT.CASH.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is automatically updated with the total cash amount to be debited from the Repo Nostro account in local currency.</p>
            <p>  The detail of this total can be viewed in the RP.ALT.NOSTRO record keyed on the DIARY id.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  No-input multi-valued field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for information only.</p>
            <p>  It allows the user to record is there are future payments for the new security to be made.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input of 0-16 numeric characters in Standard T24 format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOW.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate between the corporate action currency and the local currency of the system used to calculate the local equivalent of the reallowance amount entered into the REALLOW.AMT field.</p>
            <p>  This field is used in the calculation of the reallowance in local currency, and if modified will modify the value held in the field REALLOW.LCCY. It will default to the mid rate between the corporate action currency and the local currency of the system but can be changed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 rate field, 15 characters. Optional Input.</p>
            <p>  When the redemption currency is the local currency, input into this field will default to one.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A flag to indicate whether the Rate entered is in Percentage or not. Input allowed only if CASH field in DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>  If this field is set to Y then the figure in the associated CASH field is considered to be a percentage.</p>
            <p>  If this field is set to NO then the figure in the associated CASH field is considered to be an amount in the currency of the DIARY record.</p>
            <p>  Will default from the PRICE.TYPE record associated with the security input in the SECURITY.NO field of the DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of Y or NO is allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT1.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT1.DEPOT to OPT1.DEBIT form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT2.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT2.DEPOT to OPT2.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIA.AUTO.AUTH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the Start of Day process will automatically authorise the DIARY record.</p>
            <p>  This field is automatically populated from the parameters entered in the related DIARY.TYPE</p>
            <p>  record (fields DIA.AUTO.AUTHORISE, DIA.AUT.NB.OF.DAYS, DIA.AUT.PRI.AFT and</p>
            <p>  DIA.AUT.SEL.DATE).</p>
            <p>  This field can be amended.</p>
            <p>  The user will be prompted to bypass the date when authorising the DIARY record manually.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 Date format</p>
            <p>  The date must be at least the next working day</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAPSED.RIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields DEP.NO to RIGHTS.COST form a related multi value set. Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains any overrides that has been generated while authorising DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTITLEMENT.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>System updated field. This field indicates whether ENTITLEMENT records have been generated or not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT1.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPT1.DEPOT to OPT1.DEBIT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid entry on the SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION4</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RP.TOT.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is automatically updated with the security currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  No-input multi-valued field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A tax credit is defined as the difference between the gross dividend/interest amount declared and the net dividend/interest amount paid, or the withholding at source, regardless of how the dividend/interest is declared.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This new field is added to calculate the tax credit processing for stock movements. This field will be used to store the cash value  of the stock dividend for tax purposes. The validation on this field will be the same as that on the BOOK.COST field. No tax will be calculated if the TAX.PRICE field is null.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  optional input, Numeric field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>RETAIN.OPTION</field>
    <desc>
        <p>  When this field is set to YES those Entitlements in which option is chose will be retained on rerunning the corporate action service.</p>
        <p>  If the qualifying nominal is not changed and it is mandatory event then the newly created entitlement record will be defaulted with the nominal 

opted by the user.</p>
        <p>  If the qualifying nominal is changed and it is a mandatory event, then the freshly created entitlement will be updated with new qualifying 

nominal and the same will be defaulted in option nominal. </p>
		<p>  In the above 2 cases the entitlement will be created in INAU status.</p>
		<p>  If qualifying nominal is changed and partial option is chose then the entitlement will be generated in IHLD status without considering 

options elected by the user in this case user have to re-elect the options.</p>
		<p>  However if the qualifying nominal is not changed and partial option is opted then the newly created entitlement record will hold the 

options that were opted by the user and the record will be in INAU status.</p>
        <p>  Validation Rules</p>
        <p>  Allowed values are YES/Null only.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>CUT.OFF.TIME</field>
    <desc>
        <p>  An override will be raised if options are elected after the Cut off time associated with date in REPLY.BY.DATE field.</p>
        <p>  Validation Rules</p>
        <p>  This field accepts time in T24 standard time format.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>STP</field>
    <desc>
        <p>Holds value YES - This field is only for informatory purpose and will determine whether Diary caters to Full STP.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>LOAN</field>
    <desc>
        <p>Holds value YES - This field is only for informatory purpose and will determine whether Diary caters to lent position.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>FTT.TYPE</field>
    <desc>
        <p>Define the transaction type (DIARY.TYPE) for which FTT(Financial Transaction Tax) has to be applied</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>TOT.CASH.RECD</field>
    <desc>
        <p>This field will be updated with the amount in PSTA cash tag 19B of MT566 where there is no error encountered during processing the message MT566 and it is not a Cancellation message and and the diary does not cater to lent position.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>EVENT.NOMINAL</field>
    <desc>
        <p>Event nominal is used to record the qualifying holding as received from the issuer/counterparty.If this value is available,the same will be used to reconcile with qualifying holding calculated by the system.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Validation Rules:</p>
		<p>Input is allowed only if CASH field in DIARY.TYPE record is set to 'Y' and OPTION field in  DIARY.TYPE record is set to 'NO'.</p>
		<p>When RATE is input,value to this field is not allowed and vice-versa</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>EVENT.AMOUNT</field>
    <desc>
        <p>Event amount is used to input the pay-out amount (redemption, coupon, fractional cash and capital gains).The amount will be in event currency.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Validation Rules:</p>
		<p>Input is allowed only if CASH field in DIARY.TYPE record is set to 'Y' and OPTION field in  DIARY.TYPE record is set to 'NO'.</p>
		<p>When RATE is input,value to this field is not allowed and viceversa</p>
		<p>Input to this field is mandatory when EVENT.NOMINAL field has value</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
    <field>SYS.EVENT.NOMINAL</field>
    <desc>
        <p> This field will hold the sum of qualify holdings for all ex-dated positions.This field will be updated only if EVENT.AMOUNT is present.</p>
		<p></p>
		<p>Validation Rules:</p>
		<p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>		
		<p></p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

