<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>DIARY.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application will allow user to set up different types of events that will be included in the corporate actions/benefits processing suite of programs. In this application, for each event user can specify whether an event will simply pay cash, issue new securities, consist of a combination of both or allow the user to pick different options for a particular portfolio.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>AUTO.ENTITLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will control whether ENTITLEMENT records are automatically created when the DIARY is authorised. Valid input will be 'YES' or 'NO'. The default will be 'NO'.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid input are 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p> Default will be 'NO'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.NB.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with DEF.PRI.AFT and DEF.INSTR.SEL.DATE fields.</p>
            <p> It contains the number of days to be calculated prior or after the date contained in the DIARY field</p>
            <p> indicated in the DEF.INSTR.SEL.DATE.</p>
            <p> For example, the user may ask T24 to apply default instructions on the entitlement</p>
            <p> 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Numeric field (0 - 99)</p>
            <p> If 0 is entered the action will be done on the date (eg ON VALUE.DATE)</p>
            <p> Input allowed only if DEF.INSTR.APPLY is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>XT.PROCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of any identifiers used for this type of Corporate Action in any feeds used by the bank to automatically update the DIARY file.</p>
            <p> This will update a cross-reference file (XT.PROCESS.CONCAT) which can be used to convert the code of the fees to the ID of the corporate action as defined on the DIARY.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional input.</p>
            <p> Any input will udpdate the concat file XT.PROCESS.CONCAT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.TYPE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID for the DIARY.TYPE record. This should identify the Corporate Action to the bank. Examples are CASH.DIVIDEND, BOND.REDEMPTION, RIGHTS.ISSUE, etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Free format text identifying the DIARY.TYPE.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.PRI.AFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with DEF.NB.OF.DAYS and DEF.INSTR.SEL.DATE fields.</p>
            <p> It indicate if the default instruction will be applied n days PRIOR or AFTER the date entered in the</p>
            <p> DIARY field contained in the DEF.INSTR.SEL.DATE field.</p>
            <p> For example, the user may ask T24 to apply default instructions on the entitlement</p>
            <p> 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only 'PRIOR' or 'AFTER' allowed</p>
            <p> Input allowed if the DEF.INSTR.APPLY field is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Category Code to be used for the posting of exchange Profit &amp; Loss entries.</p>
            <p> This code classifies Profit &amp; Loss and product types.</p>
            <p> Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category Code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input of 4 or 5 numeric characters.</p>
            <p> Must be in range of 50-000 to 59-999.</p>
            <p> Must exist as a valid CATEGORY Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.CHGES.CR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Credit type Transaction code to be used while processing ENTITLEMENT records which has Foreign charges attahced to it.</p>
            <p> If a Category is entered into this field then the fields FGN.CHGES.CAT, DP.FOR.CATEGORY and DP.FOR.CR.CODE must be populated as well.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input of 1-3 numeric characters.</p>
            <p> Must exist as a valid transaction code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.CAT.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the category on which the stamp tax amount in charge of the bank will be posted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid CATEGORS record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.NOSTRO</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO field controlling whether or not the system will directly update the nostro account for the depository side accounting entries or only the suspense account identified in the SUSPENSE.ACCOUNT field.</p>
            <p> If this field is YES then the Nostro Account will be updated.</p>
            <p> If this field is NO then the Suspense Account will be updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p> Will default to YES.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
            <p> Once the DIARY.TYPE record has been authorised then this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIA.AUT.NB.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with DIA.AUT.PRI.AFT and DIA.AUT.SEL.DATE fields. It contains the number of days to be calculated PRIOR or AFTER the date contained in the DIARY field indicated in the DIA.AUT.SEL.DATE. For example, the user may ask T24 to authorise the DIARY record 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.  <p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Numeric field (0 - 99)</p>
            <p> If 0 is entered the action will be done on the date (eg ON VALUE.DATE)</p>
            <p> Input allowed only if DIA.AUTO.AUTHORISE is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERDUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date the number of Overdue days will be measured from.</p>
            <p> Possible inputs allowed are :</p>
            <p> (i) PAY.DATE   (ii) EX.DATE  (iii) REPLY.BY.DATE   (iv) VALUE.DATE</p>
            <p> Defaults to PAY.DATE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOM.ROUNDING.METHD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to specify the rounding rule to be used in the nominal calculation for the redenomination of the security. The field will be used in conjunction with the old and new trading units on the old and new securities. The possible values in the field are 'UP' for rounding up ; 'DN' for rounding down ; 'LG' for a legal rounding mechanism ; 'LOT' for LOT Rounding ; &amp;#8216;DEC&amp;#8217; for the Odd Lots consolidation.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid values are 'UP'; 'DN';'LG'; 'LOT'; &amp;#8216;DEC&amp;#8217;.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> The &amp;#8216;DEC&amp;#8217; option can only be used with &amp;#8216;FRACTION&amp;#8217; in the ROUNDING field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.PL.DB</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the transaciton code which will be used for credit transactions arising from reallowance processing in the DIARY application.</p>
            <p> This field should only be input if the bank using T24 will be receiving reallowance fees for processing corporate actions for the depositories where the stock is held.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional field.</p>
            <p> Any input must exist on the TRANSACTION file as a debit transaction</p>
            <p> If the REALLOWANCE.PL.CAT or REALLOWANCE.PL.CR fields have been entered then this field will become mandatory.</p>
            <p> Input only allowed if UPDATE.NOSTRO field is set to 'YES'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUM.MARKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the transaction indicators that will be used on transactions that have occurred after the corporate action Ex date but have been traded 'cum'.</p>
            <p> Input is only valid if the application SM.PARAMETER has field PRICE.QUAL.FORMAT set to SWIFT and the list of valid input will be set in CUM.INDICATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> As specified in SM.PARAMETER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COPY.ISIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether or not the old ISIN on the security being redenominated needs to be carried across to the new security.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Input only allowed if the 'EURO' module has been installed.</p>
            <p> Valid values are 'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of the default Commission Type to be used while processing DIARY records. Must exist in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
            <p> This is the default FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record to be used if the system cannot find a commission code from the SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION record linked to the portfolio (customer portfolios only).</p>
            <p> Note : in the SEC.TYPE field of SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION commission can be        set-up at DIARY.TYPE level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 11 characters alphanumeric input.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SBL.DIV.PROC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will indicate if SBL process is activated or not.Input of either YES or NO is allowed. Default value of NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.CREATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will control the level at which a DIARY record will be created for this type of corporate action. Valid input into this field will be 'AUT', 'NAU' or 'HLD' - meaning authorised, unauthorised and hold respectively.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid input in this field will be 'AUT', 'NAU' or 'HLD'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRM.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether confirmation advices are generated when Entitlements relating to this Diary type are authorised.</p>
            <p> See help for ADVICE and PRE.ADVICE.REQ for a more detailed description of delivery types.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be set to YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.CAEV</field>
<desc>
            <p>The SWIFT corporate action event indicator - optional input.</p>
            <p> Used in the production of swift advices</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Four character Alphanumeric.</p>
            <p> Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DERIVATIVES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This flag indicates whether or not the DIARY.TYPE record is to be used in the Derivatives (DX) module for processing of Corporate Actions against futures or options with underlying securities.  DIARY.TYPE records cannot be used within DX Corporate Actions without this flag set to 'Yes'.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Yes/No field. Not mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AM.CAPTURE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the date on which the event should be updated. The options are :</p>
            <p> 1. BK.DATE - The event is updated as of the Booking date . The day on which the event is authorised.</p>
            <p> 2. EX.DATE - The event is updated as of the EX.DATE .</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard Alphanumeric field</p>
            <p> Valid values are BK.DATE , EX.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.CR.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used to signify which type of transaction is being posted, for exchange profits.</p>
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the transaction code numbers with the application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each application.</p>
            <p> The following range has been assigned within T24 to Securities Application : 600 to 649</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input of 1-3 numeric characters.</p>
            <p> Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.TRANS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any valid SC.TRANS.TYPE is allowed.This id will be used in all transaction processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ADJ.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the category to which source tax adjustments will be posted from the ENTITLEMENT record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.SUSP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies category of the suspense  account to be updated  with the</p>
            <p> amount available for reinvestment corporate action ,</p>
            <p> till the price is known.</p>
            <p> Becomes mandatory field when DRIPS field is set to YES.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Must exist on the Category file.</p>
            <p> An internal account in the local currency must be set-up for this</p>
            <p> category.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input if DRIPS is set to YES.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.CALC.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Routine name that will be invoked from SC.STAMP.CALC.CORPORATE.ACTIONS to calculate the amount on which the stamp tax will be taken.</p>
            <p> If no routine is indicated here then the stamp tax will be based on the ENTITLEMENT.AMT field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> User defined routine. The name must be formated as       "SC.STAMP.BASE.AMT." followed by the DIARY.TYPE key.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether any securities will be issued by the diary event which it is being defined.</p>
            <p> If this field is set to 'Y' then the Corporate Actions being defined in the DIARY.TYPE record is a Rights type Corporate Action. That is holding a particular security on the Ex Div Date will result in the portfolio being credited with a number of tradable items which can then be bought or sold up to the Pay Date of the Event. On the Pay Date of the Event the Rights will be converted to another security - usually at a fixed cost per right.</p>
            <p> If this field is set to 'Y' then for the duration of the event (between ex-div date and pay date) any SEC.TRADE or SECURITY.TRANFER done by a portfolio in the Rights stock will be recorded on the ENTITLEMENT record in the SEC.TRADE.ID, BUY.NUMBER and SELL.NUMBER fields and the amount of stock movement will be taken into account when the final Rights holding is converted on pay date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are 'Y'ES/'N'O only.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUM.TIME.SCALE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will indicates the number of days after the Ex date for which transaction indicators will be checked to see if they have been traded 'cum'.</p>
            <p> NB the number of days specified includes the "ex" date</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> A number followed by either C or W to indicate either calendar or working     days respectively.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.SECURITIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether any free securities are offered by the diary event which is being defined.</p>
            <p> If this field is set to 'NO' and there are securites credited to the portfolio then T24 will assume there is a price associated with them.</p>
            <p> For example this should be set to 'Y' for a Bonus or a Stock Dividend Corporate Action and 'N' for a Call Payment or Warrant Conversion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are 'Y'ES/'N'O only.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAXABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the DIARY.TYPE as one that is subject to tax or not.</p>
            <p> If this field is set to 'YES' then the Entitlement records created for this DIARY.TYPE will be subject to tax on any cash credits.</p>
            <p> If it is 'NO' then the Entitlement records will not be subject to Tax.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
            <p> Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether multiple options are offered to portfolios as a result of the event which is being defined.</p>
            <p> If this field is set to 'Y' then ENTITLEMENT records will always be created on hold and the user will have to indicate which option the particular portfolio is going to take before the system will allow validation of the ENTITLEMENT record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are 'Y'ES/'N'O only.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIA.AUT.SEL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with DIA.AUT.NB.OF.DAYS and DIA.AUT.PRI.AFT fields. It contains the field name of DIARY that contains the date on which the system will authorise the DIARY record. For example, the user may ask T24 to authorise the DIARY record 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.  <p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only Input of 'EX.DATE', 'PAY.DATE', 'VALUE.DATE' or 'REPLY.BY.DATE' allowed.</p>
            <p> Input allowed only if DIA.AUTO.AUTHORISE is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.REMAIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO field controlling whether the system will automatically assign any unused entitlement to the cash option of this type of Corporate Action.</p>
            <p> For some types of multiple option corporate actions (such as a SCRIP Dividend) there will be one - or more - options where the portfolio receives securities and an equivalent cash option.  If this flag is set to YES then the user can select the option they require and any unused holdings (due to the terms of the offer, rounding etc.) will automatically be used for the cash equivalent. If this field is NO then selecting a particular option will cause the system to use all the holdings on that option, even if there may some part of the holding unused.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Only YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p> Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether cash is payable on type of the DIARY event which is being defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are 'Y'ES/'N'O only.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.POSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the Security Position is to be blocked by execution of a corporate action of this type.</p>
            <p> If a position is to be blocked it can be blocked either at authorisation of the DIARY record, i.e. when the unauthorised entitlements are created, or when the ENTITLEMENT is authorised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional input</p>
            <p> Possible values DIARY or ENTITLEMENT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.TYPES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued numeric field to allow a user to input which ADVICE.TYPES are allowed to be input into the ADVICE.TYPE field on the DIARY applcication. This field is designed to be fed through to delivery to aid the formatting of advices.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Will default 1, 2 and 3.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.PL.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the transaciton code which will be used for credit transactions arising from reallowance processing in the DIARY application.</p>
            <p> This field should only be input if the bank using T24 will be receiving reallowance fees for processing corporate actions for the depositories where the stock is held.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional field.</p>
            <p> Any input must exist on the TRANSACTION file as a credit transaction</p>
            <p> If the REALLOWANCE.PL.CAT or REALLOWANCE.PL.DB fields have been entered then this field will become mandatory.</p>
            <p> Input only allowed if UPDATE.NOSTRO field is set to 'YES'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DP.FOR.DR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction code for all foreign charges debited to a Depository within a Corporate Action transaction.</p>
            <p> If a Transaction code is entered into this field then the fields FGN.CHGES.CR.CODE, DP.FOR.CATEGORY and FGN.CHGES.CAT must be populated as well.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional field.</p>
            <p> Any input must exist on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIA.AUTO.AUTHORISE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicate if T24 will automatically authorise DIARY records generated with this DIARY.TYPE.</p>
            <p> The authorisation will be made during the Batch on the specified date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Default value is 'NO'</p>
            <p> Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOW.SHORT.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to process the Corporate Events on Short/Zero Positions or Not.</p>
            <p> Zero positions will be processed only when either an outstanding debit/credit transaction or a settled non-returned stock borrow/lend done via REPO exists.</p>
            <p> This field can be set to YES only if ACTUAL.SETTLEMENT is YES and SETTLE.METHOD is US in SC.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid values are YES, NO or NULL only.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.ADVICE.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether pre confirmation advices are required by default for this diary type.</p>
            <p> The default value will be used to update DIARY and ENTITLEMENT records created for this diary type.</p>
            <p> The default values can be modified at the DIARY and ENTILEMENT level.</p>
            <p> A value of YES will result in a pre confirmation advice being sent for each entitlement record as it is created either on hold or as an unauthorised record.</p>
            <p> The activity code for a pre confirmation advice as defined on EB.ACTIVITY is SC-0100.</p>
            <p> If the unauthorised record is subsequently amended or deleted then a pre confirmation amendment advice will be generated, with activity code SC-0101.</p>
            <p> The data handed of to the delivery module, which can be used to produce customised advices, is as follows</p>
            <p> Record1 - Corresponds to the DE.MESSAGE record 1500</p>
            <p> Record2 - the ENTITLEMENT record</p>
            <p> Record3 - the DIARY record</p>
            <p> Record4 - the SEC.ACC.MASTER record</p>
            <p> Record5 - the SECURITY.MASTER Master record</p>
            <p> Record6 to Record9 blank.</p>
            <p> Record9 can be updated via a user-developed routine as defined in USER.ROUTINE on the relevant EB.ADVICES record.</p>
            <p> N.B. field 3 of record 8 will contain the PRINT.FORMAT value of the relevant EB.ADVICES record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be set to YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.OR.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field should be used to specify , whether the system should post any unused</p>
            <p> entitlement amount of this type of Corporate Action to the customer or to the Bank.</p>
            <p />
            <p> To specify which, you should enter either "B", indicating Bank, or "C", indicating customer.</p>
            <p />
            <p> This field defaults to CUSTOMER if CASH.REMIAN is set to 'Y'ES.</p>
            <p />
            <p> _____________________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p> (1) Becomes mandatory field when CASH.REAMIN is set to 'Y'ES  but will default to CUSTOMER.</p>
            <p> (2) Only BANK or CUSTOMER allowed.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will control whether or not this corporate action requires Equalisation processing.</p>
            <p> Equalisation is the accrued income included in the price of units purchased during the distribution period which is refunded as part of a unitholder's first distribution on those units. The accrued income is averaged over the distribution period, resulting in the same rate of distribution (including equalisation) on all units. Equalisation is, therefore, a capital repayment and is not liable to Income Tax and must be deducted from the cost of the units for Capital Gains Tax purposes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional</p>
            <p> Only input of YES or No are allowed</p>
            <p> Default to NO</p>
            <p> Can be YES only when the following fields are set as follows :-</p>
            <p> RIGHTS is not Y</p>
            <p> OPTIONS is not Y</p>
            <p> REINVEST is not Y</p>
            <p> SECURITY.UPDATE is not Y</p>
            <p> CASH is Y</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.BOND</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the Security which is being processed is of type 'BOND' then the Transaction Type to be used for ENTITLEMENT records processing should be entered in this field. Entered value must exist in SC.TRANS.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input of 1-3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISATION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used to enable the defaulting of a different account to which to post the capital portion of the Equalisation amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1 - 3 type S ( uppercase alpha or numeric characters )</p>
            <p> Optional</p>
            <p> Must exist on SC.TRANS.TYPE file</p>
            <p> Input allowed only when EQUALISATION is YES</p>
            <p> If EQUALISATION is YES and no input is made into this field, default from TRANSACTION.TYPE field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EOD.DEF.ACT.SETT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Will determine if actual setting is to be used for either the cash, the stock or both elements of the corporate action type on the automatically generated DIARY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEMERGE.BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>For some Demergers or Spin Offs the original holding is retained but the cost of the original position is apportioned across the resulting securities (including the original holding which will have its cost of position reduced) according to the market value of each resultant holding at the time of the authorisation of the ENTITLEMENT record. If this type of book cost apportionment is required the this field should be set to 'YES'.</p>
            <p> Note : If this field is set to 'YES' then the original holding will be removed at its original cost and re-applied at the new calculated cost.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed.</p>
            <p> Will default to 'NO'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>New field that will control the level at which the ROUNDING takes place. This will be an optional field. Valid input will be 'CUSTOMER', 'DEPOSITORY'. The default will be 'CUSTOMER'.</p>
            <p> At the 'DEPOSITORY' level, the rounding can be 'STANDARD' or 'DOWN'. The 'STANDARD' option means a standard adjustment. The 'DOWN' option allows pro-rating the unallocated securities and cash remaining to customers with fractions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid inputs are 'CUSTOMER' or 'DEPOSITORY'</p>
            <p> Default will be 'CUSTOMER'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.MARKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the transaction indicators that will be used on transactions that have occurred before the corporate action Ex date but have been traded 'ex'.</p>
            <p> Input is only valid if the application SM.PARAMETER has field PRICE.QUAL.FORMAT set to SWIFT and the list of valid input will be set in CUM.INDICATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> As specified in SM.PARAMETER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DP.FOR.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default category code for all foreign charges payable/chargeable by the Depository involved in this corporate action.</p>
            <p> If a Category is entered into this field then the fields FGN.CHGES.CR.CODE, FGN.CHGES.CAT and DP.FOR.CR.CODE must be populated as well.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional field.</p>
            <p> Any input must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p> Any input must be in the range 50000 - 59999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.AUT.PRI.AFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with ENT.AUTH.NB.OF.DAY and AUT.AUTH.SEL.DATE fields. It indicate if ENTITLEMENT records generated with this DIARY.TYPE will be authorised n days PRIOR or AFTER the date entered in the DIARY field contained in the ENT.AUT.SEL.DATE field. For example, the user may ask T24 to authorise the entitlement 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.  <p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only 'PRIOR' or 'AFTER' allowed</p>
            <p> Input allowed if the ENT.AUTO.AUTHORISE field is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FACTOR.PAYMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to specify whether or not for bonds with factors an extra payment needs to be made to the customer for a factor change. The field can be set to 'Y' in the case of Mortgage Backed Securities where a decreasing factor will be paid out to the customer as an extra payment. If this action coincides with the coupon payment which will be the case in most cases the system will raise two separate accounting entries for the customer and a single entry for the depository.</p>
            <p> This field has no default setting and if an existing record is amended then the input will be required. In this case NO should be used as this is functionally equivalent to the existing setting of blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory Input</p>
            <p> Valid values in the field are 'Y' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AM.INCOME.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether this event is an income type event or not. If it is an income type event , then this field is set toYES, otherwise it is set to NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard Alphanumenric field</p>
            <p> Valid values are YES and NO.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.CHG.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax field that allows the specification of the TAX code of TAX.TYPE.CONDITION code used by the Corporate Action in the calculation of Tax on Foreign Fees. If no input is made into this field then no tax on foreign fees will be calculated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional input.</p>
            <p> Any input must exist on the TAX file or be a valid TAX.TYPE.CONDITION entry.</p>
            <p> If a TAX.TYPE.CONDITION entry is input then the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION ID must be preceded by an '*'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>New optional field that controls whether forward entries will be created by this corporate actions or not. Valid input will be 'YES' or 'NO'. If this field contains 'YES' it cannot be changed to 'NO' or null.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid input are 'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
            <p> If this field contains 'YES' it cannot be changed to 'NO' or null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.MIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the stamp tax amount in LCCY in charge of the bank.</p>
            <p> For example if 3.00 is entered here then all amount of 3.00 or less will not be charged to the customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Amount formatted in LCCY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the DIARY.TYPE record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 35 alphanumeric characters (supporting multi language).  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERIFY.REQUIRED</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO field used to control whether this type of Corporate Action needs to be verified.</p>
            <p> Only input of YES or No is allowed with the field defaulting to NO.</p>
            <p> If this field is set to YES then any ENTITLEMENT record created for this type of Corporate Action will need to be accessed with the 'V' (Verify) function before input is allowed.</p>
            <p> If it is NO then the Entitlement records can be Input or Authorised directly depending on whether the Entitlement record concerned has enough information to have an INAU or IHLD status.</p>
            <p> All the Entitlement records created by a single Diary record can verified together using the application SC.ENT.VERIFY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p> Will default to NO.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.AUT.NB.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with ENT.AUT.PRI.AFT and ENT.AUT.SEL.DATE fields. It contains the number of days to be calculated PRIOR or AFTER the date contained in the DIARY field indicated in the ENT.AUT.SEL.DATE. For example, the user may ask T24 to authorise the entitlement 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Numeric field (0 - 99)</p>
            <p> If 0 is entered the action will be done on the date (eg ON VALUE.DATE)</p>
            <p> Input allowed only if ENT.AUTO.AUTHORISE is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDENOMINATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to define whether this type of corporate action is a fixed currency rate stock conversion. If this field is set to 'YES' then this corporate action indicates security redenomination in which case the new security must be created if it does not already exist.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Input only allowed if 'EURO' module installed.</p>
            <p> Valid input values are 'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DENOM.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will control the way in which the conversion is done. If this field has been set to 'UNIT' then the system will convert the minimum trading unit first and the round the resulting figure. The resulting rounded figure will be used in calculating the new nominal figure.</p>
            <p> If the field has been set to nulls or 'HOLDING' the conversion will be done on the nominal figure and the resulting nominal figure will be rounded.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Valid values are 'UNIT' or 'HOLDING'</p>
            <p> Optional input.</p>
            <p> If no input then the 'HOLDING' method is chosen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.CHGES.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category Code to be used while processing ENTITLEMENT records which has Foreign Charges attached to the deal.</p>
            <p> If a Category is entered into this field then the fields FGN.CHGES.CR.CODE, DP.FOR.CATEGORY and DP.FOR.CR.CODE must be populated as well.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional input of 4 or 5 numeric characters.</p>
            <p> Must be in range of 50-000 to 59-999.</p>
            <p> Must exist as a valid CATEGORY Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUE.DIV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows accruing the dividends in the NET.ACCRUED.DIV and ORIG.ACCR.DIV fields of SC.POS.ASSET file. The process can be done at the company level also.</p>
            <p> If the dividends are accrued in the SC.POS.ASSET fields, the ENTITLEMENT value is reflected in the valuations for the period between Ex Date and Payment (or value) Date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Input field</p>
            <p> Values authorized are 'YES', 'NO' or Null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCUM.INCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate Accumulation unit functionality is to be used or not. Validation has been done such that when ACCUM.INCOME field is set to Y the following fields must have the given values.</p>
            <p> CASH must be set to "Yes"</p>
            <p> SECURITY.UPDATE must be set to "No"</p>
            <p> NEW.SECURITIES must be set to "No"</p>
            <p> OPTIONS must be set to "No"</p>
            <p> REINVEST must be set to "No"</p>
            <p> RIGHTS must be set to "No"</p>
            <p> FREE.SECURITIES must be set to "No"</p>
            <p> RETAIN.ORIGINAL must be set to "Yes"</p>
            <p> DEMERGE.BOOK.COST must be set to "No"</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Valid options Y/N</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The information previously stored in this field has been transferred to the PRINT.FORMAT field of the relevant EB.ADVICES records.</p>
            <p> Multi-valued field associated with the ADVICE field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is now NO INPUT, with the data transferred to the MESSAGE.TYPE field of EB.ADVICES.</p>
            <p> The EB.ADVICES record is created as follows:</p>
            <p> Record key composed of Activity Code-DIARY.TYPE.ID</p>
            <p> Where Activity Code is one of the following</p>
            <p> SC-0102 - Confirmation</p>
            <p> SC-0103 - Entitlement Reversal</p>
            <p> SC-0104 - Diary Reversal</p>
            <p> The following additional EB.ADVICE records can also be created manually for pre confirmation advices</p>
            <p> SC-0100 - Confirmation Pre Advice (unauthorised entitlement creation)</p>
            <p> SC-0101 - Confirmation Pre Advice amendment (unauthorised entitlement amendment)</p>
            <p> The message type information will be transferred to the MESSAGE.TYPE field and the ADVICE.FORMAT information will be transferred to the PRINT.FORMAT field.</p>
            <p> If existing message types are set up the delivery process will function as now.</p>
            <p> Currently the following specific confirmation message types are supported by Corporate Actions:</p>
            <p> 1505 - Dividend Tax Certificate 1510 - Capital Increase Advice 1520 - New Issue Advice 1530 - Coupon /Dividend Advice 1540 - Stock Dividend Advice 1560 - Redemption Advice</p>
            <p> Additionally if new message types are required SOFT DELIVERY processing will be invoked as described in the DELIVERY section of the T24 user guide.</p>
            <p> The information handed off to delivery for new message types will be as follows</p>
            <p> Record 1 equates to data defined in DE.MESSAGE 1500, Corporate action generic message</p>
            <p> Record 2 comprises the Entitlement record.</p>
            <p> Record 3 comprises the Diary record.</p>
            <p> Record 4 comprises the Security Account Master record.</p>
            <p> Record 5 comprises the Security Master record.</p>
            <p> Associated with the ADVICE.FORMAT field to define a particular message and message format. For example if this field contained 1560 and the ADVICE.FORMAT field associated with it contained 3 then for a French speaking customer the DE.FORMAT.PRINT record used would be 1560.3.1.FR.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-4 numeric characters. No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Category Code to be used for the posting of any unused</p>
            <p> entitlement amount as profit to the  Bank.</p>
            <p> Input allowed only when CUST.OR.BANK is set to BANK.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input if CUST.OR.BANK is set to BANK.</p>
            <p> Must be in range of 50-000 to 59-999.</p>
            <p> Must exist as a valid CATEGORY Code.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSPENSE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Mandatory field allowing the user to input the category of the suspense account to be updated with postings for the depository side of accounting entries generated by this corporate action.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Must exist on the Category file.</p>
            <p> An internal account in the local currency must be set-up for this category.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.AUT.SEL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with ENT.AUT.NB.OF.DAYS and ENT.AUT.PRI.AFT fields. It contains the field name of DIARY that contains the date on which the system will authorise the ENTITLEMENT records For example, the user may ask T24 to authorise the entitlement 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only Input of 'EX.DATE', 'PAY.DATE', 'VALUE.DATE' or 'REPLY.BY.DATE' allowed.</p>
            <p> Input allowed only if ENT.AUTO.AUTHORISE is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIA.AUT.PRI.AFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with DIA.AUT.NB.OF.DAYS and DIA.AUT.SEL.DATE fields. It indicate if the authorisation of the DIARY will be made n days PRIOR or AFTER the date entered in the DIARY field contained in the DIA.AUT.SEL.DATE field. For example, the user may ask T24 to authorise the DIARY 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only 'PRIOR' or 'AFTER' allowed</p>
            <p> Input allowed if the DIA.AUTO.AUTHORISE field is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction Type to be used while processing DIARY records which issues New Securities,</p>
            <p> OR</p>
            <p> updates Security holdings.</p>
            <p> Must exist in SC.TRANS.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input of 1-3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.TIME.SCALE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will indicates the number of days before the Ex date for which transaction indicators that will be checked to see if they have been traded 'ex'.</p>
            <p> NB the number of days specified excludes the "ex" date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> A number followed by either C or W to indicate either calendar or working     days respectively.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.FWD</field>
<desc>
            <p>New field that controls how many working days before the value date forward entries for the corporate action will be produced. If the FWD.ACCT field is not ''YES' then this field will be a no-input field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Rule 1</p>
            <p> Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.OPT.EVT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows for entry in DIARY, in field OPT.EVENT.TYPE, of valid DIARY.TYPE keys associated with each option within the DIARY. These values are then used for capital gains purposes to treat each option according to different capital gains rules.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input, either Y or N.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.SHARE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the Security being processed is of type 'SHARE' then the Transaction Type to be used while processing ENTITLEMENT records should be entered in this field. Entered value must exist in SC.TRANS.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input of 1-3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AM.FLOW.IMPACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the flow generated by this event . The various types of flows are :</p>
            <p> 1. WCF  - This stands for weighted Cash flow . This Cash flow is defined in the transaction as Z type flow. This flow is used for adjusting the average invested capital.</p>
            <p> 2. NCF - This stands for Net Cash flow. This Cash flow is defined in the transaction as an 'S' type flow . This represents a Silent flow.</p>
            <p> 3. NONE - This is a NON CASH flow . The cash flow field is not updated for this type of an event.</p>
            <p> 4. BOTH - This type of event is a normal cashflow , that is it is defined as 'Y' type flow in the TRANSACTION.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard Alphanumeric Field</p>
            <p> Valid Values are NCF, WCF, NONE and BOTH</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INSTR.SEL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must be used in combination with DEF.NB.OF.DAYS and DEF.PRI.AFT fields.</p>
            <p> It contains the field name of DIARY that contains the date on which the system will apply</p>
            <p> the default instructions.</p>
            <p> For example, the user may ask T24 to apply default instructions on the entitlement</p>
            <p> 3 days PRIOR the VALUE.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only Input of 'EX.DATE', 'PAY.DATE', 'VALUE.DATE' or 'REPLY.BY.DATE' allowed.</p>
            <p> Input allowed only if DEF.INSTR.APPLY is set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTAL.DISTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows processing either the Capital Instalment or the Capital distribution event type.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> This functionality is allowed if the CASH and RETAIN.NOMINAL options are set to YES and the other ones are set to NO. The TAXABLE field should be also set to NO.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> This functionality is not available in case of accumulation income.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> If this field is set to DISTRIBUTION then the cash to be distributed will be credited to the customer account at the authorization of ENTITLEMENT. The cost of positions in SECURITY.POSITION and SC.POS.ASSET will be reduced.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> If this field is set to INSTALMENT then the cash to be paid will be debited from the customer account at the authorization of ENTITLEMENT. The cost of position in SECURITY.POSITION and SC.POS.ASSET will be increased.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 2 options are allowed: DISTRIBUTION or INSTALMENT</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Null is the default value.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.AUTO.AUTHORISE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicate if the ENTITLEMENTS generated with this DIARY.TYPE will be automatically</p>
            <p> authorised or not.</p>
            <p> NO : No automatic authorisation will be done</p>
            <p> YES : Automatic authorisation will be done at the date specified in the DIARY record.</p>
            <p> This date will be calculated from the parameters entered in fields ENT.AUT.NB.OF.DAYS,</p>
            <p> ENT.AUT.PRI.AFT and ENT.AUT.SEL.DATE.</p>
            <p> ONLINE : The automatic authorisation of ENTITLEMENTs will be done upon DIARY's authorisation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Default value is 'NO'</p>
            <p> Only input of 'YES' ,'NO' or 'ONLINE' allowed</p>
            <p> Input of 'ONLINE' only allowed when ACTUAL.SETTLEMENT field of SC.PARAMETER is set to 'YES'</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the profit and loss category to which reallowance entries will be posted from the DIARY application.</p>
            <p> This field should only be input if the bank using T24 will be receiving reallowance fees for processing corporate actions for the depositories where the stock is held.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Optional field.</p>
            <p> Any input must be a valid profit and loss Category (in the range 50000 - 59999).</p>
            <p> 5 Numeric characters.</p>
            <p> If the REALLOWANCE.PL.CR or REALLOWANCE.PL.DB fields have been input this field will become mandatory.</p>
            <p> Input only allowed if the UPDATE.NOSTRO field is set to 'YES'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.CONTROL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the Dividend control Account category.Any valid Internal category from 10000 to 19999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether there can be a change in the Security holdings of the portfolios as a result of the diary event which is being defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are 'Y'ES/'N'O only.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether any cash offered can be reinvested in the original security.</p>
            <p> This flag should be set to 'Y' if the Corporate Action being defined is a re-investment corporate action. That is one where the dividend (or coupon) received from the holding of a particular security is reinvested in that security. The resultant ENTITLEMENT records will calculate the amount to be received by the portfolio and the number of securities that can be purchased with that amount of cash at the current market price of the security from the SECURITY.MASTER record that defines the security.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are 'Y'ES/'N'O only.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.SECURITIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether the new securities offered by the diary event which is being defined can be different from the originating security.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are 'Y'ES/'N'O only.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETAIN.ORIGINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate whether the portfolios retain their original holding once the diary event which is being defined executed.</p>
            <p> If this flag is set to 'NO' then the original holding will be backed out as a result of the Corporate Action, for example a Bond Redemption should set this flag to 'NO'. If a partial removal of the original holding is required (i.e. in a partial redemption) the RETAIN.NOMINAL field on the ENTITLEMENT application should be used in indicate that part of the holding unaffected by the Corporate Action.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are 'Y'ES/'N'O only.  Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key of the SC.REINVEST.PARAM file.</p>
            <p> This will indicate to T24 that any cash payment that will be done using the current DIARY.TYPE will be</p>
            <p> reinvested. The related record of SC.REINVEST.PARAM file contains the informations to be used to generate</p>
            <p> the SEC.TRADE.</p>
            <p> In that case, no default instructions can be setup for this DIARY.TYPE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid key of the SC.REINVEST.PARAM file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.DB.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Transaction Code used to signify which type of transaction is being posted, for exchange losses.</p>
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the transaction code numbers with the application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each application.</p>
            <p> The following range has been assigned within T24 TO Securities application : 600 - 649</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input of 1-3 numeric characters.</p>
            <p> Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field was previously called ROUND.DOWN.ONLY. The name will be changed to ROUNDING. Originally it only allowed input of 'YES' or 'NO'. This will be chaged to allow the following input: 'DOWN', 'UP', 'STANDARD' and 'FRACTION'. The default will be 'STANDARD'</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Only following input allowed: 'DOWN', 'UP', 'STANDARD' and 'FRACTION'.</p>
            <p> Default will be 'Standard'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INSTR.APPLY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicate if Default Instructions will be applied on the ENTITLEMENTS generated with this DIARY.TYPE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Default value is 'NO'</p>
            <p> Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERDUE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of Days after the date in the OVERDUE.DATE field after which this type of Corporate Action would be overdue.</p>
            <p> This field in conjunction with the OVERDUE.DATE field can be used to report ENTITLEMENT records that are still unauthorised after the 'overdue' date for the event. The enquiry OVERDUE.EVENTS can be used as an example enquiry for reporting overdue events.</p>
            <p> If for example this field contained 5 and the OVERDUE.DATE field contained VALUE.DATE then if an ENTITLEMENT record value dated 21st March 1996 was still unauthorised after the 26th March then it would be considered overdue.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Numeric and mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRIPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field distinguish DRIP event from other types of corporate events.</p>
            <p> Can to be set to YES if REINVEST flag is set to YES.</p>
            <p> This field is only used to authorise diary without reinvestment price.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are YES or NO only.</p>
            <p> Default NO.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOLERANCE.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tolerance category should be in the range of 10000-19999.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>If either tolerance percentage or currency or amount is input then this field becomes mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOLERANCE.PCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tolerance allowed for corporate action events is defined in terms of Percentage.</p>
            <p>If this field is defined then input to the field tolerance currency and amount should not be allowed and vice versa.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOLERANCE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields Tolerance.Ccy and Tolerance.Amt are associative multi value set.</p>
            <p>If the field is blank and tolerance amount is specified then it will be defaulted with local currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid CURRENCY record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOLERANCE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Tolerance for corporate action events allowed is defined here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTIAL.STP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts value ALL or SC.PARTIAL.STP id or it can be left null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

