<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>DIV.COUP.CUS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>These are system generated records which have been created as a direct result of using the DIV.COUP.DET Application. </p>
            <p>They are individual records by Customer,by Security and contain all the relevant details pertaining to that client and his Interest payment in a particular security. </p>
            <p>The System will calculate a Gross Amount payable less any commission or Foreign Charges and deduct Standard Rate Tax from the payment in accordance with the details stored within the TAX Table DIV.COUP.TAX. The system recognises two types of Tax from this table Source Tax and Local Tax. </p>
            <p>The User will be allowed the standard T24 facility of being able to authorise one or all records.  Customer Advices will be printed and all Financial entries updated. </p>
            <p>Note : The copy function is not allowed for this application. As the        customer record can only be created as a direct result of the entry        of a DIV COUP DET application. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.AMT.DIV.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of dividend [before charges/tax].  Gross amount in currency of that particular security calculated from the Nominal amount held multiplied by the rate applicable and divided where necessary to allow for the percentage type indicator. </p>
            <p>Automatically calculated figure; which uses the information in DIV.COUP.DET. i.e. Ratio and percentage Indicator to calculate the gross amount payable in the SECURITY.CCY to that particular client. </p>
            <p>Examples:  Nominal balance is 10,000 the rate applicable is GBP 0.11.            Therefore the Gross amount payable in security currency is GBP            1,100.00. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.DOMICILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVE.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provides the address where the Customer's Advices relating to this trade are to be sent (where different from the Address entered on the CUSTOMER record). </p>
            <p>If entered, will be used by the delivery system in place of any addresses stored elsewhere in the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multivalue fields available to enable the full address to be input.  (Optional input.)  (Multivalue field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the reallowance in local currency is held in this field and is calculated from the values in the fields REALLOWANCE.AMT and REALLOWANCE.XRATE. If one of these fields is modified then the contents of this field are updated automatically. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field, 19 numerioc characters.</p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates posting date of the DIVIDEND/INTEREST amount as per the nostro entry. </p>
            <p>The VALUE.DATE refers to the customer account posting regarding the actual value date.  This field contains the reference or posting date of the depository total to the nostro account. </p>
            <p>To help with nostro reconciliation problems in the event of, for example, 100 clients each receiving a Dividend/Interest payment.  The nostro total is only passed (automatically) when all the customer records have been either authorised or deleted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Commission charged in base currency equivalent. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  Figure automatically created by system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.BASE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate between the reference currency of the portfolio identified in the SECURITY.ACC field and the local currency of the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field, whose figure is automatically created by system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.TAX.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the exchange rate used to convert the amount of tax in the currency of the dividend (FOREIGN.CHGES.TAX) to the amount in local currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT system generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify a reallowance amount which is effectively a commission for the Bank for processing the dividend request. Input into this field will automatically populate the contents of the field REALLOWANCE.XRATE with the exchange rate specified in the field REDEM.BASE.RATE, if the field REALLOWANCE.XRATE is null. </p>
            <p>The amount entered into this field will be posted to the profit and loss category as specified on the appropriate SC.STD.COUPON record in the field REALLOWANCE.PL.CAT using the transaction code specified on the same record. </p>
            <p>The depository suspense account is debited with this amount in addition to any other debits which will arise as a result of this customer's redemption. </p>
            <p>This amount is also update the field AMT.DIV.CUR on the depository record for this redemption, which will eventually post the suspense account entires to the depository's NOSTRO account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field, 19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.DIV.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Net Dividend payable in Security/Dividend currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.ACC.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a client's account is in a different currency to that of the security undergoing the Dividend/Interest payment this amount will be the calculated amount in the currency of that client's account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates payment date of the Dividend/Interest concerned. i.e.  The value date for accounting purposes for that client. </p>
            <p>For reasons of Public Holidays etc. the Dividend payment date may not be the Dividend Value date. </p>
            <p>Note : This value date refers to the customer posting only. </p>
            <p>       The value date referred to in field 24 identifies the date at which        the nostro entry is generated.  i.e. clients will receive good        value for interest/coupons received while the nostro posting will        only be passed when all related customer advices have been        authorised. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format.  This date defaults to the information entered at DIV.COUP.DET.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically updated by the system from the SOURCE.TAX.CODE field in DIV.COUP.DET.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />No-input field.    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the customer who holds stock on ex. date and who is therefore eligible for the payment. </p>
            <p>A separate customer record will be created for each Client holding stock as at the Ex-date.  It is possible for a client to hold stock at 2 separate depositories - in which case 2 records will be created. </p>
            <p>Note : For various administrative reasons, Companies when paying a        Dividend on a Stock have to know their Clients' positions prior to        the actual value date of the payment and therefore an Ex.Date is        decided upon. i.e. a cut off date for calculating position.  Any        trade done after this date is normally termed Ex-Div. i.e. it does        not rank for dividend payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.DEP.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Net dividend amount in the currency of the postings made to the depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.TAX.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the amount of tax, in local currency, which is to be charged on the foreign charges. This field is automatically generated from the amount held in the field FOREIGN.CHGES.TAX. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field, system generated from the amount of the foreign charge (field FOREIGN.CHGES.AMT).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The TAX code used to calculate the tax on commission. </p>
            <p>Automatically generated by the system. </p>
            <p>Taken from the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE code used to calculate the customer commission (held in the COMMISSION.CODE field). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field automatically generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local Currency equivalent of Net Dividend amount. </p>
            <p>Converted using foreign exchange call rates. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the percentage used for calculating the local tax amount applicable on the corporate action. The tax percentage is derived from the </p>
            <p>LOCAL.TAX.CODE </p>derived. <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WANCE.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a sub valued language field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WANCE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a sub valued language field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>A number generated automatically by the system which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of a transaction entered. </p>
            <p>The system will automatically insert a number into this field and this number may refer to a statement entry or a category entry depending on the value contained in the corresponding multivalue fields.  The following example will illustrate the use of this field: </p>
            <p>Example : Any individual transaction contains a number of financial           entries.  Each one of these whether a statement entry or a P&amp;L           entry will be recorded with an unique reference number within           the transaction itself for easy retrieval and checking. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal multivalue field, therefore NOINPUT.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 29 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Net amount payable to Customer in Base Currency equivalent. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field, whose amount is automatically created by system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies uniquely each Security Dividend/Interest per customer. </p>
            <p>All Customer records are automatically generated from the authorised 'Detail' record. The key used within that Detail record obviously determines the key generated at this Customer level. </p>
            <p>Example : 665544-000.100105.DIV.20010321.100032-1.100.111</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />The ID key is made up of the following format: NNNNNN-NNN - 10 numeric character Security Master number XXXXXXXX - 1-8 Numeric depository account number &amp;#8211; 1-5 Alpha numeric characters Dividend Coupon Type YYYYMMDD - Standard Date format NNNNNN-NNN - 1-10 numeric character customer number (Mandatory input) ZZZZZ - 1-5 characters Nominee code (optional)<p />SSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS &amp;#8211; 1-16 characters Sub account (Optional).    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a particular depository is specified at the DIVIDEND COUP DETAIL level it specifies that the interest/coupon payment is only for that requested depository. </p>
            <p>The CUSTOMER records are created from the key input at DIV COUP DET. Where the depository is input as part of the key determines the information contained within this field. </p>
            <p>If no depository is input at  the detail level (Optional input) it specifies that the dividend interest is payable through all depository holdings and this field will not be updated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This displays the Portfolio account in which the security is lodged. </p>
            <p>The System automatically creates one record per Customer/Depository holding. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>It will automatically be a valid Customer SEC.ACC.MASTER number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the ID of the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record used to calculate the customer commissions charged by the bank to the customer for processing the dividend. </p>
            <p>Field automatically updated according to the rules defined on the CUSTOMER.CHARGE record for the customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT system generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>T24 will calculate Local Tax from the Rates stored within DIV.COUP.TAX. </p>
            <p>These rates are applied by Security Domicile and where rates are not entered will assume '0.00'. </p>
            <p>Numeric amount charged on gross amount in currency of that particular security. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>An automatically generated amount which uses the rate applied in DIV.COUP.DET to calculate the Bank's commission on this particular Dividend/Interest payment. </p>
            <p>The user may override the calculated amount by manual input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-18 numeric characters (including up to 3 decimals).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the Override messages which the User agreed to during Input. </p>
            <p>During the validation stage of a DIV.COUP.CUS. Transaction, the system may provide the User with a series of screen override messages, to indicate an anomaly, or an error. </p>
            <p>In the event that the User confirms the Override, the full text of the actual Override Message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field, Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of tax charged on the customer commission in the local currency of the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field, automatically generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WANCE.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a sub valued language field. Standard T24 rate field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local Tax equivalent in Base currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  Figure automatically created by system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>T24 will calculate Source Tax from the Rates stored within DIV.COUP.TAX. </p>
            <p>These rates are applied by Security Domicile and where rates are not entered will assume '0.00' </p>
            <p>Numeric amount charged on gross amount in currency of that particular security. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESS.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>If entered, it is used to check the format of the override delivery address entered, depending on the value of the carrier from the message control message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric character Message Control ID  (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>Must be the ID of a valid Message Control record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically generated unique reference number. </p>
            <p>Each Administration Application has its' own hard coded 'MNEMONIC' which the system uses to generate unique reference numbers for each of its customer records. </p>
            <p>Note : REFERENCE.NO will only appear on the CUSTOMER record.  It will not        be illustrated on the DEPOSITORY record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.  Key is: Application MNEMONIC, Julian Date and next sequential reference number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the reference number of the advices, delivery instructions and payment/receipt messages related to this transaction. </p>
            <p>This field is generated by the delivery system when the messages are created. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>External field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will hold the tax code that is to be used for calculating the </p>
            <p>LOCAL.TAX.PERC.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The field will be initially defaulted from the COUPON.TAX.CODE file. If the value on the COUPON.TAX.CODE record contains a '*' in the first character of the value it means that the field points to a TAX.TYPE.CONDITION record. In this case the system will derive the tax code applicable to that customer based on their residence.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOREIGN.CHGES.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where a Foreign charge is indicated at DIV. COUP. DET level the system will calculate a Foreign Charge per Customer/Depository holding. </p>
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>     Customer holds 1000 shares Dividend Rate 0.07 (per share) Gross      amount dividend 70.00 </p>
            <p>     (Foreign charge 10.00 indicator = 'Y') foreign charge = 7. </p>
            <p>     Amount Payable will = 63-00 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Defaults from the FOREIGN.CHARGES field in the DIV.COUP.DET application that created the DIV.COUP.CUS record.</p>
            <p>Input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBS.RED.DIV.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the amount that is paid to the customer in addition to the coupon interest as in the case of mortgage backed securities. The amount is calculated as follows : </p>
            <p>     MBS.REDEMP.AMT = (OLD.FACTOR - NEW.FACTOR)* NOMINAL </p>
            <p>The old factor is the factor field defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record that used to be current just prior to the current factor and the new factor is the the current factor defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record. This amount will be posted to the customer in addition to coupon interest as a separate entry. The other side posting to the depository will remain as one entry for a net amount of the coupon interest &amp; this amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.DIV.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically calculated amount which displays the Net Amount of Dividend/ Interest payable to the Customer after the deduction of Foreign and Commission charges. </p>
            <p>The amount to be posted to the clients account will be displayed here in the currency of the Security in question. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate between the dividend currency and the local currency is held in this field. If the dividend currency is the local currency a value of one is entered. </p>
            <p>This field is used in the calculation of the reallowance in local currency, and if modified will modify the value held in the field REALLOWANCE.BCUR. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 rate field, 15 characters. Optional Input.</p>
            <p>When the redemption currency is the local currency, input into this field will default to one.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate used to calculate the Local Currency equivalent of the tax on commission. </p>
            <p>This is the exchange rate between the two values in the COMM.TAX.BCUR and COMMISSION.TAX.AMT fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field automatically generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BND.RND.METH</field>
<desc>
            <p>When calculating the accrued interest on a bond, certain rounding parameters can be taken into account in the calculation. If a bond rounding method has been used then the method used will be stored in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the amount of tax to be charged on the COMMISSION.AMT. </p>
            <p>Automatically calculated using the CUSTOMER.CHARGE record set-up for the customer. </p>
            <p>The amount in this field is the amount of tax in the currency of the dividend (held in the DIV.CUR field). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOREIGN.CHGES.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the amount of tax which is to be charged, if any, on the foreign charge. This field is calculated from the FOREIGN.CHGES.AMT field and uses the TAX key or TAX.TYPE.CONDITION key as specified on the relevant record on the SC.STD.COUPON file. </p>
            <p>The amount held in this field is the amount in the currency of the dividend payable, normally the security currency (see field DIV.CUR). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field, system generated from the amount of the foreign charge (field FOREIGN.CHGES.AMT) and the tax code applicable, as defined on the SC.STD.COUPON file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBS.RED.LCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the amount that is paid to the customer in addition to the coupon interest as in the case of mortgage backed securities. The amount is calculated as follows: </p>
            <p>     MBS.REDEMP.AMT = (OLD.FACTOR - NEW.FACTOR)* NOMINAL </p>
            <p>The old factor is the factor field defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record that used to be current just prior to the current factor and the new factor is the the current factor defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record. This amount will be posted to the customer in addition to coupon interest as a separate entry. The other side posting to the depository will remain as one entry for a net amount of the coupon interest &amp; this amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically updated by the system from the SOURCE.TAX.CODE field.</p>
            <p>The field contains the percentage used to calculate the source tax amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />No-input field.    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECOVERABLE.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of US tax to be withheld from the net amount payable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-18 numeric characters (including up to 3 decimals).</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reference currency of customer to whom payment is being made. </p>
            <p>i.e. reference currency of that client's portfolio account. </p>
            <p>All Securities within a portfolio account are valued at the market price as picked up by the pricing service used.  This market valuation is then converted into the reference currency for display purposes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 015 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency of dividend payable. </p>
            <p>The currency of the dividend payable is normally the security currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field automatically created by System.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the tax code which is applicable, if any, to the foreign charges which have arisen as a result of an interest payment (details of which are held on the on the DIV.COUP.DET record). </p>
            <p>The tax code can be defined by referencing a record on the TAX file or on the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION file, and is taken from the SC.STD.COUPON file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the TAX file       or  Must be a valid record on the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION file, the id of which should be preceded by an asterisk (*).</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT system generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.BASE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Base Rate between Security currency and Company currency.  (Local Currency). </p>
            <p>The user may override the default value by manual input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Rate Type.  Automatically generated display.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBS.RED.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the amount that is paid to the customer in addition to the coupon interest as in the case of mortgage backed securities. The amount is calculated as follows : </p>
            <p>     MBS.REDEMP.AMT = (OLD.FACTOR - NEW.FACTOR)* NOMINAL </p>
            <p>The old factor is the factor field defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record that used to be current just prior to the current factor and the new factor is the the current factor defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record. This amount will be posted to the customer in addition to coupon interest as a separate entry. The other side posting to the depository will remain as one entry for a net amount of the coupon interest &amp; this amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINAL.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates customer holding on ex. date in that particular Security and in that particular Depositary (if specified). </p>
            <p>It is effectively the nominal balance on which any Dividend, Interest payment is to be made. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains all the customer (DIV.COUP.CUS) Keys related to the depository record. </p>
            <p>This field is only updated on the depository record showing the customer records associated to it together with their respective accounting entry numbers. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the depository where stock is held.  Where Depository is entered as part of key this field will specify that Depository. </p>
            <p>The Depository ID no is part of the key used in DIV.COUP.DET.  It is an Optional entry and where used will only create records for that particular Depository.  The logic behind the argument being that the Interest/ Dividend payment only applies to a particular Depository holding. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT internally generated field.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the Customer file as valid customer type depository.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.BASE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rate between client's financial account and dividend currency. </p>
            <p>The user may override the default value by manual input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard rate format.  Automatically calculated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies Account to be credited with payment. </p>
            <p>The system will default to a valid financial Account assigned to the actual customer, stored in the SEC.ACC.MASTER file. The inputter can specify the default Account number to be used for all Client Dividend/Interest payments on the AC.DEF.ACCT field on the SEC.ACC.MASTER file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-16 numeric character Account number or 3-10 character Mnemonic Account id (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".2). </p>
            <p>Must be a valid ACCOUNT number. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.CURR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies currency of account to be credited. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

