<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>ENTITLEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>When a DIARY record is authorised and the corporate actions service is completed the system generates ENTITLEMENT records for each portfolio. These records control how much cash and how many securities are due to each specific portfolio.</p>
            <p>   Once these records for a particular DIARY record have been authorised then no further change will be allowed to the original DIARY record.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ODD.LOT.NUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>New multi-value field associated with all the fields of NEW.SECURITY</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   This field contains the security number of the odd lot if the odd lot number is the same than the security number. Else, the field is let blank as the ODD.LOT.REF field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALIS.AMT.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the equalisation amount having been converted to the customer's account currency and will be posted to his/her account as defined in the EQUALISATION.ACC field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   This is a no-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.CHARGES.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Foreign Charges amount charged in the Currency of the event.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Source Tax that has been previously been debited by initiator of Corporate Action and so not charged to user through T24. Amount updated by the system and is for display only. This field will be updated by the system only if RATE.TYPE in the original DIARY record is set to 'N'ET.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LENT.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the net settled Lent positions as on Record Date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RCVBL.TAX.LCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the Recoverable Tax in the Local Currency. This is defaulted by the system when the Corporate Action event is subject to Recoverable Tax.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   It is a no input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.ACC.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Net amount to be credited or debited in the Currency of the Account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.ACC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stamp tax amount in account currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SBL.QUALIFY.HOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will include the net Qualify holdings for the particular Security, Customer and the Depository.It is calculated as follows:SBL.QUAL.HOLD =  QUALIFY.HOLDING + Settled Borrowed positions as on Record Date - Settled Lent positions as on Record date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BORROW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the Borrow amount.It is calculated as BORROW.NOMINAL * Dividend rate * SBL.DIV.RATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.DESC.DEP</field>
<desc>
            <p>System generated field, used to display the description of the option(s) available for the event. This field is noinput for mandatory events. The value in this field will be similar to the value in the OPTION.DESC field.</p>
            <p>   This field and the OPT.NOM.DEP field form an associated multi-value set.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.BK.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of stamp tax in charge of the bank.</p>
            <p>   This field will be populated by the system if the field STAMP.MIN.AMT field of the related DIARY.TYPE record</p>
            <p>   contains an amount which is lower or equal to the stamp tax amount.</p>
            <p>   This amount is expressed in local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RCVBL.TAX.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the rate applicable for the Recoverable Tax code which is taken from  the DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   This is an input field and can be modified at the ENTITLEMENT level if needed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   It is an optional field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.OR.LOCAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates where tax has been deducted at source.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will accept a CUSTOMER.SECURITY number. No-input system updated field when ENTITLEMENT record is created. Associated Multi value fields from BROKER.NO to BR.ENTL.AMT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the percentage used for calculating the local tax amount applicable on the corporate action. The tax percentage is derived from the</p>
            <p>   LOCAL.TAX.CODE</p>
            <p>   If the TAX record, from the associated field</p>
            <p>   LOCAL.TAX.CODE</p>
            <p>   If APPL.GEN.CONDITION application has a record with id 'DIARY' or 'ENTITLEMENT', then CONTRACT.GRP is identified based on the conditions defined in the fields from DECIS.FIELD to DECISION.TO in APPL.GEN.CONDITION. In TAX.TYPE.CONDITION, the tax codes that are assigned to particular groups of contract (CONTRACT.GRP) are populated in LOCAL.TAX.CODE and the corresponding percentage is displayed in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.PARAM.COND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will default with the key of the CG.PARAM.CONDITION record which has conditions set that apply to this transaction (if any).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   A NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>   Alpha or Numeric characters allowed</p>
            <p>   Maximum of 5 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Portfolio Number to which the ENTITLEMENT record is for.</p>
            <p>   Enriched by the Account Name field from the SEC.ACC.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT, system generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOT.HOLDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>System generated field which will reflect the effect that the position has on the Depot (Agent), a negative figure will be produced when the Portfolio has caused a shortage at the Depot and a positive figure will be produced when the Portfolio holds stock in the Depot.The field will be calculated as the QUALIFY.HOLDING - outstanding credit transactions + outstanding debit transactions + non-returned settled stock borrows - non-returned settled stock lent.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONFIRM.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether confirmation advices are generated when entitlements are created via this Entitlement record.</p>
            <p>   The value will be defaulted from the relevant DIARY.TYPE record.</p>
            <p>   The actual message types are determined via the relevant EB.ADVICES records, which will be either SC-0102-EVENT.TYPE, for entitlement creation or SC-0103-EVENT.TYPE, for entitlement reversal.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Optional Input can be set to YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of commission charged in the Currency of the event.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This field is updated by the system and is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the number of securities to which the portfolio is entitled, updated by the system taking Old &amp; New ratio defined in the originating DIARY record into consideration.</p>
            <p>   This field allows input but it should be made no input for day to day processing.  However, input may be necessary for depository rounding processes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Input only allowed if Securities are updated by this Event Type.</p>
            <p>   Multi-valued field linked to the OPTION set of fields.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Tax on the Commission amount in the Local currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contains any SEC.OPEN.ORDER ID or SEC.TRADE id that have been generated by the corporate actions STP process.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Noinput field automatically populated by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.TAX.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Manually entered tax amount in account currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Net Amount to be credited or debited in the Currency of the event.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Commission Code used to calculate the Commission charged on the account. Updated by the system from the originating DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBS.RED.LCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISATION.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the account in the EQUALISATION.ACC field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and updated by the system.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CUST.SETT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the automatic settlement of the nominal and cash for the Customers. This facility is available for the Customer side only.</p>
            <p>   The value is defaulted as 'YES', if it has been set to YES in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file. The automatic settlement can be turned OFF at transaction level, though it has been turned ON in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY. Though it has been turned ON in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY, the same could be turned OFF at the transaction namely SEC.TRADE, SECURITY.TRANSFER</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Yes, No or Null.  Null is equivalent to NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INSTR.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Noinput field that will contains the date on which the system will apply default instructions to the ENTITLEMENT record.</p>
            <p>   This field is populated from the DEF.INSTR.DATE field of the related DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Noinput field automatically populated by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.BASE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount in local currency on which the stamp tax has been calculated.</p>
            <p>   This field is populated by the routine entered in the STAMP.CALC.RTN field of the related DIARY.TYPE record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Source Tax charged in Currency of the Event.</p>
            <p>   This field will be updated by the system only if RATE.TYPE field in DIARY record is set to 'G'ROSS. Otherwise TAX.CREDIT field will be updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with the last six fields make up an 'OPTION' to choose from.</p>
            <p>   The user can select to use all their holding against one option OR split their holding between the different options by entering the number of the Nominals they wish to take up in this field. This amount added to the total of the SELL.NUMBER and BUY.NUMBER must be equal to the EVENT.NOMINAL for the ENTITLEMENT record to be activated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Optional input of numeric character but this number cannot be greater than the EVENT.NOMINAL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODD.LOT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field is updated if the odd lot number is different from the security number. The field contains the number of the sub value of NEW.SEC.NO associated to the current sub value.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROK.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as a category reference for the broker. The suspense amount of the broker is posted to it.</p>
            <p>   The value is picked up from the SC.PARAMETER which holds a similar field in it. The value is defaulted from the SC.PARAMETER fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   The value in this field should be a valid entry in CATEGORY         file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPO.RIGHTS.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Single value field which is the equivalent to DEPOT.HOLDING field and will have the Rights security nominal held with the Depository.</p>
            <p> This field will be updated only if field SETTLE.METHOD in SC.PARAMETER  is set to “US”.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.TAX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the tax rate applied to the base amount.</p>
            <p>   If the TAX record, from the associated field CGT.CODE, field LINK.TAX is populated then all linked tax rates will be shown.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.ADVICE.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether pre confirmation advices are generated when entitlements are created via this Entitlement record.</p>
            <p>   The value will be defaulted from the relevant DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   The actual message types are determined via the relevant EB.ADVICES records, which will be either SC-0100-EVENT.TYPE, for entitlement creation or SC-0101-EVENT.TYPE, for entitlement amendment or deletion.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Optional Input can be set to YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.TAX.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 rate field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Depository number the ENTITLEMENT record related to.</p>
            <p>   Enriched by short description from CUSTOMER.SECURITY file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Updated by the system and is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field showing the IDs of the delivery records produced by the transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.  Multivalued, internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the tax code to be used for the purposes of calculating the capital gains tax amount.</p>
            <p>   If this field is changed then a recalculation of the tax amount is triggered off.</p>
            <p>   The tax code will initially be defaulted by the system depending on the default settings.</p>
            <p>   If the TAX record field LINK.TAX is populated then all linked tax codes will be shown.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Input must be a valid tax code on the TAX file.</p>
            <p>   Only multi-value 1 can be used for input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUALIFY.HOLDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Portfolio's holding in the original security as at EX.DATE.</p>
            <p>   Should the underlying DIARY.TYPE be an equalisation type dividend as may be paid in respect of a UK unit trust type security, then this holding will comprise the total held prior to the equalisation date (so called "G1" amount), and is therefore ineligible for equalisation processing.</p>
            <p>   Should this field be zero, then you should refer to the EQUALISE.HLDING field as it is likely that the securities were purchased during the current equalisation period and, as a consequence, undergo a different dividend payment process.</p>
            <p>   If you change the qualifying holding then the ENTITLEMENT.AMT will be recalculated, using the newly entered QUALIFY.HOLDING to ascertain the dividend amount due.</p>
            <p>   Any amendments made to the automatically generated amount will be lost should the parent DIARY be re-run.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Field updated by the System but may be amended</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUT.AUTH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Noinput field that will contain the date on which the ENTITLEMENT record will be automatically authorised during the START.OF.DAY process.</p>
            <p>   This field is populated from the ENT.AUTO.AUTH.DATE field of the related DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Noinput field automatically populated by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.RIGHTS.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field  is equivalent to TOT.OUT.NOM field and will hold the total outstanding nominal from the Broker/Counterparty with respect to Rights Security. </p>
            <p> This field will be updated only if field SETTLE.METHOD in SC.PARAMETER  is set to “US”.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>System  updated field used to store</p>
            <p>   a)Broker and transaction reference of the original outstanding debit/credit transaction concatenated by a "*"</p>
            <p>   e.g. 100516*SCTRSC0307100013</p>
            <p>   b)Counterparty and settled non returned stock borrows/lends done via REPO concatenated by a "*"</p>
            <p>   e.g. 111111* RP0307100013</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The fields BROKER.TXN.ID through to TXN.NARR will form a multi-value set.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as a category reference for the customer.</p>
            <p>   The suspense amount of the customer is posted to it.</p>
            <p>   The value is picked up from the SC.PARAMETER, which holds a similar field in it. The value is defaulted from the SC.PARAMETER fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   The value in this field should be a valid entry in CATEGORY         file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>A brief description of the Option, updated by the system from the originating DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LCCY.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange Rate between the Event Currency and the Account Currency. Updated by the system while generating ENTITLEMENT records, but user has an option of changing this field. In the event of any change to this field, this will be validated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the number of securities credited to the portfolio account OR debited from the portfolio account as a result of the event.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAND.INST</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field that will record the standing instructions used to default option to be taken on this ENTITLEMENT record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETAIN.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the user to select some or all of the EVENT.NOMINAL and opt to have this portion of the holding do nothing. For example in a Bond Redemption corporate action when the user only wants to redeem 50% of the holding.</p>
            <p>   Any amount input in this field will cause the system to have no effect on this portion of the holding.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Optional input.</p>
            <p>   If anything is entered into this field the total of this field together with the elected option nominals must be equal to the figure input in the EVENT.NOMINAL field.</p>
            <p>   Input must be numeric.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This set of fields shows the securities that have been credited to the portfolio account OR debited from the portfolio account as a result of the event.</p>
            <p>   Enriched by the Short description of the Security from the SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>System updated field used to display the description of the options available for this event. The value in this field will be similar to the value in OPTION.DESC field.</p>
            <p>   This field along with OPT.NOM field form an associated sub-value set with the multi-value set starting from BROKER.TXN.ID to TXN.NARR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.CUSTODIAN</field>
<desc>
            <p>To identify the external custodian where position is held.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.BAMT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will signify the currency code in which the CGT base amount is denominated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.TAX.LCL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the local equivalent of the actual amount of capital gains tax that is to be debited from the customers account.</p>
            <p>   If the TAX record, from the associated field CGT.CODE, field LINK.TAX is populated then all linked local tax amounts will be shown.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALIS.EX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate between the security currency and the currency of the EQUALISATION.ACC if they are different.</p>
            <p>   This field is updated by the system when creating ENTITLEMENT records but user has an option to change this rate if necessary.</p>
            <p>   If the EQUALISATION.ACC is changed to an account having a different currency than that originally entered, then this field will be updated to the exchange rate applicable between the account and security currencies.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Input only allowed if field EQUALISATION in DIARY.TYPE is         YES by this Event Type.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reference Currency of the portfolio.</p>
            <p>   Updated by the system taking the default value from SEC.ACC.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>   Enriched by the Short description from CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISE.HLDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Nominal that has been purchased since EQUALISATION date, updated from the originating DIARY record. This amount will be worked out using the security transaction history (SECURITY.TRANS file) and will comprise the total any purchases less sales made during the so called "equalisation period".</p>
            <p>   The displayed amount may be amended but be aware that if the parent DIARY transaction is re-run, then the information you enter will revert back to the original amount.</p>
            <p>   If it is changed then both the GROUP2.AMT and EQUALISE.AMT will be recalculated using the appropriate rates from the parent DIARY transaction.</p>
            <p>   It should be bourne in mind that if the parent DIARY transaction be the subject of a re-run, then any changes you may have made in this field will be lost and replaced by the latest positional details obtained from the security transaction files for the customer / security combination.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Input only allowed if field EQUALISATION in DIARY.TYPE is         YES by this Event Type</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internally generated reference number. Display only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUST.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>New multi-valued field associated with the ADJUST.NOM field. This field will be a no input field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Rule 1</p>
            <p>   Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.SECURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>SEDOL number of the securities to which the portfolio is entitled.</p>
            <p>   Short description from SECURITY.MASTER file is enriched to this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.TAX.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Manually entered tax amount in local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the total nominal involved in the event. If the event is a RIGHTS issue then this is the total number of rights otherwise this will be equal to the QUALIFY.HOLDING.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field, updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is a calculated no-input field used to display the value of the stock dividend. The calculation of this field will use the TAX.PRICE and the NOMINAL in the standard price calculation routines to establish the security value.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax amount, associated with SC.TAX.CODE, in local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.LOC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stamp tax amount in local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RCVBL.TAX.SEC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the Recoverable Tax in the Security Currency. This is defaulted by the system when the Corporate Action event is subject to Recoverable Tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TRADE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of the SEC.TRADE transaction that may effect the event (for example selling OR buying rights). Number of shares involved is held in either the SELL.NUMBER OR BUY.NUMBER fields. Rights are often bought OR sold either to bring the number of rights the portfolio has to a number that will result in a whole number of securities when the rights are exercised. Alternatively some of the rights could be sold to fund the take-up of the remainder.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field, pdated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the rate defined in DIARY if RATE.TYPE field on DIARY  record</p>
            <p>   is GROSS and DRIPS field on DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>   The system will take this or NET.RATE  depending on the value</p>
            <p>   of the GROSS.OR.NET  field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax code used to calculate the stamp tax.</p>
            <p>   This field is automatically populated by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Must be a valid entry of TAX file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.RIGHTS.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the equivalent to BR.OUTS.NOM field and will hold the Broker/Counterparty Outstanding Nominal corresponding to individual transactions with respect to Rights Security under the associated multi value field  BROKER.TXN.ID. </p>
            <p> This field will be updated only if field SETTLE.METHOD in SC.PARAMETER  is set to “US”.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REF.LCCY.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate between the Portfolio Reference Currency and the Local Currency.</p>
            <p>   Updated by the system while generating ENTITLEMENT records but user has an option of changing the value in this field. In the event of changes, proper validations are done.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax code applicable to this event.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODD.RTS.SAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to signify the number of rights securities that can be sold without affecting then number of new securities that would be allocated when the rights securities are converted to the new securities.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax Code used to calculate the Tax amount charged on the Commission Amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field updated by the system and is for display purpose only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP2.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of cash the portfolio will receive as a result of its "Group 2" holding as reported in the EQUALISE.HLDING field, purchased since the Equalisation Date, updated from the originating DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   You may change this amount if you wish, the only proviso being the amount entered, when added to the EQUALISE.AMT must equal the sum of EQUALISE.HLDING x (GROUP2.RATE + EQUALISE.RATE). The two rates are found on the parent DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   It follows, therefore, a change to the contents of this field will require a change to the amount recorded in the EQUALISE.AMT field.</p>
            <p>   Note that the re-running of the parent DIARY will result in any manually entered amounts being recalculated. Further, any manual change to the EQUALISE.HLDING field contents will result in a recalculation of this GROUP2.AMT amount, together with the EQUALISE.AMT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Input only allowed if field EQUALISATION in DIARY.TYPE is         YES by this Event Type.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBS.RED.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.CHGES.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Foreign Charges amount in the Local Currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODD.LOT.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>New multi-value field associated with all the fields of NEW.SECURITY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   This field contains the odd lot nominal.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.LOCAL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to display the amount of LOCAL TAX applicable to the option and is a calculated no-input field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of rights portfolio has sold in the associated SEC.TRADE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field, updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.NOM.DEP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to display the amount of the option taken up for the DEPOT.HOLDING. This field will be no input for mandatory events. The value in this field cannot be greater than DEPOT.HOLDING field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of rights portfolio has bought in the associated SEC.TRADE.ID field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.BASE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the amount on which the capital gains tax calculation is to be performed.</p>
            <p>   This field is obtained from the WHT.PL field on the CG.TXN.BASE file.</p>
            <p>   The amount is maintained in the currency of the account being debited.</p>
            <p>   If the field is changed a recalculation of the tax amount is triggered off.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Populated automatically</p>
            <p>   Can be changed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the Security Position updated by the execution of the Corporate Action will be blocked.</p>
            <p>   If the position is to be blocked it can take place at the authorisation of the DIARY record (value</p>
            <p>   DIARY</p>
            <p>   ENTITLEMENT</p>
            <p>   The blocked amount is always the</p>
            <p>   QUALIFY.HOLDING</p>
            <p>   Blocks are created in the SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS application automatically when a block is required, similarly they are unblocked using the same application automatically. A block / unblock is created under the following circumstances:</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   System field No input</p>
            <p>   Values DIARY or                 ENTITLEMENT allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.TAX.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.ENT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System updated field which contains the key to ENTITLEMENT.BROKER records linked to the ENTITLEMENT. This field gets updated when either no or partial settlement is done or when there is a settled non-returned borrow/lend exists for this position. The corresponding record in ENTITLEMENT.BROKER is generated based on settled (for depository) or unsettled (for broker) nominal.</p>
            <p>   The ENTITLEMENT.BROKER key is made up of 7 elements</p>
            <p>   DIARY ID</p>
            <p>   Portfolio number</p>
            <p>   Broker or Counterparty</p>
            <p>   Nominee code</p>
            <p>   Sub account</p>
            <p>   Depository</p>
            <p>   Transaction reference or 1</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Note : If the value in the last element is 1 then it denotes that the ENTITLEMENT.BROKER record is for the depository.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internally generated lists if STMT.ENTRY IDs relating to this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields OPTION.DESC to OPTION.NOM form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the equivalent to OUTSTAND.NOM and will hold the outstanding nominal from the Broker/Counterparty with respect to Rights Security under the associated multi value field BROKER.NO. This field will be updated only if field SETTLE.METHOD in SC.PARAMETER  is set to “US”.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTITLEMENT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique identifier for ENTITLEMENT records made up of DIARY ID of the originating DIARY record, the portfolio number, the Depository, the Nominee Code and the Sub Account.</p>
            <p>   Enriched by the Narrative description of the originating DIARY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.AMT.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax amount, associated with SC.TAX.CODE, in entitlement currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field used in the calculation of consideration using the Columbian Yield Method.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FTT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
 <p> Defines the valid TAX.TYPE Record related to FTT(Finanicial Transactional Tax).Field will get defaulted from the field FTT.TYPE of DIARY </p>            
  </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FTT.PERC</field>
<desc>
 <p> Defines the valid tax rate of the FTT(Financial Transactional Tax).Field will get defaulted from the field TAX.RATE of TAX related to FTT </p>            
  </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FTT.BSE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax base amount in terms of EUR currrency on which the tax percentage is applied.</p>                     
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FTT.AMT.TCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>FTT Tax amount in account currency of the transaction.</p>                     
        </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>FTT.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>FTT Tax amount in local currency.</p>                     
        </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>FTT.AMT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>FTT Tax amount currency which is EUR.</p>          
            
        </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>FTT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax amount in EUR.</p>          
            
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FTT.EX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate between account currency and EUR.</p>          
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system from SOURCE.TAX.CODE field in DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   The field contains the key of the TAX record used to determine the source tax percentage.</p>
            <p>   If APPL.GEN.CONDITION application has a record with id 'DIARY' or 'ENTITLEMENT', then CONTRACT.GRP is identified based on the conditions defined in the fields from DECIS.FIELD to DECISION.TO in APPL.GEN.CONDITION. In TAX.TYPE.CONDITION, the tax codes that are assigned to particular groups of contract (CONTRACT.GRP) are populated in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>SEDOL number of the original security. Updated from the originating DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   Enriched by the Short description of the Security from Security Master file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the sub account of the depository.</p>
            <p>   It is defaulted from the entitlement key.</p>
            <p>   No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.SOURCE.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to display the amount of SOURCE TAX applicable to the option.It is a calculated no-input field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTITLEMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field showing Gross Cash Entitlement for each option. This field is updated by the system, taking all the parameters in the originating DIARY record into consideration.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a multivalued field.</p>
			<p>This can be amendable before authorising the ENTITLEMENT.</p>
			<p>A override will be raised when this field is amended and if that doesnt match with ORIG.ENT.AMOUNT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the capital gains tax amount to be debited from the customer's account.</p>
            <p>   If the TAX record, from the associated field CGT.CODE, field LINK.TAX is populated then all linked tax amounts will be shown.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOREIGN.CHGES.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate used to calculate Commission Tax Amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANUAL.CREATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the Entitlement is generated manually or through service. This field gets updated to 'YES' when the Entitlement is inputted manually.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISATION.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account used to post the capital equalisation amount.</p>
            <p>   This field is updated by the system when creating ENTITLEMENT records taking the default value from customers' SEC.ACC.MASTER portfolio accounts but you have the option to be able to enter any valid account whether belonging to the Customer or not, subject to override conditions being satisfied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Input only allowed if field EQUALISATION in the         underlying DIARY.TYPE is "YES"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The TAX.PRICE is the price that will be used to ascertain the cash value of a stock dividend. This price is defaulted from the DIARY record, but will allow amendment.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value date of the event, updated by the system. Fed from original DIARY record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Mandatory Field. User can change the Value of this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.OUTS.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field used to display the amount of nominal outstanding from the Broker/Counterparty for the transaction defined in the related BROKER.TXN.ID.</p>
            <p>   Input to this field is allowed to adjust fractions. When this field is changed, the value in the fields DEPOT.HOLDING and OUTSTAND.NOM of the respective Broker get adjusted accordingly.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the tax code that is to be used for calculating the</p>
            <p>   LOCAL.TAX.PERC.</p>
            <p>   The field will be initially defaulted from the COUPON.TAX.CODE file. If the value on the COUPON.TAX.CODE record contains a '*' in the first character of the value it means that the field points to a TAX.TYPE.CONDITION record. In this case the system will derive the tax code applicable to that customer based on their residence.</p>
            <p>   If the TAX record field LINK.TAX field is populated then all the taxes linked to the TAX will be shown.</p>
            <p>   If APPL.GEN.CONDITION application has a record with id 'DIARY' or 'ENTITLEMENT', then CONTRACT.GRP is identified based on the conditions defined in the fields from DECIS.FIELD to DECISION.TO in APPL.GEN.CONDITION. In TAX.TYPE.CONDITION, the tax codes that are assigned to particular groups of contract (CONTRACT.GRP) are populated in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the Nominee Company record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BORROW.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the net settled Borrow positions as on Record Date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVE.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi valued field allowing input of an alternative customer address to which advices should be sent. If an address is entered here it will be used instead of the default address on the delivery system for the customer concerned.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Optional input of 20 characters long, free format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Net Amount credited or debited to the account in the Local currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Ratio between the Nominal of the NEW.SECURITY and the Nominal of the Original Security (EVENT.NOMINAL).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System updated field used to store brokers transaction type for the transaction defined in BROKER.TXN.ID.</p>
            <p>   Must exist in SC.TRANS.NAME</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUST.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>New multi-valued field associated with the ADJUST.SEC field. This field will allow input. It will possible to input positive or negative nominal into this field however any nominal entered must be divisible by the trading units of the associated security.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SRC.TAX.ADJ.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Adjustment amount in source tax deduction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.TAX.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to display the amount of TAX CREDIT applicable to the option and will be a calculated no-input field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the Lent amount.It is calculated as LENT.NOMINAL * Dividend rate * SBL.DIV.RATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Local Tax charged in the Currency of the event. This field will be calculated by the system when the entitlement record is created.</p>
            <p>   If the LOCAL.TAX.CODE field is a TAX record with the field LINK.TAX populated then this field will be multi-valued with each tax amount identified separately.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   A valid numeric amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESS.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>MESSAGE.CONTROL ID used to check the format of the override delivery address entered in the address (previous field). If entered must exist in MESSAGE.CONTROL file. After validation enriched by the short description of the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Optional input of 1-3 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>   If entered must exist in MESSAGE.CONTROL file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Tax charged on the Commission in the Currency of the event.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field for display only and updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.OR.NET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will indicate whether the Rate is quoted as a net or gross</p>
            <p>   figure - with respect to tax.GROSS implies that the amount to be reckoned for reinvestment</p>
            <p>   would be without adjustment of source tax , while NET implies the amount available</p>
            <p>   after adjusting source tax.</p>
            <p>   Only input of GROSS or NET allowed.</p>
            <p>   The system will default to GROSS.</p>
            <p>   Input allowed only if RATE.TYPE field on DIARY  record is GROSS and</p>
            <p>   DRIPS field on DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES.</p>
            <p>   validation Rules</p>
            <p>   Only input of GROSS or NET allowed.</p>
            <p>   Defaults to Gross if the  RATE.TYPE field on DIARY  record is GROSS and</p>
            <p>   DRIPS field on DIARY.TYPE record is set to YES other wise input is not  allowed.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BND.RND.METH</field>
<desc>
            <p>When calculating the accrued interest on a bond, certain rounding parameters can be taken into account in the calculation. If a bond rounding method has been used then the method used will be stored in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the Price of the security if the securities that are offered have a cost associated with them.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains any overrides that has been generated while processing ENTITLEMENT records.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.CHANGED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field indicating whether or not the COMMISSION.AMOUNT has been manually changed by an inputter or not.</p>
            <p>   If this field is YES then the COMMISSION.AMT has been manually changed.</p>
            <p>   If this field is NO then the COMMISSION.AMT has been defaulted by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to display/input the amount of the option taken up by the Broker/Counterparty for the transaction. This field will be no input for mandatory events. For optional events the sum of OPT.NOM for the transaction cannot be greater than BR.OUTS.NOM field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 free format narrative field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.BROK.SETT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the automatic settlement of the nominal and cash for Brokers who have contractual agreements with the Bank. This value will be defaulted to YES, if there is an "YES" in AUTO.BROK.SETT field in CUSTOMER.SECURITY file. The automatic settlement can be turned OFF at transaction level, though it has been turned ON in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY. Though it has been turned ON in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY,the same could be turned OFF at the transaction namely SEC.TRADE, SECURITY.TRANSFER, etc.  <p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Yes, No or Null.  Null is equivalent to NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency of the event, defaulted from the CURRENCY field on the original DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   Enriched by the short description from the CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field, updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RCVBL.TAX.REF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the Recoverable Tax in the Customer Portfolio Reference Currency. This is defaulted by the system when the Corporate Action event is subject to Recoverable Tax.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   It is a no input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBS.PAID.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the extra payment that will be made to the customer for mortgage backed securities on the coupon date. This amount will be calculated as follows:</p>
            <p>   MBS.PAID.AMT = (LAST FACTOR - CURRENT FACTOR) * NOMINAL</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>   The field will be automatically calculated for bonds with factors, where the factors decrease.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.OUT.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will specify the total outstanding nominal entitled from all the brokers for the portfolio. No input system updated field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBS.RED.DIV.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stamp tax amount in security currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODD.RTS.BAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to signify the number of rights securities that need to be purchased to use all the rights that are allocated from the existing holding that would remain unused rights when the rights are converted to the new security.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.DIST.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Interest distribution factor for this event. Applicable to shares only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CHANGED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displaying either YES or NO depending on whether the default tax has been changed or not. If the default tax has been changed then this field will equal YES otherwise it will be NO.</p>
            <p>   This field is used by the system to prevent the source and local tax fields from being overwritten with default values if they have already been changed by a user.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>   Internal system use only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the delivery message types generated for this record.</p>
            <p>   The actual message types are defined on EB.ADVICES.</p>
            <p>   Currently the following specific "hard coded" confirmation message types are supported by Corporate Actions:</p>
            <p>   1505 - Dividend Tax Certificate 1510 - Capital Increase Advice 1520 - New Issue Advice 1530 - Coupon /Dividend Advice 1540 - Stock Dividend Advice 1560 - Redemption Advice</p>
            <p>   Additionally if new message types are required SOFT DELIVERY processing will be invoked as described in the DELIVERY section of the T24 user guide.</p>
            <p>   Information handed to delivery is always comprised of 9 records, see the Delivery user guide for more information.</p>
            <p>   The information handed off to delivery for new message types will be as follows</p>
            <p>   Record 1 equates to data defined in DE.MESSAGE 1500, Corporate action generic message</p>
            <p>   Record 2 comprises the Entitlement record.</p>
            <p>   Record 3 comprises the Diary record.</p>
            <p>   Record 4 comprises the Security Account Master record.</p>
            <p>   Record 5 comprises the Security Master record.</p>
            <p>   Records6 to 9 are left blank.</p>
            <p>   If a user routine is defined in USER.ROUTINE of the relevant EB.ADVICES record then this routine will be invoked and used to create Record9.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of commission charged in Local Currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays calculated rate after deducting source and local tax  with RATE defined in diary</p>
            <p>   if RATE.TYPE field on DIARY  record is GROSS and DRIPS field on DIARY.TYPE record</p>
            <p>   is set to YES.</p>
            <p>   The system will take this or GROSS.RATE  depending on the value</p>
            <p>   of the GROSS.OR.NET  field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount the portfolio will receive as a result of the equalisation in the currency of ENTITLEMENT, updated from the originating DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   You may change this amount if you wish, the only proviso being the amount entered, when added to the GROUP2.AMT must equal the sum of EQUALISE.HLDING x (GROUP2.RATE + EQUALISE.RATE). The two rates are found on the parent DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   It follows, therefore, a change to the contents of this field will require a change to the amount recorded in the GROUP2.AMT field.</p>
            <p>   Note that the re-running of the parent DIARY will result in any manually entered amounts being recalculated. Further, any manual change to the EQUALISE.HLDING field contents will result in a recalculation of this EQUALISE.AMT amount, together with the GROUP2.AMT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Input only allowed if field EQUALISATION in DIARY.TYPE is         YES by this Event Type</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Interest counter for this event. Applicable to shares only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>For optional events, such as rights, this indicates the current status of the ENTITLEMENT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the user to use all the holding on a single option.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Optional input of numeric characters.</p>
            <p>   Input must be a numeric and cannot be less than one or greater than the total number of options available.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MISC.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as a category reference for miscellaneous. The suspense amount of miscellaneous is posted to it.</p>
            <p>   The value is picked up from the SC.PARAMETER which holds a similar field in it. The value is defaulted from the SC.PARAMETER fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   The value in this field should be a valid entry in CATEGORY         file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.SRC.LCL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the Capital Gains Tax for this transaction is to be deducted by the bank (LOCAL) or the depository (SOURCE).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   A NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>   Field can either be 'SOURCE' or 'LOCAL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTSTAND.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will speicfy the total outstanding nominal which is pending from the Broker. This field is to allow input manually if BROKER.NO is populated. Updated by the system when ENTITLEMENT is created. Associated Multi value fields from BROKER.NO to BR.ENTL.AMT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system from the rate of the TAX record keyed on the SOURCE.TAX.CODE field.</p>
            <p>   The field contains the percentage used to calculate the source tax amount.</p>
            <p>   If APPL.GEN.CONDITION application has a record with id 'DIARY' or 'ENTITLEMENT', then CONTRACT.GRP is identified based on the conditions defined in the fields from DECIS.FIELD to DECISION.TO in APPL.GEN.CONDITION. In TAX.TYPE.CONDITION, the tax codes that are assigned to particular groups of contract (CONTRACT.GRP) are populated in SOURCE.TAX.CODE and the corresponding percentage is displayed in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax type applicable to this event.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate between the Event currency and the Account currency. Updated by the system while generating ENTITLEMENT records but user has an option of changing the value of this field. In the event any change to this field proper validations are done.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.CURR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency of the account number mentioned in the previous field.</p>
            <p>   Enriched by the Short description from CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field and updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The portfolio Account involved in the event. This Account will be used for all commissions, charges, taxes and cash entitlements.</p>
            <p>   This field is updated by the system when creating ENTITLEMENT records taking the default value from settlement defaults but user has an option to change this. If the portfolio has a suffix defined in REPO.PARAMETER as a RESO.MARGIN.SUF and ENT.CPN.SUSP is also defined then the account will be the internal account for the entitlement currency and the suspense category.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>   1-16 character Account number or 3-10 character Mnemonic Account id (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".").</p>
            <p>   Must be a valid Account on the ACCOUNT file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the relevant ACTIVITY.CODE as defined on EB.ACTIVITY</p>
            <p>   The following activity codes are possible</p>
            <p>   SC-0100 entitlement pre advice creation</p>
            <p>   SC-0101 entitlement pre advice amendment / deletion</p>
            <p>   SC-0102 entitlement confirmation advice (i.e. authorisation)</p>
            <p>   SC-0103 entitlement reversal via the ENTITLEMENT application</p>
            <p>   SC-0104 entitlement reversal via the DIARY application</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.ENT.AMOUNT</field>
		<desc>
            <p>Field showing Gross Cash Entitlement for each option. This field is updated by the system, taking all the parameters in the originating DIARY record into consideration.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
			<p>A override will be raised when this field is amended and if that doesnt match with ORIG.ENT.AMOUNT field.</p>		
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

