<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>INVESTMENT.PROGRAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>"Table" type file set up and maintained within the securities module. </p>
            <p>It helps to further categorise clients and their portfolio accounts. A typical type of INVESTMENT.PROGRAM might be an "AGGRESSIVE" policy. By using the MANAGED.ACCOUNT indicator an account executive can now extract information relating to discretionary clients with an "AGGRESSIVE" investment policy for perhaps high risk investment. </p>
            <p>Further examples of an investment policy could be "ALPHA STOCKS ONLY" or "CONSERVATIVE". </p>
            <p />
            <p>Enhancement with Asset Management product. </p>
            <p>Link portfolio to strategy, composed of main matrix, investment objective, currency, sizing. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the INVESTMENT.PROGRAM. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the INVESTMENT.PROGRAM in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters.  Multi language field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.LOTS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the treatment of standing instructions for corporate actions, more details on this can be found in the Corporate Actions user guide. It is a Multi-valued field associated with all the field to SELL.LOTS.TYPE. It will accept input of ALL, 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE, 'S-' followed by a Valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE, 'L-' followed by a product type or a valid security number.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>accept input of 'ALL',</p>
            <p>or 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'L-' followed by a product type</p>
            <p>or Valid security number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.DOMICILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the treatment of standing instructions for corporate actions, more details on this can be found in the Corporate Actions user guide. It is a Multi-valued optional field containing the country where the rights security is domiciled if rights processing instructions are set-up at a country level. Any input into this field must exist on the COUNTRY file. Associated with the field RIGHTS.TYPE, RIGHTS.CCY and RIGHTS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Country Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in COUNTRY file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.ODD.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>New multi-valued field. Input only allowed if the associated SELL.LOTS.TYPE field if not null, in which case this field is mandatory. This field will contain the standing instruction to be used when deciding whether to automatically sell any odd lots received. This field will allow input of 'YES' or 'NO' only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only 'YES' or 'NO' is allowed</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if the associated SELL.LOTS.TYPE field if not null,       in which case this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the treatment of standing instructions for corporate actions, more details on this can be found in the Corporate Actions user guide. It is a Multi-valued optional field containing the security currency if rights processing rules are set-up at a currency level. Any input into this field must exist on the CURRENCY file. Associated with the fields RIGHTS.TYPE, RIGHTS.DOMICILE and RIGHTS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 3 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if the Asset Management product is install.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PF.FEES.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It should be a valid AM.PF.FEES.TYPE record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the security currency if the  stock or cash decision is set-up at a currency level. Any input into  this field must exist on the CURRENCY file. Associated with the  fields STOCK.CASH.TYPE, STOCK.CASH and STOCK.CASH.CCY.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 3 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.LOTS.DOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the country where the redenominated security is domiciled if rights processing instructions are set-up at a country level. Any input into this field must exist on the COUNTRY file. Associated with the fields SELL.LOTS.TYPE, SELL.LOTS.CCY and SELL.ODD.LOTS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Country Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.DOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the security domicile if the reinvestment decision is set-up at a security domicile level. Any input into this field must exist on the COUNTRY file. Associated with the fields REINVEST.TYPE, REINVEST.INCOME and REINVEST.DOM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Country Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDG.MATRIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the matrix in the AM.MATRIX application that will be used to hedge a currency position in a a portfolio linked to this investment program. The hedging re-balancing function will generate forward FX transactions based on a pivot currency and 1 other selected currency and re-balance the hedging position in line with the matrix objectives. Multiple FX transactions can be generated simply by running the re-balancing process but changing the alternate and/or pivot currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RANKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.CASH.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the treatment of standing instructions for corporate actions, more details on this can be found in the Corporate Actions user guide. It is a Multi-valued field associated with all the field to STOCK.CASH. It will accept input of ALL, 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE, 'S-' followed by a Valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE, 'L-' followed by a product type or a valid security number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>accept input of 'ALL',</p>
            <p>or 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'L-' followed by a product type</p>
            <p>or Valid security number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLICY.PARAMETER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the POLICY.PARAMETER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Abbreviated description of the INVESTMENT.PROGRAM. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the INVESTMENT.PROGRAM in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters.  Multi language field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.LOTS.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field containing the security currency of the security that generated the odd lots. Any input into this field must exist on the CURRENCY file. Associated with the fields SELL.LOTS.TYPE, SELL.LOTS.CCY and SELL.ODD.LOTS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 3 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.INCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field. Input only allowed if the associated REINVEST.TYPE field if not null, in which case this field is mandatory. This field will allow input of 'YES' or 'NO' only. Will be used to indicate whether income amounts should be reinvested or not. Associated with the fields REINVEST.TYPE, REINVEST.CASH and REINVEST.DOM. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only 'YES' or 'NO' is allowed</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if the associated REINVEST.TYPE field if not null, in which case this field is mandatory.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field. Input only allowed if the associated STOCK.CASH.TYPE field if not null, in which case this field is mandatory. This field will allow input of 'RECOMMAND','STOCK' or 'CASH' only. Will be used to indicate the defaultoption when a choice of stock or cash is given. Associated with the fields STOCK.CASH.TYPE, STOCK.CASH.DOM and STOCK.CASH.CCY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This field will allow input of 'RECOMMAND', 'STOCK' or 'CASH' only.</p>
            <p> Input only allowed if the associated STOCK.CASH.TYPE field if not null, in which case this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the treatment of standing instructions for corporate actions, more details on this can be found in the Corporate Actions user guide. It is a Multi-valued option field. Input only allowed in this field if the associated RIGHTS.TYPE field if not null, in which case input is mandatory. Only input of TAKE-UP, SELL or BUY.MORE will be allowed. It will indicate the default action to be taken when a Rights Issue is being processed. Associated with the fields RIGHTS.TYPE, RIGHTS.CCY and RIGHTS.DOMICILE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only input of TAKE-UP, SELL or BUY.MORE will be allowed. </p>
            <p>Input only allowed in this field if the associated RIGHTS.TYPE field if       not null, in which case input is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p> No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATRIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The matrix field links the investment program to an investment matrix. The matrix sets the market segment weightings of the strategy being followed by the investment program. This matrix is used by the portfolio modelling functionality to rebalance a portfolio in line with the objectives.</p>
            <p>The matrix should be specifically matched with the investment objectives of the strategy and accordingly will </p>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input only allowed if the Asset Management product is install.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the AM.MATRIX file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.CASH.DOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the country where the rights security is domiciled if the stock or cash decision is set-up at a country level. Any input into this field must exist on the COUNTRY file. Associated with the field STOCK.CASH.TYPE, STOCK.CASH and STOCK.CASH.CCY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Country Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in COUNTRY file.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.OBJECTIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the AM.INVESTMENT.OBJECTIVE file.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if the Asset Management product is install.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIZING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the AM.SIZING file.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if the Asset Management product is install.     </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the treatment of standing instructions for corporate actions, more details on this can be found in the Corporate Actions user guide. It is a Multi-valued field associated with all the field to RIGHTS. It will accept input of ALL, 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE, 'S-' followed by a Valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE, 'L-' followed by a product type or a valid security number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>accept input of 'ALL',</p>
            <p>or 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'L-' followed by a product type</p>
            <p>or Valid security number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the security currency if the reinvestment decision is set-up at a currency level. Any input into this field must exist on the CURRENCY file. Associated with the fields REINVEST.TYPE, REINVEST.INCOME and REINVEST.DOM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 3 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROGRAM.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the INVESTMENT.PROGRAM record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory input) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the treatment of standing instructions for corporate actions, more details on this can be found in the Corporate Actions user guide. It is a Multi-valued field associated with all the field to REINVEST.INCOME. It will accept input of ALL, 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE, 'S-' followed by a Valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE, 'L-' followed by a product type or a valid security number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>accept input of 'ALL',</p>
            <p>or 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'L-' followed by a product type</p>
            <p>or Valid security number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.RISK.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.MATRIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the matrix in the AM.MATRIX application that will be used to rebalance the cash positions in an investment program. The currency re-balancing function will generate spot FX transactions switching cash from 1 account to another based on the absolute weightings defined in the matrix.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENTARY.DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENTARY.SUMMARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

