<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>MANAGED.ACCOUNT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                             MANAGED.ACCOUNT </p>
            <p />
            <p>Indicates the type of portfolio account, and more importantly how it is to be managed and maintained. </p>
            <p>Many banks offer a "Discretionary" service to investors, whereby the bank's officers have the "Power of Attorney" over decisions affecting the portfolio account (i.e. what, and when, to buy or sell, at what price etc.)  They will also decide the content of that portfolio with regards, to its holdings in for example equities, bonds etc. </p>
            <p>Some customers insist on running their own portfolios and these would be set up as "Non-Discretionary" accounts. </p>
            <p>Utilising this facility the ACCOUNT.OFFICER could obtain lists of, for example, all "Global" type safe custody accounts held on behalf of their branches or all "Discretionary" clients. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Abbreviated description of the MANAGED.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the MANAGED.ACCOUNT in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multi language field. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the type of MANAGED.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the MANAGED.ACCOUNT in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multi language field. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.PORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is used for grouping SEC.OPEN.ORDER. If PORTFOLIO.TYPE is selected in user defined parameter field of SC.GROUP.PARAM, then orders will be allowed for grouping based on the text defined in the field. The orders will be grouped together wherever the data on this field matches.</p>
            <p>E.g.</p>
            <p>If GRP.PORT.DESC in MANAGED.ACCOUNT record '1' is defined as 'ASD'</p>
            <p>                                                        record '2' is defined as 'ASD'</p>
            <p>                                                        record '3' is defined as 'LKJ'</p>
            <p>Then orders with portfolio set-up with MANAGED.ACCOUNT 1 and 2 will be grouped together. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />1-10 alphanumeric field(optional)     </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANAGED.ACCT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the MANAGED.ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

