<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>NOMINEE.CODE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                                NOMINEE.CODE </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any international bank offering a client a "Safe Custody" facility for stocks and shares held by that customer would have several nominee companies set up to facilitate easy transfer and delivery of those particular securities.  As these 'Instruments' are traded and delivered in various ways a bank must be able to handle each and every type of security. </p>
            <p>Registered stocks and shares are delivered by means of a stock transfer form.  The client exists on the issuing company's register.  To avoid having to contact each client for each transaction where a registered stock is traded and transfer forms need to be completed by the registered holders; the custodian bank will set itself up as a 'Nominee' company acting on behalf of its various clients.  They will have duly appointed authorised signatories and their 'Accounts' as such are audited annually as part of the pre-requisites for setting up that company. </p>
            <p>They will then act on behalf of their clients in transferring and administration duties on those securities held in that nominee name. </p>
            <p>As it is an important legal 'vehicle' it forms part of the SECURITY.POSITION key.  A shortfall due to an oversale or a wrongly utilised NOMINEE.CODE would cause delay and confusion. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Abbreviated description of the nominee company. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the NOMINEE.CODE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multi language field. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.SUPERVISED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether or not the bank has the power of attorney over the nominee company or not.   That is, it make decisions concerning securities held within that account or not.  If not, then the bank will carry out normal "Safe Custody" type duties without being able to make decisions without the "Go Ahead" from authorised personnel. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = yes or          N(O) = no, only (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the nominee company. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the NOMINEE.CODE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multi language field. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the nominee company record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric)  characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

