<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>PRICE.UPDATE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>A user maintained static information table to indicate to the system how and from where the SECURITY MASTER file, LAST PRICE field is to be updated with the latest price. </p>
            <p>There has obviously to be a certain amount of interface work to be performed at this point to enable the system to identify the price service indicated, and to pick up the prices correctly. For example, a user may utilise Reuters or Telekurs pricing services. He would therefore give each of these a separate ID and T24 would know where and how to access these particular price feeds and consequently update the SECURITY MASTER record. </p>
            <p>Additionally there are indicators within the file to:</p>
            <p>1. Illustrate whether the price update is automatic or indeed whether it needs to be done manually. </p>
            <p>2. Control the update of past prices and income details on SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PAST.UPDATE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls the input of historic prices in SECURITY.MASTER, the three inputs allowed are YES, NO or OVERRIDE, the default value is YES.</p>
            <p>If the field is YES then a user will be able to input a price in the past for any security that is linked to this PRICE.UPDATE code.</p>
            <p>If the field is NO then a user will not be able to input a price in the past for any security that is linked to this PRICE.UPDATE code.</p>
            <p>If the field is OVERRIDE then a user will be able to input a price in the past for any security that is linked to this PRICE.UPDATE code, but this will produce an override message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>An abbreviated description of the PRICE.UPDATE </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the PRICE.UPDATE method in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters Multi language field (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the PRICE.UPDATE record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.UPDATE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether Price.Updates to the SECURITY.MASTER will be automatic or manual. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes (automatic), or    N(O) = No (manual). (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the method of PRICE.UPDATE. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the PRICE.UPDATE method in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multi language field (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAST.UPDATE.INCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls the input of historic income details in SECURITY.MASTER, the three inputs allowed are YES, NO or OVERRIDE, the default value is YES.</p>
            <p>If the field is YES then a user will be able to input income details in the past for any security that is linked to this PRICE.UPDATE code.</p>
            <p>If the field is NO then a user will not be able to input income details in the past for any security that is linked to this PRICE.UPDATE code.</p>
            <p>If the field is OVERRIDE then a user will be able to input income details in the past for any security that is linked to this PRICE.UPDATE code, but this will produce an override message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

