<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>PRICE.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                      PRICE.TYPE </p>
            <p />
            <p>This table indicates to the system how a "Price Type" calculation is to be performed within any given transaction in the securities module. </p>
            <p>For example whether it is a percentage price and should be divided by 100 to obtain the correct gross amount, or where (as in the case of options) the nominal is a contract representing a given number of shares per unit (of nominal).  The user may indicate this by using the "MULTIPLY.FACTOR field" eg. Where each unit of the nominal amount represents an option on 1000 shares the "MULTIPLY.FACTOR" would be 1000. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The abbreviated description of the PRICE.TYPE. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the PRICE.TYPE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters Multi language field (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the PRICE.TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates which Price Basis is to be used. </p>
            <p>Indicates whether the price quoted for a Bond, includes or excludes interest accrued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>I = INC.ACCR, E = EXC.ACCR. (Optional Input.)  If this field is null, the system assumes EXC.ACCR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the price quoted on a security with this PRICE.TYPE is expressed as a percentage or a multiple of the nominal value. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes (a percentage), or    N(O) = No (a multiple). (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATION.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the formula used to calculate the consideration. </p>
            <p>This field is used to define the formula used to calculate the consideration. </p>
            <p>Examples: Where           C = Consideration           N = Nominal amount           P = Price           F = 1 or 100 (depending on the "PERCENTAGE" field)           T = Tenor in days           D = Number of interest days (360 or 365) </p>
            <p>                       (N * P * T) DISCOUNT  C =   N -  ---------------                          D * 100 </p>
            <p>                   N * P PRICE     C =     -------                      F </p>
            <p>                              N YIELD     C =       ----------------------                              ( T x P )                      1 +  -------------                              (D x 100) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>DISCOUNT, PRICE, YIELD (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>If "CALCULATION.METHOD" is YIELD or DISCOUNT the "PERCENTAGE" field must be YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the PRICE.TYPE. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the PRICE.TYPE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multi language field (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.INSTRUMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not the securities are discount instruments. </p>
            <p>In order to accrue or amortise the discount amount when a security is traded this flag must be st to "Y". This process will only be carried out for the banks own portfolios. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Values allowed are "Y" or "NO". (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>For "Y" to be entered the PERCENTAGE field must be set to "Y" and the CALCULATION.METHOD field cannot be set to "PRICE".</p>
            <p>For "NO" to be entered the CALCULATION.METHOD must be set to "PRICE".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTIPLY.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the weighting attached to the price quoted on a security with this PRICE.TYPE. </p>
            <p>Where (as in the case of options) the nominal is a contract representing a given number of shares per unit, (of nominal).  The user may use this field to indicate this value. </p>
            <p>Example:  Where each unit of the nominal amount represents an           option on 1000 shares the MULTIPLY.FACTOR would be           1000. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 numeric or "." characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>The default value for this field is 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

