<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>REDEMPTION.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used within the Bond Redemption module to identify and describe the various types of bond redemptions eg. Final, Partial etc. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes in abbreviated form the Redemption Type. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Redemption.Type in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multilanguage field (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTIAL.REDEMPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>To determine whether the redemption type used on the redemption detail record is partial or not. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y' or 'NO'.</p>
            <p>The validation is dependent on the value of the pre-advice run flag. a) If the pre-advice run is set to 'Y' then the partial redemption field can be 'Y' if the final redemption is set to 'NO'; or, it can be 'NO' if the final redemption is set to 'Y'. b) If the pre-advice run is set to 'NO' then the partial redemption can only be set to 'NO' and the final redemption can only be set to 'Y'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.ADVICE.RUN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the Redemption type is one where a pre-advice should be sent prior to settlement date. </p>
            <p>It is envisaged that there will be four different types of Redemption. 1 - Pre Advice of an early redemption where Securities will be automatically debited form the Base Security position and posted to a related Security Master record opened for that purpose and labelled as Early Redemption (See Redemption details for fuller explanation). </p>
            <p>2 - Early or Partial redemption where the System having effectively blocked the Securities with the pre-advice run merely withdraws the Securities from the Early Redemption Security Master opened as in 1. </p>
            <p>3 and 4 - The same format as above but for a final redemption instead. </p>
            <p>Unlike a partial or early redemption however the Securities are not blocked - as they may be traded right up to settlement date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = yes, or     N(O) = no. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Redemption Type. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Redemption.Type in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multilanguage field (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINAL.REDEMPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>To determine whether the redemption type used on the redemption detail record is final or not. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Y' or 'NO'.</p>
            <p>The validation is dependent on the value of the pre-advice run flag. a) If the pre-advice run is set to 'Y' then the partial redemption field can be 'Y' if the final redemption is set to 'NO'; or, it can be 'NO' if the final redemption is set to 'Y'. b) If the pre-advice run is set to 'NO' then the partial redemption can only be set to 'NO' and the final redemption can only be set to 'Y'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the Redemption Type record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Mandatory input) Examples:  FINAL = FINAL MATURITY PART OR EARLY = PARTIAL MATURITY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

