<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.BULK.TRANS.MATCHING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
            <p>To perform bulk matching in order to ensure integrity in parent child transactions</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the list of SEC.TRADE fields for which integrity checks are to be performed</p>
<p>Fields provided should be of only direct comparison fields (e.g.,Value date,trade date and Security No) and should not involve any calculations.</p>
<p>Local reference fields can also be provided by prefixing it as L-.</p>
<p>List of fields provided here will be compared between parent and child and exception log will be updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
            </p>            
            <p>Alphabetical characters</p>
            <p>A maximum of 21 characters may be entered</p>
   </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ORDER.EXCEP.CHECK</field>
<desc>
      <p>This field will determine whether exception checks are to be performed for order so that parent order will not be allowed to authorise until all child orders are authorised.</p>
              <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
             </p>            
               <p>Allowed value is YES</p>
   </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORD.FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the list of SEC.OPEN.ORDER fields for which exceptions are to be updated</p>
<p>Fields provided should be of only direct comparison fields(e.g.,Value date,trade date and Security No) and should not involve any calculations.</p>
<p>Local reference fields can also be provided by prefixing it as L-.</p>
<p>List of fields provided here will be compared between parent and child and exception log will be updated. This field is mainly used for reporting purpose and integrity checks similar to trade will not be performed</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
            </p>            
            <p>Alphabetical characters</p>
            <p>A maximum of 21 characters may be entered</p>
   </desc>
</t>
<t><field>APPL.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
