<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.BOOK.COST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement.</p>
            <p> As in the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to define in this file up to 999 Local Elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified. These Local Elements should be defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice.</p>
            <p> The name(s) of the new element(s), as well as the Format and <p>Validation Rules:</p>, must be defined in the LOCAL.TABLE, prior to the creation of any records.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 35 characters as defined in the LOCAL.TABLE file         definition for this LOCAL.REF field</p>
            <p> Multi-value field</p>
            <p> Optional or Mandatory depending upon the definition in         the LOCAL.TABLE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field should contain the value date from which the book cost adjustment is to apply. If left blank, will default to today's date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid date</p>
            <p> Must be equal to or greater than the TRADE.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>You should enter the id of the portfolio for which you wish to amend a particular security cost price</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a mandatory field</p>
            <p> Must be a valid portfolio, existing on the SEC.ACC.MASTER file.</p>
            <p> This cannot be a dealer book.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.BOOK.CODE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 transaction id, prefix SCCOST, julian date and transaction sequence number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the sub account for depository.</p>
            <p> SUB.ACCOUNT must be defined in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY record of the respective DEPOSITORY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-16 numeric characters</p>
            <p> Must be defined in CUSTOMER.SECURITY record for the depository</p>
            <p> Optional field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the particular security for which you wish to amend the book cost is a Kassenobligationen (KO) type security then you should enter the maturity date to assist location of the correct position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional field</p>
            <p> Input only allowed if the security is a KO type. These         are identified by the underlying SUB.ASSET.TYPE file         KASSENOBLIGATIONEN field having been set to "Y"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi-valued field to enable you to enter free-format narrative of your choice relating to the book cost adjustment of the underlying security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> None - free format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>You should enter in this field the id of the security for which you wish to amend the book cost</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> This is a mandatory field</p>
            <p> Must exist on the SECURITY.MASTER file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>In this field you should enter the nominee code in which name the security is registered. This is an optional field but if the security for which you wish to amend the book cost is held in a nominee name and you do not enter it, the System will report the position does not exist.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional field</p>
            <p> Must exist on the NOMINEE.CODE file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST.BSE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>You may enter in the base currency the amount by which you require to adjust the book cost. The fugure you supply will be an absolute amount.</p>
            <p> Whether the cost is to or decreased depends upon the SECURITY.TRANS code you specify in the TRANSACTION field.</p>
            <p> This is an optional field but at least one of this field, BOOK.COST.SEC.CCY and BOOK.COST.REF.CCY must be populated to cause the others to be calculated automatically using the appropriate exchange rate from the currency files.</p>
            <p> If you do not wish this field to be updated, you should enter a "0" (zero).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard amount field</p>
            <p> Optional</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST.REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>You may enter in the portfolio reference currency the amount by which you require to adjust the book cost. The fugure you supply will be an absolute amount.</p>
            <p> Whether the cost is to or decreased depends upon the SECURITY.TRANS code you specify in the TRANSACTION field.</p>
            <p> This is an optional field but at least one of this field, BOOK.COST.SEC.CCY and BOOK.COST.BSE.CCY must be populated to cause the others to be calculated automatically using the appropriate exchange rate from the currency files.</p>
            <p> If you do not wish this field to be updated, you should enter a "0" (zero).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard amount field</p>
            <p> Optional</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>You may enter in the security currency the amount by which you require to adjust the book cost. The fugure you supply will be an absolute amount.</p>
            <p> Whether the cost is to or decreased depends upon the SECURITY.TRANS code you specify in the TRANSACTION field.</p>
            <p> This is an optional field but at least one of this field, BOOK.COST.REF.CCY and BOOK.COST.BSE.CCY must be populated to cause the others to be calculated automatically using the appropriate exchange rate from the currency files.</p>
            <p> If you do not wish this field to be updated, you should enter a "0" (zero).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard amount, including "0" (zero) if no         change required</p>
            <p> Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>You should enter the depository at which the security is held</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> This is a mandatory field</p>
            <p> Must exist on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file and have a         CUSTOMER.TYPE of "DEPOSITORY"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>You should now enter an applicable transaction code to specify whether the amendment to the underlying book cost is a reduction or an increase.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
            <p> Must exist on the SC.TRANS.NAME file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the particular security for which you wish to amend the book cost is a Kassenobligationen (KO) type security then you should enter the interest rate to assist location of the correct position.Validation Rule.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional field</p>
            <p> Input only allowed if the security is a KO type. These         are identified by the underlying SUB.ASSET.TYPE file         KASSENOBLIGATIONEN field having been set to "Y"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>You should enter in this field the date on which the decision was made to amend the underlying book cost. If left blank, will default to the current system date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid date</p>
            <p> Must be less than or equal to the VALUE.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

