<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.BULK.TRANSFER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The application is used for bulk transfer of options. </p> 
            <p>It allows multiple positions to be transferred out from a portfolio or into a portfolio based on a single instruction.</p>            
            <p>On committing the record, T24 will create SECURITY.TRANSFER records in "IHLD " based on the selected positions.</p>
            <p>To input a record in this application OFS.SOURCE and OFS.VERSION for SECURITY.TRANSFER should be defined in SC.STD.POS.TRANSF.</p>
            
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the transaction. Only the sequence number (nnnnn) is required to be input.</p>
            <p>The Application will automatically generate the prefix (SCBLK) and the first 5 digits (yyddd) and attach the sequence number.</p>
            <p>The sequence number may be either User or System generated.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates what kind of a transaction is being processed. This field is mandatory and will accept a valid ID from SC.TRANS.NAME.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to TRANSACTION.TYPE in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the SC.TRANS.NAME file. (Mandatory input)</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Security.Account over which the  movement of the Securities, in the transaction, will be recorded.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to SECURITY.ACC in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>            
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>Standard Sec.Acc.Master id ; 1-10 numeric character Customer id (Field 8) separated by - from 1-3 numeric character Sec.Acc id. (Mandatory 
input) Default value = the Customers first Security.Acc. ie. nnnnnn-001.</p>
            <p>Must be an existing Sec.Acc.Master record.</p>
            <p>Must be a Sec.Acc. of the Customer </p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTERPARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the party to/from whom the transfer is to be made.</p>
            <p>You may input any of the following CUSTOMER.SECURITY types :            1)  Broker            2)  Counterparty            3)  Client</p>
            <p>Whereas the Broker and Counterparty are self explanatory the Client may be a Customer of the Bank who is not traditionally known as either a 
            Broker or Counterparty but as a Client (Without a Portfolio) who transacts business with the Bank.  It is therefore permissible within the 
            Sec.Trade application to enter a transaction on the Broker side of the transaction who will Purchase securities from a Client who is selling 
            those securities.</p>
            <p>The system is intelligent enough to know that the Client is effectively a Customer without a Portfolio and will ensure that the accounting 
            procedures for this transaction are dealt with properly.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to BROKER.NO in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric character Customer Id. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Customer for whom the CUSTOMER.SECURITY field CUSTOMER.TYPE equals either :       a) B    -   Broker       b) CO   -   
Counterparty       c) CL   -   Client</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.ADDR.BIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicate the BIC code of the counterparty BIC code is entered in this field if no records exists for the counterparty (CUSTOMER.SECURITY).</p>
            <p>When a BIC code is given; the DEFAULT.COUNTERPARTY from SC.STP.POS.TRANSF will be defaulted to the COUNTERPARTY.</p>
           <p>All the broker related SSI details in SECURITY.TRANSFER will be defaulted from SC.SETT.INSTRUCT record of BROKER.ADDR.BIC; if BROKER.ADDR.BIC 
           is not available then the broker fields will be defaulted from SC.SETT.INSTRUCT record of COUNTERPARTY.</p>
           <p>This field will be mapped to BROKER.ADDR.BIC in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHOW.POSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>If SHOW POSITION is set to "YES", all the underlying positions of the portfolio will be selected for generation of SECURITY TRANSFER.
             The individual positions will not be updated in the bulk transfer record. The field can be set as "YES" only while transferring positions 
             out of the portfolio.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the transaction is done is recorded in this field.</p> 
            <p>This field will be mapped to TRADE.DATE in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>            
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 9 type D date characters, (Standard Date Format in range 1950-2049). Default value = Run Date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Effective date of the transaction is recorded in this field. VALUE.DATE can not be less that the TRADE.DATE.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to VALUE.DATE in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>            
            <p>Up to 9 type D date characters, (Standard Date Format in range 1950-2049). Default value = Run Date.</p>
            <p>Can not be less than Trade Date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total charges for the bulk transfer  can be specified in the CHARGES field. If the charges are not specified in bulk transfer, the standard charges, 
            as applicable for security transfer, will be applied in the individual transfers.</p>
            <p>If a charge is specified here, then OFS.SOURCE, OFS.VERSION and FT.CHARGE.TRANS.TYPE should be defined for FUNDS.TRANSFER in SC.STD.POS.TRANSF.</p>
            <p> A funds transfer record will be created with transaction type as in FT.CHARGE.TRANS.TYPE, the debit account has CHARGE.CU.ACCOUNT, 
            credit account as CHARGE.ACCOUNT, credit and debit currencies as CHARGE.CCY and CHARGES as amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters  . (number of decimal places dependant on the currency of the Security).(Optional input)</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is mandatory when CHARGES is input, it will accept a valid T24 currency. It denotes the charge currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid T24 currency should be given</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CU.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will hold the customer account to be edited with the charge in CHARGE.CCY. This field is mandatory when CHARGES is given.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>            
            <p>Should be a customer account</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will hold the internal account in CHARGE.CCY or a PL category to which the charges will be posted. This field is mandatory when CHARGES is given.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Can be an internal account or a PL category. If a PL CATEGORY is input, it should be prefixed with PL (e.g. PL52603)</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will accept valid SC.DEL.INSTR ID. It is a mandatory field and the value in this field will be defaulted from broker SC.SETT.INSTRUCT record.</p>
            <p>If a BROKER.ADDR.BIC is given then the value will be defaulted from SC.SET.INSTRUCT of BROKER.ADDR.BIC.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to DELIVERY.INSTR in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) character Sc.Del.Instr code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the SC.DEL.INSTR file.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOT.ADVICE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This fields will accept the values "YES" and null. The value in this field will be defaulted from broker SC.SETT.INSTRUCT record.</p>
            <p>If a BROKER.ADDR.BIC is given then the value will be defaulted from SC.SET.INSTRUCT of BROKER.ADDR.BIC.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to DEPOT.ADVICE.REQD in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.HOLD.SETTLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>SEC.HOLD.SETTLE will be used to control whether stock will update the SC.SETTLEMENT application.</p>
            <p>SEC.HOLD.SETTLE will allow input of YES or NO only.</p>
            <p>The value in this field will be defaulted from broker SC.SETT.INSTRUCT record.</p>
            <p>If at all a BROKER.ADDR.BIC is given then the value will be defaulted from SC.SET.INSTRUCT of BROKER.ADDR.BIC.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to SEC.HOLD.SETTLE in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the security that is to be transferred. This field is mandatory when SHOW.POSITION is not set to "YES".</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to SECURITY.NO in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric character Security number separated from a 3 numeric character suffix by - </p>
            <p>Must be the ID of a valid Security.Master record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the place of settlement used in settlement instructions.</p>
            <p>The value will be populated from broker SC.SETT.INSTRUCT record.</p>
            <p>If BROKER.ADDR.BIC is given then the value will be defaulted from SC.SET.INSTRUCT of BROKER.ADDR.BIC.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to PSET in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicate the depository in which the security has to be delivered. The value in this field will be defaulted from SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to DEPOSITORY in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric character Customer ID number. Default value = the Depository specified on the Security.Master file record (Field Default.Depository).</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Customer in Customer.Security file with Customer.Type) as Depository.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the sub account at depository. This field will be mapped to SUB.ACCOUNT in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Nominal Amount (i.e. the face value) of the Security to be transferred. This field will be mapped to NO.NOMINAL in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the Price at which the NOMINAL.AMOUNT of the Security is to be valued for the transaction.</p>
            <p>Defaults to the LAST.PRICE, as recorded on the SECURITY.MASTER record of the Security.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to PRICE in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-15 numeric characters including if required, a decimal point.</p>            
            <p>Defaults to LAST.PRICE on the underlying SECURITY.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may be used instead of the PRICE field to record the gross cost in the portfolios specified REFERENCE.CURRENCY of the security to be 
            transferred into or out of the portfolio.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to COST in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the charges levied against the Customer for the transaction.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to CHARGES in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed when the field CHARGES has value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local tax, if any applicable, on the transfer.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to LOCAL.TAX in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the Accrued Interest due on the Security as on the VALUE.DATE of the transaction.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to INTEREST.AMT in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNDS.TRANFER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the ID of the FUNDS.TRANSFER transaction generated to collect a bulk charge on the transfer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>            
            <p>No input field, automatically generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.ADVICE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether a broker advice is to be sent. This field will be mapped to BROKER.ADVICE.REQD in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>            
            <p>It accepts the values YES/NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether a customer payment is to be made. This field will be mapped to PAYMENT.REQD in SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>            
            <p>It accepts the values YES/NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.REMARKS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to record any narrative to appear on any advices to the customer. This field will be mapped to CUST.REMARKS in SECURITY.TRANSFER</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Multivalue field.) (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies which Nominee Code, the Security in the transaction is to be moved into/out of.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) character Nominee.code. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Nominee Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUND.TRANS.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in this field will be defaulted from FUND.TRANS.STATUS of SC.STD.POS.TRANSF.</p>
            <p>The field specifies the record status to which the FUNDS.TRANSFER record will be moved on authorising the SC.BULK.TRANSFER record.</p>
            <p>If left blank then the FUNDS.TRANSFER record will be left in hold status.</p>
            <p>However reversal of SC.BULK.TRANSFER is independent of this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This field will accept the values "NAU" and "AUTH".</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TRANS.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in this field will be defaulted from SEC.TRANS.STATUS of SC.STD.POS.TRANSF.</p>
            <p>The field specifies the record status to which the SECURITY.TRANSFER record will be moved on authorising the SC.BULK.TRANSFER record.</p>
            <p>If left blank then the SECURITY.TRANSFER record will be authorised.</p>
            <p>However reversal of SC.BULK.TRANSFER is independent of this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This field will accept the values "NAU" and "HOLD".</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SSI.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be defaulted with a valid SC.SETT.INSTRUCT ID. The default will happen in the following priority (Broker_no.Portfolio_No) else with (BROKER.ADDR.BIC) else with (COUNTERPARTY).</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to SSI.CODE of SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FUNDS.TRANSFER.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
