<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.BUILD.UPFRONT.POSITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The application is used to record the NAV details for funds when known. Multiple trade references can be provided. </p> 
             <p>On committing the record, T24 will create two SECURITY.TRANSFER records in "INAU ".</p>
            <p>Transfer in record is created to buy positions of the original security for the NAV recieved.</p>            
            <p>Transfer out record is created to reverse the Dummy security positions .</p>
            
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the transaction. Only the sequence number (nnnnn) is required to be input.</p>
            <p>The Application will automatically generate the prefix (SCBUP) and the first 5 digits (yyddd) and attach the sequence number.</p>
            <p>The sequence number may be either User defined or System generated.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUND.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold Original security for which the NAV is captured. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>It should be valid security Master ID</p>
            <p>(Mandatory input)</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the Price (Net Asset Value) for the Original security. The NAV is the execution price for the fund order placed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>            
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TRADE.ID </field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the sec trade IDs for which execution details need to be updated.</p>

             <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field and it will accept valid SEC.TRADE credit transaction ids</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>UPFRONT.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This fields gets defaulted with the value in the field UPFRONT.SEC from security master application pertaining to the security defined in FUND.ID </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>