<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS </p>
            <p> This is an application which exists within the Securities' Module and allows the User to both block and to unblock security positions which exist either for his clients' Portfolios and/or the Banks' own books. </p>
            <p> When a person tries to sell a position which has been either completely or partially blocked, for whatever reason the System performs an on - line check and will advise the User accordingly. The override message will be stored at transaction level as per normal T24 proceedure. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NOTIFICATION.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the product which created the Block/Unblock record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> "NOINPUT" field</p>
            <p> Standard T24 Product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p> This is a NOCHANGE field.</p>
            <p> Must be the key to a valid entry on the NOMINEE.CODE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p> This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.AMT.BLOCKED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where the TRANSACTION.TYPE is 'BLOCK' the value of this field is the new nominal of the position that should be blocked.</p>
            <p> Where the TRANSACTION.TYPE is 'UNBLOCK' the value of this field should nominal that is being unblocked.</p>
            <p> For example, if the current blocked amount is 1000, an entry of 250 in this field (where the TRANSACTION.TYPE is 'UNBLOCK') will result in a new blocked amount of 750.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid denomination of the security.</p>
            <p> If the TRANSACTION.TYPE is 'UNBLOCK' the value of this field can not be greater than the current blocked amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.FROM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that the block / unblock should take effect. </p>
            <p> If the date entered is the system date then the block will take effect as soon as the record is authorised, however, if the date entered is a future date then it will be activated by the End of Day process.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 date field.</p>
            <p> This is a MANDATORY field.</p>
            <p> Date cannot be less than todays date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITIES.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The portfolio of the position being blocked or unblocked.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
            <p> A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p> This is a NOCHANGE field.</p>
            <p> Must be the key to a valid entry on the SEC.ACC.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 local reference field. This field allows the user to set-up their own user defined field for the application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Input only allowed if there is a record called SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS on the LOCAL.REF.TABLE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the reference of the transaction which created the Block/Unblock if it was not created by the SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> "NOINPUT" field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the sub account at depository. </p>
            <p> It must be defined in sub account fields of customer security record for the transaction depository.</p>
            <p> It is used to input the sub-account of the position to be blocked.</p>
            <p> Optional field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> 1-16 numeric characters</p>
            <p> Must be defined in CUSTOMER.SECURITY record for the depository</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will determine whether the transaction being entered is to effectively block a particular security position or to unblock it. </p>
            <p> The system will use this indicator as a pointer to whether or not the current amount blocked is being increased or decreased. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory Input. </p>
            <p> Only allowable input is "BLOCK" or "UNBLOCK"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.AMT.BLOCKED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current nominal of the security position that is blocked at the time of the transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p> This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the transaction. </p>
            <p> Only the sequence number (nnnnn) is required to be input. The Application will automatically generate the prefix (BBLKSC) and the first 5 digits (yyddd) and attach the sequence number. </p>
            <p> The sequence number may be either User or System generated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 10 Numeric characters, prefixed by BBLKSC, ie. BBLKSCyydddnnnnn. yy    = year (eg. 85 = 1985), ddd   = julian day (ie. 01/jan = 001, 02/Jan = 002, 01/Feb = 032, etc.), nnnnn = transaction sequence number (in the range, 00001 to 99999.). (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p> The sequence number (nnnnn) must be unique.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the block / unblock was created from a corporate action, this field will contain the ID of the DIARY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> No Input.</p>
            <p> Automatically updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTITLEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the block / unblock was created from a corporate action, this field will contain the ID of the ENTITLEMENT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> No Input.</p>
            <p> Automatically updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.DEPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Depository for the position being blocked or unblocked. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> 1-10 numeric character Customer ID number or 3-10 (uppercase alpha or numeric or "." character) Mnemonic Customer id. </p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
            <p> Must be a valid CUSTOMER, for whom the CUSTOMER.TYPE field on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY record is set to 'DEPOSITORY'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXERCISE.PRC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Exercise Price of the "Option" that the Security will be traded at assuming that the option has been exercised. The price is stored in the Security currency.</p>
            <p> This field will be populated automatically when an option is created in the Futures &amp; Options Module</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> "NOINPUT"         Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that the block / unblock should take effect. </p>
            <p> This is for information purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 date field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDITION.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free text field, for any additional information.</p>
            <p> Where a block / unblock has been automatically created from a corporate action, this field will contain the NARRATIVE from the DIARY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Upto 35 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p> Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.EFF.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used, together with the associated Field NEW.BLOCK.AMT , to display future Blocks or Unblocks that will apply to the SECURITY.POSITION being referenced.</p>
            <p> Displays the dates when changes in the blocked amount will change. </p>
            <p />
            <p> Shows the effects that already entered future blocking will have on the SECURITY.POSITION before this record is committed.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Shows the effects that future blocking will have on the SECURITY.POSITION if this record is authorised taking into account the changes that will be made by this record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCKED.UNTIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date that a position block will expire.</p>
            <p> This is an information field only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 date field</p>
            <p> Mandatory input if the TRANSACTION.TYPE is BLOCK.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.TO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date that a position block will expire. </p>
            <p> When the system uses this date is adds one working day before updating the record. This is done so that the block / unblock will include the EFF.TO.DATE entered.</p>
            <p> This will be activated by the End of Day process which looks for any blocking transactions which are due to be actioned upto &amp; including the next working day.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 date field</p>
            <p> Cannot be before the EFF.FROM.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.BLOCK.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used, together with the associated Field BLOCK.EFF.FROM, to display future Blocks or Unblocks that will apply to the SECURITY.POSITION being referenced.</p>
            <p> Displays the amount that the block will be on the associated date in the BLOCK.EFF.FROM field.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Shows the effects that already entered future blocking will have on the SECURITY.POSITION before this record is committed.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Shows the effects that future blocking will have on the SECURITY.POSITION if this record is authorised taking into account the changes that will be made by this record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the interest rate when the security specified is a kassenobligationen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the security of the position being blocked / unblocked.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid SECURITY.MASTER record.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the user to specify the maturity date of a kassenobligationen type security.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

