<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.CA.ERROR.LOG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>This is a error log to capture Straight Through Processing</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id is either DEPOSITORY-SEME.REF or SC.PRE.DIARY id or DIARY id</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the corporate action event being processed.</p>
            <p>This field is a single value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be set to YES if the corporate action event is being processed by Full Straight Through Processing.</p>
            <p>This field is a single value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be set to YES if the corporate action event is being processed by Straight Through Processing for the Lent portion of the security</p>
            <p>This field is a single value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Depository is updated from Diary.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Security to which the event relates to.</p>
            <p>Fields from SECURITY.NO to PSTA.CASH are associative multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Payment date of the event from the message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Ex date of the event from the message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIV.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Delivery reference of the incoming message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date of receipt of the message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of the message received.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEME.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The sender message reference from qualifier SEME in MT564 and MT566.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORP.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The corporate action reference as mentioned in the message in qualifier CORP in MT564 and MT566.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERRORS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The error details if any, are captured during every stage of the STP process.</p>
            <p>Sub value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WARNINGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The warining details if any,are captured during every stage of the STP process.</p>
            <p>Sub value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>If error is encountered in processing the Message then status will be updated as ERR and for warning as WARN</p> 
            <p>if there is no error or warning then OK and on authorising all the Entitlements as MAT.</p>
            <p>On receiving a cancellation message the status will be updated as CANC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For MT564 message it will be the processing code under tag 25D. For MT566 it will be updated as 566.</p>
            <p>When Updated from transaction, it will hold the variaous stages of transaction being processed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUANTITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Eligible quantity obtained from the tag 93B.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PSTA.QTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Quantity obtained from the Qualifier PSTA tag of MT566.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Net amount obtained from the  Qualifier NETT of TAG 92A.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Gross Amount obtained from the  Qualifier GRSS of tag 92A.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PSTA.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount obtained from the  Qualifier PSTA tag in tag 19B of MT566.</p>
      	  </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.DIARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only for manual intervention purpose.</p>
            <p>System does not perform any action on this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>User defined field. It is a multi value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.SECURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value to this field is derived based on the ISIN number in tag 35B of SECMOVE block. In case of multiple securities under ISIN, 
            this field will hold the ISIN number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an amount type field that will be updated with the value from Qualifier PSTA tag 19B in CASH MOVE block of MT566 </p>    
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
                        <p>This field holds the currency in which total cash is maintained from CASHMOVE block of MT566.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>TOT.SECURITY</field>
<desc>
                      <p>This field will be updated with security details from SECMOVE block of MT566.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>TOT.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
                        <p>This field will be updated with debit nominal from tag 36B in SECMOVE block of MT566. Will hold the debit nominal with a minus sign</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
           <p>Field that will be updated with credit nominal from tag 36B in SECMOVE block of MT566.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t><field>SC.CA.ERROR.LOG.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TOTAL.DEBIT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TOTAL.CREDIT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>

