<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.DEL.INSTR</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Table type file which needs to be set up within the Static Information area of the Security's Module.</p>
            <p>It is essential that these records exist before the user attempts to process any transactions.</p>
            <p>The file is structured to indicate to both the user and the system the type of settlement procedure to be carried out on any individual transaction within the Module.</p>
            <p>It indicates whether securities are to received or delivered and if that delivery is free or against payment.</p>
            <p>The system will then utilise this information to create open records on the Sec.Del.Control file which is effectively a record of all open settlements awaiting stock and/or monetary consideration. This file plays an important role when formatting delivery instructions to the various Clearing houses such as CEDEL and EUROCLEAR. It helps to determine the type of message being sent and the information contained therein. The Sec.Trade application is coded in such a way that certain fields become mandatory depending on the type of delivery instruction entered.For a fuller description of the validation rules and the file dependencies covering these delivery codes see the Securities User Manual covering this area.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INFORMATION.ONLY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to allow the user to define a delivery instruction that creates a SEC.DEL.CONTROL record for information purposes only. If YES is input into this field then when a transaction is input using delivery instruction a SEC.DEL.CONTROL record will be created without any checks being made to see if there is a delivery link.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Only Input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>Leaving this field blank will be treated as NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXISTS.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       Y      NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.BE.RECD.OR.DEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the transaction is of a type where Stock is to be either Received or delivered in the normal course of settlement.</p>
            <p>This transaction code is used within the Sec.Del.Control file to govern whether or not securities are expected to be delivered or received from the counterparty concerned. If set to "Y" then the Sec.Del.Control record will remain in an unauthorised state until securities are actually delivered and the nominal amount entered against the journal record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes, or      N/NO = No. Only. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       DEPOSIT      DEPOSITORY      NOMINATIVE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WITH.PAYMENT.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether (where this SC.DEL.INSTR is used) delivery is to be with payment or free of payment.</p>
            <p>If this field is set to "Y" within a given transaction payment is expected from the counterpart involved. The Sec.Del.Control application record for this transaction will remain in an unauthorised state until the amount of money to be received or paid matches that actually entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y = Yes (delivery with payment), or     N/NO = No (delivery free of payment), Only. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAND.Y.N</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       Y      NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.SETTLE.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether automatic settlement of counterparty limits take place.</p>
            <p>Input to this field is only valid if both  TO.BE.RECD.OR.DEL and COUNTERPARTY.LIMIT are set to Y.</p>
            <p>If automatic settlement of counterparty limits take place then during the batch relevant to  the value date of the SEC.TRADE deal the corresponding SEC.DEL.CONTROL record will updated as if complete settlement has taken place and the counterparty limit will reflect this.</p>
            <p>If automatic settlement is set to NO (or left blank)  then the user must update the relevant SEC.DEL.CONTROL record to indicate that delivery has taken place at which stage limits will be updated to reflect this.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.  Input is only allowed if TO.BE.RECD.OR.DEL and COUNTERPARTY.LIMIT are set to Y.  If input is made must be either Y or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTERPARTY.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether counterparty (broker) limits are to be applied for deliveries of this type.</p>
            <p>TO.BE.RECD.OR.DEL must be set to Y for input to be made.</p>
            <p>Y indicates that counterparty limit checking will take place for deals input via SEC.TRADE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input  Input is only allowed if TO.BE.RECD.OR.DEL is set to Y.  If input must be either Y or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.INSTR.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the SC DEL INSTR.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the SC.DEL.INSTR.</p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Sc.Del.Instr in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       DEPOSIT      DEPOSITORY      NOMINATIVE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes in abbreviated form the Sc.Del.Instr.</p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Sc.Del.Instr in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

