<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.DEPOT.POSITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Live file storing the nominals lent at a depository level through the application BOND.LENT.MASTER</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Either the portfolio the Security Position is for or the depot the security position is for. Format is 6N - 3N Where 6N is the customer number and 3N the suffix. The suffix is 999 is for the depository whose ID is the 6N prefix of this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sub-account that the security position is held in.</p>
            <p>   This sub account is defined in CUSTOMER.SECURITY record for this depository.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this security position is held by Nominee then this field will contain the ID of the Nominee. If this position is not held by nominee then this field will be blank.</p>
            <p>   If the position is held by nominee then this field will contain the ID of the NOMINEE.CODE record set-up for the nominee.</p>
            <p>   The Nominee Code (if any) will also make up the elements that make-up the ID of the SC.DEPOT.POSITION file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key of the SC.DEPOT.POSITION file is made up of a number of elements separated by dots. These elements are; Portfolio Number, Security Number, Depository, Nominee Code, Maturity Date, Interest Rate and Sub-Account.</p>
            <p>   Note ; The Maturity Date and Interest Rate are only included in the key of the Security Position if the Security the position is for is flagged as a KassenObligationen on the Sub Asset Type record the Security is linked to.</p>
            <p>   These fields make up the first seven fields of the SC.DEPOT.POSITION record.</p>
            <p>   The Portfolio Number is the depository where the position is held a with a suffix of '-999'. The Security Number is the Security Master ID of the Security. The Depository is the Depository where the position is held. The Nominee Code is blank if this position is not held by nominee and contains the ID from the NOMINEE.CODE file if this position is held by Nominee. The Sub Account is the depository sub account where the position is held.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Depository where the Security Position is held.</p>
            <p>   This field is a no input field that will contain the ID of the Depository where the security position is held. This field will contain the ID of a CUSTOMER record that is identified as a Depository on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file. The Depository in this field also makes the elements that make up the ID of the SC.DEPOT.POSITION file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only updated is this security position is for a Kassenobligationen security. A Kassenobligationen security is one where the Sub Asset Type record linked to the security has the KASSENOBLIGATIONEN flag set to YES.</p>
            <p>   If the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER is a Kassenobligationen security then this will be the interest rate for the security - taken from the INTEREST.RATE field on the Security Master record - at the time the SC.DEPOT.POSITION record was created.</p>
            <p>   The Interest Rate (if any) in this field will make-up the elements that make up the ID of the SC.DEPOT.POSITION file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only updated is this security position is for a Kassenobligationen security. A Kassenobligationen security is one where the Sub Asset Type record linked to the security has the KASSENOBLIGATIONEN flag set to YES.</p>
            <p>   If the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER field is a Kassenobligationen security then this will be the maturity date for the security - taken from the MATURITY.DATE field on the Security Master record - at the time the SC.DEPOT.POSITION record was created.</p>
            <p>   The Maturity Date (if any) in this field will make-up the elements tat make-up the ID of the SC.DEPOT.POSITION record.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.BOND.LENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Part - or all - of a Security Position can be lent using the application BOND.LENT.MASTER. This field will show the number of securities in the security position currently lent.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Security Number the Security Position is for.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

