<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.DAILY.ACCRUAL.DETAIL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Live file, providing a breakdown of the charge calculation for Advisory, Depository and Safekeeping charges where the PREV.MONTH.CLOSE daily accrual method is used.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ASSET.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains either a Security Number or, for a non-Securities asset, the Account Number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage used for the secondary ('fee-on-fee') calculation for a day-block.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate which was in effect for the day-block calculated by secondary ('fee-on-fee') processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ANNUAL.MIN.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where a minimum fee has been imposed, this field shows the annual minimum in local currency. Note that, in these circumstances, the calculation breakdown in the asset-based fields in this application relate to the original fee, prior to imposition of the minimum.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Result of the secondary ('fee-on-fee') calculation for the day-block in Local Currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days contained within a chargeable day-block, taking into account SAFECUSTODY.VALUES&gt;DAY.BASIS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Effective date for a chargeable day-block. If SAFECUSTODY.VALUES&gt;DAILY.ACCR.TYPE is set to DAILY.RATES then there can be multiple day-blocks for each chargeable month. Otherwise, EFF.DATE will be the first day of the charge month.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RES.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the day-block sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge type a record relates to. SC for Safekeeping, IC for Advisory, or DP for Depository.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.FT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>FT.COMMISSION.TYPE which was used to calculate the charge for a day-block.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.BASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Base amount, in local currency, used for the secondary ('fee-on-fee') calculation for a day-block. This amount is the result of the primary calculation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the asset multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge for a day-block in Local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.AC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the customer's charge account. The latter is defined on SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate which was effective on the EFF.DATE for a chargeable day-block.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.BASE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Basis amount which was used to calculate the charge for a day-block. This value is calculated by applying a charge percentage to the valuation for the asset.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge resulting from the secondary ('fee-on-fee') calculation for a day-block in the Charge Account Currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.SCALE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge Scale, derived from SEC.ACC.MASTER, which is effective for a chargeable day-block.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Effective start date for the day-block calculated by secondary ('fee-on-fee') processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the asset multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge for a day-block in the Charge Account Currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RES.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the day-block sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the asset multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Charge Period End Date for the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the asset multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days contained within a chargeable day-block, taking into account SAFECUSTODY.VALUES&gt;DAY.BASIS, and used for the secondary ('fee-on-fee') calculation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Depository key. Populated for SC and DP record types where the ASSET.TYPE is 'SC'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>SC for a Securities asset, or AC for a non-Securities asset, (e.g. precious metal account).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.AC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the customer's charge account. The latter is defined on SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RES.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the day-block sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.FT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Commission Type used for the secondary ('fee-on-fee') calculation for a day-block.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Security Account. The key to the portfolio on SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the asset multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.DET.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>A compound key consisting of the Security Account (portfolio key), Charge Type (SC for Safekeeping, IC for Advisory, or DP for Depository) and Charge Period End Date. These values are delimited with full stops (.) and are also available as fields within the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ANNUAL.MAX.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where a maximum fee has been imposed, this field shows the annual maximum in charge account currency. Note that, in these circumstances, the calculation breakdown in the asset-based fields in this application relate to the original fee, prior to imposition of the maximum.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ANNUAL.MAX.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where a maximum fee has been imposed, this field shows the annual maximum in local currency. Note that, in these circumstances, the calculation breakdown in the asset-based fields in this application relate to the original fee, prior to imposition of the maximum.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ANNUAL.MIN.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where a minimum fee has been imposed, this field shows the annual minimum in charge account currency. Note that, in these circumstances, the calculation breakdown in the asset-based fields in this application relate to the original fee, prior to imposition of the minimum.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge rate which was used to calculate the charge for a day-block.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RES.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the day-block sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCND.CHG.SCALE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge Scale (strategy) which was in effect for the day-block during secondary ('fee-on-fee') calculation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RES.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for expansion of the day-block sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

