<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.DIARY.EXEMPT.INCOME</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>SC.DIARY.EXEMPT.INCOME is used to record the proportion of income that is subject to tax (i.e. the taxable income) and also the clients. It is also used to record the details of clients exempt from tax along with the proportion of income (either percentage or amount) that is exempt from tax. The ID will be TAX TYPE* DIARY ID. It denotes the event and the tax type to which the exemption conditions apply. Validation rules : A valid tax type concatenated with a DIARY ID. </p>
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FATCA.TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc>
<p>The tax type to which the taxable income and exempt income, specified here, pertains to.  </p><p> validation rules: </p><p>The field is automatically updated based on the TAX.TYPE specified in the ID and is a no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.ID</field>
<desc>
<p>The DIARY to which the taxable income and exempt income, specified here, pertains to. </p><p> validation rules: </p><p>The field is automatically updated based on the DIARY reference specified in the ID and is a no-input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAXABLE.INCOME</field>
<desc>
<p>The proportion of income that is subject to withholding is set in this field. By default, the entire income will be considered taxable. However, in order to cater to events where certain portion of income is not subject to tax (e.g. non-US source income in the case of distribution by funds), the taxable income is given here. </p><p> </p><p> validation rules: </p><p>: </p><p> Percentage not exceeding 100%</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLIENT.ID</field>
<desc>
<p>The client (CUSTOMER) for who the exempt income has to be recorded. The field is associated with EXEMPT.AMT and EXEMPT.PERC wherein the amount or percentage of income that is exempt from tax, for the client, is specified. </p><p> validation rules: </p><p> A valid Customer ID from CUSTOMER.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXEMPT.AMT</field>
<desc>
<p>The amount of income that is exempt from tax for the client in CLIENT.ID field </p><p> validation rules: </p><p>Standard Amount field, Both exempt percentage and exempt amount cannot be defined</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXEMPT.PERC</field>
<desc>
<p>The amount of income that is exempt from tax for the client in CLIENT.ID field. </p><p> validation rules: </p><p>  Percentage not exceeding 100%, Both exempt percentage and exempt amount cannot be defined</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.OR.NET</field>
<desc>
<p>The field controls whether the reinvestment is to be on a gross basis (before application of withholding) or on net amount post the withholding.  Example: ANC Corporation declares a dividend of $1.5 per share which can be reinvested in the stock at $10 per share. A client who holds 5000 shares of ANC will receive a dividend of $7500. If the income is subject to withholding, the net amount available for reinvestment will be $5250 (30% WHT) with which he can acquire 525 additional shares of ANC. If the field is set to GROSS, the reinvestment will be based on the gross amount (in the above example, $7500 will be reinvested) with the tax amount being deducted separately. </p><p> validation rules: </p><p>GROSS or NET with input only allowed for Reinvestment event (DIARY TYPE flag). The field cannot be set to GROSS if the DIARY RATE.TYPE is net. By default, the reinvestment will be on a gross basis.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>SC.EXE.INC.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
