<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.DEF.ACCOUNT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application will only every contain one record called SYSTEM. This record will be used by the conversion routine CONV.SEC.ACC.MASTER.14.2 to set-up portfolio account defaulting from the old method using the three fields PURCHASE.ACCOUNT, SALES.ACCOUNT and DIV.ACCOUNT.NO to the new one which utilises application ids and securities transaction types (SC.TRANS.NAME). If nothing is entered then the system will default the Purchase Account for the Application SC only. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SALES.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>List of Securities Transaction Types that the user wishes to define as sales transactions. Will be used by the conversion program CONV.SEC.ACC.MASTER.14.2 to set-up the portfolio Account defaulting. The conversion program will take the account previously entered in the SALES.ACCOUNT field and then set-up the SEC.ACC.MASTER record to default this account when these transactions are used by the portfolio concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must exist on the SC.TRANS.NAME file.</p>
            <p>Must be defined as a debit transaction by SC.TRANS.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>List of securities transaction types that the user wishes to define as to default the accounts previously input in the DIV.ACCOUNT.NO field. Will be used by the conversion program CONV.SEC.ACC.MASTER.14.2 to set-up the portfolio account defaulting. The conversion program will take the accounts previously entered in the DIV.ACCOUNT.NO field and set-up the transaction types input into this field so that the accounts will default when these transaction types are used for the portfolio concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must exist on the SC.TRANS.NAME file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to the SC.DEF.ACCOUNT field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be SYSTEM</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PURCHASE.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>List of Securities Transaction Types that the user wishes to define as purchase transactions. Will be used by the conversion program CONV.SEC.ACC.MASTER.14.2 to set-up the portfolio Account defaulting. The conversion program will take the account previously entered in the PURCHASE.ACCOUNT field and then set-up the SEC.ACC.MASTER record to default this account when these transactions are used by the portfolio concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must exist on the SC.TRANS.NAME file.</p>
            <p>Must be defined as a credit transaction by SC.TRANS.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

