<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.DEPOT.ROUTING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this table is to allow the user to setup automatic depository transfer instructions for a particular depository. Records cannot be setup if actual settlement is used (see SC.PARAMETER&gt;ACTUAL.SETTLEMEN).</p>
            <p />
            <p>The automatic transfer will take place from a transaction depository to a holding depository.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatic transfers would only be produced by the applications SEC.TRADE and SECURITY.TRANSFER. They would be produced when the transaction was authorized.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The SC.DEPOT.ROUTING application is keyed on the Depository number, in this case the transaction depository. It will allow the user setup automatic depository transfers of stock.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Flexible criteria can be entered to indicate in which case the automatic transfer has to take place.</p>
            <p>he criteria can be entered on any field from CUSTOMER, SEC.ACC.MASTER and SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This means that if a portfolio is part of a bulk trade that purchases stock to be delivered to depository A (the transaction depository), then SC.DEPOT.ROUTING can be setup to automatically transfer that portion of the stock purchased on behalf of the portfolio to a different depository.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatic stock transfers would not be produced by corporate actions because the corporate action processing would take place at the depository where the stock is held. Similar logic would apply to security position blocking and bond lending. Automatic stock transfers would not be applicable for POSITION.TRANSFER as this application already has the functionality to transfer between depositories. This application would also act as a manual override for automatic depository transfers.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NATIONALITY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the fields from TRANSFER.DEPOT to TRANS.DELIVERY, containing the nationality of customers whose stock holdings should automatically transfer from the transaction depository (held in the key) to the actual depository (in the TRANSFER.DEPOT field).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2 Alphabetic (country code) characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on the COUNTRY table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEPARATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The purpose of this field is to allow the user to define a character to separate several values in the APP.VALUE field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The user can use the separator character in APP.VALUE only if the associated APP.OPERAND = EQ or NE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 1 character may be entered</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The following values are permitted: * , . /</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSFER.DEPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the Depository to which the Transfer is to be made according the conditions specified in the following fields.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field will contain the ID of a CUSTOMER record that is identified as a Depository on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-10 numeric character</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Customer ID number or       Customer id mnemonic. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid customer from CUSTOMER.SECURITY with type DEPOSITORY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the fields from TRANSFER.DEPOT to TRANS.DELIVERY, containing the type of security that should automatically transfer from the transaction depository (identified in the key) to the actual depository (in the TRANSFER.DEPOT field).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input must be as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A- followed by a valid asset type,</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>S- followed by a valid sub asset type</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>or a valid security number.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 10 characters (alphanumeric)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Security       number can be input in two different ways, either 1-6 numeric character       Security number separated from a 3 numeric character suffix by       "-". or 3-10 type MNE character Mnemonic Security id.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.DELIVERY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the fields from TRANSFER.DEPOT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If this field is YES then the depository transfer is a real transfer and d</p>
            <p>elivery messages informing the depository of the transfer should be produced</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If this field is NO then the depository transfer is a technical transfer (internal to TEMENOS T24) and</p>
            <p>the depository will not be informed of the transfer</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When stock is automatically transferred as a result of an SC.DEPOT.ROUTING record then if the TRANS.DELIVERY field on the SC.DEPOT.ROUTING record is YES, the depository to which stock is being transferred and the depository from which the stock was transferred should both receive stock transfer advices.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The depository from which the stock is being transferred should have a 522 (Delivery free of payment) message sent to it and the depository to which the stock is being transferred should have a 520 (Receipt of stock free of payment message) sent to it.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Note: this delivery will be produced in the same way as the depository advices currently produced by the POSITION.TRANSFER application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 3 Alphabetic characters may be       entered</p>
            <p>Allowed values</p>
            <p>: YES NO</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.DEPOT.ROUTING.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies a unique ID for each SC.DEPOT.ROUTING record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The key will be the depository for which the routing table is required.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A unique customer number must exist as a valid ID on the CUSTOMER file. This field will contain the ID of a CUSTOMER record that is identified as a Depository on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-10 numeric character Customer ID number or 3-10       type MNE character Mnemonic Customer id. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Must exist in CUSTOMER.SECURITY application with type DEPOSITORY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Record key, must be a valid DEPOSITORY defined in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.DOMICILE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all fields from TRANSFER.DEPOT to TRANS.DELIVERY, containing the country domicile of the security whose stock holdings should automatically transfer from the transaction depository (held in the key) to the actual depository (in the TRANSFER.DEPOT field).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2 Alphabetic (country code) characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on the COUNTRY table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the fields from TRANSFER.DEPOT to TRANS.DELIVERY, containing the residency of customers whose stock holdings should automatically transfer from the transaction depository (identified in the key) to the actual depository (in the TRANSFER.DEPOT field).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2       Alphabetic (country code) characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on the COUNTRY table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.APPLI</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Sub-valued field associated with the fields APP.FIELD, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE at a sub-value level and TRANSFER.DEPOT and TRANS.DELIVERY at a multi-value level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field contains an application name (allowed value : CUSTOMER, SECURITY.MASTER, SEC.ACC.MASTER)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field together with the fields APP.FIELD, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE are used to refine the selection of customers / securities / sec.acc.master to which routing instructions apply.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If any input is made into the APP.APPLICATION, the associated fields APP.FIELD, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE must be populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Values allowed : CUSTOMER, SECURITY.MASTER, SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Sub-valued field associated with the fields APP.APPLI, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE at a sub-value level and TRANSFER.DEPOT and TRANS.DELIVERY at a multi-valued level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the field name of a field in the APP.APPLI file.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field, together with the fields APP.APPLI, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE, are used to refine the selection of customers to which routing instructions apply.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If any input is made into the APP.APPLI field, APP.FIELD, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE must be populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input allowed only if APP.APPLI has been entered</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>0-18 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p>Must be a valid field in STANDARD.SELECTION of application specified in       APP.APPLI</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Sub-valued field associated with the fields APP.APPLI, APP.FIELD and APP.VALUE at a sub-value level and TRANSFER.DEPOT and TRANS.DELIVERY at a multi-valued level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field containing EQ, NE, LE, LT, GE or GT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If any input is made into the associated APP.APPLI then this field must be populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field, together with the fields APP.APPLI, APP.FIELD and APP.VALUE, are used to refine the selection of customers / securities / sec.acc.master</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2 characters field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid</p>
            <p>values       are :- EQ - equal to, NE - not equal to, LT - less than, LE - less than or       equal to, GT - greater than, GE - greater than or equal to</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Sub-valued field associated with the fields APP.APPLI, APP.FIELD and APP.OPERAND at a sub-value level and TRANSFER.DEPOT and TRANS.DELIVERY at a multi-valued level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field, together with the fields APP.APPLI, APP.FIELD and APP.OPERAND, are used to refine the selection of customers to which the routing instructions apply.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the content of the field defined in APP.FIELD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The user can use the separator character defined in SEPARATOR to specify several values for the associated APP.FIELD. This can be done only if the associated APP.OPERAND = EQ or NE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>0-35 alphanumeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOND.OR.SHARE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the fields from TRANSFER.DEPOT to TRANS.DELIVERY, containing the BOND or SHARE code of</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1       Alphabetic character</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values are B or S, where B = Bond and S =       Share</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

