<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.ENT.INSTR</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.LOTS.DOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field containing the country where the redenominated security is domiciled if rights processing instructions are set-up at a country level. Any input into this field must exist on the COUNTRY file. Associated with the fields SELL.LOTS.TYPE, SELL.LOTS.CCY and SELL.ODD.LOTS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Country Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the fields to REINVEST.INCOME. It will accept input of ALL, 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE, 'S-' followed by a SUB.ASSET.TYPE, 'L-' followed by a product type or a valid security number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>accept input of 'ALL',</p>
            <p>or 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'L-' followed by a product type</p>
            <p>or Valid security number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field, Input only allowed in this field if the associated STOCK.CASH.TYPE field is not null, in which case input is mandatory. Only input of RECOMMEND, STOCK or CASH will be allowed. Will be used to indicate the default option when a choice of stock or cash is given. Associated with the fields STOCK.CASH.TYPE, STOCK.CASH.DOM and STOCK.CASH.CCY</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Only input of 'CASH', 'RECOMMEND' or 'STOCK' allowed.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed in this field if the associated STOCK.CASH.TYPE field     is not null, in which case input is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.LOTS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the fields to SELL.ODD.LOTS. This field will accept input of 'All', 'A-' followed by a valid Asset Type, 'S-' followed by a sub asset type, 'L-' followed by a valid product type or a valid security number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>accept input of 'ALL',</p>
            <p>or 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'L-' followed by a product type</p>
            <p>or Valid security number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the fields to RIGHTS. It will accept input of ALL, 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE, 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE, 'L-' followed by a product type or a valid security number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>accept input of 'ALL',</p>
            <p>or 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'L-' followed by a product type</p>
            <p>or Valid security number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.DOMICILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the country where the rights security is domiciled if rights processing instructions are set-up at a country level. Any input into this field must exist on the COUNTRY file. Associated with the fields RIGHTS.TYPE, RIGHTS.CCY and RIGHTS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Country Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the currency of the security if rights processing rules are set-up at a currency level. Any input into this field must exist on the CURRENCY file. Associated with the fields RIGHTS.TYPE, RIGHTS.CCY and RIGHTS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 3 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.CASH.DOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the country where the security is domiciled if the stock or cash decision is set-up at a country level. Any input into this field must exist on the COUNTRY file. Associated with the fields STOCK.CASH.TYPE, STOCK.CASH and STOCK.CASH.CCY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Country Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the security currency if the stock or cash decision is set-up at a currency level. Any input into this field must exist on the CURRENCY file. Associated with the fields STOCK.CASH.TYPE, STOCK.CASH and STOCK.CASH.CCY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 3 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.CASH.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the field to STOCK.CASH. It will accept input of ALL, 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE, 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE, 'L-' followed by a product type or a valid security number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>accept input of 'ALL',</p>
            <p>or 'A-' followed by a valid ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'S-' followed by a valid SUB.ASSET.TYPE,</p>
            <p>or 'L-' followed by a product type</p>
            <p>or Valid security number must exist in SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.LOTS.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field containing the security currency of the security that generated the odd lots. Any input into this field must exist on the CURRENCY file. Associated with the fields SELL.LOTS.TYPE, SELL.LOTS.CCY and SELL.ODD.LOTS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 3 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.INCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field. Input only allowed in this field if the associated REINVEST.TYPE field is not null, in which case input is mandatory. Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed. Will be used to indicate whether income amount should be reinvested or not. Associated with the fields REINVEST.TYPE, REINVEST.CASH and REINVEST.DOM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed in this field if the associated REINVEST.TYPE field is not null, in which case input is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.ODD.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field. Input only allowed if the associated SELL.LOTS.TYPE field if not null, in which case this field is mandatory. This field will contain the standing instruction to be used when deciding whether to automatically sell any odd lots received. This field will allow input of 'YES' or 'NO' only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if the associated SELL.LOTS.TYPE field if not null,       in which case this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must be a valid CUSTOMER Id, SEC.ACC.MASTER Id or "DEFAULT"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard TEMENOS T24 Local reference field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the security currency if the reinvestment decision is set-up at a currency level. Any input this field must exist on the CURRENCY file. Associated with the fields REINVEST.TYPE, REINVEST.INCOME and REINVEST.DOM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Currency Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.DOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field containing the security domicile if the reinvestment decision is set-up at a security domicile level. Any input this field must exist on the COUNTRY file. Associated with the fields REINVEST.TYPE, REINVEST.INCOME and REINVEST.DOM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input of 2 alphabetic (Country Code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist in COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued optional field. Input only allowed in this field if the associated RIGHTS.TYPE field is not null, in which case input is mandatory. only input of TAKE-UP, SELL or BUY.MORE will be allowed. It will indicate the default action to be taken when a Rights Issue is being processed.  Associated with the fields RIGHTS.TYPE, RIGHTS.CCY and RIGHTS.DOMICILE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>only input of TAKE-UP, SELL or BUY.MORE will be allowed.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed in this field if the associated RIGHTS.TYPE field is not null, in which case input is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

