<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.FRONT.ORDER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a common order input screen used for capturing orders for Securities, Derivatives, Mutual Funds, Fiduciaries or requests for Fund Transfer between accounts, issue of Local or Foreign currency Drafts, Deposits and Forex deals. User can either give a Security Code or directly input the Product for placing the order. The system would automatically launch the respective detailed order input screen.  User will have to merely fill in minimal further details and the respective order would be created.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security and defaults the related fields such as Security No, Product, Order Type, Order Date and Time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Field will accept T24 SECURITY.MASTER or DX.CONTRACT.MASTER id or MNEMONIC or ALT.SEC.ID.</p>
            <p>1-6 numeric character Security number separated from a 3 numeric character suffix by "-". or 3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".") character or Mnemonic.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the product that is going to be traded like SC, DX, MF, MM, FD, FT and FX. The respective product can be selected from the drop down box provided. If a security is entered in the field SECURITY.CODE, then this field will be automatically defaulted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of the order is being placed viz., BUY, SEL, FUTURE, OPTION, FIXED, NOTICE, Subs, Redeem, AcctTrf, OutRemit etc. Order Type will automatically default, depending on the Product entered in the field PRODUCT(Product).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security Account(Portfolio)of the Customer.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard SEC.ACC.MASTER id ; 1-10 numeric character Customer id separated by "-" from 1-3 numeric character SEC.ACC.MASTER Id. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be an existing SEC.ACC.MASTER record of the Customer (CUSTOMER.NO field).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security number involved in this particular Order Transaction. This will get defaulted from the field SECURITY.CODE, if entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>T24 SECURITY.MASTER id or DX.CONTRACT.MASTER id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Time of the instructions contained within the transactions. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is the time of the order.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 8 Type T Time characters. Optional input. (Default is time the order is input)</p>
            <p />
            <p>Will default to current time unless a time is input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The time will be recorded in an HH:MM:SS format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVE.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the mode via which the order is being received like By Relationship Manager, Email, By Facsimile, Over Phone or Any other mode. A drop down box has been provided listing the standard modes of receiving the orders and the user can select the appropriate one from the list.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Customer on behalf of whom the order is being placed. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is not multivalue as it is intended as a single client,single order entry. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10 numeric character Customer ID Number or 3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".") character Mnemonic Customer id. (Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not currently in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date of the instructions contained within the transaction. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The default date is always the System date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 9 type D date characters, (Standard Date Format) Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Order ID of the final order created, i.e either SEC.OPEN.ORDER or DX.ORDER or FUNDS.TRANSFER etc.  This will be populated once the final order is created. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>