<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.GROUP.ORDERS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>SC.GROUP.ORDERS application enables to group alike SEC.OPEN.ORDER's. Multiple SEC.OPEN.ORDER's can be grouped together to make a single SEC.OPEN.ORDER. The parameter for grouping is taken from SC.GROUP.PARAM. This function of bulking SEC.OPEN.ORDER's facilitates in placing a single order to a broker for alike transactions. GROUP.ORDER field in SC.PARAMETER has to be set to MANUAL for manual grouping of orders. The OFS.SOURCE in SC.STD.SEC.TRADE must have a valid OFS.SOURCE record with a valid version of SEC.OPEN.ORDER  is to be attached in the OFS.VERSION field.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SC.GRP.ORDER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>When SC.GROUP.ORDERS record is authorised, a new bulked SEC.OPEN.ORDER record is created in IHLD status. This grouped SEC.OPEN.ORDER id is written in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SYSTEM UPDATED FIELD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.GRP.ORD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Unique Code used to identify each separate Security Group Order.</p>
            <p />Only the sequence number nnnnn is required to be input. The Application will automatically generate the prefix (GPORSC) and the first five digits (yyddd) and attach the sequence number. The sequence number may be either User entered or System generated using the Automatic numbering application.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p>10       Numeric characters prefixed by GPORSC, i.e. GPORSCyydddnnnnn. yy = year       (e.g.01 = 2001) ddd = Julian date (i.e. 01/Jan - 001, 02/Jan = 002, 01/feb       = 032, etc) nnnnn = transaction sequence number (Mandatory Input)</p><p /><p>SC.GROUP.ORDERS       cannot be duplicated.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows 'Yes' or 'NO' to be input. This field can be used to control the generation of SC.EXE.SEC.ORDERS from a grouped order as also generation of delivery messages. The value in this field would be relevant only if there is a) Routing has not been set in SC.PARAMETER or b) no SC.ROUTING record has been linked to the relevant grouped SEC.OPEN.ORDER.</p>
            <p>Note: SC.ROUTING id can be linked to a STOCK.EXCHANGE record which in turn can be linked to the Sec.Open.Order.</p>
            <p>If 'YES' is input, then the grouped order will generate an SC.EXE.SEC.ORDERS only under the following circumstances.</p>
            <p>A)</p>
            <p />If GROUP.ORDER field in SC.PARAMETER record for the relevant company id has a value MANUAL/AUTOMATIC  <p>B)</p><p />If grouped order carries the value &amp;#8220;TRANSMITTED&amp;#8221; in the field DEAL.STATUS.(This can be defaulted in the OFS.VERSION for SEC.OPEN.ORDER defined in SC.STD.SEC.TRADE-This is the OFS version used to authorize the grouped Sec.Open.Order when it is being generated). <p /><p>If 'NO' is input, then the grouped order will be created even if the value &amp;#8220;TRANSMITTED&amp;#8221; is not input in the DEAL.STATUS field.  </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p />Mandatory field   <p /><p /><p />'YES' or 'NO' allowed as valid input.     </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.GROUP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>If the SC.GROUP.ORDERS is created through AUTO-GROUPING, then the related SC.AUTO.GROUP.ORDERS id is updated in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />System updated field   <p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Reference to the grouped Sec.open.order created through the SC.GROUP.ORDER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />No input- system updated field   <p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field which can also be multivalued. A valid SEC.OPEN.ORDER id can be entered. If more than one order number is entered, then the system will check for the grouping parameters defined in SC.GROUP.PARAM application. If SEC.OPEN.ORDERs entered in this field do not satisfy the grouping criteria set in SC.GROUIP.PARAM, then they would not be allowed to be grouped.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />1-16 alphanumeric field(Mandatory)  <p /><p /><p /><p>A valid SEC.OPEN.ORDER id.</p><p /><p /><p /><p />Mandatory field     </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARENT.CHILD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allowed value is YES </p>
            <p>This is the flag to indicate whether the group order be created as parent child order or single order</p>
</desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

