<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.GROUP.TRADES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MANUAL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to manually add transactions to the multi-value set that will be processed.</p>
            <p>The record ID will be verified  the data checked to see if it is applicable for processing. The field clears after input to allow more record IDs to be entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid record ID for the application stored in the         associated field SELECT.APPL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTERPARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the Counterparty that will have their transactions grouped.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid counterparty in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY         application.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.TRADES.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the transaction.</p>
            <p>Only the sequence number (nnnnn) is required to be input. The Application will automatically generate the prefix (SCGPTD) and the first 5 digits (yyddd) and attach the sequence number. The sequence number may be either User or System generated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>10 Numeric characters, prefixed by SCGPTD, ie.         SCGPTDyydddnnnnn. yy = year (eg. 85 = 1985), ddd = julian         day (ie. 01/jan = 001, 02/Jan = 002, 01/Feb = 032, etc.),         nnnnn = transaction sequence number (in the range, 00001         to 99999.). (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Value Date entered here will be validated against the transaction being grouped. If the dates match then the transaction will be included for grouping.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid date.</p>
            <p>Populating either GRP.VAL.DATE or GRP.MAT.DATE is         mandatory.</p>
            <p>If both GRP.VAL.DATE  GRP.MAT.DATE are populated         they must be the same value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for depository messages</p>
            <p>This field is used to determine the place of settlement in MT540-MT543 messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Text of up to 15 characters can be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.SETTLE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is populated when the record is committed  is the sum of the CUR.PRIN.DR  CUR.PRIN.CR fields.</p>
            <p>This value will be used in the grouping of the transactions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.MAT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Maturity Date entered here will be validated against the transaction being grouped. If the dates match then the transaction will be included for grouping.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid date.</p>
            <p>Populating either GRP.VAL.DATE or GRP.MAT.DATE is         mandatory.</p>
            <p>If both GRP.VAL.DATE  GRP.MAT.DATE are populated         they must be the same value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CTPY.DEPO.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the account number for the Counterpartys depository  is used in generating delivery messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-6 numeric character Customer Id. or 3-10 type AAA (uppercase         alpha or numeric or .) character Mnemonic         Customer Id. or 1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters,         free format input. Multivalue field Subvalue fields to         record free format text relating to the Counterpartys         Depository.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CTPY.DEPO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the Depository that the Counterparty wishes to use for settlement.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A valid depository in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUR.MAT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Maturity Date stored in the transaction referred to by the APPLICATION  CUR.REC.ID fields.</p>
            <p>Some applications do not have a Maturity Date, in which case this field will be left blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to limit the selection of records when using the automatic version.</p>
            <p>Values can be defaulted into this field automatically by adding them to the parameter file for the specific application. The parameter files currently available are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Adding a value in this field only selects a field for possible use, populating data in the SELECT.DATA field will actually cause any selection to be performed.</p>
            <p>NOTE :- If selecting a multi-value field, then if any one of the multi-values contain the data then all the multi-values will be considered for netting.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The field must exist in the application entere in the         SELECT.APPL field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the T24 delivery message key that was used to generate the grouped message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The depository will be read from the transaction being grouped  will populated this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The determines the Credit  Debit codes that will be used when creating Swift messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in the SC.TRANS.TYPE application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a manual action is required by the user then it is displayed in this field.</p>
            <p>The manual action required can either relate to movement of CASH or the DELIVERY.  The messages displayed are configured in the application SC.GROUP.TRADES.MAN.ACT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the accounting generated by the netting is forward or not. Will be FWD if the accounting is forward, null otherwise.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.APPL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Select the application which requires grouping.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>REPO only at this time</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 statement numbers field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATCHING.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine which multi-value set to allocate each transaction to.</p>
            <p>It is determine by using the SYSTEM.FIELD  USER.FIELDs configured in the parameter files.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.SEC.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is populated when the record is committed  is the sum of the CUR.SEC.NOM field.</p>
            <p>This value will be used in the grouping of the transactions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
            <p>The value can be either positive or negative to reflect         the correct flow of the security nominal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the process that will occur when the record is authorised.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NETTING</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUR.REC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the details of this particular transaction to be deleted from the list of items to be grouped.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field does not allow data to be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOSTRO.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Nostro account will be used for the netting of delivery instructions.</p>
            <p>This field will be automatically populated but can be change manually.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid Nostro account for the currency of the Security         for the SC application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.DATA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Values from the potentially grouped transactions must match the values specified here for the associated fields set in SELECT.FIELD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSP.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Suspense account will be used for the netting of delivery instructions.</p>
            <p>This field will be automatically populated but can be change manually.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid internal account for the currency of the Security.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The sub account for the depository will be read from the transaction being grouped  will populated this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAPPING.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The system generated mapping key used in the message generation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the Security that will be grouped.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid security in the SECURITY.MASTER         application.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUR.PRIN.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the principle debit amount that is stored in the transaction referred to by the APPLICATION CUR.REC.ID fields.</p>
            <p>If the transaction is reflecting a credit then this field will be blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
            <p>Either CUR.PRIN.DR or CUR.PRIN.CR will be populated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUR.PRIN.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the principle credit amount that is stored in the transaction referred to by the APPLICATION  CUR.REC.ID fields.</p>
            <p>If the transaction is reflecting a debit then this field will be blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
            <p>Either CUR.PRIN.DR or CUR.PRIN.CR will be populated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUR.SEC.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the nominal amount in the transaction referred to by the APPLICATION  CUR.REC.ID fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
            <p>The value can be either positive or negative to reflect         the correct flow of the security nominal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUR.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Value Date stored in the transaction referred to by the APPLICATION  CUR.REC.ID fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the application for the transaction that has been selected for grouping.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.SELECT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This option allows the system to search records to determine if they meet the grouping criteria.</p>
            <p>Each application entered in SELECT.APPL will be searched  if applicable will be added to the grouping multi-value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>YES, NO or NULL.</p>
            <p>SELECT.APPL, PROCESS, COUNTERPARTY, SECURITY and either         GRP.VAL.DATE or GRP.MAT.DATE must be populated first.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.AGENT.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field was added for depository messages</p>
            <p>Forms associated sub value with BR.AGENT This field is used to determine the agents account in MT540-MT543 messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Only 10 sub values allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.AGENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field was added for depository messages.</p>
            <p>Forms associated sub value with BR.AGENT.AC This field is used to determine the agent(DEAG, DEI1, DEI2, REAG,REI1,REI2) in MT540-MT543 messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid customer number or any description</p>
            <p>Only 10 sub values allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

