<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.GROUP.PORT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The SC.GROUP.PORT application allows the grouping of a number of portfolios belonging to the same Department Account Officer so that the performance of the portfolios as a group can be monitored. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued language free-format field allowing the user to input a description of the portfolio Grouping. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Multi-valued field of free-format text.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANAGED.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub-valued field associated with the SEC.ACC.NO. These two fields are in turn linked to the multi-valued CUSTOMER.NUMBER field. These three fields are used to control which portfolios are included in the portfolio group. </p>
            <p>For example; If the CUSTOMER.NUMBER field contains 3000 This field contains                   23 The SEC.ACC.NO field contains         ALL The all portfolios belonging to customer 3000 whose MANAGED.ACCOUNT field (on the SEC.ACC.MASTER record defining the portfolio) is 23 will be included in this portfolio group. </p>
            <p>This field is sub-valued so that more than one type of managed account for a particular customer can be included in a particular group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the MANAGED.ACCOUNT file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.ADDRESS.</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The reference currency of the portfolio grouping. This is the currency all amounts relating to the portfolio group will be stored in. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Field cannot be changed once the record has been authorised.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format multi-valued field to allow the input of the address to send any reports on the information in this record to. </p>
            <p>If an address T24 will assume; Value 1 contains the Street and Street Number. Value 2 contains the town. Value 3 contains the post code. Value 4 contains country. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Free format field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERFORM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the fields CONTRIBUTIONS, WITHDRAWALS, INVESTED.CAPL and COMPARE.VALUE. This set of fields hold details of the performance of the group of portfolios. </p>
            <p>This field contains the dates that the figures relate to. The information is recorded at inception of the portfolio group and then monthly for the last 12 months. Multi-value 1 contains the inception details. Multi-values 2-13 contain the last 12 month's details. Thus the first value of this field will contain the start date of the portfolio group and the subsequent values the month end dates when the subsequent information was recorded. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INVESTMENT.PROGRAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Investment Program linked to the portfolio group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the INVESTMENT.PROGRAM file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILLER2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of the portfolio group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Will default to the current system date on first input if this field is left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILLER1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WITHDRAWALS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the fields PERFORM.DATE, CONTRIBUTIONS, INVESTED.CAPL and COMPARE.VALUE. This set of field hold details of the performance of the group of portfolios. </p>
            <p>This field contains the total of all the withdrawals from the portfolios in the portfolio group at the date in the associated PERFORM.DATE field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub-valued field associated with the MANAGED.ACCT. These two fields are in turn linked to the multi-valued CUSTOMER.NUMBER field. These three fields are used to control which portfolios are included in the portfolio group. </p>
            <p>For example; If the CUSTOMER.NUMBER field contains 3000 This field contains                   23 The SEC.ACC.NO field contains         ALL The all portfolios belonging to customer 3000 whose MANAGED.ACCOUNT field (on the SEC.ACC.MASTER record defining the portfolio) is 23 will be included in this portfolio group. If on the other hand this field contained 3000-1 then only portfolio 3000-1 will be included in the group. </p>
            <p>This field is sub-valued to allow the user to specify a number of different portfolios for a particular customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Any input must be "ALL" or exist on the SEC.ACC.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>Any portfolio input must belong to the customer identified in the associated CUSTOMER.NUMBER field.</p>
            <p>Any portfolio entered must have the same MANAGED.ACCOUNT as identified in the associated MANAGED.ACCT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the SC.GROUP.PORT file is the Account Officer who controls the portfolios grouped together in the SC.GROUP.PORT record together with a suffix of up to 5 alphanumeric characters separated by a '-'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be in the form DDDD-XXX where DDDD is the key to a Department Account Officer on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file and XXX is an alphanumerix suffix.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INVESTED.CAPL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the fields PERFORM.DATE, WITHDRAWALS, CONTRIBUTIONS and COMPARE.VALUE. This set of field hold details of the performance of the group of portfolios. </p>
            <p>This field contains the total of all the invested capital of the portfolios in the portfolio group at the date in the associated PERFORM.DATE field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field specifying the language any reports produced on this portfolio group will be reported in. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Only numeric input allowed.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the LANGUAGE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPARE.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the fields PERFORM.DATE, WITHDRAWALS, INVESTED.CAPL and CONTRIBUTIONS. This set of field hold details of the performance of the group of portfolios. </p>
            <p>This field contains the total value of all the portfolios in the the portfolio group at the date in the associated PERFORM.DATE field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRIBUTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the fields PERFORM.DATE, WITHDRAWALS, INVESTED.CAPL and COMPARE.VALUE. This set of field hold details of the performance of the group of portfolios. </p>
            <p>This field contains the total of all the contributions to the portfolios in the portfolio group at the date in the associated PERFORM.DATE field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued list of CUSTOMERs whose portfolios will be included in the group of portfolios. Field associated with the MANAGED.ACCT and SEC.ACC.NO fields so that this field will specify the customer whose portfolios - which are identified in the MANAGED.ACCT and SEC.ACC.NO field - are included in the group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory Field.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>Must be set-up on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file as a CUSTOMER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Account Officer who controls the portfolios grouped together in the SC.GROUP.PORT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
            <p>Defaulted from the key.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

