<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.GROUP.COMPARE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows a user to compare the holdings of all portfolios of a particular Account Officer linked to a particular portfolio model (or group of portfolio models) against their associated portfolio models, highlighting any difference that may occur.</p>
            <p>Data can be input into the SC.GROUP.COMPARE record using the Input or Verify functions. If the Verify function is used the record will produce an enquiry (Using one of the ENQUIRY records SC.GROUP.COMPARE.ASET, SC.GROUP.COMPARE.COUNTRY, SC.GROUP.COMPARE.GEOGRAPHIC, SC.GROUP.COMPARE.SECURITY depending on the value of the DETAIL.lEVEL field) showing all the portfolios holdings against their associated models. If this application is being run under GUI then this enquiry can be produced by typing YES in the RUN.ENQUIRY field, if it is being run under classic T24 then the Enquiry will be produced on pressing F5.</p>
            <p>Note; The Enquiry will only be produced if SC.GROUP.COMPARE is being run with the Verify Fucntion.</p>
            <p>If any of the portfolio models are defined at Security level (see POLICY.PARAMETER for more details about setting up portfolio models) then the user will be prompted whether they wish to generate security orders to bring the portfolio holdings back into line with its model. This will happen when the user leaves the record after running the Enquiry. If there is a variance between portfolio and its model then any orders will be written to the SC.SECURITY.ORDER application.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields MODEL.ID to VALUATION.AMT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The POLICY.PARAMETER records to be included in the comparison. Only those portfolios, under the responsibility of the ACCOUNT.OFFICER, associated with the stated POLICY.PARAMETER records will be reported.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid POLICY.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag controlling whether a hardcopy report is required or not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of YES/NO allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODEL.DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields MODEL.ID to VALUATION.AMT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only used when T24 is being run under GUI. In which case input of YES or NO is allowed. If T24 is being run under GUI and the function is VERIFY typing YES into this field will cause the Enquiry of the portfolio against model comparison to be produced.</p>
            <p>Under classic T24 this is a no-input field as the enquiry will be produced on pressing F5 when using the Verify function.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is a no-input field if the user is running under Classic T24 but inputtable if they are running under GUI.</p>
            <p>Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' is allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODEL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields MODEL.ID to VALUATION.AMT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXAMPLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag controlling whether to precede each model group by displaying the portfolio model.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of YES/NO allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUATION.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields MODEL.ID to VALUATION.AMT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.MODEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag that controls whether current positions are to be updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of YES/NO allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.PRINT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Pseudonym for PRINT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag controlling whether to round to the nearest whole number the variance value for viewing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of YES/NO allowed. Will default to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VARIANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Option used to calculate the variance. Controls whether the variance of the portfolio against the model, is to be calculated taking the tolerance into account of not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of TARGET or TOLERANCE allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GENERATE.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This must be set to YES if orders are to be generate in SC.SECURITY.ORDER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ACCOUNT.OFFICER for whom the comparison is requested.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ACCOUNT.OFFICER for whom the comparison is requested.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Will default the ACCOUNT.OFFICER in the ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALL.POSITIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag controlling whether all positions are to be displayed or only those will variances.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of YES/NO allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The level of detail at which the comparison is to be made.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of ASSET, SECURITY, COUNTRY or GEOGRAPHIC aloowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

