<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.GROUP.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext">
            <p>OVERVIEW</p>
            <p>SC.GROUP.PARAM is the main parameter file for both AUTOMATIC and MANUAL grouping of orders. This template takes input of various field names from SEC.OPEN.ORDER application. If a field name is input in the parameter table then while grouping the system will check for a same value in the field of the orders to be grouped.  </p>
        </p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>USER.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field to define additional parameters for grouping. This field allows ACCOUNT.MANAGER, CUST.NUMBER, LIQUIDATION.PERIOD, ORDER.DATE, PORTFOLIO.TYPE, PREMIUM.PRICE, STOCK.EXCHANGE, CUST.ACC.NO,CU and CU.EX.RATE.ACC. </p>
            <p>The grouping rules are that, if these parameters are defined in SC.GROUP.PARAM, all the above parameters except CUST.ACC.NO and CU.EX.RATE.ACC shall be the same across all the orders for grouping to take place.</p>
            <p>However if CUST.ACC.NO and CU.EX.RATE.ACC are defined then they should be the same for a specific portfolio, if the orders carrying such portfolio are to be grouped.</p>
            <p>Portfolio.type is a J descriptor linked to the SEC.ACC.MASTER and then to MANAGED.ACCOUNT. The value in GRP.PORT.DESC field in the linked MANAGED.ACCOUNT record should be the same for all the portfolios occurring across the orders that are sought to be grouped. Note: This</p>
            <p />facilitates grouping of orders by Portfolio type such as PEP portfolios, which may be defined in MANAGED.ACCOUNT file.   <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p />Multi-value, optional field.   <p /><p /><p />Allowed values are ACCOUNT.MANAGER, CUST.NUMBER, LIQUIDATION.PERIOD, ORDER.DATE, PORTFOLIO.TYPE, PREMIUM.PRICE,STOCK.EXCHANGE, CUST.ACC.NO,CU and CU.EX.RATE.ACC    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOO.LOC.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>A valid Local.reference field of SEC.OPEN.ORDER will be allowed to be input. If input, the field will act as an additional parameter for grouping.</p>
            <p>Note: The values in those Local reference fields which have not been set-up as a grouping parameter will have &amp;#8216;NULL&amp;#8217; value in the grouped Sec.Open.Order.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />1-35 Alphanumeric field   <p /><p /><p />Optional field   <p /><p /><p /><p />A valid LOCAL.REF field of SEC.OPEN.ORDER.     </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p> Input fields defined for the purpose of information only. Internally the system will use these fields from SEC.OPEN.ORDER as parameters for grouping. All these fields must be the same for any orders to be grouped together, if any of them are different then the orders will not be grouped.</p>
            <p>Care should be taken with multi-value fields as the data must be entered in the same order for the system to recognise them as the same.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid field in SEC.OPEN.ORDER</p>
            <p>NO INPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A user defined routine for specifying additional conditions to be checked for routing. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Must exist as a valid program.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>LOCAL.REF FIELD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.GRP.PARA.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid id for this record will be SYSTEM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

