<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.GENERATE.INST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows the user to define the sec trade ids for which delivery message can be generated </p>
            
            
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CU.ADVICE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag for customer advice, Yes for advice required.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.ADVICE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether a broker advice is to be sent.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    YES/NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOT.ADVICE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether a depository advice is to be produced.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    YES/NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.DELIV.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field which contains the delivery key for the clients' advice which has been produced within the Delivery Module.</p>
            <p>    Once the Sec.Trade has been picked for delivery process then Delivery Module will automaticaly produce an advice for the client with an unique key.Once this has been generated the ID will be written to the Sec.Trade and SC.GENERATE.INST.This means that all relevant information relating to an individual transaction can be retrieved allowing the user to obtain copies as and when required.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.DELIV.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Broker Delivery Key identifies each separate Delivery advice which has been produced by the Delivery module and gives the User a separate means of accesing copies as and when required.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No input allowed. Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.DELIV.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Depository Delivery Key identifies each separate Delivery produced by the System with regards the Depository used. No input allowed. Internally generated field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>SC.GEN.INST.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TRADE.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
