<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.ORDER.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ORDER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Record key, 10 character input, must be defined as a valid characters in ASCII.VAL.TABLE application, record STANDARD.S.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.ORDER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The generic order type to be used in SWIFT Messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Accepted values are BEST,MARKET,STOP,PRICE and CASH</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The input in this field determines the type of order which needs to be passed on to the broker. If set to YES, the order would be a Price Order with maximum/ minimum price to be specified and LIMIT PRICE would become mandatory in order</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>YES/NO field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input to this field determines whether the order is a cash order or not. In case of Cash orders, input of only cash amount in order is allowed and nominal becomes a no input field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>YES/NO field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the ORDER TYPE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3 to 35 type AA       (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multilanguage       field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.TRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field determining whether partial execution of orders with this ORDER TYPE could be partially executed. If this field is set to YES and partial execution of order takes place, an override is raised</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>YES/NO field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.PRICE.CHECK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input to this field is allowed only when LIMIT.PRICE is set to YES. This field determines if override needs to be raised when the execution price exceeds the limit price specified in order. If YES, execution price would be checked against LIMIT.PRICE, else no.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>YES/NO field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

