<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.POS.ISSUER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>Diversified margin value for each issuer and instrument is updated in this application based on the issuer diversification parameters in the OV.PARAMETER</p>
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ISSUER</field>
<desc>
<p>This field will hold the issuer defined in OV.ISSUER field of SECURITY.MASTER or ALL. Fields from ISSUER to EQ.MARGIN.AMT will be associated multivalue. Fields SECURITY.NO to EQ.MARGIN.AMT will be associated sub value set.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
<p>Total Margin value maintained issuer wise from SC.POS.ASSET record of securities</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ESTIMATION</field>
<desc>
<p>Total Estimation maintained issuer wise from SC.POS.ASSET record of securities</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPROVED</field>
<desc>
<p>If the issuer is in the part of APPROVED.ISSUER list in OV.PARAMETER then this field will be Y.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.POS.ASSET</field>
<desc>
<p>SC.POS.ASSET ID of the security number in SECURITY.NO field that is to be referred on applying diversification.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
<p>List of security numbers under the issuer that will undergo diversification checks. Associated sub value field with SC.POS.ASSET field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.MARGIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
<p>Adjusted Margin amount as a part of margin value check</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQ.MARGIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
<p>Adjusted Margin amount as a part of net equity check</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCEPTION</field>
<desc>
<p>Field to indicate that the security is excepted at the security level or sub asset level</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDEX</field>
<desc>
<p>Index field contains Security and depository concatenated with * for uniqueness in identifying the depository wise details while SEP.DEPOSITORY is set in SC.PARAMETER. For Fx transactions SECURITY.CCY is concatenated to differentiate buy or sell leg position</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.MARGIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
<p>This will be same as MARGIN.VALUE field in SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.ESTIMATION</field>
<desc>
<p>This will be same as VALUATION.AMT field in SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
</desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>
