<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.PRICE.CHANGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application stores information of all the Securities for which the Price/Yield is updated Manually. Information stored is New Price, Old Price, Bid Price, Offer Price, Income, Accumulated Income, Price change Date, User ID &amp; Date &amp; Time of changes done.</p>
            <p>  The information in fields TIME.CHANGE, NEW.PRICE, OLD.PRICE, INCOME, ACCUM.INCOME is updated during the Authorisation of a modification to a Security master record. Records can also be created and amended manually, at which time all fields can be input.</p>
            <p>  An archive facility is available to archive data in this file to SC.PRICE.CHANGE$ARC. This will be based on the date in ARCHIVE table, record 'SC.SEC.ARCHIVAL', field PURGE.DATE. Any information prior or equal to this date will be archived when Adhoc service SC.INT.ARCHIVAL is run.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the User ID. who initiated the changes to the Current Price/Yield.</p>
            <p>  Format : a) Standard User ID. format          b) Display Only</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>ACCR.DIV.RATE</p>
            <p>  This field is used to input the rate at which the dividend is to be accrued. This rate is then multiplied with the nominal balance on the SECURITY.POSITION of the security The product is then populated in the DAILY.ACCR.DIVIDEND file in the CURR.ACCR.DIV field. This is all done as part of the EOD process for Money Reserve (MRF) and on line for Money Market Fund(MMF).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Input specified by the customer. The amount will be in         units.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.CAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field captures the daily market capitalisation of the instrument. The market capitalisation is a product of the number of shares issued times the price.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.CHANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the time of day when a change of price or income details was recorded.</p>
            <p>  Part of multi-value set TIME.CHANGE to ACCUM.INCOME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.CHANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Security Code &amp; the value date for which the Price or Yield is changed on the Security.</p>
            <p>  Format : a) Valid Security Number &amp; b) '.' &amp; c) Standard Date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The new income amount recorded on the SECURITY.MASTER after a change to the INCOME field on the SECURITY.MASTER record</p>
            <p>  Part of multi-value set TIME.CHANGE to ACCUM.INCOME</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIF.WEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Foreign Inclusion Factor (FIF) of an instrument is a weighting assigned to an instrument that represents the proportion of shares outstanding that are deemed to be available for purchase in the public equity markets by international investors. In practice limitations on availablity include:</p>
            <p>  strategic and other shareholdings in an instrument</p>
            <p>  limits on foreign ownership.</p>
            <p>  The FIF is used by companies who compile indexes to provide a more accurate representation of company weighting in the index calculation.</p>
            <p>  A value between 0 and 1 should be entered.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.QUAL.MARK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This input for this field is determined in the application SM.PARAMETER, if the field PRICE.QUAL.FORMAT is not SWIFT then no input will be allowed, otherwise the list of valid entries will be determined from the fields CUM.INDICATE and EX.INDICATE in the same application.</p>
            <p>  This field indicates the price condition, as specified by SWIFT, for example CDIV indicates the price is 'cum dividend', XWAR indicates the price is 'ex warrants'. The user should consult the SWIFT manual for a full list of price conditions.</p>
            <p>  This field will be automatically updated if a price change is made to the SECURITY.MASTER record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Entry will be limited to values from CUM.INDICATE and EX.INDICATE</p>
            <p>  Only inputtable if PRICE.QUAL.FORMAT is SWIFT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Old Price/Yield input by the User.</p>
            <p>  Part of multi-value set TIME.CHANGE to ACCUM.INCOME</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFER.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 rate field.</p>
            <p>  Part of multi-value set TIME.CHANGE to ACCUM.INCOME</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the New Price/Yield input by the user.</p>
            <p>  Part of multi-value set TIME.CHANGE to ACCUM.INCOME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Security No. for which the Price/Yield/Income has been Changed by the User.</p>
            <p>  Format : a) 1 - 6 numeric chars Security Number separated from 3 suffix numeric chars by '-'. b) Display Only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCUM.INCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The new accumulated income amount recorded on the SECURITY.MASTER in the ACCUM.INCOME field.</p>
            <p>  Part of multi-value set TIME.CHANGE to ACCUM.INCOME</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BID.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 rate field.</p>
            <p>  Part of multi-value set TIME.CHANGE to ACCUM.INCOME</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.CHANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the date of the price or income recorded on this record.</p>
            <p>  Format : a) Standard Date Format b) Display Only</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Date &amp; Time at which the User made changes to the Price/Yield field on SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
            <p>  Format : a) Standard Date &amp; Time format.          b) Display Only</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

