<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.PORT.CONDITION.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the operator used to compare the value of the field in FIELD.NAME to the FIELD.VALUE(s).</p>
            <p>Mandatory value if  FIELD.NAME is entered must be either:</p>
            <p>EQ - Equals</p>
            <p>NE - Not equal</p>
            <p>LK - Like</p>
            <p>UL - Unlike</p>
            <p>RG - In the range</p>
            <p>NR - Not in the range</p>
            <p>GE - Greater than or equal</p>
            <p>GT - Greater than</p>
            <p>LE - Less than or equal</p>
            <p>LT - Less than</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value to be compared with the value extracted from the FIELD.NAME defined. Together with the OPERAND this is used to define if a condition is met.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies if special processing is required to the FIELD.VALUE defined before comparison can take place.</p>
            <p>A value of PERIOD will result in the FIELD.VALUE being added to the current T24 system date. For example a condition may be defined for bonds maturing in 6 months. This would be defined as FIELD.VALUE of 6M. If PERIOD is defined in this field a value of today plus 6 months would be compared to the bond maturity date.</p>
            <p>The type of field which requires special processing to determine the condition.</p>
            <p>Possible values:</p>
            <p>PERIOD - Used to determine a period on from a date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMBINE.COND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the ID to the SC.PORT.CONDITION.TYPE to allow combinations of existing conditions to be defined.</p>
            <p>This can be combined with conditions defined in FIELD.NAME to FIELD.VALUE or can simply be combined conditions. When conditions are specified here all combined conditions must be met in order for a comparison to be true.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>Must exist in SC.PORT.CONDITION.TYPE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONDITION.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the number of the condition. This is also the multi value location of the percentage of the portfolio meeting the specified conditon held in SC.PORT.MODEL in the fields CONDITION, COND.REF.VALUE and COND.REF.PERC.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Noinput field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONDITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Record id, minimum 3 characters, maximum 10, alpha numeric input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the field whose value is used in checking the Condition Type. This can be specified in the following formats:</p>
            <p>Field name</p>
            <p>Field name&gt;File&gt;Target Field</p>
            <p>The field name must exist in the Standard Selection record for SC.POS.ASSET, the file specified must be defined in Standard Selection, Target Field must be a valid field in that Standard Selection record. I-descriptors may be defined if required.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Field Name must exist in the Standard Selection record for SC.POS.ASSET</p>
            <p>File must a valid file with a Standard Selection record</p>
            <p>Target Field must be a valid field in the Standard Selection record of the File Name</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

