<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains company level default values that must be set up for the Securities module to run correctly.</p>
            <p>                These defaults will apply irrespective of the application, transaction type, or user. One record must be created for each company running the Securities module.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SPLIT.COMM</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field should be used to specify whether the commission plus commission tax should be shown as a separate accounting entry in the customer account. This 'split' applies only to the accounting generated from ENTITLEMENT.</p>
        <p>&#160;</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued numeric field associated with the BULK.TRANSACT field. Allows the user to define the maximum number of portfolios on a SEC.TRADE using the transaction code in the associated BULK.TRANSACT field before bulk processing is invoked to write to disk.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input must be numeric.</p>
            <p>                Input only allowed if something has been input in the</p>
            <p>                associated BULK.TRANSACT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CANTONAL.ROUNDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the rounding factor to be used for calculating the deal amount on which Cantonal tax will be calculated.</p>
            <p>                Example:  If a SEC.TRADE on a bond is done where the gross           amount of the trade was CHF1000 and the interest amount           was CHF45.  Assuming that the user had extered 1000 in           this field then the total deal amount of CHF1045 would be           rounded up to CHF2000 before the Cantonal tax rate was           applied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                0 - 10 Numeric characters (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPD.COB.EXCEP.LOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls the running of the close of business job SC.EOD.EXCEPTION.LOG. Unless this field is set to YES the job will not run.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.APPL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The valuation application is used to define routines called to evaluate, modify and enter selected portfolio positions in the SC.POS.ASSET file. This field specifies the module code for which the associated routines are intended. This forms a multivalue set with fields USR.PORT.SEL.RTN and USR.POS.RTN.</p>
            <p>                Purpose - These user defined routines are intended to give the flexibility to include or exclude contracts from a particular portfolio when updating the SC.POS.ASSET file for valuation purpose. In order to amend or make changes to the SC.POS.ASSET file, the user defined routines will be called from existing routines.</p>
            <p>                USR.PORT.SEL.RTN  routine will be invoked just prior standard search of customer contracts which are included in portfolio.</p>
            <p>                USR.POS.RTN routine will be invoked just prior to the write statement on SC.POS.ASSET. The routine is passed the record of the SC.POS.ASSET after processing in the calling routine and just before the updating the SC.POS.ASSET file, the user can make the modifications to this record to his requirement and pass back the array to the calling routine. So the changes can be reflected in the SC.POS.ASSET file.</p>
            <p>                 If the VAL.APPL is SC then the USR.POS.RTN  routine is passed the record of SC.POS.ASSET, after processing in the calling routine and just before the updating the SC.POS.ASSET file. But this routine doesnt overwrite the value calculated by the System. </p>
            <p>    The USR.PORT.SEL.RTN routine is not triggered for SC application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                2 alpha character Module Code. Input must be one of the following</p>
            <p>                AC, FD, FR, FX, DP(Deposits), MD, LC, RP,SW,SC     (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.REMAIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to control to retention of SC.PRE.DIARY records. If not set SC.PRE.DIARY records will be retained for 180 working days.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAR.VALUE.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls whether the value of the PAR.VALUE of a security (as set-up in the PAR.VALUE field on SECURITY.MASTER) is used in the calculation of the interest amount for bonds or not.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to YES then the par value of a bond will be included in any interest amount calculation. For example, if a bond has a par value of 2.00 dollars, an interest day basis of 360/360, an interest rate of 10 %, and two equal payments a year then the interest amount for a portfolio holding 100,000 bonds for a half year (180 days) payment is</p>
            <p>                AMOUNT = (180 * 10.00 * 100,000 * 2)          ---------------------------                (360 * 100)</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to NO  then the value of the PAR.VALUE field is ignored and for the example given above the interest amount will be calculated </p>
            <p>                AMOUNT = (180 * 10.00 * 100,000)          -----------------------               (360 * 100)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>                Will default to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD.MAXIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Rule 1</p>
            <p>                Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.CUST.DEPO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag controlling whether Custodian Depository in SEC.OPEN.ORDER should be defaulted or not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Only input of YES or NO is allowed.</p>
            <p>                Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field that allows the user to define the format of the ID of the SECURITY.MASTER file. Input is designed to be of a ######-### type format.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                No change field.</p>
            <p>                Will default to ######-###</p>
            <p>                Input must consist of only #s and -s. Where each # will</p>
            <p>                represent a number on the actual ID. Maximum length of Input is 12. Minimum will be of 4 #s.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the COMPANY to which the user must be signed on in order to use the application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                9 Alphanumeric characters in the format CCGGGLLLL where: CC is a 2 alpha character COUNTRY code. GGG is a 3 numeric character COMPANY code. LLLL  is a 4 numeric character local code or 2-3 numeric company mnemonic characters or 2-3 uppercase alpha numeric company mnemonic characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMPAIRMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether IMPAIRMENT is enabled. Allowed value is YES </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.HISTORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the length in working days that a Blocking record will remain in the live file of SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS before being moved to the History file by the End of Day processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                0 to 999 working days</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.CR.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Purchase transaction code to be used for external transaction </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if EXTERNAL.TXN is set to YES and is mandatory if EXTERNAL.TXN is set to YES </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.SUFFIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether, and for which modules, the Security valuation process will automatically assign deals for a customer which have not been specifically assigned to a portfolio to a default portfolio.</p>
            <p>                This field will be used by valuations update module to determine the customers portfolio when receiving non-securities data. If a portfolio is not entered on the transaction then the system will assign a default depending on the application supplying the data and this being in this field and also ensuring the customer is also a Securities customer.</p>
            <p>                Example  If customer number 123456 has two portfolios, 123456-1 and 123456-2, and they do a FOREX trade in which the PORTFOLIO.NUMBER field is left blank then</p>
            <p>                a    If this field is left blank then the deal will not be included on any portfolio valuation for this      customer.</p>
            <p>                b    If FX or ALL is entered in this field then T24 will default to the first portfolio it finds          for this customer (123456-1) that has not been closed and include the deal on that valuation. If all portfolios for this customer are closed then the first portfolio will be assigned.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                0 to 3 Alphabetic characters (Multi-value field) (Optional input)</p>
            <p>                Only the following values are allowed: Null - No applications will default. ALL - All applications will default. MM, FX etc which will be validated against the APPLICATIONS field in the COMPANY record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.STOCK.EXCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the STOCK EXCHANGE where the COMPANY usually trades.</p>
            <p>                If the company is resident in Geneva then they usually trade on the Geneva stock exchange, thus they should enter 003, (The Telekurs number for the Geneva stock exchange) in this field.</p>
            <p>                Also if the local stock exchange is the same as the stock exchange on the trade and the securities customer is a Swiss resident and an Effektenhaendler then there are no EBV fees.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                one to five Alphanumeric characters Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>                Must exist on the STOCK.EXCHANGE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a non-input field which will be released at a future date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISIN.VALIDATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional field.</p>
            <p>                Validation Rule</p>
            <p>                Only YES or NO only allowed. YES will be defaulted.</p>
            <p>                If it is set to YES then the field ISIN codes entered in SECURITY.MASTER will be validated otherwise they will not. Validation will be for a 12 character code with the first 2 characters being alphabetic and that the code validates against the check digit which is the last digit using the double add double algorithm (mod 10).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INC.OPEN.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used by ORDER.BY.CUST application to determine whether net open order positions are to be included or excluded in calculations of buy or sell nominals. If YES then open orders will be included, otherwise they will not.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXEMPT.EBV.FEES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Certain companies may be exempt stock exchange (EBV) fees for various reasons in various countries. (e.g. Finance companies are exempt EBV fees when trading on their local exchange in Switzerland)  This field defines whether or not the COMPANY is exempt EBV fees.</p>
            <p>                If the user enters YES in this field then the TAX.SUBROUTINE will not calculate EBV fees.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                2 or 3 Alphabetic characters (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>                Only the values YES or NO are allowed in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.HOUSE.DEALING</field>
<desc>
            <p> Determine whether Inhouse dealing is allowed.Allowed value is YES</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.ACCR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows accruing the dividends in the NET.ACCRUED.DIV and ORIG.ACCR.DIV fields of SC.POS.ASSET file. The process can be done at the event type level also.</p>
            <p>                If the dividends are accrued in the SC.POS.ASSET fields, the ENTITLEMENT value is reflected in the valuations for the period between Ex Date and Payment (or value) Date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input field</p>
            <p>                the values authorized are GROSS, NET, or null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMPAIRMENT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p> Determines Profit and loss category to be posted for impairment.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if IMPAIRMENT is set to YES and is mandatory if IMPAIRMENT is set to YES </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALC.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the cost of position fields in the SECURITY.POSITION application will be maintained on a trade date or a value date basis.</p>
            <p>                If the user enters Trade.Date in this field then the COST.INVST.SEC.CCY, COST.INVST.REF.CCY and COST.INVST.BSE.CCY fields will be maintained in trade date order, whereas if the user enters Value.Date in this field then they will be maintained in value date order.</p>
            <p>                If nothing is entered in this field the cost of position will be maintained in trade date order.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                1 - 10 Alphabetic characters. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>                Only TRADE.DATE, VALUE.DATE, or null can be entered in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the local reference field that can be used in entitlement instructions, security constraints AND investment programs to categorise securities</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.ORD.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO flag to allow the bank to specify whether they want to display the total customer nominal entered to be displayed in the top right hand corner of the SEC.OPEN.ORDER application or not. If YES is entered into this field then the total customer nominal entered for the order will be displayed in the top right hand corner of the SEC.OPEN.ORDER application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input restricted to YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MISC.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used as a category reference for miscellaneous items such as commission. The suspense amounts of miscellaneous items are posted to it.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                The value in this field should be a valid record existing in CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.SOO.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines the maximum number of sub-valued lines permitted in the SEC.OPEN.ORDER&gt;NARRATIVE field.</p>
            <p>If entered, the value must be in the range 1 to 999 inclusive.</p>
            <p>If this field is left blank then no maximum will be imposed.</p>
            <p>When choosing a setting for this field bear in mind that, if grouping orders, the resultant group order will collate the Narrative lines from the individual orders, and this field should reflect the maximum lines for such a combined record.</p>
            <p>Note that this setting does not apply to the fields DEAL.NARRATIVE and ACCT.NARRATIVE in the same application, which are restricted to a maximum of 3 lines.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARCH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts a date which denotes the Purge date until which the transactions will be archived.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Standard Date Format</p>
            <p>                Cannot be greater than or equal to the current system date.</p>
            <p>                Cannot be less than or equal to the last archived date ( field : LAST.ARCH.DATE )</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.DESC.SEARCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input allowed are YES or NO.</p>
            <p>                If the input is YES, the search of Security Master IDs by DESCRIPTION is enabled.</p>
            <p>                Input to field SEC.DESC.ENQUIRY becomes mandatory.</p>
            <p>                If the input is NO, then the field SEC.DESC.ENQUIRY will become NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.INCLUDE.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Mandatory field controlling whether or not accrued interest us included in the calculation of month end balances for Safecustody Fees and Advisory Charges.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to YES then any accrued interest for the portfolio will be included in the calculation of the month end balances used in the calculation of Safecustody Fees and Advisory Charges.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to NO or left blank then any accrued interest for the portfolio will be ignored when calculating the month end balance for the portfolio.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>                Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>                If no input has been made then the system will default NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT536.MAX.NO.TXNS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value in this field signifies the maximum the number of transactions that can be carried per message, provided it does not exceed the 10000 character limit set by SWIFT. If it exceeds 10000 characters, the message will be split. </p>
            <p>      Input to this field is allowed only if PRODUCE.MT536 is set to YES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>      Optional input. </p>
            <p>      Input must be numeric between 1 - 9999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-value field to allow a user to define which countries are local.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Will default to the Local Country defined on the COMPANY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCTP.BACK.VAL.MAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the setting used when maintaining the earliest date for which transactions details are to be retained in SC.TRANS.POS.HISTORY. Any transaction falling before this date will be removed from the history.</p>
            <p>                The field is a number of days and will default to 7300 if not set.</p>
            <p>                This field should only be set on instruction from Temenos and only when the implications of setting it are understood.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.DEL.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the outstanding amount and the outstanding nominal amount will be defaulted into the SEC.DEL.CONTROL record. Input of YES will cause the amounts to be defaulted.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to YES then any SEC.DEL.CONTROL record where there is no money or securities outstanding will automatically be authorised.</p>
            <p>                If the value of this field is changed to YES then any unauthorised SEC.DEL.CONTROL records where there is no money or securities outstanding will be authorised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input of YES or NO allowed</p>
            <p>                No input will be treated as NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLE.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows input of value US. This field controls the Special Processing such as</p>
            <p>                Generation of Broker Positions</p>
            <p>                Generation of SC.STOCK.ENTRY to record each position movement. (Refer to STOCK.RECORD functionality in User Guide for detailed information)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input allowed only if ACTUAL. SETTLEMENT field is set to YES</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCL.ACCR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in the field will decide if the the accrued interest has to be calculated until the next working day so that SC.POS.ASSET record will reflect the accrued interest value accordingly.</p>
            <p>                When this field contains the value NEXT.WORK.DAY, interest will be accrued until the Next working day.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JOB.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Rule 1</p>
            <p>                Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.NS.LOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a flag that when set to YES the log file SC.TXNS.WHILE.COB will be updated.</p>
            <p>             Valid inputs are YES or NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Intended for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCE.MT536</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value in this field determines whether system will support generation of outbound MT536 message or not. It should be set to YES in order to allow for generation of the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>      Allowed input is YES or NO.</p>
            <p>      Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUILD.CUS.PORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether Balance Movement related data needs to be maintained for Security  transactions in Customer Portfolios. A value in this field would be relevant only if the Balance Movement related data is specified for maintenance for SC or ALL applications  in  the field BAL.MVMT.APPS of  MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Valid values are YES/NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.ORD.MAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines to message number to be used by SEC.OPEN.ORDER confirmations.</p>
            <p>                This field is used to define which message will be produced by SEC.OPEN.ORDER as a confirmation. If 599 or 999 is input then the message concerned will be produced by delivery. If 500/501 is input then no SEC.OPEN.ORDER confirmation will be produced.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input must be 599 or 999 or 500/501</p>
            <p>                Input is mandatory and must be either 500, 999 or  500/501. Currently there is no default.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.BONDS.WTH.FTRS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a flag that will be used to indicate to the system when or not dealer books will trade in bonds with factors.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional Input</p>
            <p>                valid inputs are YES or NO</p>
            <p>                Null corresponds to NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the product category to be used as a default if system is unable to use the specified product category for any reason.</p>
            <p>                If the user has failed to enter a CATEGORY code in the SC.TRANS.TYPE table then the system will use the value defined in this field instead.</p>
            <p>                Prior to release 11.0.0 this value was hard coded as 22-999.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                4 or 5 Numeric characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>                Must exist as a valid CATEGORY code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMPTAX.LOCAL.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether stamp tax will be posted in Local or Foreign currency.</p>
            <p>                If the user enters YES in this field then Stamp Tax and EBV Fees on a trade will be collected in the currency of the trade, and posted in Local currency.</p>
            <p>                If, however, this is left blank then the flag on the file STK.EXC.LOCAL will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                0 - 3 Alphabetic characters (Optional input)</p>
            <p>                Only the values YES, NO or null can be entered in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TRANS.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Controls update of SEC.TRANS.INFO (for eu savings tax), set to NO to supress the update.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUPON.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the bank wishes to use the Corporate Actions system to process their coupons this field will contain the ID of the DIARY.TYPE that they will use to process coupon payments. If this field is entered then the system will cycle the INT.PAYMENT.DATE field on the SECURITY.MASTER record for the security concerned when a coupon is processed for the security. Also if this field has been updated then DIARY records will automatically be created by DIV.AUT.REQ and EOD.DIV.AUT.REQ instead of DIV.COUP.CUS records.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Must exist on the DIARY.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>                Optional Input.</p>
            <p>                If a DIARY.TYPE ID is entered here then the DIARY.TYPE record must be a CASH only record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHARED.SOO.EXE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.TRANSACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field linked to the BULK.LIMIT field. Input into this field will be validated against the SC.TRANS.NAME file. Used to define the transaction codes for which the bulk processing proceedure will be invoked if the number of portfolios on the SEC.TRADE transaction is greater than the figure in the BULK.LIMIT field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Must exist on the SC.TRANS.NAME field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEP.DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a YES/NO flag designed to allow the user to specify whether they want securities held in different depositories to be shown as such on portfolio valuations reports and sceens.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input of YES or NO only allowed. Defaults to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Suspense category to be used for external transaction in order to raise entry in the broker side and can be only contingent</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if EXTERNAL.TXN is set to YES and is mandatory if EXTERNAL.TXN is set to YES </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVER.TRADE.UNIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO flag to allow the bank to specify whether they want to allow transactions to be entered where the nominal of the securities on the customer side is not exactly divisible by the number of trading units or not. If this field is set to YES then if a Securities transaction is entered where the number of nominal on the customer side is not exactly divisible by the number of trading units for the Security concerned an override will result. The broker side will never allow the input of a nominal figure that is not exactly divisible by the number of trading units of the Security. If the field is set to NO all nominals entered must be exactly divisible by the number of Trading Units defined on the SECURITY.MASTER record for the Security Concerned.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input restricted to YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.EOD.ACCT.POST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not the DIV.COUP.CUS application should do its accounting at end of day to save time during on-line mode.</p>
            <p>                If the DIV.COUP.CUS application is to do its accounting at end of day then the user should enter YES in this field, otherwise they should answer NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                1 - 3 Alphabetic characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>                This field can only contain the values YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the end of the date range within which transactions should be selected. If entered, the date must be greater than the start date (entered in the previous field). This field is associated to JOB.NAME</p>
            <p>                Note</p>
            <p>                This date will be automatically cycled during the Start of Day processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                0 - 11 date characters. The year must be in the range 1950 - 2049</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.HOUSE.CR.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p> Purchase transaction code to be used for external transaction.</p>
            <p> Transaction code defined in EXT.CR.TXN cannot be defined.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if IN.HOUSE.DEALING is set to YES and is mandatory if IN.HOUSE.DEALING is set to YES </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.DIVIDEND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the maximum number of dividends for which details are retained on the SECURITY.SUPP for the purpose of calculating yields. If no input is made then details of all dividends will be retained.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional input</p>
            <p>                Any input made must be numeric.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUP.ACT.FWD.ENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is input able only when the settlement field is used, ACTUAL.SETTLEMENT field. This field has two options YES or NO.</p>
            <p>                YES enables the suppression of the forward entries.</p>
            <p>                That is, there will not be a STMT.ENTRY with a prefix F or a Forward dated entry when the Settlement is involved.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPD.STOCK.ENTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define whether records should be generated in the live file STOCK.ENTRY, which shows the movement for securities. Input in this field is only permitted where SETTLE.METHOD is set to US.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                YES if stock updates are required.</p>
            <p>                Otherwise leave blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.TOL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether the settlement tolerance values will be posted to an internal account or to PL. Must be in the range 10000 to 19999 for an internal account or 50000 to 59999 for a PL category. Unless this field is set no postings will be made to settlement tolerances accounts or categories.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.CLASS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used in conjunction with the previous field to populate the class on the SC transaction. Without this field set, the user will not be able to control the delivery message. This message class should be used in EB.ADVICES, which are associated to SC activity.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Cannot use the same EB.CLASS.NO for several LC.CLASS.TYPE (only 1 to 1 mapping is allowed).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.DIV.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO flag controlling whether tax calculated on dividends generated by the corporate actions suite of programs will post tax (YES) or simply record the amounts for information (NO).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input must be either YES or NO.</p>
            <p>                Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>                Will default to YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHARE.LENDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows shares to be lent using the application BOND.LENT.MASTER. If left blank or set to NO then the use of shares will be blocked in BOND.LENT.MASTER, if set to YES then the use of shares will be allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHF.ROUNDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field used to determine whether CHF rounding is required or not.</p>
            <p>                Value YES or  null indicates that CHF rounding is required and current way of CHF rounding will be followed.</p>
            <p>                Value NO will turn off CHF rounding</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHARED.SAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.BROKER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customer number(s) of the bank acting as a broker on its own or its customers behalf.</p>
            <p>                When the bank acts as a broker either on its own behalf or on behalf of its customers, the user should enter the customer number(s) of the bank as it operates in this regard.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                1 - 6 Numeric customer numbers or 3-10 alpha numeric customer mnemonic characters. (Multivalue field) (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>                Must exist on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file with the CUSTOMER.TYPE field having a value of Broker.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUATION.SUBR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the company specific valuation sub-routine that will be used to produce the customer or internal valuation reports as defined in the CUSTOMER.SECURITY, SEC.ACC.MASTER or OL.VAL.REPS applications.</p>
            <p>                Since every bank is likely to have special requirements vis-a-vis the layout of its valuation reports, this field will allow the easy implementation of different reports at different T24 sites and even for different companies on the same machine.</p>
            <p>                If no value is entered is this field then the system will use the default valuation sub-routine SC.ASSET.VAL.REPORTS.</p>
            <p>                If the company is entered (XXXX) this will default to SC.ASSET.VAL.REPORTS.XXXX.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                1 - 27 Alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>                Must exist as a Verb in the VOC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORP.ACTN.FX.SPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES or NO flag to allow the bank to specify whether they want corporate action financial postings produced by the ENTITLEMENT application that have a foreign exchange component to have the number of spot days that are defined on the FX.PARAMETERS file added to the value date or not.</p>
            <p>                YES will result in the spot days being added to the value date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input restricted to YES or NO.</p>
            <p>                Will default to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.ARCH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>No-input field which contains the Last Archived Date of TRN.CON.DATE file.</p>
            <p>                This will be used for validation purposes in the application level</p>
            <p>                i.e.Transactions cannot have a trade date falling before this date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.OLD.PORT.MODEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Can be used to stop the updates to the old portfolio modelling files when a valuation is run.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALTERNATE.INDEX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using this field user can define an ALTERNATE INDEX for the system other than SECURITY.NO.</p>
            <p>                Allowed values for alternate index are </p>
            <p>                (1) I.S.I.N. (2) EUROCLEAR.NO (3) CEDEL.NO (4) SEDOL.NO (5) SWISS.NO (6) CUSIP.NO</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                12 character alphanumeric</p>
            <p>                Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOD.ACCTG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to to post the settlement accounting entries during Start of Day instead of during End of Day. Inputting ALL in this field will post all the settlement accounting entries during Start of day.</p>
            <p>                Inputting nothing in this field will post the settlement accounting entries during End of Day.</p>
            <p>                Currently this field only allows inputting ALL. This field is made as a multi value set for the future enhancement.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                If ALL is entered in this field then this field is not         allowed for multivaluing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.SPLIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field should be used to specify whether the Local Tax should be shown as a separate accounting entry in the Customer account. The Customer will be posted with the Gross amount and a separate Local Tax amount.</p>
            <p>                This split applies only to the accounting generated from ENTITLEMENT.</p>
            <p>                The System will default to this field for Local Tax entries.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional Input.</p>
            <p>                Input can be YES, No or left Blank. Blank is equivalent to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERMEDIARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum number of intermediaries (agents) that can be used in SEC.TRADE  SECURITY.TRANSFER. If this number is exceeded then an override message will be raised. If not set then the maximum number will assumed to be zero.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the start of the date range within which transactions should be selected. This field is associated to JOB.NAME and must be entered.</p>
            <p>                Note:</p>
            <p>                This date will be automatically cycled during the Start of Day processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                0 - 11 date characters. The year must be in the range 1950 - 2049</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the method to use when calculating the margin value. This may be by asset only or by both asset and liability. Where ASSET is entered, all asset margin values will be calculated using the respective MARGIN.RATE in either ASSET.TYPE, SUB.ASSET.TYPE or ASSET.BY.CATEG and liability values will be 0.</p>
            <p>                Where BOTH is entered, the asset value will be calculated as stated above and the liability value will be calculated using the LOSS.MARGIN.RATE from ASSET.TYPE, SUB.ASSET.TYPE or ASSET.BY.CATEG</p>
            <p>                Where this field is left blank, both asset and liability values will be calculated based on the MARGIN.RATE field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input must be ASSET, BOTH or null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERPOST.SETT.TOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether values greater than the settlement tolerance, as defined in each CUSTOMER.SECURITY record, will be posted to the tolerance category account or PL account.</p>
            <p>                Can be YES, NO or blank, with YES indicating that values greater than the tolerance value will be posted.</p>
            <p>                Unless SETT.TOL.CATEG is set this field will have no effect.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.INP.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in the corporate actions service to automatically populate entitlement records using AUT.NEW.CONTENT (APIs and subroutines only).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether or not the COMPANY is involved in FUND type operations.</p>
            <p>                This field is reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                1 - 3 Alphabetic characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>                This field can only have the values YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.CLOSEDPORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to provide an option to switch off the calculations on closed customer portfolios in order to</p>
            <p>                increase the performance of some of the securities related COB jobs listed below.</p>
            <p>                EOD.PERFORM.UPDATE, SC.EOM.UPDATE and WRITE.SC.VAL.EXTRACT</p>
            <p>                A portfolio will only be considered as closed if the following conditions apply,</p>
            <p>                1)Closure date in SEC.ACC.MASTER is less than the current system/bank date</p>
            <p>                2)If safekeeping fees are setup then the fees must be posted or zero in SAFEKEEP.HOLDING</p>
            <p>                3)If advisory fees are setup then the fees must be posted or zero in SC.ADVISORY.CHG</p>
            <p>                This parameter will only apply to customer portfolios, dealer books will not be ignored.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to NO, any calculation on closed portfolios will be switched off.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.DESC.ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enquiry name is attached here.</p>
            <p>                The record name should be a valid input in Enquiry file.</p>
            <p>                The enquiry, which would search the Securities by the DESCRIPTION, should be attached here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Mandatory when field SEC.DESC.SEARCH is YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.MT548.IN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value in this field determines whether system will support inbound MT548 message or not. It should be set to YES in order to allow inbound MT548 message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Allowed input is YES or null.</p>
            <p>     Optional input. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.MAT.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input the number of days after a SC.SETTLEMENT has been completely settled that it will be written to history.</p>
            <p>                Once the settlement record has been moved to history it will not be possible to reverse the underlying transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                3 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESEQUENCE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days back the application RESEQ.TRN.DATE can go to find securities transactions for resequencing when resequencing a security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional numeric field allowing input of between 0 and 999 days.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.INCLUDE.SHORT</field>
<desc>
            <p> Indicates whether or not short position is included for both safekeep fee and PM  fee type calculation.</p>
            <p> There are four possible values for this field . They are </p>
            <p> YES - short position can be included in either of the fee type calculations.</p>
            <p> NO - short position cannot  be included in either of the fee type calculations.</p>
            <p> SAFE - short position will be considered only on calculation of safekeep fee and not for calculation of PM fee.</p>
            <p> ADV - short position will be considered only on calculation of PM fee and not for calculation of safe keep fee.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.SUBROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the country specific subroutine used to calculate Stamp tax and/or Cantonal tax and EBV fees where applicable.</p>
            <p>                Since every country is likely to have its own unique tax rules, the use of this field will allow easy implementation of those different tax rules at sites in different countries.</p>
            <p>                If the country code of the T24 user is entered (XX), it will then default to SC.SE.CALC.LOCAL will be used to carry out the calculations.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                0 - 27 Alphanumeric characters (Optional input)</p>
            <p>                Must exist as a Verb in VOC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSP.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Portfolio ID of the suspense portfolio to be used in orporate action processing when original portfolios are closed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Must be a valid SEC.ACC.MASTER record with memo account</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.LOCAL.TRADING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Controls updates of daily concat file, SEC.TRADE delivery and supression of some concat file updates when set to Y.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPD.VAL.EXTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p> If set to YES SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT is updated when AM module is not installed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.EOD.RTNE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used by EOD.DIV.AUT.REQ when generating automatic diary events in the close of business</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIN.COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will accept a value TRANSACTION. Once specified, SECURITY.POSITION field FIN.COMPANY will hold only the company where first position is created. This field is mainly used for ACU, DBU processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determine whether external transaction is allowed. Allowed value is YES</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.CLASS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>SC.CLASS.TYPE and EB.CLASS.NO are used to formulate the class mapping between SC internal class and EB.MESSAGE.CLASS. The main driving concept of ACTIVITY and CLASS has lend itself to facilitate the user by automatically trigger only the message related to the operation, which user are currently do. In a sense, the system will try to default a sensible CLASS tiding to corresponding activity, and populate the information on the SC transaction. Consequently, the user can take control of the class to choose whether he/she wants to produce as per suggestion by the system.</p>
            <p>                The following types are valid types:</p>
            <p>                + BASIC.MESSAGE</p>
            <p>                + NEW.MESSAGE</p>
            <p>                + MODIFICATION</p>
            <p>                + CANCELLATION</p>
            <p>                + USER.DEFINE1</p>
            <p>                + USER.DEFINE2</p>
            <p>                + USER.DEFINE9</p>
            <p>                NEW.MESSAGE will be triggered for new SEC.OPEN.ORDER where CONFIRMATION is set to YES</p>
            <p>                MODIFICATION will be triggered If there is a change in AMT.TO.BROKER field between R.NEW and R.OLD of SEC.OPEN.ORDER</p>
            <p>                CANCELLATION will be triggered when SEC.OPEN.ORDER is reversed or BROKER is deleted from SEC.OPEN.ORDER</p>
            <p>                If message class needs to be triggered irrespective of any condition then,  message BASIC.MESSAGE and USER.DEFINE1 to USER.DEFINE9 will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Only the following values are allowed </p>
            <p>                BASIC.MESSAGE</p>
            <p>                NEW.MESSAGE</p>
            <p>                MODIFICATION</p>
            <p>                CANCELLATION</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE1</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE2</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE3</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE4</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE5</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE6</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE7</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE8</p>
            <p>                USER.DEFINE9</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDEMPTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the bank wishes to use the Corporate Actions system to process their bond redemptions this field will contain the ID of the DIARY.TYPE that they will use to process redemptions.</p>
            <p>                If this field has been updated then DIARY records will automatically be created by EOD.REDEM.AUT.REQ instead of REDEMPTION.DET records.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Must exist on the DIARY.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>                Optional Input.</p>
            <p>                If a DIARY.TYPE ID is entered here then the DIARY.TYPE record must be a CASH only record that does not retain the original holding.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.TAX.SPLIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field should be used to specify whether the Source Tax should be shown as a separate accounting entry in the Customer account. The Customer will be posted with the Gross amount and a separate Source Tax amount.</p>
            <p>                This split applies only to the accounting generated from ENTITLEMENT.</p>
            <p>                The System will default to this field for Source Tax entries.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional Input.</p>
            <p>                Input can be YES, No or left Blank. Blank is equivalent to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.TRANS.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will take entries defined on SC.TRANS.NAME file. Input to this field is only permitted if field SECT.PEND is set to #8220;YES#8221;. Otherwise no input is allowed. Any SECURITY.TRANSFER with a transaction code defined on this field will be a free transfer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALN.DATA.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Integer, up to 999, determines the number of seconds for which valuation data (SC.POS.ASSET) will be deemed as current before a rebuild is done. Currently not used. Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OBC.CASH.ORD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used as the order type in SEC.OPEN.ORDER when a cash order is created from ORDER.BY.CUST.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAFEKEEP.REPORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name of the routine which produces an alternative safekeeping journal report</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional Input</p>
            <p>                Must exist in PGM.FILE as a TYPE S record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A check to determine whether issuer limits are to be updated with nominal or traded amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Accepted values are CASH and NOMINALS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.BASE.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field decides whether the Capital Gains Base is updated or not. A value of YES or RULES indicates that the system will maintain the CG base and otherwise it will not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Valid values YES, RULES or NO</p>
            <p>                Null is treated like NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAV.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the NAV to be recorded either NET or GROSS of transaction costs.</p>
            <p>                When processing SEC.TRADE and SECURITY.TRANSFER records,it is possible to record the NAV either Net or Gross of transaction costs.</p>
            <p>                If NET is selected then,the cost of the acquisition is NAV plus all charges and commissions,</p>
            <p>                and the sale consideration is NAV minus charges and commissions.</p>
            <p>                If GROSS is selected then charges and commissions are ignored.</p>
            <p>                The difference between the cost of acquisition and sale consideration is considered as the Capital gain and taxed accordingly.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.CCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the default currency market that will be used to calculate all foreign exchange values in the Securities Module.</p>
            <p>                The user may choose to define different exchange rates for different currency markets.  (e.g. 1 is the T.T. rate  2 might be the rate for notes and coin etc).  This field defines the currency market to be used in all foreign exchange transactions within the Securities module.</p>
            <p>                The default value for this field is 1.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                1 - 3 Numeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>                Must be numeric.</p>
            <p>                Must exist on the CURRENCY.MARKET table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.HOLD.CHECK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Rule 1</p>
            <p>                Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD.MINIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the minimum yield for the Asset type defined in the YIELD.ASSET field. This value is used as the minimum allowable yield before the Valuation Integrity report SC.INTEGRITY reports an error.</p>
            <p>                Only numeric input allowed.</p>
            <p>                Multi-valued field associated with the YIELD.ASSET and MAXIMUM.YIELD fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional input.</p>
            <p>                Input only allowed if associated YIELD.ASSET has be entered, in which case an entry must be made in either this field or the YIELD.MAXIMUM field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.POR.SEL.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies</p>
            <p>                the user defined subroutine for the respective valuation application entered in field VAL.APPL. This form a multivalue set with field VAL.APPL  USR.POS.RTN</p>
            <p>                Purpose </p>
            <p>                Invoked</p>
            <p>                This routine</p>
            <p>                Output array contains list of contracts which should be included in portfolio valuation.</p>
            <p>                If the output array is empty the calling routine searchs for the list of contract Ids as it does usually (i.e. if array is empty SC.OL.VAL.FX reads CUSTOMER.FOREX file and looks for deals attached to this portfolio).</p>
            <p>                Routine usage example</p>
            <p>                EX.USR.PORT.SEL.RTN ( IN.PORTFOLIO, OUT.ID.LIST1, OUT.ID.LIST2, OUT.ID.LIST3)</p>
            <p>                Where</p>
            <p>                OUT.ID.LIST1  is list of contract Ids separated by Field marks (for example for application FOREX it will look as FX0110100001:@FM:FX0110100003.).</p>
            <p>                OUT.ID.LIST2  This is used only in case if LC and represents the contract ids from LC.BENEFICIARY separated by Field marks.</p>
            <p>                OUT.ID.LIST3  This is used only in case of LC and represents the contract ids from LC.ISSUING.BANK separated by Field marks.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.CUSTODIAN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default external custodian to be used if custodian is unknown at transaction level.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.NO.ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enquiry name is attached here.</p>
            <p>                The record name should be a valid input in Enquiry file.</p>
            <p>                The enquiry, which would search the Securities by the Alternate Index, should be attached here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.DEPO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customer number(s) of the bank acting as depository on its own or its customers behalf.</p>
            <p>                When the bank acts as a depository on its own behalf, or on behalf of its customers, the user should enter the customer number(s) of the bank as it operates in this regard.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                1 - 6 Numeric customer numbers or 3 - 10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic characters. (Multivalue field) (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>                Must exist on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file with the CUSTOMER.TYPE field having a value of Depository.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.HOUSE.DR.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>   Sale  transaction code to be used for external transaction.</p>
            <p>   Transaction code defined in EXT.DR.TXN cannot be defined.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if IN.HOUSE.DEALING is set to YES and is mandatory if IN.HOUSE.DEALING is set to YES </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The suspense account to be credited/debited for customer amount due in respect of actual settlement trades pending settlement of trade.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Valid category in Range - 10000 to 19999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls the grouping method to be used and allows the values MANUAL, AUTOMATIC or BOTH.</p>
            <p>                If this field is left blank (none), then grouping of orders will not be allowed. If manual or automatic is selected then TRANSMIT.ORDER field in SC.STD.SEC.TRADE must be set to Yes. Also, if MANUAL is selected, an OFS.SOURCE and OFS.VERSION for SC.GROUP.ORDERS should be defined and linked in SC.STD.SEC.TRADE. Additionally, if AUTOMATIC is selected, an OFS.SOURCE and OFS.VERSION for SEC.OPEN.ORDER should also be defined and linked in SC.STD.SEC.TRADE. These versions would be used for generation and update of Grouped Sec.Open.Order through OFS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Appropriate version of SC.GROUP.ORDERS</p>
            <p>                Appropriate version of SEC.OPEN.ORDER besides that of SC.GROUP.ORDERS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the No. days between the Current date and the DATE.LAST.PRICE on the SECURITY.MASTER before a security with an ASSET.TYPE equal to the asset input into the associated PRICE.ASSET field is considered to have an old price and an error is reported by SC.INTEGRITY.</p>
            <p>                Note : PRICE.ASSET  PRICE.DAYS are associated Multivalues.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional field.</p>
            <p>                Numeric input only is allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.ASSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the Asset Type for which the Valuation Integrity Checks are to be performed on the Price Securities.</p>
            <p>                Format : Valid Asset Type Code.          (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.TAX.ACCRUAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify whether the recoverable tax should be included in the valuation and performance calculation.</p>
            <p>                CUM  The recoverable Tax will be accumulated and shown in valuation files (SC.POS.ASSET and SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT) as field REC.TAX.CUM.AMT. This field will be reset to 0 when the Reset occurs through the EOD process EOD.RECOVERABLE.TAX. This option is only available if AM is installed.</p>
            <p>                BOOK -</p>
            <p>                The recoverable tax amount will be added to the valuation tables on the same day and will not be accumulated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                field     (A) field.</p>
            <p>                Allowed     values are CUM BOOK.</p>
            <p>                If     left Blank considered as BOOK.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINVEST.ORD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used when automatically creating SEC.OPEN.ORDER records from ENTITLEMENT records. Mapped to ORDER.TYPE field in associated SEC.OPEN.ORDER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.DEPO.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not a depository advice is to be produced when dividends are received.</p>
            <p>                If the Securities module is to produce a depository advice on receipt of a dividend then the user should enter YES in this field, otherwise they should enter NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                1 - 3 Alphabetic characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>                This field can only contain the values YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOFT.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field controlling whether or not the bank wants to be able to produce portfolio valuation reports through the Enquiry system or not. Input of YES in this field builds the data files used to produce portfolio valuation reports through Enquiry.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>                Defaults to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECT.PEND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will allow input to field SC.TRANS.NAME if set to YES;. Default is NO. By setting the field to YES, the user is declaring that any SECURITY.TRANSFERS with transaction codes defined on SC.TRANS.NAME are free transfers.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROK.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used as a category reference for the broker amount to be deferred. The suspense amount of the broker is posted to it.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                The value in this field should be a valid record existing in CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRANT.PERMISSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>It controls the number of Permissions to be met to allow a transaction to be completed</p>
            <p>Single - If single permission is met, will allow the transaction to complete</p>
            <p>Blank or Null - All permissions should be met, to allow the transaction to complete</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSTRAINT.FAILURE</field>
<desc>
            <p>During the execution of trading restriction testing (configured in SC.SECURITY.CONSTRAINT) many restrictions may be tested. This field allows the following settings</p>
            <p>                SINGLE - Once one restriction test has failed, the restriction testing program will return control back to the main application.</p>
            <p>                MULTIPLE - Each restriction test that fails will be displayed to the user in turn, therefore if 20 tests fail the user will see 20 error messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                SINGLE, MULTIPLE or NULL. (If NULL the         systems assumes SINGLE mode)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls whether the current yield or the yield to maturity is used in the update of Sc.Cash.Flow and Sc.Pos.Asset.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to 1 then the yield to maturity will be used from the Security.Supp record.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to 2 then the current yield will be used from the Security.Supp record.</p>
            <p>                See the helptext for Sc.Pos.Asset, yield, for a more detailed explanation</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Only input of 1 or 2 allowed.</p>
            <p>                Will default to 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the message number to be used to send a Broker Confirmation.</p>
            <p>                This may either be 512 or 518.</p>
            <p>                This field is used to determine whether an MT512 or MT518 is sent for a Broker Confirmation. Please note that an MT512 may only be sent by members of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority</p>
            <p>                If this field is left blank, an MT512 will be assumed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Input may be 512, 518 or blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INFL.INDX.METH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to specify how the captial gains indexation values have been entered in the COUNTRY and REGION applications. Can be either ES, indicating that the values entered are indexation coefficients, or STD, indicating that the values are index values. For example -</p>
            <p>                ES</p>
            <p>                The current dates value is entered as 1 and preceding values increase (generally due to inflation)</p>
            <p>                STD</p>
            <p>                A base date (some past date) value is expressed as 100 and all dates forward of this are expressed as increasing values (again due to inflation).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional Input, if not entered will be assumed to be STD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.DR.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sale  transaction code to be used for external transaction</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input allowed only if EXTERNAL.TXN is set to YES and is mandatory if EXTERNAL.TXN is set to YES </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERFORM.MONTHS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the number of months that performance details for the SEC.ACC.MASTER record will be retained by the system.</p>
            <p>                The default value for this field is 13 months, this also being the minimum allowed value.  The maximum being 99 months.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.ORD.FWD.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls whether or not forward accounting entries are generated by SEC.OPEN.ORDER.</p>
            <p>        Allows NONE, NO, Y and UNAUTH</p>
            <p>        NO or NONE - This setting indicates no accounting entries will be generated at any stage of the process.</p>
            <p>        UNAUTH - This setting allows STMT.ENTRY records to be generated at the unauthorised stage. Suitable ACCOUNT balance messages and the appropriate OVERRIDE messages will be generated.</p>
            <p>        Y - This setting produces suitable ACCOUNT balance messages and the appropriate OVERRIDE messages will be stored on the transaction. However, STMT.ENTRY records will only be generated at authorization stage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.STOCK.EXCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this field is set to Yes, Stock exchange in SEC.OPEN.ORDER would be defaulted based on the stock exchange specified in SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                YES/NO are the accepted values</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.ST.CHGS.IHLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field indicates whether charges, accrued interest and taxes are to be calculated when SEC.TRADE record is created from SC.EXE.SEC.ORDERS (transmitted orders) and SEC.OPEN.ORDER (traded orders).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                YES or NO field. Blank would be considered NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD.ASSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the Asset Type for which the Valuation Integrity Checks are to be performed.</p>
            <p>                Any input must exist on the ASSET.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>                Multi-valued field associated with the MAXIMUM.YIELD and MINIMUM.YIELD fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Optional input.</p>
            <p>                Any input must exist on the ASSET.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>                If something has been entered in an associated YIELD.MAXIMUM or YIELD.MINIMUM field then this field becomes mandatory. YIELD.MINIMUM field then this field will be required.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCLUDE.NAU.TXNS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the user to specify how unauthorised transactions are dealt with in the portfolio valuation.</p>
            <p>         If set to YES then unauthorised transactions will appear on the valuation.</p>
            <p>         If set to NO or blank then unauthorised transactions will not appear on the valuation, irrespective of whether an authorised record exists.</p>
            <p>         If set to AUTH then the authorised value of the transaction will be included on the valuation. Note that changes where the customer is deleted or the portfolio changed are not included on the valuation for this setting.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Valid input  YES, NO or AUTH. Default NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.POS.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the user defined subroutine for the respective valuating application entered in field VAL.APPL. Forms a multivalue set with field VAL.APPL and USR.PORT.SEL.RTN</p>
            <p>                Purpose </p>
            <p>                Invoked</p>
            <p>                This user routine will be invoked just prior to the write statement on SC.POS.ASSET.</p>
            <p>                The routine is passed the SC.POS.ASSET record, After processing in the calling routine and just before updating the SC.POS.ASSET file. The user can make the modifications to this record to his requirement and pass back the array to the calling routine. So the changes can be reflected in the SC.POS.ASSET file.</p>
            <p>                The routine should be specified as</p>
            <p>                EXAMPLE.ROUTINE(IN.SC.POS.ASSET.REC)</p>
            <p>                Where IN.SC.POS.ASSET.REC contains the SC.POS.ASSET record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.ORDER.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Controls which Account balance to use when carrying out cash availability checks for portfolios in the ORDER.BY.CUST application.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to ONLINE then the ONLINE balance of the account will be used. If this field is set to FORWARD then the balance used will include forward entries.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Only input of FORWARD or ONLINE allowed.</p>
            <p>                Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>                Will default to ONLINE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.SETTLEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a flag that will be used to facilitate Actual or Contractual Settlement.</p>
            <p>                If this field is set to YES, then it would be Actual Settlement.</p>
            <p>                Optional Input</p>
            <p>                valid inputs are YES or NO</p>
            <p>                Null corresponds to NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.DEFAULT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the default setting for delivery suppression advices in SEC.TRADE  SECURITY.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.USER.INDEX</field>
<desc>
            <p>A multi-valued field containing the IDs of the record from ALT.SEC.PARAMETER that will be used as the alternative lookup keys of SECURITY.MASTER. These fields will used in addition to the standard key and mnemonic fields in SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                The record must exist in the file ALT.SEC.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>                The number of alternative lookups is     unlimited although performance may be affected if too many are defined.</p>
            <p>                NOINPUT if ALTERNATE.INDEX is used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HUB.COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input to this field is allowed only when SEC.ACC.MASTER is shared. The value of this field will be defaulted to PORT.COMP.ID of the new SEC.ACC.MASTER record.</p>
            <p>This field will indicate in which company the securities transaction will be done.</p>          
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Allowed only when SEC.ACC.MASTER is shared.</p>
            <p>                Accepts a valid company code.</p>
            <p>                The field will not accept a company to which SEC.ACC.MASTER is not shared.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.EXPOSURE.RTN</field>
<desc>
	<p>Routine attached to fetch the forex currency exposure amount for the portfolio or group based on the parameter.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.EXPOSURE.RATE</field>
<desc>
	<p>Exposure rate used to calculate the forex currency exposure amount.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCL.INC.VALUATION</field>
<desc>
	<p>Field to specify whether income account in one portfolio can be defined as a capital account in another portfolio.</p>
	<p>If the field is YES then income accounts of the portfolio will be excluded from the valuation of portfolio.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.ENT.SC.TAX.SRC</field>
<desc>
<p>Field to specify whether SC.AMT.ACY amount in ENTITLEMENT needs to be populated in SOURCE.TAX.AMT field. This functionality is applicable only if there is only one tax defaulted in SC.TAX.CODE/SC.TAX.TYPE in entitlement/diary record. If there are multiple tax, this value will not be populated to SOURCE.TAX.AMT even though this field is set in SC.PARAMETER. </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INC.ACC.INT.MV</field>
<desc>
<p>Options possible in the field are Yes Or Blank</p>
<p>If YES is Specified then the Accrued Interest will be included in the calculation of Margin value else if left blank it will be excluded from the calculation of margin value</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FTT.TRANS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
<p>Multivalue Field to define more than one TRANS TYPE</p>
<p>Define the transaction type (SC.TRANS.NAME or DIARY.TYPE) for which FTT(Financial Transaction Tax) has to be applied  </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FTT.INC.ACC</field>
<desc>
<p>Options possible in the field are Yes Or Blank</p>
<p>IF YES is specified then interest will be included for the calculation of BASE.AMT in FTT</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FTT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
<p>Accepts only Valid TAX.TYPE Record</p>
<p>Defines the TAX.TYPE record for the FTT(Financial Transaction Tax)</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>INC.FTR.SEC.COST</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
