<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.PORT.ORDER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of shares to be bought or sold.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.DISCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the commission discount to be used for the specific order.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of "S"tandard, "F"ull or "N"one allowed.</p>
            <p>Will default to "S"tandard if DIRECTION is BUY                 "N"one if DIRECTION is SELL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the ID of any SEC.OPEN.ORDER records created by the verification of this SC.PORT.ORDER record. If orders have been generated from this SC.PORT.ORDER record then this field will have been updated and consequently the only functions allowed on this record are 'S' and 'P'.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price the order is to use. Obtained from the SECURITY.MASTER file, depending on the Price Type calculation method used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINAL.HELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Current nominal held by the portfolio.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
            <p>Obtained from SECURITY.POSITION.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the portfolio.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GENERATE.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must be set to YES if SEC.OPEN.ORDER records are to be created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the currency to be used to settle the trade.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input allowed. Will default to PORTFOLIO.CCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-value list of SEDOL numbers with a one to one relationship with the next eight fields. Will contain a list of securities that are required to be bought or sold to bring the portfolio in line with its model.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.CURR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the default settlement currency for any trades generated from the SC.PORT.ORDER record. While the settlement currency for the order for any particular security can be changed by amending the value in the SETTLEMENT.CCY field associated with the particular security all the settlement currencies can be changed together by changing the value in this field. Note; The currency used in the SEC.OPEN.ORDER will be the currency in the associated SETTLEMENT.CCY field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must exist on the Currency file.</p>
            <p>Will default to the reference currency of the portfolio when the SC.PORT.ORDER record is created by SC.PORT.COMPARE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Cost or proceeds of transaction, calculated using the PRICE shown in the next field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Either to BUY or SELL depending on whether the portfolio is short or long in respect to the portfolio model for the associated security.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates commission discount to be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of (S)tandard, (N)one or (F)ull. Will default to "S".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate used in converting the variance value into the PORTFOLIO.CCY. Sell or Buy rate used depending on the direction of the order.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

