<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.REPORT.VAR</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This report request is to be used in conjunction with the Policy Parameter tables as set up in the 'POLICY PARAMETER' Table. </p>
            <p>The User is able to determine when and what criteria should apply to a holding or a price before he should receive a warning report of the variance.  For example the User may input at Fields 1 and 2 the Price Variance percentage of 10 and the Frequency of Daily.  This will provide the User with a list of all Securities which have moved by that percentage since the last update.  To begin with it will read the Average cost price of each Security account and compare it with the market price of each Security where it varies by more than the specified amount it will update a report with details of that Security. </p>
            <p>Field 3 of the Report request stipulates what percentage variance, Performance - wise of a Clients' Portfolio account the User needs details of. </p>
            <p>Field 4 dictates the percentage variance of a Clients' portfolio plan needed to update a warning report. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRICE.VAR.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>When entered this variance of price movement by the specified percentage will update a warning list for the user to utilise. </p>
            <p>System compares cost price on portfolio account with the current market price and updates a report with details of those Securities which have exceeded or reached that variance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard numeric type input up to 5 characters in length.  No decimals allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.MOVE.FQU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Informs the system of the Frequency of the check it needs to perform with one variance percentage in Field 1 on the price of each Security held. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard frequency format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLICY.VAR.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The system will compare the actual holdings percentage - wise against the policy parameters set up and generate a report as and when indicated by the Frequency specified in Field 5. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric type input 5 characters maximum length.  No decimals allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Company to which the User must be Signed On in order to use the Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>9 alphanumeric characters 'CCGGGLLLL' where: CC   is 2 alpha characters Country Code GGG  is 3 numeric characters Company Group LLLL is 4 numeric local code. or     2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or '.') Company Mnemonic characters. Mandatory input.  No Default Value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PER.POLICY.VAR.FQU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Frequency of check to be carried out to calculate and illustrate the exceptions encountered by the criteria specified in Fields 3 &amp; 4. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard frequency format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERFORM.VAR.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The user will store a Performance Variance percentage figure in this field and the system will compare this performance with the performance of the Individual Portfolio Account and Update a report with exceptions at the Frequency specified in Field 5. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Frequency specified in Field 5 Numeric type input 5 characters in length No decimals allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

