<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.REFNO.SEQ</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is an installation type file which must be set up by an T24 Securities Module user prior to being able to access automatic customer records form applications such as Redemptions, Dividend payments etc. Whereas all transactions from Security Transfer, Security Trade through to Option Trade can be accessed by either a manual entry of an ID or by utilising the Automatic ID at F3; the Customer records are created solely by the System within the Administration Area and it is for this purpose that the Application MNEMONIC needs to be sanctioned for this process and given a number with which to commence. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Details the date at which the record was opened.  Should be Julian date as in company record.  Each day this is automatically altered as the Julian date forms part of the transaction ref. no. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format. (Mandatory Input).</p>
            <p>Should always be the Julian date as stored in company record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODULE.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the application within the security administration duties which need an automatic ID allotted by the system. </p>
            <p>To be used in conjunction with redemptions dividends etc. where the reference no is automatically chosen by the system. </p>
            <p>Examples: COUP = Coupon payment transaction.           BDRD = Bond Redemption type transaction.           BDLD = Bond Lending Type transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Format is module MNEMONIC 1-4 Alpha Numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid application MNEMONIC. COUP/BDRD/BDLD/CAPI/STKD/MEWI/SFKP/.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEQUENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction reference number from which all sequential numbers should follow within the specified application. </p>
            <p>Each time a transaction is entered during the day the sequence no stored here will be increased so that along with the date in Field 1 it forms a unique key for each days transactions. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 numeric character input. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

