<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.REPORTS.REQUEST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>While Portfolio valuation statements are automatically printed at End of Day according to the type of report and the frequency as stored at CUSTOMER.SECURITY level it is desirable to have the flexibility to request these reports on an ad hoc basis without the necessity for having to change the static Data Base each time. </p>
            <p>This facility enables the user to do just that: </p>
            <p>He specifies what customer, what report and whether the report is to go out to the customer or is for internal purposes. </p>
            <p>This application is then processed at End of Day and the valuations etc. printed via Delivery. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REPORT.MONTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields REPORT.TYPE to REPORT.MONTH form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated multivalue field which specifies whether the report specified at field is for 'EXTERNAL' use or not. </p>
            <p>Various reports are for analysis and decision making only and as such are not intended for external use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only allowed input in 'Y'(es) or    'N'(O) (Mandatory Input).</p>
            <p>Reports 1-5 are customer related and can be for external use.</p>
            <p>Reports 11-14 are for internal use only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field used to specify the desired valuation. </p>
            <p>This field is linked to a table 'SC.REPORT.TYPE'.  Report ID's 1-14 are hard coded within this application. </p>
            <p>Note:     As extra reports are created for local requirements and           enhancements, their ID will be added to the table           SC.REPORT.TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric report number 1-14 is the only allowed input. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid report type on the 'SC.REPORT.TYPE' table, or on the SC.VAL.REPORT if the Valuation subroutine entered on the SC PARAMETER record is SC.VAL.REPORT$RUN.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to indicate to which client's portfolio the specified report refers to. </p>
            <p>If no specific portfolio account is indicated the system will assume the request is for all safecustody reports and default to 'ALL'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid customer portfolio account made up of a valid customer number separated by ' ' from the portfolio account reference number. (Default value = 'ALL'</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid security account number within the 'SEC.ACC.MASTER' file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Company to which the User must be Signed On in order to use the Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>9 alphanumeric characters 'CCGGGLLLL' where: CC   is 2 alpha characters Country Code GGG  is 3 numeric characters Company Group LLLL is 4 numeric local code. or    2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or '.') Company Mnemonic characters. Mandatory input.  No Default Value.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Company code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.REP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to specify the particular month to which a report may refer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only allowed input is 1-12. Where  1  = January and 12 = December</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

