<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.REPORT.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                    SC.REPORT.TYPE </p>
            <p />
            <p>This table is used by the securities report request sub-system and contains the names of those reports, together with their associated report number, which may be requested for printing directly by the users. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REPORT.ANALYSIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the Security module (SC) REPORT TYPE record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 to 5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>1st Character must be a number from 1-9</p>
            <p>2nd character must be "A"</p>
            <p>3rd to 5th character will allow alpha numeral.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes in abbreviated form the SC.Report.Type. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the SC.Report.Type in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.PARAM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 14 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the SC.VAL.PARAM.NBK file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the SC.Report.Type. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the SC.Report.Type in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multilanguage field (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.REPORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the report is external or not. </p>
            <p>This field has been replaced by the field EXTERNAL REP (field 3.1) in the application OL.VAL.REPS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only Y(es) or N(o). be alpha) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the required version of the valuation report which is to be run. </p>
            <p>As to which file to point to depends upon the value entered in the field VALUATION.SUBR (9) on the SC.PARAMETER file. </p>
            <p>If this field is left blank then it is assumed that the basic T24 revaluation format is to be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 25 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the SC.VAL.PARAM.*** applicable to the          T24 user - where *** denotes the T24 user's COMPANY mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

