<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.STD.BOND.RED</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains company level default values which will be used when processing bond redemption type transactions. </p>
            <p>These defaults will be applicable irrespective of the transaction type and the user must create one record for each company on the system. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>WANCE.PL.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a sub valued language field. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where and if a Nominee code formed part of a Redemption Transaction.  At transaction level the system would default or assume the Nominee Code ID entered here. </p>
            <p>As the nominee code is part of the stored security position great care should be used when setting up standard defaults to ensure no problems at Transaction level. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alpha numeric characters, (type S) standard nominee code. Optional input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Nominee Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.DR.TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Redemptions are by nature security debit type transactions.  Here we are setting up a transaction code for that security debit; this code will then be linked within.  SC.Trans. type to Form A unique Dr. + and Cr. for all Redemption Type Transactions. </p>
            <p>Cancellations will automatically assume the CR Type Transaction code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 Alpha numeric characters, (Type S). Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Security Transaction.  Name (SC.TRANS.NAME)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WANCE.PL.DB</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a sub valued language field. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Company to which the User must be Signed On in order to use the Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>9 alphanumeric characters 'CCGGGLLLL' where: CC   is 2 alpha characters Country Code GGG  is 3 numeric characters Company Group LLLL is 4 numeric local code. or     2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or '.') Company Mnemonic characters. Mandatory input.  No Default Value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.PL.DB</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the debit transaction code which will be used for reallowance transactions within the REDEMPTION.CUS application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Commission rate to be applied to Customers for Redemption type transactions </p>
            <p>Standard Commission rates are normally published by a Banks' Portfolio Managers and where a commission is indicated for Bond Redemptions that rate can be stored once and for all.  '0.00' is allowed to cater for no change on Redemption Type Transactions. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-5 characters Standard Rate format. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.CR.TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If bonds are to be withdrawn from our safe custody account either via a physical depository (our own Securities Vault) or a Global Depository such as Euroclear in our books the Dr. transaction to the client must have a matching credit to a valid depository Account. </p>
            <p>For early redemptions where we advise the customer of an impending withdrawal we will likewise effectively do the same for the depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 Alpha numeric characters (Type S). Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Security Transaction name (SC.TRANS.NAME).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the category code to be used for the posting of exchange Profit &amp; Loss entries. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit &amp; loss and product types. Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's position. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Must be in range 50-000 to 59-999.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid CATEGORY code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.ADVICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used when the automatic bond redemption facility is requested - as it dictates the type of advice run to be processed.  In this instance whether it's a pre advice type or not. </p>
            <p>A pre advice type transaction will remove stock from base security and place it on an identical security no. but with a suffix '-234'.  This is the acknowledged early redemption indicator. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:      This type is used for the Automatic Redemption request            where the System indicates that the type of Redemption            should be a Final type.  System cannot possibly identify            early or partial draw downs - therefore it can only create            a pre advised Final Redemption. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alpha numeric characters (Type S). Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Redemption Type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.BOOK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies "Own Account Trading/Investment" portfolio.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DP.CHG.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the Category Code for the Depository Charge (Foreign Charge) applicable on a Redemption Transaction. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit and loss and product types. Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's operation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters: a)   Product/P&amp;L classification in the range 1-99. b)   Sub-classification of product/P&amp;L in the range 000-999. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Category Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.HIGHER.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maximum Charge Indicator.  The system will utilise Field 13 for calculating commission but where it exceeds Field 14 the amount is Field 14 i.e. the maximum charge will be displayed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-5 characters Standard Rate format. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.DB.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used to signify which type of transaction is being posted, for exchange Losses. </p>
            <p>To facilitate the recognition of the transaction code numbers with the application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each application. </p>
            <p>The following range has been assigned within T24: </p>
            <p>           600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.LOWER.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Minimum Charge indicator.  Where the commission calculated for this Redemption, using the rate stored in Field 13 falls below this amount the System will default to this Minimum Charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-5 characters Standard Rate format. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.CR.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used to signify which type of transaction is being posted, for exchange Profits. </p>
            <p>To facilitate the recognition of the transaction code numbers with the application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each application. </p>
            <p>The following range has been assigned within T24: </p>
            <p>           600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DP.FOR.DR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Depository Foreign Charge Debit transaction code to be utilised by the SYSTEM when processing Redemption transactions. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DP.CHG.DR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used to signify what type of transaction has created the category entry it relates to for the depository charge on Redemption transactions. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPO.SUSP.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Suspense Account for depository posting to be used while processing Redemption transactions. </p>
            <p>Effectively a suspense or wash account for all Redemption Nostro entries.  Until all entries for on Bond Redemption are authorised the Depository entry will not be posted to the nostro concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4-10 type 'AAA'(uppercase or lowercase alpha) characters. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Account Class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CL.FOR.CR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the transaction code to be utilised when passing the Foreign Charge applicable to the client on a redemption transaction. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Change Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.SUFFIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is anticipated that where the User advises Clients' of an early redemption by means of a PRE-ADVICE the Stock concerned will be attributed a different suffix number.  T24 will recognise -234 as an early Redemption Type Security which cannot therefore be re-sold.  Addition to a valid security number of '-234'. </p>
            <p>To prevent a Client or Account Officer Reselling stock which has been effectively 'Drawn' a separate Security position will be created for the 'Drawn stock'. </p>
            <p>Note:      For all early redemptions a user will first have to open a            new Security (the copy function can be used) and it can            be titled "Early Redemption". </p>
            <p>           Two positions will be shown on a Client's valuation -            although no financial entries will be passed until the            Bonds are actually redeemed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the standard delivery instructions to be used with a redemption type transaction i.e. delivery of stock out free or against payment. </p>
            <p>For a redemption the normal type of delivery instruction would be of a type delivery against payment.  The delivery instructions impact for example on the SEC. DEL. Control section of portfolio management i.e. is stock to be physically received and/or against a financial consideration. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alpha numeric characters, (type S). Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Security Delivery Instruction (SC DEL INSTR) code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FGN.CHG.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WANCE.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a sub valued language field. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DP.FOR.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>As with Field 8 Customer (Client) foreign charge code and where all credits must have a mirror debit here we store the category code for the depositories' charge to the client. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit and loss and product types. Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's operation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters: a)   Product/P&amp;L classification in the range 1-99. b)   Sub-classification of product/P&amp;L in the range 000-999. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Category Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Profit and Loss category to which reallowanced entries are to be posted is defined in this field for use within the REDEMPTION.CUS application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid P &amp; L category (50000 - 59999).p</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REALLOWANCE.PL.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the transaciton code which will be used for credit transactions arising from reallowance processing of bond redemptions. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used when the automatic bond redemption facility is requested.  It dictates the type of final advice to be produced; user definition can indicate whether eg. final maturity total or early maturity. </p>
            <p>Used for SYSTEM created automatic redemption records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alpha numeric characters (Type S). Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Redemption Type.  For purposed of the AUTOMATIC REDEMPTION facility. The only advice Type possible should be a Final Redemption Type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CL.CHG.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category code used for the change apportioned to the Client in Fields 13, 14 and 15. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit and loss and product types. Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's operation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters. a)   Product/P&amp;L classification in the range 1-99. b)   sub-classification of product/P&amp;L in the range 000-999. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Category Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CL.CHG.CR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction Code used in conjunction with Field 16 to indicate for P and L purposes the category and transaction used in creating the commission amount. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>  
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CL.FOR.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Category Code to which the Foreign Charges for this type of transaction (i.e. Depository Charge) will be posted. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit and loss and product types. Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's operation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters: a)   Product/P&amp;L classification in the range 1-99. b)   Sub-classification of product/P&amp;L in the range 000-999. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Category Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

