<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.SUB.ACC.ROUTING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>SC.SUB.ACC.ROUTING is an application that the user can use to set-up the routing instructions for the sub-accounts of a particular depository.</p>
            <p>This application has the same way as the routing from depository to sub-depository in SC.DEPOT.ROUTING.</p>
            <p>These sub-accounts must exist in SUB.ACCOUNT field of CUSTOMER.SECURITY file keyed on the depository.</p>
            <p>The sub-account can't be removed from the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file if it always exists in SC.SUB.ACC.ROUTING application.</p>
            <p>The routing on the-sub account is based on criteria that are :</p>
            <p>- security domicile</p>
            <p>- selections on customer which are defined by the fields on CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>The sub-account is now an element of the key of SECURITY.POSITION, CAPTL.INCREASE.CUS, DIV.COUP.CUS, ENTITLEMENT, REDEMPTION.CUS, REPO.POSITION and STOCK.DIV.CUS files.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NATIONALITY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the nationality of customers whose stock holdings should go to the associated sub account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>2 </p>
            <p>characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field reserved for future used</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future used</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The sub account to be used at the depository for securities of this domicile with the types of customers identified in the customer selection fields.</p>
            <p>This must be a valid sub account in the SUB.ACCOUNT field of CUSTOMER.SECURITY record keyed on this depository (id).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p />
            <p>0 -16 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field reserved for future used</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field reserved for future used</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key is the depository for which the routing is required.</p>
            <p>The depository must exist on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file and defined as DEPOSITORY in CUSTOMER.TYPE field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Must be 1-10 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Local reference field</p>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement.</p>
            <p>As in the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to define in the SC.SUB.ACC.ROUTING file up to 999 Local elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified. These local elements should be defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice.</p>
            <p>The name of the new element(s), as well as the Format and <p>Validation Rules:</p>, must be defined in the LOCAL table (Ref: UTILITIES) and LOCAL.REFERENCE table (Ref: UTILITIES) prior to their use in the SC.SUB.ACC.ROUTING Application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-35 characters as defined in the LOCAL table (Ref:       UTILITIES) definition for this local reference field. Multivalue field.       (Optional or Mandatory input according to definition in LOCAL table (Ref:       UTILITIES) for this Local Reference element.) As defined by the User       within the individual LOCAL Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.CHANGED</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Three values are possible: blank, NEW and CHANGED.</p>
            <p>This field is updated with NEW when the SC.SUB.ACC.ROUTING record is input and CHANGED when this record has been changed.</p>
            <p>If the status is NEW or CHANGED then no sub account defaulting will take place.</p>
            <p>The end of day routine SC.EOD.SUB.ACC.CHG clears this field to set-up the sub account of the depository according to the new rules defined on this record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No-input field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically update by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the residency of customers whose stock holdings should go to the associated sub account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p />
            <p>2 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.DOMICILE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The security domicile that sub-account routing instructions are required for.</p>
            <p>It must be a valid country in COUNTRY file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p />
            <p>2 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field reserved for future used</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No-input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.APPLI</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This sub-valued field is associated with the fields APP.FIELD, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field contains an application name </p>
            <p>and allows to</p>
            <p>gether with the fields APP.FIELD, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE defining the selection of customers or securities to which sub-account routing instructions apply. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If any input is made into the APP.APPLICATION, the associated fields APP.FIELD, APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE must be populated. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Values allowed :       CUSTOMER, SECURITY.MASTER</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field linked to APP.OPERAND and APP.VALUE fields.</p>
            <p>Any input into this field must exist as a field on STANDARD.SELECTION record for APP.APPLI specified</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field linked to APP.FIELD and APP.VALUE fields.</p>
            <p>If any input is made into APP.FIELD field then this field must be populated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field can only contain EQ, NE, LE,       LT, GE or GT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field linked to APP.FIELD and APP.OPERAND fields.</p>
            <p>If any input is made into APP.FIELD and APP.OPERAND fields then this field must be populated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>35 characters maximum</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

