<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.SEC.TIME.SERIES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
        <p> The application will store unit accruals and yield on a daily basis for all interest bearing securities.  A record will be maintained for every interest payment cycle of the security. Any back dated price or interest rate change, done after the first recording, will be considered. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.TIME.SERIES</field>
<desc>
            <p> ID of the SC.SEC.TIME.SERIES record. A record will be maintained for every interest payment cycle of the security. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The ID for this application will be in the following format (SecurityNo.InterestPaymentDate).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The security ( a bond-type instrument from SECURITY MASTER) for which the unit accrual and yield is calculated. </p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the security mentioned in the previous field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The issue date of the security.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will holds the accrual start date of the security.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the interest payment date of the security.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maturity date of the bond is stored in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INETEREST.DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will hold the day basis that should be considered for calculating the accrued interest and yield.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUSINESS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field stores the working day for which the accrued interest and yield is calculated. The fields from BUSINESS.DATE to YIELD are associated multi values.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will hold the price of the security for the corresponding BUSINESS.DATE. The fields from BUSINESS.DATE to YIELD are associated multi values.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will hold the interest of the security for the corresponding BUSINESS.DATE. The fields from BUSINESS.DATE to YIELD are associated multi values.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUED.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will hold the accrued interest for one nominal (Unit Accrual) from the accrual start date to BUSINESS.DATE. The fields from BUSINESS.DATE to YIELD are associated multi values.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the yield on the corresponding BUSINESS.DATE. The fields from BUSINESS.DATE to YIELD are associated multi values.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t><field>INT.PAYMENT.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INTEREST.DAY.BASIS</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
