<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.STOCK.POSITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DT.SHORT.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated short position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sub-account that the position is held in.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the position record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER field is a Kassenobligationen security then this will be the maturity date for the security at the time the record was created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Security Number the Position is for.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The broker or depository number for which the position is held.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DT.LONG.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated long position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.SETT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the next settlement is due for this position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DT.OPEN.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated opending balance (for today).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DT.OPEN.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The trade dated opening balance (for today).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.SETT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the last settlement occured for this position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this security position is held by Nominee then this field will contain the ID of the Nominee. If this position is not held by nominee then this field will be blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSING.BAL.NO.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the trade dated number of securities held.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.LAST.TRADED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Trade Date of the last transaction to update this Position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Note; this field will contain the latest date for a trade date that updated this record. Thus if the record has been updated by two transactions; One with a trade date of 30th May 1996 and the other 5th June 1996 then this field will contain 05/06/1996 even if the transaction with this trade date had been entered into the system before the transaction with the trade date of 30/05/1996.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Depository where the Position is held.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER is a Kassenobligationen security then this will be the interest rate for the security at the time the record was created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

