<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.SEC.TRADE.CUST.DETAIL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Holds the details of the customer transaction for an associated SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CU.INCOME.ACC</field>
<desc>
        <p>Income account to which charge are to be posted.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.INCOME.CCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Currency of income account.Associated multi-value with CU.INCOME.CCY</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.GROSS.AM.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculates the Gross value of the trade (in the currency of the Security).</p>
            <p>     Used for display purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     NOINPUT. Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.BEN.BANK.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer beneficiary bank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.EX.RATE.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate of exchange between the Customer's Reference Currency (Field 44.1) and the Base currency of the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-10 numeric characters &amp; "." (1-6 integers and 1-9 decimal places). Default value = rate calculated as per the CURRENCY file records.</p>
            <p>     Where input manually the rate must fall between the parameters set on the CURRENCY files.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.BEN.BANK.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer beneficiary bank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.CAP.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the capitalised interest calculated on this trade for the customer's side.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     No Input Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.CUSTODIAN</field>
<desc>
            <p>To identify the external custodian where position is held..</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.DELIV.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field which contains the delivery key for the clients' advice which has been produced within the Delivery Module.</p>
            <p>     Once the Sec.Trade has been authorised the Delivery Module will automaticaly produce an advice for the client with an unique key.Once this has been generated the ID will be written to the Sec.Trade and stored.This means that all relevant information relating to an individual transaction can be retrieved allowing the user to obtain copies as and when required.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.NO.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Nominal Amountof the Security traded. NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.ACCOUNT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the currency of the Customer's Account (Field 21.1).</p>
            <p>     Information purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     No input required Automatic default to the ACCOUNT record Field 8 - Currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.UNF.SEC.GROS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CUSTOMER.NO to CU.UNF.SEC.GROS form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     A maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>     This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.BEN.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer beneficiary account</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.OVE.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provides the address where the Customer's Advices relating to this trade are to be sent (where different from the Address entered on the Customer record).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-35 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Multi value field. Sub-Value fields available to enable the full address to be input. (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency in which the trade will be settled. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The security that is being traded.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.BASE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the amount on which the capital gains tax calculation is to be performed.</p>
            <p>     This field is obtained from the WHT.PL field on the CG.TXN.BASE file.</p>
            <p>     The amount is maintained in the currency of the account being debited.</p>
            <p>     If the field is changed a recalculation of the tax amount is triggered off.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Populated automatically</p>
            <p>     Can be changed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of price calculation relevant to the Security. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.STAMP.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the Stamp Tax amount charged to the Customer for the trade.</p>
            <p>     Where indicated by the flag set within the Stock Exchange table the system will default the stamp/tax fee in accordance with the</p>
            <p>     If TAX.ROUTINE in SC.PARAMETER is null, STAMP.TAX is calculated according to</p>
            <p>     charge structure defined in STK.EXC.LOCAL only if local country of the company is 'CH'</p>
            <p>     otherwise the stamp tax is calculated as zero</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If the TAX.ROUTINE in SC.PARAMETER is entered with a routine, then the</p>
            <p>     parameters given in the SC.TAX.PARAMETER will be taken to calcuate stamp</p>
            <p>     tax.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      There are few tax routines in T24 to calculate stamp tax like</p>
            <p>     SC.CALC.STAMP.TAX, SC.CALC.TAX.CH. If SC.CALC.STAMP.TAX is the tax routine</p>
            <p>     entered to calculate stamp tax, then SC.TAX.PARAMETER should have a record</p>
            <p>     with id STAMP.TAX and only if the values set in the STAMP.TAX record</p>
            <p>     coincide with the transaction entered stamp tax will be calculated.</p>
            <p>     Similarly if SC.CALC.TAX.CH is the tax routine entered to calcualte stamp</p>
            <p>     tax, then SC.TAX.PARAMETER should have record like SHARES, BONDS, etc. to</p>
            <p>     calculate stamp tax.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Automatic default to charge as calculated by the system. or     1-14 numeric characters &amp; "." (number of decimal places dependant on the currency). Where Field 9, Net trade = NO, Mandatory input Where Field 9, Net Trade = Y(es), Automatic default is to 0.00. as laid down within that particular Stock Exchange. The values for which will be found within the Calculation table for that individual Stock Exchange.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.UNF.GROSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CUSTOMER.NO to CU.UNF.SEC.GROS form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     A maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>     This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.WHT.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of Tax on the Securities up to the Value Date of the trade. The calculation is used for Tax payable on any Bond / Share on Sale.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     The Tax rate to be applied is fetched from the field CU.WHT.PERC. This is automatically calculated by the system based on TXN.TAX.CODE linked to SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     System updated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.AMOUNT.DUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculates the amount due to be debited from (purchase) or credited to (sale) the Customer's Account (Field 22.1), IE. Net Amt Trade Ccy (Field 39.1) multiplied or divided by (dependant on the currencies involved) Cu Ex Rate Acc (Field 41.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     No input required. Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.GROSS.AM.TRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculates the Gross value of the trade (in the Trade Currency).</p>
            <p>     Whereas Field 26.1 illustrates the Gross amount of the transaction in the Security Currency this Field displays the total in the currency of the trade.i.e the currency to be settled with the Broker concerned.</p>
            <p>     The Gross amount in security currency is used to calculate commissions etc.which are then calculated back to the trade currency for purposes of enetering the transaction.</p>
            <p>     All Stock Exchange rates as contained within the Stock Exchange calculation tables will calculate the commissions in the security currency before converting this amount back into the trade currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     NOINPUT. Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODD.RTS.CGT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field indicating whether the transaction is for rounding of rights relating to a corporate action. This flag is determined by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     NOINPUT</p>
            <p>     Y or blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates which Depository the Security traded is to be delivered from or to. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates with which Broker the trade has been placed. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.COMM.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CUSTOMER.NO to CU.UNF.SEC.GROS form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     A maximum of 018 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>     This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Customer(s) with whom the trade is made. NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.TRD.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time at which the broker trade was recorded. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency of the Security (Field 1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     NOINPUT. Automatic default is to the Ccy of the Security as per the Security.  Master record (Field 7 - SECURITY CURRENCY).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.DISC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>DISCOUNT AMOUNT</p>
            <p>     Customer discount amount to reduce CU.NET.AM.TRD</p>
            <p>     Calculated using CU.DISC.PCENT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.COUP.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the coupon tax amount of the customer side. This field will only be populated if gross up entries are required; i.e. instrument traded net of tax and coupon receivable gross of tax.</p>
            <p>     This field is used to raise the additional gross up entries.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Standard amount field. (NOINPUT)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.BRKR.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of Broker Commission charged to the Customer for the trade.</p>
            <p>     The stock exchange entered within STOCK.EXCHANGE Field of the transaction determines several events within the Sec.Trade application.</p>
            <p>     1. Automatic calculation of the Value date depending on the information opened within that Stock.Exchange record</p>
            <p>     2. Automatic link to the standard stock Exchange commissions and charges as stored within the various Stock.Exchange tables and again determined by the information within that particular Stock.Exchange record.</p>
            <p>     Each Stock Exchange is linked to a seperate Stock.Exchange Calculation table which contains all the local charges, stamps and taxes. Plus it allows the user to store the commission rates that YOU the Bank would normally charge to the client yourselves.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Automatic default to charge as calculated by the system or 1-14 numeric characters &amp; "." (number of decimal places dependant on the currency). Where Field NET.TRADE = NO. Mandatory input. Where Field NET.TRADE= Y(es). Automatic default is to 0.00.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code eg. BUY/SEL TRI/TRO depending on whether it is a debit/credit transaction. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.CONST.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Portfolio constraint id</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.SEC.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security Account of the Customer. NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.ADVICE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Will send advices to the customer if set to Y, otherwise no advice will be sent.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.INT.CTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer interest counter, applicable for shares only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the statement numbers generated by the tranaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOO.CUST.DETAIL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>SC.SOO.CUST.DETAIL key that created this record throught the service.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.MANTAXTCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer manually entered tax amount in trade currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer tax code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.TAX.XRTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer commissions in SEC.TRADE are defaulted from the CUSTOMER.CHARGE record for the customer using the SC.APPLICATION set of fields. It will use the set of fields linked to SC.TRADING if they are present and default to ALL otherwise. From there the system links to the SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION application and then onto the SCTR.CHARGE.PARAMETER application to get the actual FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record used. Some commissions have a tax code associated with them which is used to charge tax on the commission.</p>
            <p>     If Tax is raised on the customer commission then the amount is calculated in the local currency of the system and recorded in the COM.TAX.BCUR field. This field will contain the exchange rate used between the local currency of the system and the trade currency of the SEC.TRADE, used in calculating the amount of tax in the Local currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.MANTAXLCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer manually entered tax amount in local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCOUNT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System defined field to store the discount or premium amounts on the Treasury Bill transactions. This field's value is arrived at by calculating the difference between the Redemption Price from the SECURITY.MASTER and the custmer price on the transaction, multiplied by the number of Nominals transacted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> - NOINPUTSystem field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.FOREIGN.FEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the Foreign Fee amount charged to the Customer for the trade.</p>
            <p>     As explained within the help text for Field 9 Stock Exchange if the link exists within that Stock Exchange to the Calculation tables then all local commissions and brokerages applicable to that particular Stock Exchange will default according to the rules laid down for that Stock Exchange convention.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Automatic default to charge as calculated by the system. or 1-14 numeric characters &amp; "." (number of decimal places dependant on the currency). Where Field 9, Net trade = NO. Mandatory input. Where Field 9, Net Trade = Y(es). Automatic default is to 0.00.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.HOLD.SETTLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>SEC.HOLD.SETTLE will be used to control whether stock will update the SC.SETTLEMENT application. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.TRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The NET.TRADE field enables you to specify whether or not the underlying SEC.TRADE is being entered NET of commissions or with commissions. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NET.AM.TRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculates the Net Amount of the trade (in Trade Ccy) for this Customer. IE. Cu Gross Amt Trd (Field 28.1) + Cust Intr Amt (Field 31.1) +/- Charges &amp; Commission (Fields 33.1-38.1).</p>
            <p>     This will contain the total amount to be debited to a Clients financial account in th instance of a purchase of securities and will constitute the Gross Amount of the Trade Plus all the sundry commissions and charges.</p>
            <p>     In the case of a Sale it will contain the Net amount payable to the Client minus any charges or commissions.</p>
            <p>     Note:      This amount is illustrated in the Trade currency and may            well differ from the Clients actual Account CCy which is            calculated and stored within Field 42.1</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     NOINPUT required. Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer commissions in SEC.TRADE are defaulted from the CUSTOMER.CHARGE record for the customer using the SC.APPLICATION set of fields. It will use the set of fields linked to SC.TRADING if they are present and default to ALL otherwise. From there the system links to the SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION application and then onto the SCTR.CHARGE.PARAMETER application to get the actual FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record used.</p>
            <p>     When the customer commissions are worked out the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE code used is put in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.WHT.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field detailing the percentage</p>
            <p>     Tax rate in percentage terms. This tax rate will be defaulted from the TAX record associated with</p>
            <p>     the customer / depository</p>
            <p>     .</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The service reference if this SEC.TRADE has been created through a service</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MISC.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as a category reference for miscellaneous. The suspense amount of miscellaneous is posted to it.</p>
            <p> NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.MESS.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>If entered, it is used to check the format of the override delivery address entered, depending on the value of the carrier from the message control message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-3 numeric character Message Control Id (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>     Must be the Id of a valid Message Control record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the sub account at depository. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.TAX.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer commissions in SEC.TRADE are defaulted from the CUSTOMER.CHARGE record for the customer using the SC.APPLICATION set of fields. It will use the set of fields linked to SC.TRADING if they are present and default to ALL otherwise. From there the system links to the SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION application and then onto the SCTR.CHARGE.PARAMETER application to get the actual FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record used. Some commissions have a tax code associated with them which is used to charge tax on the commission.</p>
            <p>     If Tax is raised on the customer commission then the amount of tax raised in the local currency of the system is recorded in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.GROSS.ACCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the sum of the Customer Gross amount in trade currency and the customer interest amount.</p>
            <p>     This field defaults automatically with the total of the Gross plus accrued interest for the Client as defined and entered within the first set of sub value fields.</p>
            <p>     All commissions and Brokerage calculations are carried out on the sum total of these two amounts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.TAX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the tax rate applied to the base amount.</p>
            <p>     If the TAX record, from the associated field CGT.CODE, field LINK.TAX is populated then all linked tax rates will be shown.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.HOLD.SETTLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>CASH.HOLD.SETTLE will be used to control whether cash will update the SC.SETTLEMENT application. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer commissions in SEC.TRADE are defaulted from the CUSTOMER.CHARGE record for the customer using the SC.APPLICATION set of fields. It will use the set of fields linked to SC.TRADING if they are present and default to ALL otherwise. From there the system links to the SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION application and then onto the SCTR.CHARGE.PARAMETER application to get the actual FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record used.  Some commissions have a tax code associated with them which is used to charge tax on the commission.</p>
            <p>     If Tax is raised on the customer commission then the Tax Code used (from the TAX file) to calculate the tax on the commission is recorded in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.BAMT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will signify the currency code in which the CGT base amount is denominated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.DELIV.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the delivery instruction for the client.</p>
            <p>     System indicator which is used to define whether the delivery is to be made free of payment or against payment.</p>
            <p>     It is used for two purposes within the securities processing.</p>
            <p>     1) The first is merely to control the delivery/receipt of the securities within the Sec.Del.Control appliaction and the subsequent reports which are provided.</p>
            <p>     2) The second use is within the automatic settlement proceedure which will produce, for example Swift messages to Cedel and /or Euroclear. The type of message is determined by the delivery instructions input.i.e is it free of payment or delivery against payment. The clearing systems within the Securities' Module will determine the type of validation within the Sec.Trade.</p>
            <p>     For a complete description see the Securities Settlement and Delivery Manual.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1 to 3 alpha code delivery instruction</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Maturity Date of the Security (Field 1). NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.INTR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of interest accrued on the Securities (CUST.TOT.NOM) up to the Value Date of the trade.</p>
            <p>     The calculation used within the Sec.Trade application for accrued interest payable on any Bond Purchase or Sale is:-</p>
            <p>     Nominal x Rate / No. of days x Interest day basis.</p>
            <p>     All this information is contained within the Static File SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
            <p>     The amount can be overridden at transaction level however:- As pointed out already the End of Day processing will automatically adjust any daily accruals on transactions done for the Banks own portfolio to agree with the static information and great care should therefore be taken before any manual adjustments are made to this calculated amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     1-14 numeric characters (including up to 3 decimal         places, dependant on currency). Multipliers T,M &amp; B         may be used. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input.) Default         value = Interest Amount as calculated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.REALLOW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculated as the value of the reallowance based on the CUST.TOT.NOM and the CU.REALLOWANCE.</p>
            <p>     The system will calculate the reallowance amount by multiplying the amount contained within CUST.TOT.NOM by the rate defined in the CU.REALLOWANCE Field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     1-14 numeric characters including up to 3 decimals.         Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.PARAM.COND</field>
<desc>
            <p>A multi-value NOINPUT field. The condition id allocated to this transaction relating to application CG.PARAM.CONDITION. This will determine the Capital Gains method and tax to be applied</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.REALLOWANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the reallowance rate allowable against the price paid, for New Issue traders.</p>
            <p>     NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.BEN.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer beneficiary address</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the date that the trade is made on. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the capital gains tax amount to be debited from the customer's account.</p>
            <p>     If the TAX record, from the associated field CGT.CODE, field LINK.TAX is populated then all linked tax amounts will be shown.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.DISC.PCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>DISCOUNT PERCENT</p>
            <p>     Customer discount applied to CU.NET.AM.TRD</p>
            <p>     default: obtained from SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.ENTITL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ENTITLEMENT number from which this trade was generated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Free text field automatically updated by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format field for carrying forward user specified information, if any. Authomatically carried forward from sec open order to trade, if input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1-35 Alphanumeric input (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.TAX.TCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer tax amount in trade currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the date on which the trade is to be effected. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.TAX.LCL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the local equivalent of the actual amount of capital gains tax that is to be debited from the customers account.</p>
            <p>     If the TAX record, from the associated field CGT.CODE, field LINK.TAX is populated then all linked local tax amounts will be shown.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     A NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.TOT.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculates the total nominal amount for the customer. NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.COMMISSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the Commission amount charged to the Customer for the trade.</p>
            <p>     The stock exchange determines several events within the Sec.Trade application.</p>
            <p>     1. Automatic calculation of the Value date depending on the information opened within that Stock.Exchange record</p>
            <p>     2. Automatic link to the standard stock Exchange commissions and charges as stored within the various Stock.Exchange tables and again determined by the information within that particular Stock.Exchange record.</p>
            <p>     Each Stock Exchange is linked to a separate Stock.Exchange Calculation table which contains all the local charges, stamps and taxes. Plus it allows the user to store the commission rates that YOU the Bank would normally charge to the client yourselves. Normally when entering a Sec.Trade the User is obliged to enter the Stock Exchange at which the transaction was effected.</p>
            <p>     The system will then go via the Stock Exchange to the Calculation table and default all the brokerage, stamps taxes etc. according to the rates stored within those tables.</p>
            <p>     However there are 3 separate options available to the User when entering a Sec.Trade which directly affects the commissions etc being calculated.</p>
            <p>     1. In Sec.Trade Field 9 there is a GROSS/NET indicator which defaults at the moment to NO i.e. NOT NET.</p>
            <p>     This means that the trade is Not Net of commission and the default commissions should take affect.</p>
            <p>     If the flag is set to YES however that tells the system that it is a Net trade and that No commissions whatsoever are to be charged. This then overrides all other default commission rates.</p>
            <p>     2. Within the Stock.Exchange table there is a link to the Calculation Table at Field 3 which is called "CALC COUNTRY". If input here the country code specifies which if any Calculation table is to be used. It is an optional field and if there is no link to the Calculation Tables then the system will default 0.00s.</p>
            <p>     3. Stored within the Customer.Security record are Customer and Broker rates which if input will obviously override any general rates as stored within the Stock.Exchange Tables.</p>
            <p>     The Flow within Sec.Trade is therefore:-</p>
            <p>     1. Check Net/Gross flag. If "YES" No Automatic calculation. If "NO" System carries on.</p>
            <p>     2. For Customer and Broker it then checks the Customer.Security record for individual commission tariffs.</p>
            <p>     If the "Calc.Country" indicator within the Stock.Exchange record is links to the Stock.Exchange calculation tables then the system will use these rates to default all the other fees payable under that Stock Exchange.</p>
            <p>     If it finds no individual tariffs within Customer.Security for either the Client or Broker then it will use the default rates within the Stock Exchange calculation tables.</p>
            <p>     If there is NO link between the Stock Exchange Table and the Stock.Exchange Calculation tables and there are No individual tariffs for the Client or Broker then the system will default 0.00s.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-14 numeric characters &amp; "." (number of decimal places dependent on the currency). Where Field 9, Net trade = NO. Mandatory input. Where Field 9, Net Trade = Y(es), Automatic default is to 0.00.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.SRC.LCL.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>A NOINPUT multi-value associated field. This indicates whether the tax is to be deducted by the bank (LOCAL) or the depositor (SOURCE).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     A NOINPUT field</p>
            <p>     Either SOURCE or LOCAL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.TAX.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer tax amount in local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the Customer's Reference Currency, IE. the currency specified in the Customer's SEC ACC MASTER record (Field 2: Reference Currency)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     NOINPUT required. Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the tax code to be used for the purposes of calculating the capital gains tax amount.</p>
            <p>     If this field is changed then a recalculation of the tax amount is triggered off.</p>
            <p>     The tax code will initially be defaulted by the system depending on the default settings.</p>
            <p>     If the TAX record field LINK.TAX is populated then all linked tax codes will be shown.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Input must be a valid tax code on the TAX file.</p>
            <p>     Only multi-value 1 can be used for input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.ORDER.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi value NOINPUT field which contains the reference numbers which belong to the open orders belonging to the client which have generated the sec.trade.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROK.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as a category reference for the broker. The suspense amount of the broker is posted to it.</p>
            <p>     NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer tax type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.NOMINEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Nominee with whom the Security is registered.</p>
            <p>     The nominee code forms part of the "key" by which the system identifies holdings by individual clients by depository holding.</p>
            <p>     Great care should be taken at transaction level when using the nominee code.</p>
            <p>     Because the nominee code will form part of the key when buying or selling securities an override message may well have to be overridden at transaction level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) character Nominee.code. Multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>     Must be a valid Nominee.Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the Price at which the trade has been dealt. NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.EBV.FEES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the amount of EBV Fees charged to the Customer for the trade.</p>
            <p>     Where indicated by the flag set within the Stock Exchange table the system will default the EBV (Effectenboursenverein) fees in accordance with the rules as laid down within that particular Stock Exchange.</p>
            <p>     The values for which will be found within the Calculation table for that individual Stock Exchange.</p>
            <p>     Note:      These charges being a LOCAL requirement for the Swiss            Stock Exchange charges.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Automatic default to charge as calculated by the system. or     1-14 numeric characters &amp; "." (number of decimal places dependant on the currency). Where Field 9, Net trade = NO, Mandatory input Where Field 9, Net Trade = Y(es), Automatic default is to 0.00.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi Value field which is used to store any comments or free format narrative concerning the customer or the transaction.</p>
            <p>     Additionally, if the SEC.TRADE was produced as a direct result of an executed SECURITY.OPEN.ORDER which contained any narrative, then that narrative is carried over for subsequent display on the SEC.TRADE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Free Format narrative text. Up to 35 maximum characters per line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THREAD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The thread key that was used in the creation of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Coupon Rate of the Security, ie. the rate at which interest is to be accrued from Last Payment Date (Field 11) to Value Date (Field 6).</p>
            <p>     The system uses the accrual date as displayed within Field 10 along with the interest rate and the Interest day Basis as per the Security.Master record to calculate both the number of days accrued and the amount of accrued interest payable on any individual bond transaction.</p>
            <p>     Whilst the number of days and the actual accrued interest amount can be overridden at transaction level the interest rate has to be changed at Security.Master level.</p>
            <p>     IMPORTANT.</p>
            <p>     The User must understand any change to the number of days accrued or the calculated amount will merely be recovered by the system at the End of Day processing when dealing with the Banks Own Portfolio Transactions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     NOINPUT required. Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer commissions in SEC.TRADE are defaulted from the CUSTOMER.CHARGE record for the customer using the SC.APPLICATION set of fields. It will use the set of fields linked to SC.TRADING if they are present and default to ALL otherwise. From there the system links to the SCTR.GROUP.CONDITION application and then onto the SCTR.CHARGE.PARAMETER application to get the actual FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record used.</p>
            <p>     When the customer commission is calculated the percentage used to calculate the commission will be recorded in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.FEES.MISC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the amount of Miscellaneous Fees charged to the Customer for the trade.</p>
            <p>     It cannot be automated as its very name suggests, its intended usage would normally cover telex and perhaps postage or cable charges for example.</p>
            <p>     Within the standard default table SC.STD.SEC.TRADE the User can determine to which P&amp;L category code these miscellaneous fees are to be posted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1-14 numeric characters &amp; "." (number of decimal places dependant on the currency). Where Field 9, Net trade = NO, Optional input Where Field 9, Net Trade = Y(es), Automatic default is to 0.00.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Customer's Account, over which financial entries relating to the trade are to be passed.</p>
            <p>     Multi-valued Field.</p>
            <p>     Default is to the Account specified on the Customer's SEC ACC MASTER record, for the Trade currency (TRADE.CCY) or (if no Account in the Trade currency is specified) to the Customer's first account on the SEC.ACC.MASTER record (CUST.SEC.ACC) - ACCOUNT.NOS field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>     1-16 numeric character Account number or 3-10 character Mnemonic Account id (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".").</p>
            <p>     Default value = the Account specified on the Customer's SEC.ACC.MASTER record.</p>
            <p>     Must be a valid Account on the ACCOUNT file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.ACT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as a category reference for the customer.The suspense amount of the customer is posted to it.</p>
            <p>     The value is picked up from the SC.PARAMETER which holds a similar field in it. The value is defaulted from the SC.PARAMETER fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     The value in this field should be a valid entry in CATEGORY         file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.EX.RATE.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate of exchange between the Trade Currency (Field 7) and the Cu.Account.Ccy (Field 42.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-10 numeric characters &amp; "." (1-6 integers and 1-9 decimal places). Default value = rate calculated as per the CURRENCY file records.</p>
            <p>     Where input manually the rate must fall between the parameters set on the CURRENCY files.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CUST.SETT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the automatic settlement of the nominal and cash for the Customers who have contractual agreements with the Bank.</p>
            <p>     This facility is available for the Customer side only.</p>
            <p>     The value is defaulted as 'YES', if it has been set to 'YES' in the AUTO.CUST.SETT field in CUSTOMER.SECURITY</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Allows only Yes, No or Null.  Null is equivalent to NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Account over which financial entries relating to the Broker for the trade, are to be passed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.NO.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Nominal Amount of the Security traded. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the Price at which the Nominal Amount has been traded. NOINPUT field replicating data input on the parent SEC.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

