<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.SPLIT.TRADE.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CU.BROKER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the broker related to the customer as against the street side broker specified for the order. In the case of this customers, the order execution would be routed through the routing company as specified in ROUT COMPANY</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This field will allow input of a CUSTOMER.SECURITY id with CUSTOMER.TYPE set to BROKER/CLIENT/COUNTERPARTY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORD.COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be a multi-value field associated with ORD.COMP.PORT and specifies the company to which the portfolio as specified in ORD.COMP.PORT relates to, in the routing company defined as ID.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This field will allow a valid company to be input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with APP.FIELD to APP.VALUE and specifies the file from which the conditions could be specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Allows specification of conditions based on fields in SECURITY.MASTER, CUSTOMER.SECURITY and SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORD.COMP.PORT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The field is a multi-value field associated with ORD.COMPANY field. This field will allow a SEC.ACC.MASTER to be input. The portfolio must be CUSTOMER PORTFOLIO not a Dealer-Book. This field also allow a value CLIENT to be input. This identifies the omnibus portfolio related to ORD.COMPANY maintained in the ID company. If no portfolio is maintained, "CLIENT" could be specified.</p>
            <p>Wherever ORD.COMP.PORT is set to CLIENT the respective companies customers are to be defined as both CUSTOMER and CLIENT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid portfolio or "CLIENT" is accepted</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Record id, must be a valid COMPANY id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with APP.FIELD to APP.VALUE and specifies the file from which the conditions could be specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Allows specification of conditions based on fields in SECURITY.MASTER, CUSTOMER.SECURITY and SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.DELIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Delimiter specified for separating set of values in APP.VALUE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example *</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field in the application specified in FILE based on the values of which conditions for depository default are set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid field in the application specified in FILE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Operand associated with APP.FIELD and APP.VALUE to construct as selection sentence which will be executed to determine the conditions for defaulting depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Input must be one of EQ,LT,NE,LE,GT or GE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field associated with APP.FIELD,APP.DELIMIT and APP.OPERAND. The value in this field read in conjunction with above three fields would determine whether conditions for defaulting routing company are met.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

