<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.STD.NEW.ISSUE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains company level default values which will be used when processing new issue transactions. </p>
            <p>These defaults will be applicable irrespective of the transaction type and the user must create one record for each company on the system. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.CR.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used to signify which type of transaction is being posted, for exchange Profits. </p>
            <p>To facilitate the recognition of the transaction code numbers with the application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each application. </p>
            <p>The following range has been assigned within T24: </p>
            <p>           600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.DR.TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default transaction code for all Security Debit type entries within this application. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETRO.PL.CAT.DB</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 6 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPLY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date by which replies must be received in order for Subscribers to any New Issue to be considered for possible allotment by the Issuing agent concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETRO.PL.CAT.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 6 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard default to the Nominee Co. indicated.  It is unlikely that this facility be utilised but may be necessary where a Nominee Co. is not controlled by the Bank concerned. </p>
            <p>Where entered at a Companies' Standard default Level the System will automatically create New Issue Transactions with an inherent Nominee Code relating to the Code as entered here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alpha numeric characters, (type SS) Standard nominee code. Optional input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Nominee Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.DB.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code used to signify which type of transaction is being posted, for exchange Losses. </p>
            <p>To facilitate the recognition of the transaction code numbers with the application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each application. </p>
            <p>The following range has been assigned within T24: </p>
            <p>           600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.CR.TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default transaction code for all Security Credit type entries with this application. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Bank's own account for posting cost and proceeds for any New Issue transaction. </p>
            <p>Internal Account or New Issues' Account for default purposes when processing New Issues. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard account format. Optional input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Account Number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Company to which the User must be Signed On in order to use the Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>9 alphanumeric characters 'CCGGGLLLL' where: CC   is 2 alpha characters Country Code GGG  is 3 numeric characters Company Group LLLL is 4 numeric local code. or     2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or '.') Company Mnemonic characters. Mandatory input.  No Default Value.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid company code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard default for the delivery of the new issue. </p>
            <p>Whenever New Issue Transactions are created by the System they will automatically assume the Delivery Instructions as contained within the Standard Default Tables. </p>
            <p>Examples:  Receive new issue against payment delivery free of            payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alpha numeric characters, (type S). Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid Security Delivery Instruction (SC. DEL. Instr) code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the category code to be used for the posting of exchange Profit &amp; Loss entries. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit &amp; loss and product types. Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's position. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Must be in range 50-000 to 59-999.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid CATEGORY code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

