<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.SETTLEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>BR.NOM.DEL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The delivery reference of the incoming message that settled/unsettled the nominal.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.REVERSE.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to reverse(unsettle) stock for the customer.</p>
            <p>  An input into this field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field and</p>
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOM.RECD.DEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to input the number of stock to be settled.</p>
            <p>  Input into this field immediately updates</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field and</p>
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than</p>
            <p>  The value in this field would be cleared including the         fields upto</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.RESERVED4</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.AUTO.SETT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows whether the broker settlement is automatic (Y) or not. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUS.AMT.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total amount of cash settled as a result of the current input to the Customer side in this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input at</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is cleared at authorisation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.TOL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the amount posted to the settlement tolerances internal account, only shown when full settlement of nominal is made and only if settlement tolerances are setup for the depository involved.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.ACC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the currency on the settlement account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique transaction reference.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.REVERSE.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to reverse(unsettle) stock which was previously settled in this transaction.</p>
            <p>  An input into this field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field and</p>
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains details of any overrides applicable to this transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>  Multivalue field. (Internal field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security to be settled.</p>
            <p>  Each security involved in the original transaction will have a separate settlement record.</p>
            <p>  Therefore there will be only one settlement record from transactions in SEC.TRADE and SECURITY.TRANSFER that have requested actual settlement.</p>
            <p>  Transactions from DIARY and ENTITLEMENT may create more than one settlement record.</p>
            <p>  Transactions from POSITION.TRANSFER will create two settlement records, one each for the transfer of stock out of one depository and the transfer into another depository.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Defaulted from the         transaction which created this settlement record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.SETT.DEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether MT544-547 Confirmation of Delivery advice should be generated for the Customer. This field gets populated from GEN.SETT.DEL field in CUSTOMER.SECURITY for the particular customer which can be overridden at the tranasction level. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Single value field within the customer mutli value set which would accept ‘YES' or null as a valid value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOM.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value date of the settled/ unsettled nominals.</p>
            <p>  If data in input in the</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than today.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARENT.TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value to this field is populated from the field PARENT.TXN.ID of SECURITY.TRANSFER record. This field is a no-input field and is updated only for those transaction that come from REPO.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  No input, Updated from Security Transfer record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CPTY.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether or not counterparty limit checking is taking place.</p>
            <p>  If this field is set to "YES", then counterparty limit is associated with the first broker and the BR.AMT.OUTSTAND field will be used to update the counterparty limit.</p>
            <p>  Counterparty limit would work with single broker.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.EXPOSURE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the Local Currency Equivalent of Broker's Outstanding Amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LT.AMT.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the lending amount to be settled.  This field is mapped  from the LENT.AMT field of ENTITLEMENT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINAL.TO.SETTLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the number of nominals yet to be settled on the customer's side.</p>
            <p>  This field will be updated at the same time as</p>
            <p>  The value in this field will start with the value in</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally calculated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input at</p>
            <p>  Must be zero at the time of committment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.AUTO.SETT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows whether the customer settlement is automatic (Y) or not. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value date of the trade i.e. date after which the transaction can be settled.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Defaulted from the         transaction which created this settlement record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total number of shares for settlement for the security specified in the field</p>
            <p>  Where Multi Client/Multi Broker transactions have been input, the system will calculate the total per broker to be received or delivered and populate the appropriate fields at the time of creation of the settlement record.</p>
            <p>  At this level we are not concerned with the Customer/Broker breakdown, merely the Net amount of stock to be settled.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally calculated at the time of creation of the         record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.XRATE.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This shows the exchange rate between the account currency and the trade currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.NOM.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total number of nominals settled as a result of current input to the Broker side of this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally calculated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input in</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.AMT.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the total amount of outstanding(unsettled) cash for the associated portfolio.</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is updated at Input stage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LT.AMT.VAL.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is similar to CU.AMT.VAL.DATE and is used to capture the settlement/reversal date for the lending amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.NOM.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total outstanding (unsettled) securities for the associated Broker.</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally calculated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input in</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>A number Generated automatically by the system after authorisation which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of a transaction. After validation but before authorisation, the value 'VAL' will be inserted in this field to indicate that the transaction has been validated successfully but is still waiting authorisation.</p>
            <p>  After authorisation of a Funds Transfer transaction, the system will automatically insert a number into this field and this number may refer to a statement entry or a category entry depending on the value contained in the corresponding multivalue fields. The following examples will illustrate the use of this field.</p>
            <p>  Example 1:</p>
            <p>  On the execution date of a transaction there will normally be an entry on a Customer account and the following type of number will be generated at this field:</p>
            <p>  92.1 STMT.NO  673732684.48 92.2 STMT.NO  1</p>
            <p>  The number automatically generated in field 92.1 is unique to the transaction in question and is built in the following way:</p>
            <p>  1. The first four digits '6737' indicate the number of days since the 1st of January 1968. In our example, it corresponds to the 11th of June 1986.</p>
            <p>  2. The next five digits '32684' indicate the number of seconds since midnight. In our example, it corresponds to an entry generated on line at 09:04:44 AM.</p>
            <p>  3. The last two digits '48' indicate the number of hundreds of seconds.</p>
            <p>  The value assigned (again automatically) to field 92.2 identifies the number in 92.1 as a statement entry number. If the User wishes to call this statement entry record on to the screen the User will invoke the STMT.ENTRY Application and the type the following at 'Awaiting ID' :-</p>
            <p>  673732684.480001</p>
            <p>  where the suffix '0001' identifies it as the first statement entry (there will normally be more than one as the next example will illustrate).</p>
            <p>  Example 2:</p>
            <p>  A second example outlined here is similar to that in example 1, in that there is a statement entry on value date for both the our account and the customer account. The system handles this case as follows:</p>
            <p>  92.1 STMT.NO  673732684.48 92.2 STMT.NO  1-2</p>
            <p>  Once again field 92.1 contains the identification number automatically generated by the system while field 92.2 now contains two separate numbers signifying that there are infact two separate statement entries, one in respect of the our account pay and one in respect of the our account receive. If the User wishes to see either of these he must first of all invoke STMT.ENTRY followed by the desired function and then at 'Awaiting ID' type EITHER:</p>
            <p>  673732684.480001</p>
            <p>  where the addition of the suffix '0001' identifies the statement entry in respect of the our account OR</p>
            <p>  673732684.480002</p>
            <p>  where the addition of the suffix '0002' identifies the statement entry in respect of the customer account.</p>
            <p>  Example 3:</p>
            <p>  A third example might be that of a category entry generated at initiation of a transaction where commission or charges have been debited to the customer and credited to a profit and loss category code. In this case the following entries are generated on the transaction:</p>
            <p>  92.1 STMT.NO  673732684.48 92.3 STMT.NO  1</p>
            <p>  Once again the standard type number is generated and inserted at field 92.1</p>
            <p>  Now, however, field 92.2 is replaced by field 92.3 which now identifies the number in 92.1 as a category entry and not a statement entry.</p>
            <p>  To call this category entry record onto the screen the User must now type:</p>
            <p>  CATEG.ENTRY at 'Awaiting Application'</p>
            <p>  followed by:</p>
            <p>  673732684.480001 at 'Awaiting ID'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internal Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOM.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the total nominals settled so far for the associated portfolio.</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field would be updated at Input stage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LT.AMT.REV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is similar to CU.REVERSE.AMT and is used to capture the customer settled lending amount being reversed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date of the trade. Deal Date. Tax Point.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Defaulted from the         transaction which created this settlement record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.NOM.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the security was settled/ unsettled.</p>
            <p>  Defaults to the value of</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than today.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CUST.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total amount of cash to be Debited from or Credited to the Customers on this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally calculated at the time of creation of the         record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Broker involved in the transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Defaulted from the         transaction which created this settlement record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Picks up the date when the settlement is completed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated with today's date when settlement is complete. ie         when the outstanding nominals and amounts are zero.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRK.AMT.REVERSED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the total amount of cash reversed(unsettled) as a result of the current input to the Broker side in this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input at</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is cleared at authorisation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.AMT.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the amount was settled/ unsettled.</p>
            <p>  Defaults to the value on VALUE.DATE if null and if data exists in BR.AMT.REC.PAID or BR.REVERSE.AMT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Cannot be greater than today.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRK.AMT.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total amount of cash settled as a result of current input to the Broker side in this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input at</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is cleared at authorisation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency that the trade is to be settled in.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Defaulted from the         transaction which created this settlement record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.AMT.DEL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The delivery reference of the incoming message that settled/unsettled the nominal.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For future use</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.REVERSE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to reverse(unsettle) the cash amount that was previously settled.</p>
            <p>  When data is input into the</p>
            <p>  An input into this field updates the</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is mutually exclusive with</p>
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than the value         in</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CPTY.LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the limit reference, if this transaction has updated counterparty limit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPO.CONF.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds incoming MT544-547 delivery reference.</p>
            <p>  system updated field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 35 characters in length</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.RESERVED4</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Depository that holds or is to receive the Security concerned.</p>
            <p>  In the case of POSITION.TRANSFER, two records are created for each security involved with the depository field differing in the two records as the DEPOSITORY.FROM and the DEPOSITORY.TO from the POSITION.TRANSFER record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Defaulted from the         transaction which created this settlement record.</p>
            <p>  Cannot contain the value 'ALL' for a rights issue.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THREAD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the service agent reference from which the transaction originated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.RESERVED5</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BW.AMT.VAL.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is similar to CU.AMT.VAL.DATE and is used to capture the settlement/reversal date for the borrow amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BW.AMT.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is similar to CU.AMT.SETTLED and stores the borrow amount settled till date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LT.AMT.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is similar to CU.AMT.SETTLED and stores the lending amount settled till date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.AMT.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the amount to be credited/ debited to the settlement account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.REVERSE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to reverse (unsettle) cash amounts for the broker.</p>
            <p>  When data is input into the BR.REVERSE.NOM field, a suggested amount for reversal is defaulted into this field using the formula BR</p>
            <p>  An input into this field immediately updates the TOTAL.AMT.REVERSED and AMOUNT.TO.REVERSE fields, increasing them.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field and BR.AMT.REC.PAID are mutually exclusive.</p>
            <p>  Cannot be greater than the value in BR.AMT.SETTLED.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LT.AMT.REC.PAID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is similar to CU.AMT.REC.PAID and is used to capture the customer lending amount being settled.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.NOM.RECD.DEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to input the number of stock to be settled.</p>
            <p>  Input into this field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field and</p>
            <p>  The value in this cannot be greater than</p>
            <p>  At Authorisation the value starting from this field to</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BW.AMT.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field  stores the borrow amount to be settled. This field is mapped  from the BORROW.AMT field of ENTITLEMENT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.NOM.REVERSED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total number of nominals reversed (unsettled) as a result of the current input to the Broker side on this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input at BR.REVERSE.NOM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BW.AMT.REC.PAID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is similar to CU.AMT.REC.PAID and is used to capture the customer borrow amount being settled.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINAL.TO.REVERSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the number of nominals yet to be reversed on the customer's side.</p>
            <p>  This field will be updated at the same time as</p>
            <p>  The value in this field starts with the value of</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input at</p>
            <p>  Must be zero at the time of committment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.DEL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Single value field within the customer multi value set which will store the outward MT544-547 delivery reference key generated by the system.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.NOM.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of nominals settled so far for the associated Broker.</p>
            <p>  Thisvalue in this field will be</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is updated at Authorisation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.DEL.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Delivery instructions for the original transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Defaulted from the         transaction which created this settlement record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.BROKER.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total amout of cash to be Credited to or Debited from the brokers in this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally calculated at the time of creation of the         record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the SC Transaction code of the Customer side.</p>
            <p>  If the</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>  Obtained from the transaction which has created the         particular</p>
            <p>  Will comprise a valid</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Portfolio which holds the unsettled cash/stock.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Copied from the Transaction         which has created the particular</p>
            <p>  The value in this field must exist in the</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.AMT.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the total amount of cash settled so far, for the associated portfolio.</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is updated at Authorisation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.AMT.REC.PAID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to input the amount of cash to be settled for the porfolio.</p>
            <p>  When data is input into the</p>
            <p>  Input into this field updates</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is mutually exclusive with</p>
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than the value         in</p>
            <p>  The value starting from this field to</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOM.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total number of outstanding(unsettled) nominals with the associated portfolio.</p>
            <p>  The value in this field would be</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is updated at Input stage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field which is used to store any comments or free format narrative concerning the customer or the transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Free Format narrative text. Up to 35 maximum characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field which is used to store any comments or free format narrative concerning the Broker or the transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Free Format narrative text. Up to 35 maximum characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BW.REV.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is similar to CU.REVERSE.AMT and is used to capture the customer settled borrow amout being reversed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.MC.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUS.AMT.REVERSED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total amount of cash reversed(unsettled) as a result of the current input to the Customer side in this transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>  Updated as soon as data is input at</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is cleared at authorisation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOMINEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Nominee for the unsettled stock/ cash.</p>
            <p>  This field contains the value that is part of the</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Internally generated field. Copied from the Transaction         which has created the particular</p>
            <p>  An input to this field must exist in</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.AMT.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value date of the settled/ unsettled amount.</p>
            <p>  If data is input in the</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than today.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOM.DEL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Delivery reference of the incoming message that settled/unsettled the nominal.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For future use.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.AMT.DEL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the delivery instruction of the incoming message that settled/ unsettled the nominal.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.AMT.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total amount of outstanding(unsettled) cash for the associated broker.</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is updated at Input stage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.AMT.REC.PAID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to input the amount of cash to be settled for the broker.</p>
            <p>  When data is input into the</p>
            <p>  Input into this field immediately updates the following fields</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is mutually exclusive with</p>
            <p>  The value in this field cannot be greater than</p>
            <p>  At Authorisation the value starting from this field to</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.AMT.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the total amount of cash settled so far for the associated Broker.</p>
            <p>  The value in this field is</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is updated at Input stage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field> PARENT </field>
<desc>
            <p> Allowed value is YES </p>
            <p> This field is to determine whether the order is a parent order </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field> PARENT.REFERENCE </field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will accept alphanumeric Value </p>
            <p> Unique parent reference that is common for both parent and child orders and will serve as a link.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>