<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.STD.OPTIONS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains company level default values which will be used when processing OPTION.TRADE transactions. </p>
            <p>These defaults will be applicable irrespective of the transaction type. The user must create on record for each company on the system. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MARKET.PL.CR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default TRANSACTION code for all Credit transactions within OPTION.TRADE where market profit &amp; loss occurs. </p>
            <p>To facilitate the matching of the TRANSACTION code to the application to which it refers ranges have been assigned to each application. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24: </p>
            <p>           600 - 649 = Securities </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>Must exist as a valid TRANSACTION code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the nominee company in whose name a security is registered. </p>
            <p>In the eventuality that all OPTION.TRADES within a company are settled into and out of a particular nominee company this field would contain the standard default key for that nominee company. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alphanumeric input, (type S) standard nominee code. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the NOMINEE.CODE table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.DB.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.PL.DB.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The debit TRANSACTION code for all market profit &amp; loss entries within the OPTION.TRADE. </p>
            <p>To facilitate the matching of the TRANSACTION code to the application to which it refers ranges have been assigned to each application. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24: </p>
            <p>           600 - 649 = Securities </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the profit &amp; loss category for any potential 'Market' profit or loss with an OPTION.TRADE. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit and loss and product types. Each business transaction within T24 will be allocated a CATEGORY code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's operations. </p>
            <p>Note:      At the moment the customer price must equal broker price            so there is no possible chance of market profit and loss            occuring within an OPTION.TRADE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters. a)   Product/P&amp;L classification in the range 1-99. b)   Sub-classification of product/P&amp;L in the range 000-999. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid CATEGORY code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the COMPANY to which the user must be signed on in order to use the application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>9 alphanumerid characters 'CCGGGLLLL' where: CC   is 2 alpha characters COUNTRY Code GGG  is 3 numeric characters COMPANY Group LLLL is 4 numeric local code or         2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or '.') Company Mnemonic characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid COMPANY code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of delivery involved in settling any OPTION.TRADE. </p>
            <p>Used as the standard delivery instructions for any particular OPTION.TRADE.  It may, however, be changed at transaction level. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alphanumeric characters, (type 'S') standard delivery instruction. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the SC.DEL.INSTR table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.PL.CR.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

