<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.TRAIL.FEES.HOLDING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds information relating to a trailer fees for each issuer as on the payment date.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi Value No Input field which is used to store any comments or free format narrative concerning the customer or the transaction. Free Format narrative text. Up to 35 maximum characters per line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>System defaults the currency of the account mentioned in PAYMENT.ACCOUNT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No input field. Updated by the system</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies end date for which the holding record is been created. It is updated by the system with the NEXT.PAY.DATE set in corresponding SC.TRAIL.FEES.ARRANGEMENT record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No input field. Updated by the system</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>XRATE.CALC.PAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the exchange rate applicable between the calculation currency and payment currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a single value field.</p>
            <p> 1-10 numeric characters &amp; "." (1-6 integers and 1-9 decimal places).</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define which payment account to be used to make the payment. It is defaulted from the corresponding arrangement record. It can however be changed at the transaction level.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field used to capture the payment amount received from the issuer.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ISSUER for whom the holding is been created. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field. Updated by the system </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THRESHOLD.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Threshold amount and it gets defaulted from the corresponding issuer level arrangement. If the difference amount is within the threshold amount, single entry will be raised for the issuer receivable account against Profit &amp; Loss booked for the issuer. If the difference amount is not within the threshold amount then adjustment entries is raised against individual client level </p>
            <p> The functionality of this field is effective only if the payment is marked as ‘COMPLETE’.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a single value field which accepts numeric character</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIFF.AMT.PAY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the difference amount (in payment ccy) that is prorated against the client level</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a Noinput field and is within the associated multivalue set</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVABLE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defaults the account from SC.TRAIL.FEES.ARRANGEMENT application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the payment made is partial or complete. If SETT.STATUS is marked as Complete, then there cannot be any further payments and adjustment entries will be raised (if there is any difference between the actual amount due and the received amount). System automatically marks the payment as COMPLETE, if the payment amount is exactly equal to the amount due.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a single value field and the valid input is ‘COMPLETE’</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the total amount paid by the Issuer </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a Noinput field which gets defaulted by the system.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>A number Generated automatically by the system after authorisation which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of a transaction. After validation but before authorisation, the value 'VAL' will be inserted in this field to indicate that the transaction has been validated successfully but is still waiting authorisation.</p>
            <p>     After authorisation of a Funds Transfer transaction, the system will automatically insert a number into this field and this number may refer to a statement entry or a category entry depending on the value contained in the corresponding multivalue fields. The following examples will illustrate the use of this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Internal Multivalue field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.UNSETT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the outstanding amount that is due from the Issuer</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a singe value and Noinput field which gets defaulted by the system.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies start date for which the holding record is been created. It is updated by system with the LAST.PAY.DATE set in corresponding SC.TRAIL.FEES.ARRANGEMENT record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No input field. Updated by the system</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALCULATED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the recalculated trailer fee amount when a back valuation process is triggered</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a Noinput field and is defaulted by the system</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIFF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the difference between the PAYMENT.AMT and the ACT.CALC.AMT which is expressed in Payment currency. This field is populated only when the payment is marked as ‘COMPLETE’</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a single value and Noinput field. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>XRATE.PAY.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the exchange rate applicable between the payment currency and local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a single value field.</p>
            <p> 1-10 numeric characters &amp; "." (1-6 integers and 1-9 decimal places).</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Noinput field which store the overrides raised by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.TRA.FEE.HLD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key of this application is &lt;SC.TRAIL FEES ARRANGEMENT id&gt;.&lt;Payment Date&gt;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIFF.AMT.CALC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the difference amount (in calculation ccy) that is prorated against the client level</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a Noinput field and is within the associated multivalue set</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.CALC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is updated by the system with the actual calculated trailer fee amount for this payment period</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a Noinput field and is defaulted by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.IN.CALC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the trailer fee amount that is accrued for this issuer in specific calculation currency</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a Noinput field and is within the associated multivalue set</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.IN.PAY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the trailer fee amount that is accrued for this issuer in equivalent payment currency</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a Noinput field and is within the associated multivalue set</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency in which calculation is been made. It updated by the system with the CALC.CCY set in corresponding SC.TRAIL.FEES.ARRANGEMENT record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field. Updated by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

