<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.TR.FEE.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains company level default values that must be set up for the Trailer fees.      </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TR.FEE.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the suspense category which is treated as a wash account for posting capitalization entry and apportioning of difference amount (if any). </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a single value and mandatory field. </p>
            <p> Standard Category field. (Category code from 10000 – 19999)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this field is set to DAILY, then the trailer fee accrual entries will be raised on a daily basis for all issuers who have an arrangement with the respective customer company. Otherwise the accrual entries will be raised only on the calculation date as per the arrangement of the issuer.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a single value and optional field.</p>
            <p> Only valid value is DAILY. This field cannot be changed from DAILY to Null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This table contains company level default values that must be set up for the Trailer fees    </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Should be a valid Company and one record must be created for each company running the trailer fees</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field needs to be set to indicate which day basis has to be used for daily accrual. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> This is a single value and optional field.</p>
            <p> This field becomes mandatory if the field ACCRUAL.METHOD is set to DAILY and change is not allowed in this field once it is set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the default product under which the bank would like to report their PL earned on account of trailer fees.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 4 or 5 Numeric characters. Must exist as a valid CATEGORY code.</p>
            <p> This is a single value and mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

