<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.TRAIL.FEES.EXTRACT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Record which gets build on every Calculation date or Month end (in case of special frequency) mentioned in the SC.TRAIL.FEES.ARRANGEMENT record. This is a Live file and it holds the trailer fees at the individual portfolio level.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Depository for whom the extract was built. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.NO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of trade dated nominal as on the Extract date while running Back Valuation process. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUER</field>
<desc>
            <p> Specifies the ISSUER for whom the EXTRACT is been created. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIFF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the difference amount in payment currency that is prorated against the individual client level</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTRACT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on which the extract details got updated. It is based on the calculation date set in SC.TRAIL.FEE.ARRANGEMENT. This field along with its associated set of fields gets deleted upon authorizing the SC.TRAIL.FEE.HOLDING till the period for which payment has been made</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will store the Value from the SC.PRICE.CHANGE File as on each Calculation date while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.V.DATE.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of value dated nominal as on the Extract date while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRAIL.REF.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of  Trailer ref level of the related security as on the extract date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.TRAIL.REF.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the  value of Current TRAIL.REF.LEVEL from SECURITY.MASTER while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.INDEX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the  value of Current INDEX from SECURITY.MASTER while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.TOT.ACCR.AMT.PAY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the total recalculated accrual amount in equivalent payment currency that is accrued till date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.T.NO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the  sum of NO.NOMINAL and BV.NO.NOMINAL as on the Calculation Date while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of trade dated nominal as on the extract date. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.T.V.DATE.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the  sum of V.DATE.NOMINAL and BV.V.DATE.NOMINAL as on the Calculation Date while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.TOT.ACCR.AMT.CALC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the total recalculated accrual amount in calculation currency that is accrued till date. </p>
            <p />
            <p> EXAMPLE:- (The Back valuation process is Triggered After the Creation of the Payment record) :- </p>
            <p> CALC DATE | EXTR.ACC.AMT </p>
            <p> 10-JAN-2008 | 100</p>
            <p> 15-JAN-2008 | 100</p>
            <p> 16-JAN-2008 | 100</p>
            <p />
            <p> TOT.ACCR.AMT.CALC.CCY = 300</p>
            <p />
            <p> If the SECURITY price is changed on 15-JAN-2008 then the Back valuation process is triggered and Recalculation is done for the 15-JAN-2008, 16-JAN-2008 and it will Update in the BV.EXTR.ACC.AMT with the new recalculated values.</p>
            <p> The BV.CAL.DATE is updated with the value as 15-JAN-2008 and 16-JAN-2008. </p>
            <p> The sum of Recalculated price is stored in the BV.TOT.ACCR.AMT.CALC.CCY</p>
            <p />
            <p> After Back valuation service:- </p>
            <p> CALC DATE   |EXTR.ACC.AMT| BV.CALC.DATE | BV.EXTR.ACC.AMT</p>
            <p> 10-JAN-2008 | 100                    |                              | </p>
            <p> 15-JAN-2008 | 100                    | 15-JAN-2008     |  110</p>
            <p> 16-JAN-2008 | 100                    |  16-JAN-2008    |  100</p>
            <p />
            <p> BV.TOT.ACCR.AMT.CALC.CCY = 310</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.FEE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate that is applied in the calculation of trailer fee</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.TR.FEE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the  value of Current TR.FEE.RATE from ARRANGEMENT record while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency in which calculation is been made. It is updated by the system with the CALC.CCY set in corresponding SC.TRAIL.FEES.ARRANGEMENT record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the SECURITY.NO for which the extract was built</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.ACCR.AMT.CALC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the total accrual amount in calculation currency that is accrued till date </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.RATE.CALC.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the exchange rate applicable between the Calculation and the Local currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.TRAIL.EXT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key of the SC.TRAIL.FEES.EXTRACT record. The Key will be of format </p>
            <p>     &lt;SECURITY NUMBER&gt;.&lt;CUSTOMER&gt;.&lt;PORTFOLIO SUFFIX&gt;.&lt;DEPOSITORY&gt;.</p>
            <p>     Once the payment date is reached, the extract record is moved from the current reference to </p>
            <p>     &lt;SECURITY NUMBER&gt;.&lt;CUSTOMER&gt;.&lt;PORTFOLIO SUFFIX&gt;.&lt;DEPOSITORY&gt;.&lt;PAYMENT.DATE&gt;.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>V.DATE.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of value dated nominal as on the extract date. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INIT.REF.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of Initial ref level of the related security as on the extract date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Customer for whom the extract was built. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.INIT.REF.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the  value of Current INIT.REF.LEVEL from SECURITY.MASTER while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDEX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of Index value of the related security as on the extract date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of last price as on the extract date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.RATE.CALC.PAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the exchange rate applicable between the calculation currency and payment currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will store the actual calculation date as per the arrangement</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.ACCR.AMT.PAY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the total accrual amount in equivalent payment currency that is accrued till date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of accrued amount calculated as on the extract date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.AMT.PAY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the accrued amount calculated as on the extract date in equivalent payment currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.ACCR.AMT.PAY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Recalculated accrued amount as on the calculation date in equivalent payment currency . </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.CALC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will store the actual calculation date as per the arrangement while running Back valuation process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.EXT.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the  value of Recalculated EXT.ACCR.AMT as on the Calculation Date while running Back Valuation Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>REIMBURSE.TR.FEE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
