<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.UNSETTL.TXNS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Live file for holding details of unsettled transactions and the contra settlement record in</p>
            <p>the original security for a Stock Conversion event</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DIARY.ACT.SETT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate if Diary is processed under Actual Settlement or not.</p>
            <p>Holds the value of the field SEC.HOLD.SETTLE from DIARY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Portfolio for which entitlement is created.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSAL.MARKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate the Reversal if Entitlement record is reversed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNSETT.TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Record key containing</p>
            <p />
            <p>Entitlement id '*' Transaction Ref incase the record holds detail of unsettled transactions.</p>
            <p>or</p>
            <p>The Contra Settlement Record id if the records holds the contra settlement record detail.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOM.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unsettled nominal for the customer in the underlying transaction.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESSED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate that the record is already processed to avoid the same record getting selected for processing next time.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate that the record is already processed to avoid the same record getting selected for processing next time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.NOM.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Settled nominal(out of the unsettled nominal in the CU.NOM.OUTSTAND field) for the customer in the underlying transaction.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOM.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unsettled nominal for the broker in the underlying transaction for the specific customer for whom entitlement is created.</p>
            <p />
            <p>(Associated multivalue - fields BROKER to CASH.SETTLED)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOM.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Settled nominal (out of the unsettled nominals in the NOM.OUTSTAND field) for the broker in the underlying transaction for the specific customer for whom entitlement is created.</p>
            <p />
            <p>(Associated multivalue - fields BROKER to CASH.SETTLED)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.CASH.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Settled cash(out of the unsettled cash in the CU.CASH.OUTSTAND field) for the customer</p>
            <p>in the underlying transaction.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Broker ID (Associated multivalue - fields BROKER to CASH.SETTLED)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unsettled amount for the broker in the underlying trade for the specific customer</p>
            <p>for whom entitlement is created.</p>
            <p />
            <p>(Associated multivalue - fields BROKER to CASH.SETTLED)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.SETTLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Settled cash (out of the unsettled cash in the CASH.OUTSTAND field) for the broker</p>
            <p>in the underlying transaction for the specific customer for whom entitlement is created.</p>
            <p />
            <p>(Associated multivalue - fields BROKER to CASH.SETTLED)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.CASH.OUTSTAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unsettled cash for the customer in the underlying transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

