<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SC.VALUATION.GROUP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>Application to define the list of child portfolios for the master portfolio for the valuation of the group based on the LINK.TYPE field.</p>
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CHILD.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
<p>List of child portfolios. Associated multivalue set with PLEDGE.PCT and PLEDGE.AMT</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.TYPE</field>
<desc>
<p>Allowed options are FIXED, VARIABLE, NETTING, MASTER FIXED AND MASTER VARIABLE. If NETTING then individual positions of child portfolios will be consolidated after applying the netting rules (long and short, for example). If VARIABLE, then only one single amount will be updated in master SC.POS.ASSET, which will be the lower of net margin value and amount specified for lending. If percentage is specified, Amount will be percentage of net margin value. If FIXED, then percentage cannot be specified. One single amount will be updated in master SC.POS.ASSET, which will be the amount specified for lending.</p>
<p>If MASTER FIXED OR MASTER VARIABLE is Specified then only a Portfolio which has a SC.VALUATION.GROUP record can be linked to the CHILD.PORTFOLIO Field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLEDGE.PCT</field>
<desc>
<p>Pledge percent that will be applied on MARGIN.VALUE field of SEC.ACC.MASTER. Can be specified only if child portfolio customer is different from master portfolio customer. Cannot be specified if PLEDGE.AMT is entered.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLEDGE.AMT</field>
<desc>
<p>Pledge amount in reference currency of child portfolio that will be considered if less than the MARGIN.VALUE field of SEC.ACC.MASTER. Can be specified only if child portfolio customer is different from master portfolio customer. Cannot be specified if PLEDGE.PCT is specified.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBAL.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
<p>To specify the global limit (i.e. In format 10000.xxx). Enquiry for limit utilization will pick the right limit reference by prefixing customer of portfolio based on the query run (group, individual portfolio, etc.)</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
<p>To denote whether valuation has to be performed. In case of valuation has to be stopped for master portfolio, STATUS field has to be set as INACTIVE. This field will be automatically updated if master portfolio is set as closure in SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.VALUATION</field>
<desc>
<p>Field to request for online valuation of master portfolio. Must be set as YES. Cannot be set as YES if STATUS field is INACTIVE.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHILD.VALUATION</field>
<desc>
<p>Multivalue field. Accepted values are ALL or list of portfolios for which child valuation has to be performed. If this field is null child valuation will not be performed.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.VALUATION.RUN</field>
<desc>
<p>Date and time of online valuation run on request of online valuation. No input field</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MASTER.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
<p>Multi value field and a Noinput field. This will store the master portfolio in which the current portfolio is pledged as either MASTER FIXED or MASTER VARIABLE.</p>  
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>SC.VAL.GRP.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>SEL.CCY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
