<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SCSF.CHARGE.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this table is to define the rules for deriving the base amount to be used when calculation charges and commissions. </p>
            <p>    Different rules may be required for different types of security and therefore these must be grouped into types for commission purposes. </p>
            <p>    For maximum flexibility the IDs to this file represent different levels of classification or type:- </p>
            <p>  Classification/Type   ID Format                 Example</p>
            <p>  "ALL"                                           ALL</p>
            <p>  ASSET.TYPE            A-{Asset Type Id}         A-20</p>
            <p>  SUB.ASSET.TYPE        S-{Sub Asset Id}          S-300</p>
            <p>  SECURITY NUMBER       {Security Master Id}      123456-000 </p>
            <p>  Local Reference       L-{Local Reference value} L-ABC</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Each record will then define a rule which is used to calculate the base amount for use in the calculation of commission for that security type. </p>
            <p>  NOTE: L- keys can only be used when FEE.GROUP is defined in SAFECUSTODY.VALUES for charge type SC.</p>
            <p>  All of these key formats can additionally have an associated depository appended to the key. For example</p>
            <p>  ALL.100317, applies the parameter to all securities held at depository 100317.</p>
            <p>  S-301.100313, applies the parameter to all securities with sub asset id 301 held at depository 100313.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PARAM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the trading charge parameter code. </p>
            <p>    The parameter codes is referred by the group condition file. this will either be a valid security code, an asset type prefixed with a "A-", a sub asset type prefixed with a "S-", a local reference value prefixed by "L-" or "ALL" for all other security types. </p>
            <p>    If a depository is specified then holdings in that depository will be take this set of parameters in preference to the standard records of the same level (i.e. security.no, sub asset type, asset type or ALL.)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Input is Mandatory </p>
            <p>    Upto 10 characters (alphanumeric) plus optionally the         separator '.' and a depository number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage applied to either "Nominal" or "Value". </p>
            <p>    A percentage of either the nominal value and/or the market value will be calculated for the base amount. </p>
            <p>    Each of these percentages is associated to the base code entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Input is Mandatory Must be numeric and positive.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVERAGE.CLOSING</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Mandatory input. </p>
            <p>    A maximum of 16 characters may be entered. </p>
            <p>    The following values are permitted: AVERAGE, CLOSING, MONTH.AVERAGE and PREV.MONTH.CLOSE</p>
            <p>    Note that PREV.MONTH.CLOSE may only be used where SAFECUSTODY.VALUES&gt;PERFORM.ACCRUAL for CHARGE.TYPE 'SC' is set to 'DAILY' accrual, in which case all records in this application must be set to the same value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the base to be used for calculating the basis amount. </p>
            <p>    When calculating the basis amount for trading charges if            "VALUE" is entered here then basis amount will be calculated based on the current market price and/or "NOMINAL" is entered a basis amount will be calculated based on the current Nominal Value. When NOMINAL.LCY is entered a basis amount will be calculated based on the current Nominal value converted into Local Currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Input is Mandatory Valid input is "VALUE" or "NOMINAL" or   "NOMINAL.LCY".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the description of the parameter code. </p>
            <p>    This field will be used for enrichment purposes by other screen inputs to identify the charge parameter code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Input is Mandatory upto 35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.LOWEST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the level of calculation. </p>
            <p>    If both base codes are entered (NOMINAL and VALUE) then the user must enter "HIGHEST" or "LOWEST". </p>
            <p>    When an amount has been calculated for each of the base codes then the safecustody fee amount will be calculated using one of these amounts based on the HIGHEST/LOWEST flag. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Input is optional unless more than the base code is         entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

