<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SCSK.GROUP.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This module defines the specific charge details for each customer group.</p>
            <p>ID format for the group condition can be "NNN.DDMMYYYY" ,"C-NNNNNN.DDMMYYYY" or "P-NNNNNN-N.DDMMYYYY" where NNNNNN is the customer ID and NNNNNN-N denotes the portfolio ID and DDMMYYYY represent date </p>
            <p>On authorization of the customer level record, the ID (C-NNNNNN) will update the ACTUAL.GROUP in CUSTOMER.CHARGE to be used as the default condition for the charge type.</p>
            <p>If a Portfolio level record exists, the ACTUAL.GROUP (for the portfolio) in CUSTOMER.CHARGE, for the charge type, will be updated with the portfolio record ID.</p>  
            <p>The following data will be recorded on this file:- </p>
            <p>  Calculation Method  "DETAIL" or "TOTAL" </p>
            <p>  Security Type                 Multi-valued which must exist                               on the Safekeeping charge                               parameters. </p>
            <p>  Detail Commission CodeValid FT.COMMISSION.TYPE codes. </p>
            <p>  Detail Percentage   Percentages applied to the charge calculated                     for each commission type. </p>
            <p>  Total Commission CodeValid FT.COMMISSION.TYPE code. </p>
            <p>  Total Percentage    Percentage applied to the total charge                     calculated using the Total Commission Code. </p>
            <p>  Global Code         Valid FT.Commission.Type Code. </p>
            <p>  When Safekeeping charges are processed, each security in the portfolio is processed in turn.  There are two possible ways of calculating the total commission for the portfolio. </p>
            <p>  The table below shows how the two methods work and the different results achieved: </p>
            <p>  PARAMETER FILE DEFINITION GROUP CONDITION FILE DEFINITIONS SEC.NO.SEC.TYPERULEBASE AMTCOMM/CHG CODECUST. PERC.CHG.AMT111111-111 </p>
            <p>  855555-555 </p>
            <p>  999999-999SHARES </p>
            <p>  BONDS </p>
            <p>  FUND 1 NOMINAL (100%) </p>
            <p>  VALUE (100%) </p>
            <p>  VALUE (100%) XXX </p>
            <p>  YYY </p>
            <p>  ZZZSCSK 0122 </p>
            <p>  SCSK 04321 </p>
            <p>  SCSK 11990290 </p>
            <p>  100 </p>
            <p>  50  NNN.NN </p>
            <p>  NNN.NN </p>
            <p>  NNN.NN TOTALSTOTAL 2TOTAL 1 Method 1 </p>
            <p>  This is to take the total "TOTAL 1" as the total charge amount for the portfolio.  In this way different commission codes can be used and the band and level processing be applied for each security. </p>
            <p>  Method 2 </p>
            <p>  This is to take the total "TOTAL 2" and then apply the TOT.COMMISSION.CODE and percentage to that total.  In this way only one FT.COMMISSION.TYPE is applied to the total base amount for the portfolio. </p>
            <p>  The use of either method 1 or 2 will be controlled at level of each charge condition record. </p>
            <p>  Therefore if the calculation Method is "DETAIL" then Method 1 is used and for "TOTAL" Method 2 is used. </p>
            <p>  Finally the total Commission the GLOBAL.CODE if required needs to be applied. </p>
            <p>  If say the total; charge was 129.5 and the global code takes 90% of the total charge then the final charge to be applied to the customer is 116.55 plus the depository charges. </p>
            <p>  Depository Charges </p>
            <p>  The depository charge is calculated in exactly the same way as the customer charge, i.e. the depository has a customer and a CUSTOMER.CHARGE record.  The group number to be used when calculating the depository commission on Safekeeping charges is held on the DEPOSITORY.GROUP field on the CUSTOMER.CHARGE record of the depository concerned. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.NO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to the SCSK.GROUP.CONDITION file. It consists of two parts. The first part is the fee scale and the second the effective date that the fee scale is to be applied from. </p>
            <p>  The fees scale is either a single customer fee scale, where the scale will be of the form C-########## where ########## is the customer number or a fee scale that will be validated against the SCSK.GEN.CONDITION file. If the fee scale is on the SCSK.GEN.CONDITION file it can be applied to many customers. </p>
            <p>  The second part of the key is the date the scale is applied from. When deciding which scale to use T24 uses the SCSK.GROUP.CONDITION applicable at the start of the date range when the Safecustody fees are to be calculated from. </p>
            <p>  The two parts are separated by a '.'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  The date will default to the current system date.</p>
            <p>  The date cannot be in the past is the user is copying SCSK.GROUP.CONDITION records.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Commission type to calculate the Safekeeping charges. </p>
            <p>  This field relates to a record on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE table which will be used to calculate the Safekeeping amount based on the total of the base amounts for each portfolio. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  To be entered only if the calculation method is "TOTAL". Upto 11 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the minimum safekeeping charge amount in the associated MIN.MAX.CCY.</p>
            <p>  When the Safekeeping charges are calculated, less any discount amount, a minimum and maximum value can be specified. This value can be specified in any currency. </p>
            <p>  The system will first attempt to determine if the min/max is specified in the currency of the account that the charge (field ACCOUNT.CCY in the file SAFEKEEP.HOLDING) will be posted to, if not found the value defined for the DEF.MIN.MAX.CCY will be used and converted at mid rate to the account currency.</p>
            <p>  For non DAILY accruals this value represents the minimum amount to be charged to the customer for the charge period. For DAILY accruals this value represents the minimum annual charge and so will be adjusted in relation to the charge period length, for example $1000 will be adjusted to $250 for a quarterly charge period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Input</p>
            <p>  Input only allowed with associated MIN.MAX.CCY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field allowing the user to specify the end of the fee charging period for the period type defined in the associated CALC.TYPE field. This is done using the characters -,+,L,C and O together with numeric input where; O represents the date of the portfolio opening. L represents the date of the Last Fees Run. C represents todays system date. </p>
            <p>  Thus C-1 is the calendar date before today.      O+1 is the calendar date after the opening date of the          portfolio. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of a number or the characters -,+,L,C or O allowed.</p>
            <p>  If the SAFECUSTODY.VALUES field COMPANY.CALC is set to 'Y' this field is a no input field that will default from SAFECUSTODY.VALUES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the level for calculating the basis amount. </p>
            <p>  This field will be used to decide on the Commission type to calculate the safekeeping charges based on the holdings of the portfolio. </p>
            <p>  Where a variety of levels of parameter are set, the system will select a charge parameter in the following order of priority:</p>
            <p>  Priority   Classification                 ID format             Example</p>
            <p>  1          Security Number '.' Depository nnnnnn-nnn.depository 123456-000.100001</p>
            <p>  2          Security Number                nnnnnn-nnn            123456-000</p>
            <p>  3          SUB.ASSET.TYPE '.' Depository  S-nnnn.depository     S-300.100001</p>
            <p>  4          SUB.ASSET.TYPE                 S-nnnn                S-300</p>
            <p>  5          ASSET.TYPE '.' Depository      A-nnn.depository      A-10.100001</p>
            <p>  6          ASSET.TYPE                     A-nnn                 A-10</p>
            <p>  7          Default '.' Depository         ALL.depository        ALL.100001</p>
            <p>  8          Default                        ALL                   ALL</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1. Security Number : 6N-3N or 2. Sub-Asset type prefixed with "S-". or 3. Asset Type prefixed with "A-". or 4. "ALL" - all others. Any of these four levels can be suffixed with a depository id after the separator '.'</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input is Mandatory</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must exist as an SCSF.CHARGE.PARAMETER record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIV.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field allowing the user to specify the end date printed on any delivery produced by fees charged for the period type defined in the associated CALC.TYPE field. </p>
            <p>  This is done using the characters -,+,L,C and O together with numeric input where; O represents the date of the portfolio opening. L represents the date of the Last Fees Run. C represents todays system date. </p>
            <p>  Thus C-1 is the calendar date before today.      O+1 is the calendar date after the opening date of the          portfolio. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of a number or the characters -,+,L,C or O allowed.</p>
            <p>  If the SAFECUSTODY.VALUES field COMPANY.CALC is set to 'Y' this field is a no input field that will default from SAFECUSTODY.VALUES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum safekeeping charge amount in the associated MIN.MAX.CCY.</p>
            <p>  When the Safekeeping charges are calculated, less any discount amount, a minimum and maximum value can be specified. This value can be specified in any currency. </p>
            <p>  The system will first attempt to determine if the min/max is specified in the currency of the account that the charge (field ACCOUNT.CCY in the file SAFEKEEP.HOLDING) will be posted to, if not found the value defined for the DEF.MIN.MAX.CCY will be used and converted at mid rate to the account currency.</p>
            <p>  For non DAILY accruals this value represents the maximum amount to be charged to the customer for the charge period. For DAILY accruals this value represents the maximum annual charge and so will be adjusted in relation to the charge period length, for example $1000 will be adjusted to $250 for a quarterly charge period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Input</p>
            <p>  Input only allowed with associated MIN.MAX.CCY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the the Charge Code or Group to determine the TAX code to be used for Safekeeping Charges. </p>
            <p>  This field will be used to calculate the Tax Amount for resultant Safekeeping charge. </p>
            <p>  Optional Input. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.MONTHS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field allowing the user to specify the number of months in the period for the period type defined in the associated CALC.TYPE field. This is done using the characters -,+,L,C and O together with numeric input where; O represents the date of the portfolio opening. L represents the date of the Last Fees Run. C represents todays system date. </p>
            <p>  Thus C-1 is the calendar date before today.      O+1 is the calendar date after the opening date of the          portfolio. </p>
            <p>  e.g. for PERIODIC.NORMAL this field will typically contain C-L. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of a number or the characters -,+,L,C or O allowed.</p>
            <p>  If the SAFECUSTODY.VALUES field COMPANY.CALC is set to 'Y' this field is a no input field that will default from SAFECUSTODY.VALUES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIV.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field allowing the user to specify the start date printed on any delivery produced by fees charged for the period type defined in the associated CALC.TYPE field. </p>
            <p>  This is done using the characters -,+,L,C and O together with numeric input where; O represents the date of the portfolio opening. L represents the date of the Last Fees Run. C represents todays system date. </p>
            <p>  Thus C-1 is the calendar date before today.      O+1 is the calendar date after the opening date of the          portfolio. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of a number or the characters -,+,L,C or O allowed.</p>
            <p>  If the SAFECUSTODY.VALUES field COMPANY.CALC is set to 'Y' this field is a no input field that will default from SAFECUSTODY.VALUES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECOND.FEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Commission Type used to perform a secondary calculation on the result of the primary safekeeping fee calculation. This 'fee-on-fee' method is only supported for daily accrual, i.e. where SAFECUSTODY.VALUES&gt;PERFORM.ACCRUAL for CHARGE.TYPE 'SC' is set to 'DAILY', and where SCSF.CHARGE.PARAMETER&gt;AVERAGE.CLOSING is set to 'PREV.MONTH.CLOSE' for all records.</p>
            <p> This field is ignored during the calculation of Depository Fees.</p>
            <p>    Validation rules</p>
            <p>     If used, must be entered in conjunction with a SECOND.FEE.PERC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCSK.GROUP.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the group of customers. </p>
            <p>  If the input is numeric it must be previously defined on the Safekeeping General Condition record and enriched with its description. </p>
            <p>  If the input is for a specific customer then this is enriched with the short name of the customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input is Mandatory Three numeric characters formatted with leading zeros or a valid customer number prefixed with "C-".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECOND.FEE.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the percentage to be applied when performing a secondary calculation on the result of the primary safekeeping fee calculation. This 'fee-on-fee' method is only supported for daily accrual, i.e. where SAFECUSTODY.VALUES&gt;PERFORM.ACCRUAL for CHARGE.TYPE 'SC' is set to 'DAILY', and where SCSF.CHARGE.PARAMETER&gt;AVERAGE.CLOSING is set to 'PREV.MONTH.CLOSE' for all records.</p>
            <p> This field is ignored during the calculation of Depository Fees.</p>
            <p>    Validation rules</p>
            <p>     If used, must be entered in conjunction with a SECOND.FEE.CODE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DET.PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines a percentage to be applied to the charge positive amount calculated. </p>
            <p>  When the basis amount is calculated then this percentage together with the charge rate is used to calculate the final Customer charges. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input must be numeric and not more than 100%.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DET.COMM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Commission type used to calculate the charge amount relating to the security type. </p>
            <p>  The Commission Code is predefined on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE table which will be used to calculate the charge amount for safekeeping. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input is Mandatory of upto 11 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.MAX.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency in which the associated minimum and maximum amount fields are defined.</p>
            <p>  When the Safekeeping charges are calculated, less any discount amount, a minimum and maximum value can be specified. This value can be specified in any currency. </p>
            <p>  The system will first attempt to determine if the min/max is specified in the currency of the account that the charge (field ACCOUNT.CCY in the file SAFEKEEP.HOLDING) will be posted to, if not found the value defined for the DEF.MIN.MAX.CCY will be used and converted at mid rate to the account currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Input</p>
            <p>  Must be a valid CURRENCY code</p>
            <p>  No duplicates allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBAL.REDUCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Commission type to calculate the final charge. </p>
            <p>  Relates to a record on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE which is used to calculate the final charge based on the total of all individual charges for the portfolio. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input is optional Must be a valid FT.COMMISSION.TYPE if entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBAL.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>FT.COMMISSION.TYPE to be applied to the final total of calculated charge if a 'Foreign Fees' type charge is to be applied to the Safecustody Fees charged to the portfolio. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input.</p>
            <p>  Must exist on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field allowing the user to specify the start of the fee charging period for the period type defined in the associated CALC.TYPE field. This is done using the characters -,+,L,C and O together with numeric input where; O represents the date of the portfolio opening. L represents the date of the Last Fees Run. C represents todays system date. </p>
            <p>  Thus C-1 is the calendar date before today.      O+1 is the calendar date after the opening date of the          portfolio. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Only input of a number or the characters -,+,L,C or O allowed.</p>
            <p>  If the SAFECUSTODY.VALUES field COMPANY.CALC is set to 'Y' this field is a no input field that will default from SAFECUSTODY.VALUES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage to be applied to the charge calculated. </p>
            <p>  Defines a percentage to be applied to the total charge calculated using the commission type from the previous field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Optional input unless the calculation method is "TOTAL" Must be numeric</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.DEP.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>  The following values are permitted:       NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the method for calculating the basis amount to calculate Safekeeping charges. </p>
            <p>  This field will be used to determine the method for calculating the Safekeeping charges: </p>
            <p>  i.e.  If "TOTAL" then a total base amount for the portfolio's holdings will be used to calculate the charge.  If "DETAIL" then for each "SEC.TYPE", individual charges will be calculated for each portfolio, based on the base amount for each security and then accumulated to determine the total charge. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input is Mandatory Enter "TOTAL" or "DETAIL"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with all the field down to DELIV.END to form a group of fields that indicate the dates to be used in calculating the portfolio advisory charges for portfolios connected with this charging group. </p>
            <p>  This field along with its associated multi-valued fields allow the user to specify the different date ranges for the four different types of date range that can occur when calculating Safecustody Fees. </p>
            <p>  These four ranges are; PERIODIC.OPEN   Used when the Charges run is an automatic                 charging run controlled by the SAFECUSTODY.FREQ field                 on the SEC.ACC.MASTER record for the portfolio and                 this is the first automatic run for the portfolio. PERIODIC.NORMAL Used when the charges run is an automatic charging                 controlled by the SAFECUSTODY.FREQ field on the                 SEC.ACC.MASTER record for the portfolio and the                 portfolio has previously had Safecustody Fees                 calculated for it. CLOSURE.NORMAL  Used when the fees are being calculated because                 a portfolio is being closed and the portfolio has                 previously had Safecustody Fees calculated on it. CLOSURE.OPEN    Used when the fees are being calculated because                 a portfolio is being closed and the portfolio has                 never had Safecustody Fees calculated on it. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input must be PERIODIC.NORMAL, PERIODIC.OPEN, CLOSURE.NORMAL or CLOSURE.OPEN.</p>
            <p>  Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>  If the SAFECUSTODY.VALUES field COMPANY.CALC is set to 'Y' this field is a no input field that will default from SAFECUSTODY.VALUES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.MIN.MAX.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency code that will contain the default minimum / maximum values for safekeeping charges.</p>
            <p>  If the system cannot find a definition in the currency in which the charges are calculated, the definitions for this currency will be taken and will be converted at mid-rate to the charge account currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory if  MIN.MAX.CCY is specified</p>
            <p>  Value must be defined in MIN.MAX.CCY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

