<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SCTR.CHARGE.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                 SCTR.CHARGE.PARAMETER </p>
            <p>SECURITIES TRADING CHARGE PARAMETERS </p>
            <p>The purpose of this table is to define the rules for deriving the base amount to be used when calculation charges and commissions. </p>
            <p>Different rules may be required for different types of security and therefore these must be grouped into types for commission purposes. </p>
            <p>For maximum flexibility the IDs to this file represent different levels of classification or type:- </p>
            <p>Classification/Type           ID Format            Example DEFAULT                                                     "ALL"ALL ASSET.TYPE                                         A-N to A-NNNA-20 SUB.ASSET.TYPE                          S-N to S-NNNNS-300 SECURITY NUMBER                       NNNNNN-NNN123456- 000 </p>
            <p>Each record will then define a rule which is used to calculate the base amount for use in the calculation of commission for that security type. </p>
            <p>The user is required to enter a base code which defines a method of calculation along with a percentage which is to be applied to the value calculated for the specific base code.  Valid base codes are:-                               NOMINAL   The nominal quantity/value of shares                        held.              VALUE     The market value of shares held. </p>
            <p>The "HIGHEST.LOWEST" field will determine which of the base code values will be taken. </p>
            <p>i.e. if the "HIGHEST" is entered then all the defined combinations of values and percentages will be taken and the highest resultant value will then be used for commission calculations. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>ID     Type                        All       Default </p>
            <p>2.1    BASE.CODE      NOMINAL             Nominal value of shares 3.1    PERCENTAGE      75 2.2    BASE.CODE      VALUE                   Market value of shares 3.2    PERCENTAGE        90 4      HIGHEST.LOWEST    LOWEST </p>
            <p>In this example 75 percent of the average nominal and 90 percent of the average market value are calculated and the "lower" of these values (base amount) will be used to calculate the commissions. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PARAM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the trading charge parameter code. </p>
            <p>The parameter codes is referred by the group condition file.  this will either be a valid security code, an asset type prefixed with a "A-", a sub asset type prefixed with a "S-" or "ALL" for all other security types. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input is Mandatory Upto 10 characters (alphanumeric)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future expansion.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage applied to either "Nominal" or "Value". </p>
            <p>A percentage of either the nominal value and/or the market value will be calculated for the base amount. </p>
            <p>Each of these percentages is associated to the base code entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input is Mandatory Must be numeric and positive.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the base to be used for calculating the basis amount. </p>
            <p>When calculating the basis amount for trading              charges if "VALUE" is entered here then basis              amount will be calculated based on the current              market price and/or "NOMINAL" is entered a basis              amount will be calculated based on the current              Nominal Value. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input is Mandatory Valid input is "VALUE" or "NOMINAL"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the description of the parameter code. </p>
            <p>This field will be used for enrichment purposes by other screen inputs to identify the charge parameter code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input is Mandatory upto 35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.LOWEST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the level of calculation. </p>
            <p>If both base codes are entered (NOMINAL and VALUE) then the user must enter "HIGHEST" or "LOWEST". </p>
            <p>When an amount has been calculated for each of the base codes then the management fee amount will be calculated using one of these amounts based on the HIGHEST/LOWEST flag. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input is optional unless more than the base code is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field not in use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

