<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SEC.DEL.CONTROL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Security delivery control is an automated delivery control application within the securities module. </p>
            <p>It receives data regarding how much stock is to be received or delivered from broker A or B and whether that is against payment or free of any payment and the effective value date of the particular transaction. </p>
            <p>Having copied across all the relevant details necessary for the user to identify the individual transaction and the relevant broker details; it allows the user to perform stock delivery entries against that particular transaction; along with an effective date and any consideration which may have been paid or received; again with an effective date. </p>
            <p>A user reference number can be attached to each of these part delivery/payments and the record remains in an unauthorised state until the totals agree i.e. amount to be received = amount received and amount to be paid = amount paid. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security involved in the transaction i.e. the security to be settled. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input. Internally generated field. Copied from the Transaction which has created the particular SEC. DEL. CONTROL Record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Broker involved in the transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field and copied over from the transaction details</p>
            <p>To have been allowed at Transaction level it must have been a valid Broker no. in existence as a Broker type Customer on the Customer Security File.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.NO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of shares involved in the Transaction awaiting settlement </p>
            <p>Where Multi Client transactions have been input the SYSTEM will amalgamate the totals per broker to be received or delivered.  At this level we are not concerned with the Customer break down, merely the Net amount of stock to be settled. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input. Internally generated field. Copied over from the Broker details input at Transaction Level.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security Transaction involved in the open delivery area. </p>
            <p>May have been a Purchase Sale of Securities or a Transfer in of securities or it may have been created by a Capital Increase type of transaction. </p>
            <p>Examples:  Each Reference will have a transaction            type prefix which will identify the            individual applicable concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Copied over from the transaction concerned.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies which Depository holds the securities or is to hold the Security concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Copied across from the transaction concerned.</p>
            <p>To have been accepted at transaction level it must have been a valid Depositary Account</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.RECD.DEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the nominal number of the securities to be received/delivered. </p>
            <p>Multivalue field to cater for part deliveries and part payment of transactions. </p>
            <p>Occasionally owing to market conditions it will not be possible for a counterparty to deliver all of an outstanding Stock position.  It is Standard practice sometimes in the UK.  For example for a Broker upon confirmation from his Client to delivery part of the Stock against a Nominal Consideration. </p>
            <p>The Delivery Control Record will not be removed until the nominals and amounts to be delivered and paid agree. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 characters, standard amount format. Optional input. (Multi value field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.SETTLEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A value of Y Indicates that automatic settlement of delivery will take place during the batch relating to the value date of the contract. </p>
            <p>This can only relate to SEC.TRADE deals subject to counterparty limit checking with delivery instructions indicating automatic settlement. </p>
            <p>The record will be updated as if complete delivery has taken place, limits will be backed out and the contract will be authorised. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the currency that the trade is to be settled in </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Copied over from Transaction details.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date delivery has taken place. A multi-value to cater for partial deliveries and receipts. Associated with fields NO.NOM.RECEIVED.DEL and  NO.NOM.REF.NO </p>
            <p>Although not a mandatory field, it should be used to record the date on which actual delivery/receipt has been effected. Historical data is retained for the SEC.DEL.CONTROL file and therefore completing this information can provide you with such information as late deliveries when this file is interrogated  using a suitable enquiry.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format. Optional input. (Multi value field.) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value date of the trade i.e. date at which the transaction should have settled. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Copied over from the transaction details.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WITH.PAYMENT.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines if the transaction has a payment of funds involved.  i.e. is it a Receive Stock against payment type transaction or a Deliver Free of Payment type transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Copied over from the transaction details Delivery instructions where the payment Flag is linked to the Delivery instructions. Examples:  Suggested delivery type codes and normal payment type indicators. TRIP = Transfer In against Payment TRIO = Transfer Out against Payment</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the type of Transaction which has created this control record. </p>
            <p>A Security Transfer may well be identified system wide as e.g. SECTFR with the Julian date and an automatically generated ID No.  However the Transaction Type will identify the type of Security Transfer involved. EG. Transfer IN/OUT AGAINST/FREE PAYMENT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input. Internally generated field. Copied over from the transaction details.</p>
            <p>Must have existed on the Transaction Type File to have been used in the Transaction details.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies uniquely each Security Delivery Control and is made up of the Security Number, Depository concerned, transaction ID. and the Broker reference number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The detail key is made up of the following format:- NNNNNN-NNN - 6 numeric character Security Master number. NNNNNN - 1-6 numeric character Customer Security number SECTSCYYDDD - 5 numeric digit Security Transfer NNNNN - number, prefixed by (SECTSC) YY (Year) DDD Julian Day. NNNNNN - 1-6 Customer Security number. (type Broker) Examples:  Where customer A has bought Securities through Broker B against payment of Nominal Consideration. The Sec. Deb. Control will specify the amount of stock expected and the Consideration to be paid away.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINAL.OUTST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the current nominal outstanding amount ie. The TOTAL.NO.NOMINAL amount minus the     NO.NOM.RECD.DEL amount. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CPTY.LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The limit reference of the associated SEC.TRADE contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.AMOUNT.DUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total Monies to be settled against an individual broker for Stock Received or Delivered i.e. Broker Net Amount awaiting Settlement. </p>
            <p>Again at this application we are not concerned with Customer details.  Merely with the amount of money outstanding with any particular Broker. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input. Internally generated field. Copied over from Broker details at Transaction level.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the date of the trade. Deal Date. Tax Point. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input. Internally generated field. Copied over from the transaction record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTERPARTY.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A value of  Y indicates that counterparty (broker) limit checking is to take place. </p>
            <p>If limit checking is to take place then even for deals which are free of payment the TOTAL.AMOUNT.DUE and TOTAL.AMOUNT.OUSTANDING (which indicates the limit exposure)  will be updated. </p>
            <p>When delivery takes place and  the amounts received fields are updated then these values will be used to update the counterparty limit, i.e. the amount will be backed out of the current counterparty limit. </p>
            <p>Partial deliveriees can be catered for in this way. </p>
            <p>Until the amount oustanding is reduced to zero the limit will remain. </p>
            <p>If the delivery is set for automatic settlement then during the batch relating to the value date of the SEC.TRADE deal then delivery will be automatically settlled and the amount oustanding backed out of limits. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Each separate delivery receipt of Stock will be assigned a separate Ref. No. </p>
            <p>Multi value to allow for part deliveries and part payment. </p>
            <p>It is envisaged that the User will enter a unique Ref. No. at this point to identify the past delivery (suggested Ref. Number could be the Brokers own reference, for easy reconciliation </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multi Value Associated Fields linked to FIELDS 14 NOMINAL RECEIVED/DELIVERED AND 15 EFFECTIVE DATE OF RECEIPT OR DELIVERY 8 CHARACTER UPPERCASE ALPHA REF. NO. Optional input. (Multi value field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with Multi value at Field 17 and defines the date at which the payment signified at Field 17 was made. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format. Optional input. (Multi value field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.OUTST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the current amount outstanding ie. The TOTAL.AMOUNT.DUE minus the     AMT.RECD.PAID. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with Fields 17 and 18 this allows the User to enter an unique reference number relating to the payment made.  User defined. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 Character Upper case Alpha Ref. Number. Optional input. (Multi value field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.RECD.PAID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount to be received or paid for the security transaction involved. </p>
            <p>Multi value to allow for part payment in or out. Associated with fields 18 and 19. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 characters standard amount format. Optional input (Multi value field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the type of price i.e. Bond share etc. which has been used in the calculation of Gross and Net Amounts in the Transaction awaiting settlement. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Copied over from the Transaction (STATIC) details.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency of the security being delivered or received, which defaults to the Static Information Files maintained on each security SECURITY MASTER. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPIRY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not used at present.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

