<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SEC.POS.BASE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SUB.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sub-account that the security position is held in.</p>
            <p>This sub account is defined in CUSTOMER.SECURITY record for this depository.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a SECURITY.POSITION has a block associated with it to prevent it from trading then the total amount blocked is stored in the NOM.AMT.BLOCKED field.</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi-value set and represents the Transaction Reference number of the application which created the block.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>"NOINPUT" field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total weighted cost of the security position in the security currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field, System generated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>URLZ.CCY.GN.CR.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input redundant field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Security Number the Security Position is for.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPENING.BAL.NO.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Opening Balance - in number of securities - for this Security Position. This field will always be zero unless it has been updated by the takeover processing when T24 was first installed on the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.BLOCK.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>No Input field showing the amount that the existing block will be effected by when the next change in blocking value will occur.</p>
            <p>This field is associated with BLOCK.EFF.FROM , to display future Blocks or Unblocks that will apply to the SECURITY.POSITION being referenced.</p>
            <p>If a NEW.BLOCK.AMT is positive then the block will be increased by this amount.</p>
            <p>If a NEW.BLOCK.AMT is negative then the block will be reduced by this amount.</p>
            <p>This field is updated when an SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS record is authorised &amp; it has an EFF.FROM.DATE later than the system date or an EFF.TO.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RP.BROKER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the Broker number from whom the position raised from REPO is unsettled. The fields RP.BROKER.NO and RP.UNSETT.NOM is a associated multi value set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input. System Generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>URLZ.MRK.GN.CR.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input redundant field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>URLZ.MRK.GN.ST.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input redundant field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELD.SINCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the date the security in this position has been held since.</p>
            <p>This field will be first updated by the system with the Trade Date of the transaction that created this Security Position record. However if the Security Position goes to zero - i.e. the CLOSING.BAL.NO.NOM field becomes 0 - then this field will be set to null. It will then be updated with the trade date of the transaction that updates the CLOSING.BAL.NO.NOM with a non zero position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.DAT.BKCOST.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total gross weighted cost of the value dated security position in the reference currency of the portfolio.</p>
            <p>The gross weighted cost is calculated ignoring the impact of commissions, charges and taxes etc</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.COB.TXNS</field>
<desc>
            <p>List of COB transactions entering during the current COB, non-stop processing only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.INVST.REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The year to date cost of the Trade Dated Security Position in the Reference Currency of the portfolio identified in the SECURITY.ACCOUNT field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COST.INVST.BSE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the cost of the security position identified in the CLOSING.BAL.NO.NOM field in the local currency os the T24 system</p>
            <p>Note; Any exchange rates used will be as of the individual transaction that have built this security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DAT.COST.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>No Input field showing the value dated cost of the position in the reference currency of the portfolio identified in the SECURITY.ACCOUNT field.</p>
            <p>The field contents are updated automatically during the System EOD phase but may be updated on-line by running an on-line valuation on behalf of the underlying SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system during         Batch Processing or by running an on-line valuation on         behalf of the underlying SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.DAT.BKCOST.BSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total gross weighted cost of the value dated security position in local currency</p>
            <p>The gross weighted cost is calculated ignoring the impact of commissions, charges and taxes etc</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key of the SECURITY.POSITION file is made up of seven elements separated by dots. These elements are; Portfolio Number Security Number Depository Nominee Code Maturity Date Interest Rate and Sub-Account.</p>
            <p>Note ; The Maturity Date and Interest Rate are only included in the key of the Security Position if the Security the position is for is flagged as a KassenObligationen on the Sub Asset Type record the Security is linked to.</p>
            <p>These fields make up the first seven fields of the SECURITY.POSITION record.</p>
            <p>The Portfolio Number is the portfolio whose position this is if this is a portfolio position or it is the Depository Number with a suffix of '-999' if it is a depository position. The Security Number is the Security Master ID of the Security. The Depository is the Depository where the position is held. The Nominee Code is blank if this position is not held by nominee and contains the ID from the NOMINEE.CODE file if this position is held by Nominee. The Sub Account is the depository sub account where the position is held.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNSETTLED.NOM.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The nominal of securities relating to this security position that remains unreceived.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RP.UNSETT.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the undelivered nominal due from the Broker raised from REPO transaction. The fields RP.BROKER.NO and RP.UNSETT.NOM is a associated multi value set. The value in this field will be reduced to the extent the position is settled for that broker.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input. System Generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNSETT.NOM.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-value list of Brokers with corresponding unsettled credit nominal amounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only updated is this security position is for a Kassenobligationen security. A Kassenobligationen security is one where the Sub Asset Type record linked to the security has the KASSENOBLIGATIONEN flag set to YES.</p>
            <p>If the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER field is a Kassenobligationen security then this will be the maturity date for the security - taken from the MATURITY.DATE field on the Security Master record - at the time the SECURITY.POSITION record was created.</p>
            <p>The Maturity Date (if any) in this field will make-up the fifth (of six) elements tat make-up the ID of the SECURITY.POSITION record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST.REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total weighted cost of the security position in the reference currency of the underlying portfolio.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RLZ.CURR.GN.ST.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input redundant field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BE.SOURCE.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains any local stock exchange fees charged on transactions that have updated this security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of nominal that has been lent from this position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.LAST.TRADED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Trade Date of the last transaction to update this Security Position Record.</p>
            <p>Note; this field will contain the latest date for a trade date that updated this SECURITY.POSITION record. Thus if the record has been updated by two transactions; One with a trade date of 30th May 1996 and the other 5th June 1996 then this field will contain 05/06/1996 even if the transaction with this trade date had been entered into the system before the transaction with the trade date of 30/05/1996.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOM.AMT.BLOCKED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Part - or all - of a security position can be blocked (and unblocked) using the application SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS. This field will show the number of securities in the security position currently blocked.</p>
            <p>If part - or all - of the security position is blocked then this portion of the position will not be included when calculating orders. Also the system will prevent the user form selling the blocked position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.INVST.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Year to date cost of the Trade Dated Security Position in the Security Currency of the Security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DT.SHORT.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value dated short position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COST.INVST.REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the cost of the security position identified in the CLOSING.BAL.NO.NOM field in the reference currency of the portfolio identified in the SECURITY.ACCOUNT field of this record.</p>
            <p>Note; Any exchange rates used will be as of the individual transaction that have built this security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATED.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the value dated cost of the position identified in the VALUE.DATE.POSN field in the security currency of the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER field.</p>
            <p>It is updated in the EOD each day but can be updated on-line by running a portfolio valuation for the underlying SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system during         Batch processing by the Batch Job EOD.VAL.UPDATE1 or by         running an on-line valuation on behalf of the underlying         SEC.ACC.MASTER record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GR.BK.COST.BSE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total gross weighted cost of the security position in local currency</p>
            <p>The gross weighted cost is calculated ignoring the impact of commissions, charges and taxes etc</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.SETT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the last settlement occured for this position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.COB.TXNS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date of COB transactions entering during the current COB, non-stop processing only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNSETTLED.RP.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The nominal of securities relating to this security position raised from REPO that remains undelivered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.COST.BSE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the gross cost of the security position - i.e. the cost before charges, commissions, taxes etc. have been applied - in the local currency of the system.</p>
            <p>Note; Any exchange rates used will be as of the individual transaction that have built this security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCOME.CURR.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Income in the form of coupons and dividends generated by the Security Positon.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GR.BK.COST.REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total gross weighted cost of the security position in the reference currency of the portfolio.</p>
            <p>The gross weighted cost is calculated ignoring the impact of commissions, charges and taxes etc</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.NOM.PEND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds a sum value of the unsettled nominal amount. During a free transfer (SECURITY.TRANSFER), the nominal being traded is not settled and is not part of the customer portfolio valuation. It is therefore stored on this field, and every time an amount is settled, the value on this field is reduced by the settled amount until all the nominal is settled.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSING.BAL.NO.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the trade dated security position.</p>
            <p>This field contains the trade dated number of securities held by the Security Position. This field is updated online at the validation of transactions. This is the field used to update the NO.NOMINAL field on SC.POS.ASSET file and hence is the number of securities held by the position so far as the T24 Portfolio Management System is concerned.</p>
            <p>The value dated position is contained in the VALUE.DATED.POSN field and is updated overnight during the Batch processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST.BSE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total weighted cost of the security position in the local currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNSETTLED.RP.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The nominal of securities relating to this security position raised from REPO that remains unreceived.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODD.LOT.UNCONSOLID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is updated with the nominal of the unconsolidated odd lots nominal.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DT.OPEN.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Trade date opening balance.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOM.AVAIL.SELL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Nominal available for sale.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.EFF.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>No Input field showing the dates when the next change in blocking value will occur.</p>
            <p>This field is associated with NEW.BLOCK.AMT , to display future Blocks or Unblocks that will apply to the SECURITY.POSITION being referenced.</p>
            <p>This field is updated when an SC.BLOCK.SEC.POS record is authorised &amp; it has an EFF.FROM.DATE later than the system date or an EFF.TO.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only updated is this security position is for a Kassenobligationen security. A Kassenobligationen security is one where the Sub Asset Type record linked to the security has the KASSENOBLIGATIONEN flag set to YES.</p>
            <p>If the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER is a Kassenobligationen security then this will be the interest rate for the security - taken from the INTEREST.RATE field on the Security Master record - at the time the SECURITY.POSITION record was created.</p>
            <p>The Interest Rate (if any) in this field will make-up the sixth (of six) elements that make up the ID of the SECURITY.POSITION file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Either the portfolio the Security Position is for or the depot the security position is for. Format is 6N - 3N Where 6N is the customer number and 3N the suffix. If the suffix is 999 then the security position is for the depository whose ID is the 6N prefix of this field, if the suffix is 777 then then security position is for the boker whose ID is the 6N prefix, otherwise (suffix is not 999 or 777) then this is the ID of the portfolio the security position is for.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field, Internally generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RLZ.MRK.GN.CUR.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Redundant no input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.COST.INVST.SEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Redundant field no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field no longer used by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATED.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the value dated security position.</p>
            <p>The field contains the value dated number of securities held by the Security Position. This field is normally only updated during Batch processing and is not updated online unless a portfolio valuation is requested for the underlying portfolio (SEC.ACC.MASTER).</p>
            <p>This field is used to update the V.DATE.NOMINAL field on the SC.POS.ASSET file and hence is used as the number of securities held as at the value date by the T24 Portfolio Management System.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system during         Batch processing by the Batch Job EOD.VAL.UPDATE1 oy by         performing an on-line revaluation for the unerlying SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.DAT.BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total gross weighted cost of the value dated security position in the security currency</p>
            <p>The gross weighted cost is calculated ignoring the impact of commissions, charges and taxes etc</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DAT.COST.BSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>No Input field showing the value dated cost of the position in the base currency of the system.</p>
            <p>This field is updated during the System EOD phase or on-line only if a portfolio valuation is requested for the underlying SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field - automatically updated during the EOD or         on-line of a portfolio valuation requested for the         underlying SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXERCISE.PRC</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a SECURITY.POSITION has a block associated with it to prevent it from trading then the total amount blocked is stored in the NOM.AMT.BLOCKED field.</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi-value set and represents the Excercise Price which is created by the Futures &amp; Options Product.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>"NOINPUT" field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of nominal that has been borrowed for this position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.OPEN.ORD.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of securities related to this Security Position record that are the subject of open SEC.OPEN.ORDER records. If a SEC.OPEN.ORDER is created then this field will be updated with the number of securities on the order that relate to this security position. When the SEC.OPEN.ORDER is executed then the number of securities concerned are removed from this figure. This figure is used when calculating subsequent orders from ORDER.BY.CUST or the Portfolio Modelling suite of programs to prevent duplicate orders being created. This field is always updated by orders that debit the position. Setting the UPD.OUTST.ORD.CRED field on SC.STD.SEC.TRADE to YES will result in this field being updated by orders tht credit the position also.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.COST.REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the gross cost of the security position - i.e. the cost before charges, commissions, taxes etc. have been applied - in the reference currency of the portfolio identified in the SECURITY.ACCOUNT field of the record.</p>
            <p>Note; Any exchange rates used will be as of the individual transaction that have built this security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-value list of Brokers with corresponding unsettled credit nominal amounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RLZ.CCY.GN.CUR.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is no longer used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input redundant field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.BOND.LENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Part - or all - of a Security Position can be lent using the application BOND.LENT.MASTER. This field will show the number of securities in the security position currently lent.</p>
            <p>If part - or all - of the security position is lent then this portion of the position will not be included when calculating orders. ALso the system will prevent the user form selling the lent bond position.</p>
            <p>Only updated for bonds.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DT.LONG.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value dated long position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DT.OPEN.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value dated opening balance.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.INCOME.CR.PER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>.</p>
            <p>No input field no longer used by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.INCOME.ST.PER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field no longer used by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUST.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>New field containing the total adjustment nominal for this security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.BLOCKED</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a SECURITY.POSITION has a block associated with it to prevent it from trading then the total amount blocked is stored in the NOM.AMT.BLOCKED field.</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi-value set and represents the amount of nominal which currently has a Block on the position. The total of all the mult-values will equate to the total amount blocked.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>"NOINPUT" field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RLZ.MRK.GN.ST.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input redundant field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNSETTLED.NOM.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The nominal of securities relating to this security position that remains undelivered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the capitalised interest amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GR.BK.COST.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total gross weighted cost of the security position in the security currency.</p>
            <p>The gross weighted cost is calculated ignoring the impact of commissions, charges and taxes etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input, System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this security position is held by Nominee then this field will contain the ID of the Nominee. If this position is not held by nominee then this field will be blank.</p>
            <p>If the position is held by nominee then this field will contain the ID of the NOMINEE.CODE record set-up for the nominee.</p>
            <p>The Nominee Code (if any) will also make up the fourth (of six) elements that make-up the ID of the SECURITY.POSITION file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a SECURITY.POSITION has a block associated with it to prevent it from trading then the total amount blocked is stored in the NOM.AMT.BLOCKED field.</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi-value set and represents the product which currently has a Block on the position. The total of all the mult-values will equate to the total amount blocked.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>"NOINPUT" field</p>
            <p>Standard T24 Product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIN.COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This indicates the company to which the SECURITY.ACCOUNT belongs, for depository and broker positions, those SECURITY.ACCOUNT ending in -999 and -777 respectively, this field will be blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Issue Date of the Security this Security Position record is for.</p>
            <p>Normally this field will contain the Issue Date of the Security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER field taken from the ISSUE.DATE field of the SECURITY.MASTER record that defines Security at the time of the creation of the SECURITY.POSITION record.</p>
            <p>However if the security is a Kassenobligationen security the Issue Date can be entered into the transactions that have updated this SECURITY.POSITION record. In this case this field will contain the date entered into the ISSUE.DATE field of the transaction that created this SECURITY.POSITION record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>URLZ.CCY.GN.ST.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field no longer used by the system</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input redundant field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.COST.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the gross cost of the security position - i.e. the cost before charges, commissions, taxes etc. have been applied - in the security currency of the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER field of the record.</p>
            <p>Note; Any exchange rates used will be as of the individual transaction that have built this security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Depository where the Security Position is held.</p>
            <p>This field is a no input field that will contain the ID of the Depository where the security position is held. This field will contain the ID of a CUSTOMER record that is identified as a Depository on the CUSTOMER.SECURITY file. The Depository in this field also makes the third (of six) elements that make up the ID of the SECURITY.POSITION file. Every SECURITY.POSITION record must have something in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPN.COST.INVST.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Redundant field no longer used by the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field no longer used by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COST.INVST.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the cost of the security position identified in the CLOSING.BAL.NO.NOM field in the Security Currency of the security identified in the SECURITY.NUMBER field of the SECURITY.POSITION record.</p>
            <p>Note; Any exchange rates used will be as of the individual transaction that have built this security position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically updated online by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.SETT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the next settlement is due for this position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCOME.START.PERID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is no longer used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Redundant field no longer used by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRILATERAL.RESO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

