<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SEC.TRANSFER.AMEND</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application updates a file called SEC.TRANSFER.AMEND This file gets updated whenever there is a change in PRICE field of SECURITY.TRANSFER record after authorisation. This file will be used in the End Of Day to produce a report detailing all the SECURITY.TRANSFER price changes made that day. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the  transaction. </p>
            <p>Only the sequence number (nnnnn) is required to be input. The Application will automatically generate the prefix (SECTSC) and the first 5 digits (yyddd) and attach the sequence number. The sequence number may be either User or System generated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10 Numeric characters, prefixed by SECTSC, ie. SECTSCyydddnnnnn. yy    = year (eg. 85 = 1985), ddd   = julian day (ie. 01/jan = 001, 02/Jan = 002, 01/Feb = 032, etc.), nnnnn = transaction sequence number (in the range, 00001 to 99999.). (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The sequence number (nnnnn) must be unique.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TRANSFER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Date &amp; Time at which the User made changes to the Price/Yield field on SECURITY.TRANSFER </p>
            <p>Format : a) Standard Date &amp; Time format.          b) Display Only </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the User ID. who initiated the changes to the price field of the security transfer. </p>
            <p>Format : a) Standard User ID. format          b) Display Only </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the cost of the security transfer at the new price in local currency </p>
            <p>Format : a) Standard Rate Format </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the cost of the security transfer at the original price in local currency </p>
            <p>Format : a) Standard Rate Format </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

