<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SECURITY.SUPP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to store additional information to that held on the SECURITY.MASTER file. </p>
            <p> It is an optional file and does not have to exist, but if properly maintained and used in conjunction with SECURITY.MASTER, will provide comprehensive details on an Security issued. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>QUANTITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field is Reserved for Future Use </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKING.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the price at which the owner of an option can buy or sell the underlying stock. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROBABILITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field is Reserved for Future Use. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate the End Date of the Yield Calculation </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> For Yield to Maturity, the system wil default the Maturity Date from the Security.Master</p>
            <p> For Call or Put - Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAXATION.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field is used to Store the Value of the Secuirty for Taxation Purposes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates when the Security went for the purpose of dividend or interest calculation. </p>
            <p> If entered and authorised in the DIV.COUP.DET application, this field and its' associated fields PAY.DATE and DIVIDEND.RATE are automatically updated as historical details of all Dividend payments. </p>
            <p> Note:     Each subsequent payment will update the next set of           multivalue fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Standard Date Format. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p> Updated by DIARY and DIV.COUP.DET.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION.PREMIUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the conversion premium of convertible stock. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-18 numeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAXATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the Date the Taxation Value was calculated </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.EARN.RATIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the latest or projected price earnings ratio, i.e. price over its earnings per share. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the price currency of the Security. Currency is entered automatically from the SECURITY.MASTER file. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.PRICE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the date at which the "MINIMUM.PRICE" was reached. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Standard date format No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHARE.ANALYSIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not a particular Security is to be included in analysis reporting. </p>
            <p> Not used currently but included for future enhancement. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 - 2 Alphabetic characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> Only "Y" or "NO" can be entered in this field.</p>
            <p> Default is "NO".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DURATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated automatically with Duration of the Yield </p>
            <p> These figures are updated automatically when the SC.CALC.YIELD routine is run during the end of day process. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to Denote the Price to be used in the Yield Calculations. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Yield to Maturity Optional Input - Default 100%</p>
            <p> Call or Put Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates when the current dividend is payable. </p>
            <p> If entered and authorised in the DIV.COUP.DET application, this field and its' associated fields FX.DATE and DIVIDEND.RATE are automatically updated as historical details of all Dividend payments. </p>
            <p> Note:     Each subsequent payment will update the next set of           multivalue fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Standard Date Format. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p> Updated by DIARY and DIV.COUP.DET</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the lowest price paid for this Security within a particular time period. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 - 18 Numeric characters (No Input field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.DECLARE.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to record the value (price) of the security at the financial year-end, for Tax purposes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 - 18 Numeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.RATING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the market rating of the Security according to a particular rating service such as Standard and Poor's etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Security number entered here relates to the number opened on the SECURITY.MASTER file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-6 numeric characters Security number separated from 3 suffix numeric characters by '-'. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> An authorised record must exist already on the SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
            <p> Leading 0's will be input automatically.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFER.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the latest 'lowest' price a Seller is prepared to accept for his security and will be updated automatically from the Pricing System. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUPON.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the coupon number associated with the payment specified in "EX.DATE", "PAY.DATE" and "DIVIDEND.RATE". </p>
            <p> This field is automatically updated by the DIV.COUP.DET application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 0 - 3 Numeric characters No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.PRICE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the date at which the "MAXIMUM.PRICE" was reached. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Standard Date format No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TICKER.SYMBOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the U.S Stock Exchanges' stock codes where known.  Each Ticker Symbol must be unique. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10 Alphabetic characters. (Optional Input) Examples: I B M Corp. Common Stock = IBMco.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.DIV.PAID</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 - 18 Numeric characters (No input field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement. </p>
            <p> As in the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to define in this file up to 999 Local Elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified. These Local Elements should be defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice. </p>
            <p> The name(s) of the new element(s), as well as the Format and </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Up to 35 characters as defined in the Local Table definition for this Local Reference field. Multivalue field. (Optional or Mandatory input according to definition in the LOCAL.TABLE for this local reference element.) creation of any records.</p>
            <p> As defined by the User within the LOCAL.TABLE and LOCAL.REF.TABLE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TK.EX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically updated as part of the Telekurs Price update process indicate an event due on the Security, eg. Dividend due, Rights Issue pending etc. </p>
            <p> 29.1 contains the latest code received.           29.2 contains the previous code. </p>
            <p> Note:     A value of '0' denotes no pending events. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 numeric character. No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD.TO.MAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculates automatically the Yield to Maturity of the particular Bond i.e. if the Investor were to hold the Bond until its final maturity. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.ISSUED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the total number of shares or bonds issued or in circulation in this particular Security. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-18 Numeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the DIARY.ID for the Equalisation corporate action that had an EX.DATE of the date held in the EQUALISE.PRD.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> 1 - 16 type S ( uppercase alpha or numeric characters )</p>
            <p> Optional</p>
            <p> No Input field</p>
            <p> Automatically updated from DIARY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the currency of the Security.  Currency is entered automatically from the SECURITY.MASTER file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 3 Alphabetic characters No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CPN.NO.CALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the Security has numbered coupons attached and if the interest contained in these should be calculated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 - 2 Alphabetic characters.</p>
            <p> Only "Y" or "NO" can be entered in this field.</p>
            <p> Default value is "NO".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EQUALISE.PRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the dates of previous distributions for the Unit Trust.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 date format</p>
            <p> Optional</p>
            <p> Automatically updated from DIARY or alternatively by user         input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field is Reserved for Future Use </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD.TO.CALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated automatically with the Yield to Call i.e. assuming the Bond will be redeemed at the first available call date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 - 18 Numeric characters No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BETA.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated automatically with a rating for each particular Security. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BID.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the latest 'highest' price a prospective buyer is prepared to pay for a security and will be updated automatically from the Pricing System. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALL.DATES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records when calls are due on partly paid securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Standard date format (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALL.PUT.MATRTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate whether : Call, Put or Yield to Maturity information is required </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> C = Call to Maturity P = Put to Maturity M = Yield to Maturity</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the highest price reached for this Security within a specified period of time. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 0 - 18 Numeric characters No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVEXITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field is Reserved for Future Use. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.DIV.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the date at which the last Dividend was paid. Used in conjunction with the LAST.DIV.PAID field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Standard date format (No Input field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD.TO.LIFE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated automatically with the Yield to Life (or Average Life) of a Bond. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.YIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated automatically with the Current Yield i.e. the annual interest of a Bond divided by the market price. </p>
            <p> These figures are updated automatically when the SC.CALC.YIELD routine is run during the end of day process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 - 18 Numeric characters No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DURATION.MODIFY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated automatically with the Duration Modifier </p>
            <p> These figures are updated automatically when the SC.CALC.YIELD routine is run during the end of day process. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates what rate (amount) is applicable. </p>
            <p> If entered and authorised in the DVI.COUP.DET application, this field and its' associated fields EX.DATE and PAY.DATE are automatically updated as historical details of all Dividend payments. </p>
            <p> Note:     Each subsequent payment will update the next set of           multivalue fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-6 Numeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EXP.YEAR</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the Period/Year to which the associated expenses and fees relate to</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>NET.EXP.RATIO</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the Net expense ratio for the fund for the associated period</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>NET.EXP.CATEG.AVG</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the average for the other funds in the category</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MGT.FEE.ACTUAL</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the Management fees for the period</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MGT.FEE.CATEG.AVG</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the Average for the other funds in the category</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ADMIN.FEE.ACTUAL</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the Admin fees for the period</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ADMIN.FEE.CATEG.AVG</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the Average for the other funds in the category</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>PERIOD</field>
<desc>
<p>This field denotes the period to which associated return relates to. Can be 1-Mo, 3-Mo, 6-Mo, YTD, 1-Yr, 3-Yr, 5-Yr,10-Yr or Since Inception. Free format</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RETURN</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the Return for the period associated</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>BENCHMARK</field>
<desc>
<p>The benchmark against which performance is compared. Some of the ratios are also in relation to the benchmark</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ALPHA</field>
<desc>
<p>Denotes the alpha. Along with other statistical measures like Beta, Standard deviation, R-Squared, etc., these are used as indicators of investment risk in the analysis of funds.</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>BETA</field>
<desc>
<p>Beta - a measure based on volatility</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>STND.DEVIATN</field>
<desc>
<p>The measure used to gauge a fund's risk</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>R.SQUARED</field>
<desc>
<p>This field measures the performance record of the fund in correlation to the index</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>SHARPE.RATIO</field>
<desc>
<p>This field measures the risk-adjusted performance of the fund</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>SORTINO.RATIO</field>
<desc>
<p>Statistical measure of the performance of the fund</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>TREYNOR.RATIO</field>
<desc>
<p>Measure of the returns on the fund</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>INFO.RATIO</field>
<desc>
<p>Measure of risk-adjusted return of the fund</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>BENCHMARK.RTN</field>
<desc>
<p>Performance of the benchmark</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CATEG.RTN</field>
<desc>
<p>Performance of the category to which the fund belongs to</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>SUB.CATG.RTN</field>
<desc>
<p>Performance of the sub-category to which the fund belongs to</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RTN.CATG.RANK</field>
<desc>
<p>Rank of the fund in the category in terms of performance</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RISK</field>
<desc>
<p>Risk associated with the fund (expressed in applicable risk measure- Free format) - e.g. Below average, above average, etc.</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RATING</field>
<desc>
<p>Free format rating- example: 4-Stars, ***. The field from period to rating will be associated multi-value fields.</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>TOT.ASSETS.CCY</field>
<desc>
<p>Currency in which total assets below is expressed</p>
<p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 Alphabetic (currency code) characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CURRENCY table.</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>TOT.ASSETS</field>
<desc>
<p>Field associated with ccy above to express total assets (amount) of the fund.</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>GEOG.REG.CNTY</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the holdings by Region (continent) or country (free format)</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>GEOG.PERC</field>
<desc>
<p>This field indicates the holdings  by region in percentage. The fields Geog Region Cnty and Geog Percent will be associated multi value fields</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>LARGEST.HLDNG</field>
<desc>
<p>Instrument name (free format or ISIN)</p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>LARGEST.HLD.PERC</field>
<desc>
<p>This indicates Percentage holding in the instrument specified above. </p>
</desc>
</t>

</menu>
</t24help>

