<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>STK.EXC.CH</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains all the Local Stock Exchange Commissions and Fees as payable on the SWITZERLAND Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>It contains standard default Category and Transaction codes for all P&amp;L related entries as well as the various bands at which different percentages are to be applied and the asset type to which those rates refer. </p>
            <p>Additionally, it allows the user to store whenever possible the minimum charges payable within that specified Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>It must be pointed out that whereas the system is completely flexible regarding the different levels and rates applicable - a change in the fundamental calculation process would inevitably lead to a program change. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SWISS.MIN.COM.B.S</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to store the minimum commission payable on shares or bonds traded in Switzerland. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRST.CERTS.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 18.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on trust and certificate type securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWISS.MIN.COM.TRST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default value for minimum charge payable on certificates and trust like securities traded in Switzerland. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CL.COM.DB.TRANS.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default debit transaction code for all commissions levied from a customer and contained within this application. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1) 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>    
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field.  Field automatically defaults to currency of the country as specified at ID. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type CCY (Currency Code) characters. (Default Value).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTES.SHDS.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 16.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on notes and schuldsheine type securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHARES.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with fields 21 and 22 to store the different levels and rates applicable on foreign shares traded abroad. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the country domicile to which the rates and commissions applicable within any particular stock exchange apply. </p>
            <p>Notes:     At Stock.Exchange the user is prompted for a            (CALL&gt;COUNTRY) ID at Field 3.  Whenever a transactio            is entered with a given stock exchange the system will            read the appropriate stock exchange calculation tables. </p>
            <p>           It is possible to have 2 or more stock exchanges reading            the same calculation table eg. Basle, Geneva and Zurich. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type SS (uppercase alpha) country code characters. (Mandatory Input).</p>
            <p>Must exist on the COUNTRY.CODE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWISS.BNDS.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 13.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on Swiss domiciled bonds. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.DB.TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Debit transaction code for all brokerage type P &amp; L entries created within this application. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1) 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FRGN.SH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 10.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on foreign domiciled shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FRGN.BNDS.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 14.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on foreign domiciled bonds. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWISS.BNDS.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 12.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on Swiss domiciled bonds. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.TRANS.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Minimum amounts can be fixed at will for all transactions having a gross value of less than SFR 250. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRST.CERTS.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 19.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on trusts and certificate type securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CL.COM.CR.TRANS.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default credit transaction code for all commission levied from a customer and contained within this application. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1) 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>    
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FRGN.MIN.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard default value for all transactions effected abroad i.e. the minimum charge payable by a client no matter how small the gross consideration. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FRGN.SH.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with Field 11.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on foreign domiciled shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.CR.TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Credit transaction code for all brokerage P &amp; L type entries which will be created by this application. </p>
            <p>The following ranges have been assigned within T24:            600 - 649 = Securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1) 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p> To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWISS.SH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 8.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on Swiss domiciled shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FRGN.BNDS.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 15.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on foreign domiciled bonds. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHS.CNTRY.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 20 &amp; 22 to store the different levels and rates applicable on foreign shares traded abroad. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CL.COMMISSN.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default category code for all commission levied from a customer according to the rates as stored within this application. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit and loss and product types. Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's operation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters. a)   Product/P&amp;L classification in the range 1-99. b)   Sub-classification of product/P&amp;L in the range 000-999. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTES.SHDS.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 17.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on notes and schuldscheine type securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHARES.RATE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWISS.SH.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 9.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on Swiss domiciled shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BNDS.FRGN.CCY.MIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default value for minimum charge payable on all transactions in foreign currency bonds, notes and promissory notes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type amount (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BONDS.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 24.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on Bonds traded abroad. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BONDS.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field to be used in conjunction with field 23.1 to store the different levels and rates applicable on bonds traded abroad. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.BROKRGE.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default category code for all brokerage type entries contained within these tables. </p>
            <p>This code classifies profit and loss and product types. Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's operation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters: a)   Product/P&amp;L classification in the range 1-99. b)   Sub-classification of product/P&amp;L in the range 000-999. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

