<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>STOCK.DIV.DET</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW FOR STOCK DIV DET </p>
            <p>This file contains all the relevant details necessary to process a stock dividend, stock split type transaction within the securities module. </p>
            <p>The conditions relating to each transaction are entered within this file and it enables the system to calculate 'balances' due to each customer with a holding in the specified security as at an 'extraction' date. </p>
            <p>The sub-system allows the ratios and/or percentages value dates, commissions and any foreign charges passed on by the depository concerned.  It enables the user to update a separate security suffix position should the transaction necessitate this; where for example the new or bonus shares do not rank equally along with the old shares.  Advices are produced and financial entries passed. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the extraction date of the dividend. </p>
            <p>Only positions held up to and including this date are eligible for any additional stock or bonus entered at this level. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must be same or after ID reference date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.CREATED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically created multivalue  field related to fields 16, 18, 19 and 20 to store details of records per depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. (Multivalue field).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the currency that the stock is priced in. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 uppercase alpha characters (SSS). or     1-3 numeric character currency code. Default from security master record can be altered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RERUN.CANCEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used only when C - want to cancel customer details, R - rerun Stock Dividend Details. </p>
            <p>If an error discovered in a Client's position after Customer records have been created. The User has the facility to rerun the Stock Dividend records at E.O.D by entering R at the Stock Dividend Detail record. </p>
            <p>Similarly by entering C for Cancel the user can cancel all records created by a Stock Dividend run; but again at E.O.D. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only input R or C or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.PERC.IND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether (field 5) dividend is a percentage of unit amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only input allowed is: (Y)es - % or     (N)o  - unit Default = Y if field 5 input N if field 5 not input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOR.OLD.SHARES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates number of old shares to be held.  Field 7 indicates how many new shares per number of old shares field 8 are available to the client. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format. Optional input. (Must be entered if field 7 used).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATIO.NEW.SHARES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates when a company is offering new shares for old. </p>
            <p>May be used for a stock split, i.e. so many new shares for old shares held. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 type numeric input. Optional input.  Must be entered if fields 5-7 not.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies uniquely each Stock Dividend Detail(s). </p>
            <p>Note:     Depository can be input to specify only            security in that particular depot are            eligible for stock. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The detail key is made up of the following format:- NNNNNN-NNN - 6 numeric character Security Master number. NNNNN      - 1-5 Alpha numeric Stock Dividend Type. YYYYMMDD   - Standard date format which defines the extraction date. Examples:  000050-000        . .     SD      19861101 Security Master  depot    type    exdate Jaguar           not      stock   1st Nov specified dividend  1986</p>
            <p>Security must be a valid security master.</p>
            <p>Stock dividend type must be valid input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.POSTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically created multivalue field related to fields 16, 17, 19 and 20 to store details of the records per depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. (Multivalue field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically created multivalue field related to fields 17, 18, 19 and 20 to store details of the records per depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input. Internally generated field. (Multivalue field).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESULT.SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates new security number if the bonus issue or stock dividend does not rank pari-passu with base security. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 digit numeric Security Master number. Default to security master/id number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the payment date of the stock dividend. </p>
            <p>When is the stock split to take effect from.  What value date will accounts be updated with additional stock. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format. Defaults to field 3.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the amount of the stock dividend. </p>
            <p>Must be entered if fields 7 and 8 not entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format. Default to zero.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Security Master by the short name of the stock (field 3). </p>
            <p>Information purposes:  Name copied over from the authorised Security Master File. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid SECURITY MASTER File record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOREIGN.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies rate of charge, charged by depository on this transaction. </p>
            <p>Foreign charges are to be passed on to client along with any bank commission specified in field 13. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format. Optional input.  Defaults to zero.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the depository where stock is held per ex. date.  The specified depository is effectively carrying out the transaction on behalf of the co. concerned. </p>
            <p>Will form part of the customers id once authorised at details level, thus allowing one or more depositories to hold stock.  Where no depository entered the system assumes all depository holdings are eligible for the stock dividend transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Defaults where input on ID.</p>
            <p>If input it must be a valid depository type record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.DELETED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically created multivalue field related to fields 16, 17, 19 and 20 to store details of the records per depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. (Multivalue field).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies price of stock involved in this transaction. </p>
            <p>Price of stock in currency as specified in field 9.  Price currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format. Defaults to security master but can be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHORISER</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES.PERC.IND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether field 11 is a percentage of unit amount rate which is applicable to the transaction. </p>
            <p>Both foreign charges and bank commission will be debited to the client.  Foreign charges will be credited to the depository while bank commission will be credited to P+L category type 'Account". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only input allowed is (Y)es - % or     (N)o  - unit Default = (N)o.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage charge. Taken as commission on gross amount. Where this commission represents the Banks' commission for processing this Div/Coup payment. </p>
            <p>The standard commission rate for a coupon/interest payment are picked up from the standard default table but these can be altered at transaction level. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard rate format up to 6 integers and decimal point only. (Defaults to SC.STD.DIV.COUP).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

