<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>STOCK.EXCHANGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                    STOCK.EXCHANGE </p>
            <p />
            <p>The Stock Exchange code is used at various levels throughout the securities module.  At a static information level it is used to record the Stock Exchange where a particular security is usually dealt. </p>
            <p>For example when setting up details of a security like the Swiss Co. Sulzer Gebruder SF100 within the security master file the inputter would specify that the security was normally traded at the Zurich or Geneva Stock Exchange at transaction level the security purchase/sale facility when accessed with the Sulzer security I.D. Number e.g. 678954-000 the transaction would default automatically to the Stock Exchange entered within the security master.  The system would then calculate all local and foreign charges applicable to that security according to the details stored within the Stock Exchange commission tables which are linked to each Stock Exchange by a country code. </p>
            <p>The user however has the facility to override this Stock Exchange depending on where he has dealt. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CU.BOND.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub valued field associated fields BR.BOND.CNTY TO CU.BOND.COMM. Will contain the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE ID that defines that levy charged for a customer dealing in bonds at this Stock Exchange. Will be used to calculate the CU.EBV.FEES on any SEC.TRADE done for a bond on this Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.SHR.CNTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub valued field associated fields BR.SHR.CNTY TO CU.SHR.COMM. Will contain a valid Country code or 'ALL'. Will be used by SEC.TRADE to calculate the CU.EBV.FEES for a share trade done across this stock exchange. Will be used by the system to test against the security domicile to work out which FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record to use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Input must be 'ALL' or exist on the COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.SHR.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub valued field associated fields BR.SHR.CNTY TO CU.SHR.COMM. Will contain the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE ID that defines that levy charged for a customer dealing in shares at this Stock Exchange. Will be used to calculate the CU.EBV.FEES on any SEC.TRADE done for a share on this Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will link the Stock Exchange to a country code which then will access the Stock Exchange calculation tables for automatic calculation of commissions and charges applicable. </p>
            <p>Each Stock Exchange calculation table has a unique code which happens to be the country code (common T24 country code table) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 Alpha character input.  Standard country code.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Country Code which exists on the Country Code Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Full Description of the Stock Exchange as uniquely identified in Field 'O' </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Stock Exchange in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 Alpha numeric characters free format (Mandatory Input) (Multi language field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CU.BOND.CNTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub valued field associated fields BR.BOND.CNTY TO CU.BOND.COMM. Will contain a valid Country code or 'ALL'. Will be used by SEC.TRADE to calculate the CU.EBV.FEES for a bond trade done across this stock exchange. Will be used by the system to test against the security domicile to work out which FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record to use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Input must be 'ALL' or exist on the COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.DAYS.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the value date is to be calculated on a business or calendar day basis. </p>
            <p>The basis entered in this field will be used to determine how the value date will be calculated given the trade date and the settlement days for  this stock exchange. </p>
            <p>Example   The holiday table being set up with Saturdays and           Sundays as the weekend days. Trade date of Thursday 4th           March and settlement days of 2.           If the basis is BUSINESS then the value date will be           Monday 8th.           If the basis is CALENDAR then the value date will be           Saturday 6th. If the basis is FIXED, then the value date will be cal culated on the basis of calendar defined for that particular Stock Exchange &amp; Year in STK.EXCH.CALENDAR (where a Settlement Day is defined for a period) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Values allowed are BUSINESS OR CALENDAR OR FIXED. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.SHR.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub valued field associated fields BR.SHR.CNTY TO CU.SHR.COMM. Will contain the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE ID that defines that levy charged for a broker dealing in shares at this Stock Exchange. Will be used to calculate the BR.EBV.FEES on any SEC.TRADE done for a share on this Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOCK.EXCHANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique Code used to identify each separate Stock Exchange where securities may be traded. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-5 Alpha numeric characters. Mandatory input. Examples: Zurich Stock Exchange would be set up as Zurich. Basle = Basle</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Short version of Stock Exchange description as uniquely identified in Field 'O' </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Stock Exchange in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-15 Alpha numeric characters, free format. (Mandatory Input) (Multi Language field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOMICILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifices the country of domicile of the Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>Each Stock Exchange calculation table has a unique code which happens to be the country code (common T24 country code table) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 Alpha character input.  Standard country code. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Country Code which exists on the Country Code Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIFID.COMPLIANT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHARE.LEVY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field and the fields BR.SHR.CNTY to CU.SHR.COMM associated with it allows the used to define any stock exchange levies that will be charged by this Stock Exchange, EBV fees, PTM levy etc. They will be used to update the CU.EBV.FEES or BR.EBV.FEES fields on a SEC.TRADE that uses this STOCK.EXCHANGE. </p>
            <p>This set of fields will be used to define the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE records to be used for these fees for shares. The fields BOND.LEVY.DATE to CU.BOND.COMM do the equivalent for bonds. </p>
            <p>A share is defined in T24 as a Security Master record where the BOND.OR.SHARE flag is set to 'S'. </p>
            <p>This set of flags works as follows; The system will check whether we are dealing with a bond or a share to work out which set of fields to use. It will then take the trade date and compare it against the set of dates in this field until it finds the one that is less than the trade date. It will then decide if we are calculating a customer levy (CU.EBV.FEES) or a broker levy (BR.EBV.FEES). If it is a broker levy it will use BR.SHR.CNTY and BR.SHR.COMM if it is a customer CU.SHR.CNTY and CU.SHR.COMM. It will then take the security domicile of the share and look for this country in the BR.SHR.CNTY (or CU.SHR.CNTY) field. If it locates it, it will take the associated FT.COMMISSION.TYPE ID from the BR.SHR.COMM (or CU.SHR.COMM) field and use it to calculate the levy. If it does not find the country code then it will look for 'ALL' in the BR.SHR.CNTY(or CU.SHR.CNTY) field and if it is there use the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record associated with it. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Any input must be of a standard T24 date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MKT.IDN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The swift market identifier code is defined in this field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 Alphabetical characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the number of days forward the value date is it be. </p>
            <p>Multi value field associated with TRANSACTION.TYPE and TRADE.CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>Accepts a value when SETT.DAYS.BASIS is BUSINESS or CALENDAR. The number of days entered will be used to calculate the value date (forward) when a security is traded using this Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>This field can be used with the combination of TRANSACTION.TYPE and TRADE.CURRENCY. A settlement day can be defined for each combination. </p>
            <p>Value date will be calculated based on the following priority. </p>
            		<p>If only the settlement date is defined, use the same for calculating the value date.  </p>
            		<p>If there is a match with any transaction type and trade currency combination, use the corresponding settlement days for calculating the value date. </p>
            		<p>If there is no exact match with any combination, use the first matched criteria based on TRANSACTION.TYPE for calculating the value date. </p>
            		<p>If there is no match, use the settlement days for which no transaction type or trade currency is linked. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory when either TRANSACTION.TYPE or TRADE.CURRENCY is input.</p>
            <p>1-3 Numeric characters. Input mandatory if SETT.DAYS.BASIS is BUSINESS Input not allowed if SETT.DAYS.BASIS if FIXED. Otherwise input is optional.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOND.LEVY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field and the fields BR.BOND.CNTY to CU.BOND.COMM associated with it allows the used to define any stock exchange levies that will be charged by this Stock Exchange, EBV fees, PTM levy etc. They will be used to update the CU.EBV.FEES or BR.EBV.FEES fields on a SEC.TRADE that uses this Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>This set of fields will be used to define the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE records to be used for these fees for bonds. The fields SHARE.LEVY.DATE to CU.SHR.COMM do the equivalent for shares. </p>
            <p>A bond is defined in T24 as a Security Master record where the BOND.OR.SHARE flag is set to 'B'. </p>
            <p>This set of flags works as follows; The system will check whether we are dealing with a bond or a share to work out which set of fields to use. It will then take the trade date and compare it against the set of dates in this field until it finds the one that is less than the trade date. It will then decide if we are calculating a customer levy (CU.EBV.FEES) or a broker levy (BR.EBV.FEES). If it is a broker levy it will use BR.BOND.CNTY and BR.BOND.COMM if it is a customer CU.BOND.CNTY and CU.BOND.COMM. It will then take the security domicile of the bond and look for this country in the BR.BOND.CNTY (or CU.BOND.CNTY) field. If it locates it, it will take the associated FT.COMMISSION.TYPE ID from the BR.BOND.COMM (or CU.BOND.COMM) field and use it to calculate the levy. If it does not find the country code then it will look for 'ALL' in the BR.BOND.CNTY(or CU.BOND.CNTY) field and if it is there use the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record associated with it. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Any input must be of a standard T24 date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.BOND.CNTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub valued field associated fields BR.BOND.CNTY TO CU.BOND.COMM. Will contain a valid Country code or 'ALL'. Will be used by SEC.TRADE to calculate the BR.EBV.FEES for a bond trade done across this stock exchange. Will be used by the system to test against the security domicile to work out which FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record to use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Input must be 'ALL' or exist on the COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.BOND.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub valued field associated fields BR.BOND.CNTY TO CU.BOND.COMM. Will contain the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE ID that defines that levy charged for a broker dealing in bonds at this Stock Exchange. Will be used to calculate the BR.EBV.FEES on any SEC.TRADE done for a bond on this Stock Exchange. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUT.OFF.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field accepts time .Which is cutoff time for stock exchange </p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.SHR.CNTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub valued field associated fields BR.SHR.CNTY TO CU.SHR.COMM. Will contain a valid Country code or 'ALL'. Will be used by SEC.TRADE to calculate the BR.EBV.FEES for a share trade done across this stock exchange. Will be used by the system to test against the security domicile to work out which FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record to use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Input must be 'ALL' or exist on the COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGGREGATION</field>
<desc>
            <p> Allowed value is YES </p>
            <p> Field to determine whether stock exchange is enabled for aggregation. This will be additionally checked if broker is enabled for aggregation. Aggregation will be performed only if stock exchange and broker are enabled for aggregation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGGR.CUT.OFF.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p> This Field accepts time </p>
            <p> Cut off time at which trades will be authorised OR mt515 will be received to authorise the aggregated trades.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p> Multi value field associated with SETTLEMENT.DAYS and TRADE.CURRENCY. </p>
            <p> This field will be used with combination of SETTLEMENT.DAYS and TRADE.CURRENCY for calculating the value date of the contract. </p>            
            <p> Refer SETTLEMENT.DAYS for defaulting logic of value date of the contract. This field is mandatory when TRADE.CURRENCY is defined. </p>
            <p> Accepts the values 'CREDIT' 'DEBIT' 'BOTH'</p>
            		<p> CREDIT - All buy transactions. </p>
            		<p> DEBIT - All sell transactions. </p>
            		<p> BOTH - Both buy and sell transactions. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory when TRADE.CURRENCY is defined.</p>                        
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p> Multi value field associated with SETTLEMENT.DAYS and TRANSACTION.TYPE. </p>
            <p> This field will be used with combination of SETTLEMENT.DAYS and TRANSACTION.TYPE  for calculating the value date of the contract. </p>
            <p> Refer SETTLEMENT.DAYS for defaulting logic of value date of the contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Accepts a valid currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSPEND.TRADING</field>
<desc>
            <p> Trading can be suspended in the stock exchange due to some unforeseen circumstances such as a natural calamity. Such a suspension is communicated to the system by setting this field to "Yes". Once the trading resumes, this flag needs to be cleared</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

