<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>STOCK.DIV.CUS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW OF STOCK DIV CUS </p>
            <p>These are system generated records which have been created as a direct result of using the Stock.Div.Det application. </p>
            <p>They are individual records by security per customer and contain all the relevant details pertaining to that client and his stock split/dividend in a particular security.  The system will calculate a stock amount to be credited to the client, and a financial amount to be debited and made up of commission and foreign charges changed on the nominal balance. </p>
            <p>The user will be allowed the standard T24 facility of being able to authorise one or all records. </p>
            <p>Customer advices will be printed and all financial entries updated. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies where security is held, and at which depository the stock dividend transaction is too effected. </p>
            <p>Where no depository entered at STOCK.DIV.DET. level the system will create customer records for each depository holding. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.  Defaults to the depository field entered as part of the key in STOCK.DIV.DET.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.BASE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency of price traded. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the amount of commission applied to the transaction customer, by the bank concerned. </p>
            <p>No. nominal x commission = amount. Currently the Old Balance multiplied by the commission ratio and it equals the banks P &amp; L on this transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 characters plus a decimal point (standard amount format) Type AMT.  Input allowed where change may be necessary from standard default amounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the payment date of the stock dividend. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.  Created from the details as specified at STOCK.DIV.DET.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of 'stock' dividend to be received by customer from company. </p>
            <p>Round up and down facility will automatically give a round amount.  This nominal amount is calculated according to the balance held and the ratio to be applied to that holding. </p>
            <p>Examples:  250 nominal   1 new for 6 old/            Dividend    = 42 shares. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  System creates the record from the details entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVE.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>If entered, it is used to check the format of the override delivery address entered, depending on the value of the carrier from the message control message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric character Message Control Id (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>Must be the Id of a valid Message Control record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOMINAL.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of stock held by client as per ex.date and therefore liable for any stock dividend, bonus issue involved within this transaction. </p>
            <p>The system calculates the clients' holding as per the EX.DATE, per depository.  If no depository entered one record for each customer/depository relationship will be created. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Automatically generated security position as per the criteria entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the reference number of the advices, delivery instructions and payment/receipt messages related to this transaction. </p>
            <p>This field is generated by the delivery system when the messages are created. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>External field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EBV.FEES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the amount of EBV Fees charged to the Customer for the trade. </p>
            <p>Charges will only be applied where NET TRADE INDICATOR (Field 11) is set to NO. This field will be calculated automatically but may be overridden by manual input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters &amp; "." (number of decimal places dependant on the currency). (Optional input). (Multivalue field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the customer who holds stock as per ex.date. One customer record per depository holding will be created by T24. </p>
            <p>In the case where no depository is entered i.e. the Stock Dividend is a global transaction, the system will create one customer record per depository.  In the event of a customer holding securities with 2 depositories - 2 separate advices will be created. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field created from the details specified at STOCK.DIV.DET.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the reference currency of the customers portfolio account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.  Defaults to the SEC.ACC.MASTER file for this particular customer.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.ACC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total financial debit from client in reference currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Automatically generated ID No.  Unique to this STOCK DIV record. </p>
            <p>Because this is an automatically created record the system gives it a unique ID.  The prefix is hand coded STKD.  Julian date plus sequential number thus completes the ID. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field. Prefix 'STKD' plus Julian date and next sequential number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAMP.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the Stamp Tax amount charged to the Customer for the trade. </p>
            <p>Charges will only be applied where Net Trade indicator (Field 11) is set to NO. This field will be calculated automatically but may be overridden by manual input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters &amp; "." (number of decimal places dependant on the currency). (Optional input). (Multivalue field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains details of any overrides applicable to this Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Internal field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 015 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.DIV.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Net Dividend payable in the currency of the depository account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 42 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQ.DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates posting date of the DIVIDEND/ INTEREST amount as per the nostro entry. </p>
            <p>The value date at field 3 refers to the customer account posting regarding the actual value date.  This field contains the reference or posting date of the depository total to the nostro account. </p>
            <p>To help with nostro reconciliation problems in the event of, for example, 100 clients each receiving a Dividend/Interest payment.  The nostro total is only passed (automatically) when all the customer records have been either authorised or deleted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format. No input, internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provides the address where the Customer's Advices relating to this trade are to be sent (where different from the Address entered on the CUSTOMER record). </p>
            <p>If entered, will be used by the delivery system in place of any addresses stored elsewhere in the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue fields available to enable the full address to be input. (Optional input.) (Multivalue field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.PRICE.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate between account currency and base currency where different. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Rate format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.BASE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate between price currency and base currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input allowed.  Defaults.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 rate field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the TAX file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITIES.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the customers security account where stock will be posted to and in which the particular security is held. </p>
            <p>This is the security account which belongs to the customer as defined in Field 2. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESS.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains all the Customer Keys related to the depository record. </p>
            <p>This field is only updated on the depository record showing the customer records associated to it together with their respective accounting entry numbers. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input. Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.AMT.REF.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate between base currency and reference currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard rate format 6,9 (max 10 digits plus a decimal point). Input allowed. Default to currency field - mid rate value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount of Net Dividend payable in Security/Dividend currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>A number Generated automatically by the system after authorisation which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of a transaction. After validation but before authorisation, the value 'VAL' will be inserted in this field to indicate that the transaction has been validated successfully but is still waiting authorisation. </p>
            <p>After authorisation of a Funds Transfer transaction, the system will automatically insert a number into this field and this number may refer to a statement entry or a category entry depending on the value contained in the corresponding multivalue fields. The following examples will illustrate the use of this field. </p>
            <p>Example 1: </p>
            <p>On the execution date of a transaction there will normally be an entry on a Customer account and the following type of number will be generated at this field: </p>
            <p>           92.1  STMT.NO  673732684.48            92.2  STMT.NO  1 </p>
            <p>The number automatically generated in field 92.1 is unique to the transaction in question and is built in the following way: </p>
            <p>1.         The first four digits '6737' indicate the number of days            since the 1st of January 1968. In our example, it            corresponds to the 11th of June 1986. </p>
            <p>2.         The next five digits '32684' indicate the number of            seconds since midnight. In our example, it corresponds            to an entry generated on line at 09:04:44 AM. </p>
            <p>3.         The last two digits '48' indicate the number of hundreds            of seconds. </p>
            <p>The value assigned (again automatically) to field 92.2 identifies the number in 92.1 as a statement entry number. If the User wishes to call this statement entry record on to the screen the User will invoke the STMT.ENTRY Application and the type the following at 'Awaiting ID' :- </p>
            <p>                673732684.480001 </p>
            <p>where the suffix '0001' identifies it as the first statement entry (there will normally be more than one as the next example will illustrate). </p>
            <p>Example 2: </p>
            <p>A second example outlined here is similar to that in example 1, in that there is a statement entry on value date for both the our account and the customer account. The system handles this case as follows: </p>
            <p>                92.1  STMT.NO  673732684.48                 92.2  STMT.NO 1-2 </p>
            <p>Once again field 92.1 contains the identification number automatically generated by the system while field 92.2 now contains two separate numbers signifying that there are infact two separate statement entries, one in respect of the our account pay and one in respect of the our account receive. If the User wishes to see either of these he must first of all invoke STMT.ENTRY followed by the desired function and then at 'Awaiting ID' type EITHER: </p>
            <p>                673732684.480001 </p>
            <p>where the addition of the suffix '0001' identifies the statement entry in respect of the our account OR </p>
            <p>                673732684.480002 </p>
            <p>where the addition of the suffix '0002' identifies the statement entry in respect of the customer account. </p>
            <p>Example 3: </p>
            <p>A third example might be that of a category entry generated at initiation of a transaction where commission or charges have been debited to the customer and credited to a profit and loss category code. In this case the following entries are generated on the transaction: </p>
            <p>                92.1  STMT.NO 673732684.48                 92.3  STMT.NO 1 </p>
            <p>Once again the standard type number is generated and inserted at field 92.1 </p>
            <p>Now, however, field 92.2 is replaced by field 92.3 which now identifies the number in 92.1 as a category entry and not a statement entry. </p>
            <p>To call this category entry record onto the screen the User must now type: </p>
            <p>           CATEG.ENTRY at 'Awaiting Application' </p>
            <p>followed by: </p>
            <p>           673732684.480001 at 'Awaiting ID'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>If a particular depository is specified at the DIVIDEND COUP DETAIL level it specifies that the interest/coupon payment is only for that requested depository. </p>
            <p>The CUSTOMER records are created from the key input at DIV COUP DET.  Where the depository is input as part of the key determines the information contained within this field. </p>
            <p>If  no depository is  input at the detail level (Optional input) it specifies that the dividend interest is payable through all depository holdings and this field will not be updated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated.  No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total amount to be debited from clients account in currency of price. </p>
            <p>(No. nominal x price)-(fgn chg + commission) = net amount.  Total commissions and charges to be posted to clients' account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.DETAIL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies uniquely each Stock Dividend Customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />The detail key is made up of the following format:- NNNNNN-NNN - 6 numeric character Security master number. NNNNNN - 106 numeric character Customer Security number -Depository. QQQQQ - 1-5 Alpha numeric Dividend Type code. YYYYMMDD - Standard Date Format. NNNNNN-N - 1-6 numeric Security Account master number. SSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS 1-16 characters Sub account number (Optional)  <p /><p /><p />Must exist as a valid Stock Dividend Customer.     </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOR.CHGES.BASE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Commission charged in base currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISS.BASE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total financial debit in base currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOREIGN.CHGES.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount to be debited to client for depository's charges. </p>
            <p>No nominal x fgm chg = amount. Currently calculated on old balance.  It specifies what one depository is charging for this particular transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TAX.BCUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REF.BASE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Depository foreign charges in base currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.EX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total financial amount to be debited from clients account, in the account currency. </p>
            <p>Where account currency may be different form the charge commission 'the securities' module calls forex and converts the amount into the Account currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the currency of the account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.  Internally generated field coped over from the static information files and merely identifies the currency of the Account field 5.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates which of the customer's Accounts will be debited with any financial amounts. i.e. commissions, foreign charges etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-16 numeric character Account number or 3-10 character Mnemonic Account id (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".").</p>
            <p>Default value = the Account specified on the Customer's SEC.ACC.MASTER record.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Account on the ACCOUNT file. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.DEP.CUR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local Currency equivalent of Net Dividend amount. Converted using foreign exchange call rates. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

