<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>SUB.ASSET.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                    SUB.ASSET.TYPE </p>
            <p />
            <p>     As the title suggests this file contains a further definition of an asset. </p>
            <p>     For reporting purposes and information retrieval at account officer level. </p>
            <p>     Once a security is opened at security master level and given an asset number the user can further define that position by utilising this file. </p>
            <p>     A suggested example would be where for reporting purposes both within the Bank and as regards the client an Equity would be given an asset type"1". But within the Securities Module there are many different types of security. To which end the Sub Asset type is used to define these various holdings. </p>
            <p>     Partly paid shares,fully paid shares and new nil paid shares are just 3 examples of sub asset types within the asset type Equities. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CCY.LOSS.MGN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Loss margin rate of the currency . This is of numeric type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOSS.MARGIN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the percentage of the asset/liability as defined by the SUB.ASSET.TYPE to be used in portfolio valuations. </p>
            <p>     This is the second level of checking when Securities programs value other (non securities) assets.  If a value is not found on the ASSET.BY.CATEG file then this percentage rate is applied to the value of the sub-asset involved. </p>
            <p>     Depending upon whether a valuation should include/exclude liabilities, either this field or MARGIN.RATE will be used to calculate the margin value. The method of calculation is defined in the field MARGIN.VALUE in SC.PARAMETER </p>
            <p>     If no value is found on either file then a margin rate of 0% is assumed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-5 characters Standard Rate format. Optional Input.</p>
            <p>     If entered, must identify a record on the MARGIN.CONTROL file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes in abbreviated form the Sub.Asset.Type. </p>
            <p>     This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Sub.Asset.Type in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.INIT.SUBS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the minimum initial subscription if any in terms of amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input.Standard T24 Amount format</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KASSENOBLIGATIONEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether or not the SUB.ASSET.TYPE is a Kassenobligationen. </p>
            <p>     If a new security masterfile record is being set-up and the specified SUB.ASSET.TYPE contains "YES" in this field, then the user is able to leave the MATURITY.DATE blank. Usage of this facility will necessitate your being forced to enter any Kassenobligationen trade maturity date directly onto the SEC.TRADE or other T24 security transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Only input of 'KASBON', 'YES' or 'NO' allowed.</p>
            <p>     Optional Input. Default is NULL (meaning NO) (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.SEC.MGN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Asset margin rate of the currency. This is of numeric type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.REDEMPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum amount or number of units that could be redeemed at any point of time. If the holdings are less than the minimum specified here, the transaction would be allowed without any checks</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input. Standard T24 nominal / amount ( NOMAMT ) format.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.REDEM.UNIT.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the Minimum redemption specified is in terms of value or units. If VALUE is defined here and the redemption is in terms of units, the system would convert the units into value terms at order / trade stage based on prevailing NAV and raise override/error as the case may be and vice versa.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input. Allowed values are 'UNITS' or 'VALUE'</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.HLDG.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether error or override needs to be raised when minimum condition as above is not met.</p>
            <p>    If MINIMUM.HOLDING is specified and this field is left blank,the system would raise override when the condition is not met.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input. Allowed values are  'ERROR' or 'OVERRIDE'.</p>
            <p>    Would be defauled to 'OVERRIDE' when left blank and MINIMUM.HOLDING is specified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.REDEM.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether error or override needs to be raised when minimum condition as above is not met.</p>
            <p>    If MIN.REDEMPTION is specified and this field is left blank,the system would raise override when the condition is not met.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input. Allowed values are  'ERROR' or 'OVERRIDE'.</p>
            <p>    Would be defauled to 'OVERRIDE' when left blank and MIN.REDEMPTION is specified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.OUT.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate for calculating sell-out margin amount</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum of 9 numeric characters is allowed </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YEAR.BREAKS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Only required if field 4 set to "Y". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Up to 4 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID of FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record where fee details are stored.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Must be a valid FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record</p>
            <p>    Fields from TRANS.TYPE to DISC.AMT would be associated multi-value fields.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.ENS.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether error or override needs to be raised when minimum condition as above is not met.</p>
            <p>    If MIN.ENSUING.SUBS is specified and this field is left blank,the system would raise override when the condition is not met.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input. Allowed values are  'ERROR' or 'OVERRIDE'.</p>
            <p>    Would be defauled to 'OVERRIDE' when left blank and MIN.ENSUING.SUBS is specified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the SUB ASSET TYPE. </p>
            <p>     This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the SUB ASSET TYPE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     3 to 35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction type for which this charge would be applicable. If ALL is specified, this charge would be applicable for all transaction types, if ALL.CREDIT is specified, this would be applicable for all credit (subscription) transactions, if ALL.DEBIT is specified, this would be applicable for all redemptions. By using different transaction types, it is possible to levy different charges for initial subscription, partial redemptions, full redemptions, switches, etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Allowed values are 'ALL' or 'ALL.CREDIT' or 'ALL.DEBIT' or a valid SC.TRANS.NAME record</p>
            <p>    Fields from TRANS.TYPE to DISC.AMT would be associated multi-value fields.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency for which margin rate is to be specified. Will hold the valid CURRENCY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP1.GRP2.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will select what gets defaulted into a SECURITY.MASTER record in the GRP1.GRP2.METHOD field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     LIFO, FIFO or SUMLIFO</p>
            <p>     Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Risk level for suitability checking.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Cross-referenced to EB.LOOKUP table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CGT.BASE.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the percentage of the CGT Base amount that will be included in the tax calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Optional Input</p>
            <p>     Must be a percentage</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAR.INTEREST.BONDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.HOLDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum units that needs to be held at any point of time. While redeeming, the system would check the units being redeemed against the current holding to see whether the condition is met. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input. Standard T24 nominal / amount ( NOMAMT ) format.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.INIT.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether error or override needs to be raised when minimum condition as above is not met.</p>
            <p>    If MIN.INIT.SUBS is specified and this field is left blank,the system would raise override when the condition is not met.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input. Allowed values are  'ERROR' or 'OVERRIDE'.</p>
            <p>    Would be defauled to 'OVERRIDE' when left blank and MIN.INIT.SUBS is specified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is either discount percentage or amount. If DISC.TYPE is blank, then this would be considered in terms of percentage. The discount would be limited to the extent of fees calculated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    If DISC.TYPE is percentage, this should be 1- 100 ( %) else any numeric character indicating amount. Standard T4 Amount format.</p>
            <p>    Fields from TRANS.TYPE to DISC.AMT would be associated multi-value fields.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MF.ROUNDING.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the rounding parameters for subscription, redemption and NAV</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Must be a valid MF.ROUNDING.PARAM record id.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.UP.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate for calculating top-up margin amount</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum of 9 numeric characters is allowed </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.HLDG.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum holding period in days, months or years. At the time of redemption, the system would check whether the units being redeemed have been held for the period specified in this field. The system would check against the holdings being allocated towards the redemption</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input.Could be nD, nW, nM or nY where n is the number of calender days, Working days, Months or Years</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.ENSUING.SUBS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the minimum amount of subscription if customer already has a holding in the fund. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input.Standard T24 Amount format</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the Adjusted margin rate for calculating ADJ.MARGIN.AMT in SC.POS.ASSET.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALERT.PRICE.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts two numeric values. When the percentage of price change, for the security is greater than ALERT.PRICE.PERC, then an alert will be sent to the portfolio owner, if the portfolio has subscribed for price movement alert. A check will be made to this field, only when ALERT.PRICE.PERC is not defined in SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.TYPE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Asset.Type that this SUB ASSET TYPE is a sub-classification of. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1 to 3 numeric character Asset.Type code. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>     Must exist as a valid ASSET TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPITAL.BOND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to indicate whether or not this SUB.ASSET.TYPE refers to capitalisation bonds. Currently this field is only used by the Bon De Caisse regional development. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed.</p>
            <p>     Must be 'NO' or left blank except when the KASSENOBLIGATIONEN field is set to 'KASBON' when this can be 'YES', 'NO' of left blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This would specify whether discount, if any, is in terms of percentage or amount</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Allowed values are 'PERCENTAGE' or 'AMOUNT'</p>
            <p>    Fields from TRANS.TYPE to DISC.AMT would be associated multi-value fields.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.STAT.GRP.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the SUB ASSET TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-5 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.MARGIN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the percentage of the asset/liability as defined by the SUB.ASSET.TYPE to be used in portfolio valuations. </p>
            <p>     This is the second level of checking when Securities programs value other (non securities) assets.  If a value is not found on the ASSET.BY.CATEG file then this percentage rate is applied to the value of the sub-asset involved. </p>
            <p>     Depending upon whether a valuation should include/exclude liabilities, either this field or LOSS.MARGIN.RATE will be used to calculate the margin value. The method of calculation is defined in the field MARGIN.VALUE in SC.PARAMETER </p>
            <p>     If no value is found on either file then a margin rate of 0% is assumed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1-5 characters Standard Rate format. Optional Input.</p>
            <p>     If entered, must identify a record on the MARGIN.CONTROL file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.PERIOD.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether error or override needs to be raised when minimum condition as above is not met.</p>
            <p>    If MIN.HLDG.PERIOD is specified and this field is left blank,the system would raise override when the condition is not met.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input. Allowed values are  'ERROR' or 'OVERRIDE'.</p>
            <p>    Would be defauled to 'OVERRIDE' when left blank and MIN.HLDG.PERIOD is specified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.TOLERANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price tolerance corresponding to sub asset type. Used as a check to ensure that the difference between the current mid price and that received from the overnight price feed, is within the specified tolerance. If not, reported in the exception report. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Supports EU Saving directives.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     LIFO, FIFO or AVERAGE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRUCTURE.NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>A value of 'YES' indicates that all instruments linked to this SUB.ASSET.TYPE are structured notes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Allowed Value - Yes, default value is NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYOUT.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The user defined routine invoked to calculate the pay-out details and update SC NOTE PAYOUT is attached in this field.</p>
              <p>
              <p>Validation Rules:</p>
              </p>
                <p> This routine will be invoked when the note payout is processed in the SC.NOTE.PAYOUT application and logic within the routine will update the field PAYOUT.PRICE in SC.NOTE.PAYOUT application if the field PAYOUT.PRICE field is left blank.</p>
             
            
 </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

