<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>TELEK.PARAMETERS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains information that will enable the bank to interface to the Telekurs price feed service, through a variety of commercially available packages. </p>
            <p>Seven different record types may be created viz. </p>
            <p>          SYSTEM              Mandatory           HEADER.EXT          Optional           RECORD.EXT          Mandatory           FOOTER.EXT          Optional           HEADER.REC          Optional           RECORD.REC          Optional           FOOTER.REC          Optional </p>
            <p>SYSTEM contains the commands to extract and receive Telekurs information only.  These commands may be shell scripts, programs, or voc entries, so it is vitally important that the full command be entered in this field (e.g. "SH - c'unix command'") </p>
            <p>HEADER.EXT is used to provide a header for the data record(s) sent to the package to extract Telekurs data. </p>
            <p>RECORD.EXT is used to define the body of the data record(s) sent to the package to extract Telekurs data. </p>
            <p>FOOTER.EXT is used to define a footer for the data record(s) sent to the package to extract Telekurs data. HEADER.REC is used to provide header template for data record(s) received from the package. </p>
            <p>RECORD.REC is used to provide a record template for data records received from the package. </p>
            <p>FOOTER.REC is used to provide a footer template for data records received from the package. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of record created. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 to 11 Alphanumeric characters. Only the following values will be accepted: Key         Description                        Status SYSTEM      Extract &amp; Receive commands         Mandatory HEADER.EXT  Header information for the extract processOptional RECORD.EXT  Detail information for the extract processMandatory FOOTER.EXT  Footer information for the extract processOptional HEADER.REC  Header information for the receive processOptional RECORD.REC  Detail information for the receive processOptional FOOTER.REC  Footer information for the receive processOptional</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates what type of Reports are required. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid values are: DETAIL    Prints the full status Report ERROR     Prints only errors.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.SEPERATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to separate the header, footer and detail records. </p>
            <p>If the Telekurs interface package used by the bank requires records to be separated by a specific character (e.g. "," or NUL or LF) then this is where that value is entered.  Non printable ASCII characters may be input by using their three digit ASCII ordinal value (e.g. 000 = NUL, 010 = LF etc,) printable characters may be entered literally, spaces must be enclosed in quotes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 - 4 Alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains either a string literal (enclosed in quotes) or a field from the "FILE.NAME" file. </p>
            <p>When this field contains a string literal then the quotes will be stripped out and the literal inserted into the extract file.  When this field contains another value it is assumed to be a field from the "FILE.NAME" file and is checked against the STANDARD.SELECTION for that file.  Any valid "D"ata type or "I" type is acceptable and the resultant value is inserted into the extract file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 to 20 Alphanumeric characters (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Non string literals must exist on the STANDARD.SELECTION file for the file in "FILE.NAME".</p>
            <p>Non string literals must be unique.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TELEK.EXTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>UNIVERSE command to execute or program to call after having extracted the TELEKURS data. </p>
            <p>When the first character of this field is an @, it means that           it is a program name, and this program must be called           (instead of being executed like </p>
            <p>This field can contain a VOC entry, a shell script, a T24 program, a Unix command etc., which is used to extract the data           required from the banks Telekurs interface package. </p>
            <p>          Note: If a Unix command or shell script is used from                 within UniVerse the command must be in the                 format SH -c "Unix command". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 to 40 Alphanumeric characters (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRNT.COMPLEMNT.ERR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether or not the complement error is reported. </p>
            <p>All errors identified when validating the data from the Telekurs tape will be reported except the error message for the complement code validation unless the flag in this field is set to 'Y'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or NO may be entered. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TELEK.RECEIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the command used to receive data from the banks Telekurs interface package. </p>
            <p>This field can contain a VOC entry, a shell script, a           T24 program, a Unix command etc., which is used to           receive the data           required from the banks Telekurs interface package. </p>
            <p>          Note: If a Unix command or shell script is used from                 within UniVerse the command must be in the                 format SH -c "Unix command". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 to 40 Alphanumeric characters (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the file to be used in creating the extract file. This file is used to define the data to be extracted from Telekurs and in most cases will probably be the SECURITY.MASTER file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 to 35 Alphanumeric characters (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>The file must exist in the FILE.CONTROL file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT.WRITTEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate if the Report should contain details of every record that is written to the Output file. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y - Print "Written to T24 File " text. N - Do not print</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALL.REPORTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if all reports are to be produced or not. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y - Will produce Reports N - Will not produce Reports</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONV.TABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the table used to convert data values from T24 format to Telekurs format. </p>
            <p>If a table name is entered in this field then the value returned from the "FIELD" field is converted from T24 format to Telekurs format using XT.TABLES.  (e.g. the T24 format for Australian dollars is AUD whereas the Telekurs format is 088). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 - 20 Alphanumeric characters (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>The table must exist in the XT.TABLES file in the format "TELEKURS".CONV.TABLE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.LAST.UPD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FEED.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

