<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>TRANS.FUND.FLOW</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The TRANS.FUND.FLOW application allows the user to specify which transactions types are to be treated as contributions or withdrawals with respect to updates of the portfolio value. The only two fields used on this application are SETUP.CASH.TR and SETUP.SEC.TR. The first lists the list of Accounting transactions that are treated as contributions to or withdrawals from the portfolio and the second Security Transactions (from the SC.TRANS.NAME file) that are considered as contributions to or withdrawals from the portfolio. </p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>Must be keyed on the company that the TRANS.FUND.FLOW record belongs to.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Transaction code as defined on the transaction file </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry on the transaction file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETUP.SEC.TR</field>
<desc>
            <p> Specifies the Transaction code as defined on the transaction file  <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p>   Must be a valid entry on the transaction file.   </p>
            <p>   The code entered here valid for Security movements.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MGTFEE.TR</field>
<desc>
            <p> Specifies the Transaction code as defined on the transaction file. This multivalue field must contain all transaction codes identified as management fees.  <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p>   Must be a valid entry on the transaction file.   </p>
            <p>   The code entered here valid for MANAGEMENT FEE, which is defined in     SAFECUSTODY.VALUES.   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETUP.CASH.TR</field>
<desc>
            <p> Specifies the Transaction code as defined on the transaction file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry on the transaction        file.   </p>
            <p>The code entered here used for the cash        movements.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SFKFEE.TR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Transaction code as defined on the transaction file. This multivalue field must contain all transaction codes identified as safecustody fees.  <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p>   Must be a valid entry on the transaction file.   </p>
            <p>   The code entered here valid for SAFEKEEPING FEE, which is defined in      SAFECUSTODY.VALUES.   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

