<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>VAULT.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to set up parameters for use in the VAULT CONTROL application </p>
            <p>This application controls whether or not the Vault (T24 Safecustody funcationality) is turned on or off, and which depositories is is turned on or off for. </p>
            <p>If the Vault is active then VAULT.EXPECT records can be produced from which the VAULT.CONTROL - certificate file - can be updated. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If certificates are held by Nominee then this field indicates the particular nominee they are held by in a specific depository. </p>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the NOMINEE and DEPOSITORY field. </p>
            <p>This field will be used to default the Nominee Code into the Nominee fields of the Securities module applications ; SEC.TRADE, SECURITY.TRANSFER and SEC.OPEN.ORDER if the transaction is done for the associated depository. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input only allowed if associated NOMINEE field is YES - in which case it is mandatory.</p>
            <p>Any input must exist on the NOMINEE.CODE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls whether certificates held in the associated Depository field are held by Nominee or by customer own name. YES indicates the certificates are held by Nominee. NO indicates the certificates are held by client own name. </p>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the NOMINEE and NOMINEE.CODE fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>Will default to YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVE.VAULT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls whether tha Vault Functionality is active in this company. If YES is input then the Vault is turned on. If NO is input then the Vault is turned off. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input no default.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOW.REMOVAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field controlloing whether or not VAULT.CONTROL records can be removed from the Vault (using the REMOVE field) if they have a trade attached. </p>
            <p>Only input of YES or NO allowed. YES indicates that VAULT.CONTROL records that were created by a trade can be removed from the VAULT - subject to override. NO indicates that VAULT.CONTROL records that were created by a trade cannot be removed from the Vault. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only input of YES or NO allowed.</p>
            <p>Will default to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the VAULT.PARAMETER is the ID of the COMPANY that the Vault is for. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must exist on the COMPANY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Depositories in use for Vault control purposes This field controls wheich depositories will update the Vault. The Depositories can be input individually, ALL can be input to signify all Depositores or NONE can be input to signify No Depositories. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Input can be 'ALL', 'NONE' or a valid DEPOSITORY form the CUSTOMER.SECURITY application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

