<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>VAULT.EXPECT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>VAULT CONTROL  -    VAULT EXPECT </p>
            <p> VAULT.EXPECT (expectation) records are created from the following applications: SEC.TRADE, SECURITY.TRANSFER, POSTITION.TRANSFER for every expected receipt or delivery </p>
            <p />
            <p> DELIVERY expectation records are updated when certificates from the banks vault (VAULT CONTROL removal) are removed (&amp; subsequently delivered) </p>
            <p> RECEIPT expectation records are updated when certificates are received and placed in the banks vault (VAULT CONTROL creation) </p>
            <p> The expectation record is moved to the authorised file when it is satisfied ie. the sum of nominal amounts received/delivered match the total nominal </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Settlement date of transction that generated the Expectation record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field populated by the system when the VAULT.EXPECT record was created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Direction of the VAULT.EXPECT record. Either RECEIPT or DELIVERY. If RECEIPT then this record concerns securities that will be received by the banks vault. If DELIVERY then this record concerns securities that will be removed from the banks vault. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Automatically generated by the transaction that created the VAULT.EXPECT field.</p>
            <p> No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Certificate ID as displayed on the actual certificate. If the DIRECTION is DELIVERY then this is a no input field that is automatically populated from the VAULT.CONTROl record that is linked to this expectation record, the ID of which is in the VCL.REFERENCE field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Text up to 35 chars WITHOUT SPACES</p>
            <p> Mandatory input if the DIRECTION is RECEIPT.</p>
            <p> No input field if the DIRECTION is DELIVERY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Free format text upto 35 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date the Receipt or Delivery was made. Will default to the current system date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Standard T24 date field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field containing YES if the VAULT.EXPECT record has been created by the reversal of the transaction identified in the REFERENCE.NO field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field. Automatically gemerated by the system in the originating transaction was a reversal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency of transaction that generated this record </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field automatically populated by the system when the VAULT.EXPECT record is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the certificates in the Vault are held by Nominee then this field will contain the nominee they are held under. Automatically populated by the system according to the set-up of the VAULT.PARAMETER application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Security Number of the security the Expectation record if for. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field, automatically generated by the system when the VAULT.EXPECT record is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the Transaction that generated the Expectation record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field automatically generated by the system when the VAULT.EXPECT record is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Type of transaction that created this Expectation record. This field will be updated with SC.TRANS.NAME ID of the transaction that created this VAULT.EXPECT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field automatically generated by the system when the VAULT.EXPECT record is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the certificates held in the Vault are held by the customer who owns the securities then this field will contain the portfolio who owns the securities. Automatically populated by the system depending on the set-up of the VAULT.PARAMETER application </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.RECD.DEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Nominal amount received/delivered in respect of the associated certificate contained in the VCL.REFERENCE field associated with this field. If the DIRECTION of the VAULT.EXPECT record is DELIVERY then this field will default from the VAULT.CONTROL record linked to this expectation record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Mandatory input if the DIRECTION is RECEIPT.</p>
            <p> No input field if the DIRECTION is DELIVERY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key format: </p>
            <p> SECURITY.NUMBER : DEPOSITORY : TRANSACTION REF : CUST/NOM CODE </p>
            <p> Note the CUST/NOM CODE conatians either the customer or nominee who owns the securities depending on the set-up of the VAULT.PARAMETER application. </p>
            <p> Automatically generated by the Securities Transaction that generated the VAULT.EXPECT record. </p>
            <p> In addition the key can have a suffix. These suffixs are shown below; .BAL  This is a balance record created by a reversal. .R    This is the credit of Rights from a Corporate Actions       Rights Issue. .D    This if the debit of Rights from a Corporate Actions Rights       Issue. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VCL.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi valued field containing the IDs of the VAULT.CONTROL records linked to this expectation record. Associated with the fields NO.NOM.RECD.DEL, NO.NOM.REF.NO, NO.NOM.REF.DATE, NO.NOM.DATE and NO.NOM.NARR. If the DIRECTION of VAULT.EXPECT record is DELEIVERY then this field allows the user to select record from the VAULT.CONTROL file to satisfy the number of securities that need to be delivered. If the DIRECTION is RECEIPT then this field will be automatically updated by the system with the next ID for the VAULT.CONTROL file as new VAULT.CONTROL records are created in the Vault. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOM.OUTSTANDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total nominal still outstanding on the expectation. If the DIRECTION is RECEIPT this field contains the number of securities the bank is still waiting to receive to satisfy this expectation. If the DIRECTION is DELIVERY then this field contains the number of securities the bank still has to deliver from the Vault to satisfy this expectation. When this field goes to zero then the VAULT.EXPECT record automatically moves to the authorised fiel. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field automatically updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOM.REF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date displayed on actual certificate whose reference number is contained in associated NO.NOM.REF.NO field. If the DIRECTION is DELIVERY then this is a no input field and this field will be automatically populated from the VAULT.CONTROL record that is linked to this Expectation record and the ID of which is contained in the associated VCL.REFERENCE field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field if the DIRECTION is DELIVERY.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input if the DIRECTION is RECEIPT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.NO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total nominal of original transaction that created the VAULT.EXPECT record. This is the total number of securities that have to be received into or delivered out of the Vault. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field automatically generated by the system when the VAULT.EXPECT record is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the trade that created this expectation record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field automatically created by the system when the VAULT.EXPECT record is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE.CERT</field>
<desc>
            <p>If set to Y and the record pertains to DELIVERY and the nominal to be delivered does not match the certificate total then a balance certificate will be generate for the non-delivered element.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Broker of the transaction that created the VAULT.EXPECT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field automatically generated by the system when the</p>
            <p> VAULT.EXPECT record is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Customer number or Nominee code involved with the transaction If the VAULT.PARAMETER file indicates that certificates are held in the Vault are by Nominee then this field will contain the nominee who controls the securities otherwise this field will contain the customer who actually owns the securities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field. Automatically updated from the transaction that produced the VAULT.EXPECT record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Depository where the certificates that this VAULT.EXPECT record relates to are or will be held. Depository of receipt/delivery </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field automatically updated from the transaction that built the VAULT.EXPECT record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

