<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SC</product>
<table>VAULT.CONTROL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>VAULT CONTROL </p>
            <p> The vault control application enables a bank to maintain details of certificates retained by the bank </p>
            <p> Each Vault control record represents an actual certificate retained in the Banks vault. </p>
            <p> Records can be input &amp; maintained manually </p>
            <p> OR </p>
            <p> Records are automatically created for receipt transactions when using the following applications:      SEC.TRADE      SECRURITY.TRANSFER      POSITION.TRANSFER </p>
            <p> Records are automatically removed for delivery transactions when using the above applications. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXPECT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>VAULT EXPECT RECORD ID </p>
            <p> Vault expect records satisfied by this record </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>DEPOSITORY </p>
            <p> The depository where the certificate is held </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.ENTERED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date the record was input </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REMOVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to move manually created VAULT.CONTROL records to history. If a VAULT.CONTROL record was created by user input and the user now wants to indicate that the item in the bank vault that the VAULT.CONTROL record represents has been removed from the Vault then the user should input 'YES' in this field. On authorisation this will result in the VAULT.CONTROL record being written to history. </p>
            <p> With regard to VAULT.CONTROL records generated through the input of a transaction, such as SEC.TRADE, these cannot normally be removed. However, if the need arises, you can effect the removal of an automatically created VAULT.CONTROL by setting the ALLOW.REMOVAL field in the VAULT.PARAMETER file to "Y". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field if VAULT.CONTROL record has been created from a VAULT.EXPECT record - i.e. linked to a trade unless the ALLOW.REMOVE flag has been set to "Y" in VAULT.PARAMETER</p>
            <p> Only input of 'YES' or 'NO' allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MOVE.TO.HIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System generated field indicating the record is to be processed by the service VAULT.PROCESSING and will be moved from the live to history file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOMINEE CODE </p>
            <p> Nominee code in whose name the certificate is registered </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>PORTFOLIO NUMBER </p>
            <p> The nu,ber of the customer portfolio in whose name the certificate is registered. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The nominal amount of the certificate </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> numbers only</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>SECURITY NUMBER </p>
            <p> Security number of the certificate </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELEASE.MARKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>RELEASE MARKER </p>
            <p> Flag usedto indicate whether the certificate has been released before the releasing transaction has been authorised on T24 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> YES OR NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOMINAL.USED</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOMINAL USED </p>
            <p> Nominal used to satisfy the Vault Expect record </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOMINEE </p>
            <p> The nominee code in whose name the certificate is registered </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Trades that have updated this record </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CERT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>CERTIFICATE DATE </p>
            <p> The date displayed on the actual certificate </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CERTIFICATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>INTERNAL CERTIFICATE ID </p>
            <p> ID is made up as follows: </p>
            <p> 'CERT' : YYDDD : XXXXX </p>
            <p>    YY = year    DDD = julian day    XXXXX = sequence number for the day </p>
            <p> The key is automatically generated by pressing F3 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CERTIFICATE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>CERTIFICATE NUMBER </p>
            <p> The actual certicate number as printed on the certificate </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 35 CHARACTERS FREE FORMAT TEXT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to allow input of a CUSTOMER number for manually input VAULT.CONTROL records that are not linked to a trade. If the VAULT.CONTROL record was created by a trade then this field will be a no input field. If the depository is a Nominee Depository then this field will be blank, otherwise this field will contain the CUSTOMER Number of the portfolio. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> No input field if VAULT.CONTROL record created from a VAULT.EXPECT record.</p>
            <p> Mandatory input for manually input VAULT.CONTROL records.</p>
            <p> Any input must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

