<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CD</product>
<table>CRS.CUST.SUPP.INFO</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
        <p>CRS.CUST.SUPP.INFO table holds the supplementary information for a customer related to CRS. The ID of the record will be the Customer number.</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CRS.CUST.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>The ID will be the CUSTOMER number. </p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Must be a valid record on the Customer table.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRS.CUSTOMER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to state whether the customer is an ‘Individual’ or an ‘Entity’.</p>
        <p>If the client is an ‘Entity’, then further granular level classification is required in to the Entity as a Reportable Person Entity as a Passive NFE.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        <p>Allowed values are Individual, Entity-Reportable Person, Entity-Passive NFE</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KYC.CHECK</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to record whether the KYC checks have been done or not.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Allowed values are YES, NO.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELF.CERTIFICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to determine whether the Reporting Financial Institution has obtained a self-certification as part of the account opening documentation to determine Account Holder’s Residence for tax purposes.</p>
        <p>This is mandatory for the customers opening by a Reporting Financial Institution after the Effective date of the regulation</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Applicable in case of the followings: Pre-existing Entity High,  New Individual Accounts, New Entity Accounts</p>
        <p>Allowed values are YES, NO.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BIRTH.INCORP.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to record the birth/incorporation date of the beneficial owner. In case of Individuals – Date of Birth, in case of Entities – Date of Incorporation. </p>
        <p> If this has been specified in the CUSTOMER table then that will be defaulted from there.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        <p>If BIRTH.INCORP.DATE is present in the CUSTOMER application, then the date specified in this field should be same with the Customer application.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BIRTH.INCORP.PLACE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to record the place of birth/incorporation place for the beneficial owner. In case of individuals - Place of Birth, in case of entities - Place of incorporation.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        <p>Must be a valid country code.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to specify the Tax Residence of the customer based on the self-certification.</p>
        <p>It will be an associated multi-valued field with the TAX.IDENTITY.NO in case of customers having more than one Tax Residence.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        <p>Must be a valid country code.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.IDENTITY.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>Allows to define the Tax Identification Number (TIN).</p>
        <p>It will be an associated multi-valued field with the TAX.RESIDENCE in case of customers having more than one TIN.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Alpha numeric characters are allowed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is associated with the ADDRESS.COUNTRY field and can be multi-valued.</p>
        <p>These fields are in line with Indicia checks for customer address.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p> Allowed values are Mail, Permanent, In Care, Hold Mail, PO Box.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESS.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to specify the country code for the specified address type.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Must be a valid country code.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TELEPHONE.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to record a valid Telephone Number of the customer.</p>
        <p>This field will be associated with the TELEPHONE.COUNTRY Field.</p>
        <P>These fields are in line with Indicia checks for telephone number.</P>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>ISD code should be separated with the '-' symbol.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TELEPHONE.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
        <p>System populates the country code from the PARTICIPANT.JUD field of CRS.PARAMETER, if the ISD code from TELEPHONE.NO field matches with the TELEPHONE.CODE defined in CRS.PARAMETER.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>No input field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STANDING.INSTRUCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the country codes, if the customer is having Standing Orders instructions.</p>
        <p>System has the logic to identify the Reporting Jurisdiction based on the parameter if standing order instruction has been given in that jurisdiction.</p>
        <p>This field can be multi-valued and in line with Indicia checks for standing order instruction.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Must be a valid country code.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POA.HOLDER.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to hold the country code for effective power of attorney or signatory authority granted to a person with an address in a Reportable Jurisdiction.</p>
        <p> This field can be multi-valued field and in line with the Indicia checks for the POA holder or signatory authority.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Must be a valid country code.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROLE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to specify the details of the controlling persons of Entity-Passive NFE.</p>
        <p>Allowed to input only when the CUSTOMER.TYPE field is selected as Entity-Passive NFE.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Values to be picked from EB.LOOKUP table.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>If the customer record exists for the controlling persons, then the ID of the particular customer record has to be specified in this field.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Valid customer number</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>If no customer record exists for the controlling person then name needs to be specified in this field.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Multi-lingual field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to hold the Unique ID reference for the controlling persons specified.</p>
        <p>The value contains two parts, first part should be CRS.CUST.SUPP.INFO ID, separator hyphen “-“, second part with sequence number.</p>
        <p>For example, if the record is being input for customer 100291, the CUSTOMER REFERENCE will be 100291-1 for the first beneficial owner</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Duplicate values in this field are not allowed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.OF.BIRTH</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to specify the Date of Birth of the Controlling person.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Mandatory when ROLE.TYPE is defined.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLACE.OF.BIRTH</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field used to specify the Place of Birth of the Controlling person.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Mandatory when ROLE.TYPE is defined.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RT.TAX.RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field used to specify the Tax Residence of the Controlling person.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Mandatory when ROLE.TYPE is defined.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to specify the Tax Identification of the Controlling person.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDICIA</field>
<desc>
        <p>System will populate 'YES' if any of the indicia's are met or else 'NO'.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>No input field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORTABLE.JUR.RES</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to store the residences of the Participating Jurisdictions after performing residential address check or electronic record search.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>No input field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.WAIVER.REC</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to record if a waiver document has been received by the Financial Institution from the customer if they want their account information to be Non-Reportable.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Allowed values are YES, NO.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRS.STATUS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to hold the status of the customer as Reportable or Non-reportable.</p>
        <p>User can change the system calculated value only once the system calculated value is populated.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Allowed values are Reportable, Non-Reportable and Inactive.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS.CHNG.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to hold the date on which the CRS.STATUS is changed to INACTIVE.</p>
        <p>This date is used for calculating the previous day's customer balances.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Date can't be less than today's date.</p>
        <p>Mandatory when the status is changed by the user.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGE.REASON</field>
<desc>
        <p>Descriptive field to record the reason, if the CRS.STATUS populated by the system is changed by the user..</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Mandatory when the status is changed by the user.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>