<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>PD</product>
<table>PD.PROV.EXCEPTION.LOG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The table is used to record Exceptions raised during Provision processing.</p>
            <p>Currently, exception is raised in the following scenario:</p>
            <p>When the asset classification  reaches the WRITE.OFF stage and the Underlying contract of the PD (the Parent LD/MG record) is not liquidated, system will not be able to FWOF the contract automatically and it raises an exception Log.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p />
            <p>Updated during COB.</p>
            <p>Records cleared based on the days set in EXC.PURGE.DAYS set in       ASSET.CLASS.PARAMETER.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ROUTINE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Actual routine within the Batch process which raised this Exception Log.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 35 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The PD contract ID which triggered this exception.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid key in PD.PAYMENT.DUE record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the Exception was raised. This field is also used by the system to check if the record had reached the maximum limit of purge days set on EXC.PURGE.DAYS stated in ASSET.CLASS.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual Exception log message is stored in this Field. The field is Multi-valued to store multiple lines of Exception message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 70 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Free text field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The account officer of the contract which triggered this exception would be recorded in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 10 Numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Should be a valid key to DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Application Product for which Exception log is raised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 3 Alphanumeric Characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BATCH.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Batch process which raised this Exception log.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid key to BATCH records.</p>
            <p>Maximum of 30 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The base file name which caused the exception log. Corrections should be carried out on this file Manually.</p>
            <p>For Provision, this file would be PD.PAYMENT.DUE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid T24 file names.</p>
            <p>Maximum of 35 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

