<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SY</product>
<table>SY.OTCGROI</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Input screen for an over the counter Guaranteed return of Investment</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency of the segregated account.</p>
            <p>This field is part of the currency/account pair that describes the segregated account which is              used for cash movements against the individual units of work.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in the CURRENCY table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date from which the interest Rate will apply</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A brief description of this deal</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the deal is input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the index will be observed and rate will be set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDEX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The index whose rate is to be observed on the Fix Date</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in the SC.INDICES table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which this deal matures</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The portfolio to which this deal belongs</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in the SEC.ACC.MASTER table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The interest Basis that is applicable to this deal</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.RATIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Ratio between the rise in the indices (above the threshold) and the final interest rate that will be applied on the Fix date.</p>
            <p>If the observed index is 4620 on the Fix date, the Threshold is 4200 and the Ratio is 1.5.</p>
            <p>This means that the FTSE is 10% above the threshold. The interest rate applied will be 1.5 x 10% = 15% for the term of the GROI</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THRESHOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The index of the indices above which the customer will begin to accrue interest.</p>
            <p>If the index is on or below this Threshold the Guaranteed Rate will be applied.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK</field>
<desc>
            <p>The dealer desk for this and any underlying deals</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GUARANTEE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum Guaranteed Rate of Return which will be applied to the pricipal amount for the term of the investment</p>
            <p>This rate will be applied if the index is less than or equal to the threshold on the Fix Date</p>
            <p>If this exceeds the Cap Rate then the Cap Rate will apply</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customers account to be used to fund the deal</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in the ACCOUNT table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The principal investment amount </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximum Rate that will apply</p>
            <p>If the Guarantee Rate or the rate calculated on the Fix Date are greater than the Cap Rate the Cap Rate will override the greater rate</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deposit Category for the deal.  This must be a valid category for MM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>