<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IA</product>
<table>EB.CASHFLOW.HIS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The EB.CASHFLOW.HIS is the central data repository of the cash flow engine.  It maintains the history for EB.CASHFLOW</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXPECTED.LIFE.END</field>
<desc>
        <p>Updates the expected life end date from the expected term date contracts. </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.CFLOW.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to identify the type of cash flow.</p>
            <p>Example: Principal, Interest, Charge, Commission etc.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EIR.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will have a flag to indicate whether EIR calculation is required or not.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.ASSET.TYP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the IFRS asset type for which the below IFRS adjustment amount are calculated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.COLL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to denote the value of the collateral assigned to this contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the event that led to the change in the cash flow. </p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.CFLOW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to denote the expected cash flow amount post impairment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXLD.FROM.EIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the cash flows which are not considered for EIR calculation or for any IFRS related calculations.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The cash flows which are marked EXLD.FROM.EIR are only for informative purpose.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECLASSIFIED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.FLOW.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denoting the type of cash flow.</p>
            <p>Example: Principal, Interest, Commission.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTSTANDING.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the outstanding amount to the bank as on the rate fix date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAKEOVER.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the contract is taken over to IFRS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the market rate for the contract.</p>
            <p>This can either be a ID in PERIODIC.INTEREST table or the actual rate itself.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.FLOW.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the date of the cash flow.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.IMPAIRED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that a contract has been impaired for the first time and impairment loss has been raised, status becomes ‘IMPAIRED’</p>
            <p />
            <p>This date will not change even when the contracts becomes ‘UNIMPAIRED’</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the contract is ‘UNIMPAIRED’ and is then  ‘IMPAIRED’ again, then the date will change to the date it is impaired again.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the INTEREST.BASIS of the underlying contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the contract currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHORISER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.UNIMPAIRED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that a contract has been unimpaired, status has moved from ‘IMPAIRED’ to ‘UNIMPAIRED’</p>
            <p />
            <p>This date is not changed until the contract is ‘UNIMPAIRED’ again.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.CFLOW.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to denote the currency of the expected cash flow.</p>
            <p>Reserved for future.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLAT.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to hold the Collateral percentage  from  the corresponding Collateral.right</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRFT.LOSS.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes whether a contract is fetching profit or loss to a bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMPAIRMENT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to denote the status of the contract with respect to impairment.</p>
            <p>Below are the possible values,</p>
            <p />
            <p>IMPAIR.EVIDENCE : Evidence of impairment but no loss or no impairment accounting raised.</p>
            <p />
            <p>IMPAIRED : Evidence of impairment with loss and impairment accounting raised. </p>
            <p />
            <p>UNIMPAIRED : No longer evidence of impairment and impairment loss has been reversed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>WRITE-OFF : When the contract is written off.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMPAIR.EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.IAS.SUB.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the previous IFRS.SUB.TYPE under which this contract was classified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the OPERAND which will be used along with MARKET.MARGIN.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example: +/-  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING.DETAILS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will have the IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS ID, which will be updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLL.EXPIRY.DAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field that will hold  the expiry date of the collateral as defined in COLLATERAL.RIGHT</p>
            <p />
            <p>This is not inputtable</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMPAIRMENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides the key to the table IFRS.IMPAIRMENT.CODE which denotes the reason for the impairment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.EXLD.EIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the cash flows which are not considered for EIR calculation or for any IFRS related calculations.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The cash flows which are marked EXLD.FROM.EIR are only for informative purpose.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.COLL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to denote the date on which the collateral can be realised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.FIX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the date from which the new rate, in case of a rate fixing contract, will be applicable.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLL.RATE.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to define how to Calculate the value of Collateral  under the Amortised method</p>
            <p>The possible values are:</p>
            <p>STRAIGHT: This is to use the Collateral Amount as it is held in EXP.COLL.AMT or RECOVERABLE.AMT</p>
            <p />
            <p>EIR: This is to do an NPV of the Collateral details held in Collateral Date and EXP.COLL.AMT or RECOVERABLE.AMT using the EIR of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MARKET: To do an NPV of the collateral details  at the Market Rate</p>
            <p>Blank – If left blank, the default value ‘EIR’ will be defaulted.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IAS.CLASSIFICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the IAS.CLASSIFICATION id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IAS.SUB.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the IFRS.SUB.TYPE id assigned to this contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.IMP.EVIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that a contract has been impaired for the first time but for which no impairment loss has been raised, status becomes ‘IMPAIR.EVIDENCE’</p>
            <p />
            <p>This date will not change even when the contract becomes ‘IMPAIRED’</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLL.RATE.FV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to define how to Calculate the value of Collateral  under the fair value method</p>
            <p>The possible values are:</p>
            <p>STRAIGHT: This is to use the Collateral Amount as it is held in EXP.COLL.AMT or RECOVERABLE.AMT</p>
            <p />
            <p>EIR: This is to do an NPV of the Collateral details held in Collateral Date and EXP.COLL.AMT or RECOVERABLE.AMT using the EIR of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MARKET: To do an NPV of the collateral details  at the Market Rate</p>
            <p>Blank – If left blank, the default value ‘MARKET’ will be defaulted.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.LIAB.IND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will have the Asset and Liability indicator, which will be updated based on the initial sign of the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASHFLOW.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID will be similar to the EB.CONTRACT.BALANCES id concatenated with semicolon and curr number</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECOVERABLE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field that denotes the maximum amount that can be recovered from the collateral.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARRY.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the net present value of the contract as per the ASSET.TYPE.</p>
            <p>This field along with ASSET.TYPE form a multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALC.LOGIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields EVENT.TYPE and RECALC.METHOD will form a multi-value set, where different events related to cash flow amendments can be given along with the recalculation methods. The two recalculation methods which can be specified are EIR and CARRY.COST. When the recalculation method is specified as EIR, the system will recalculate the EIR in case of a cash flow change whereas the system will adjust the carrying amount of the contract when the recalculation method is specified as CARRY.COST.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLATERAL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denotes a valid Collateral that is used for impairment loss calculation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMD.PRV.MON.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the IFRS adjustment amount for the previous month.</p>
            <p>Changes to the contractual cash flows triggers IFRS amendment processing. Entries for this amount will be raised during cob.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDITOR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMENDMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>In case of an amendment to the cash flow, this field will hold the date on which the amendment happened. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:</p>
            <p>This field will not contain the system date. It holds the date of amendment as per the cash flow.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the value date of the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flexibility is given to the user through the field MARKET.MARGIN to include margin as a percentage of the market rate in to the calculation of the fair value. Both positive and negative margin percentage can be inputted. </p>
            <p />
            <p>For example if the market rate is 10%. With the positive margin of +0.50%, the net rate for the calculation will be 10.50% and with a negative margin of -0.50%, the net rate for the calculation will be 9.50%.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denoting the overall status of the EB.CASHFLOW record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the maturity date of the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNTING.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will have the IFRS.ACCT.METHODS ID, which will be updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denoting the accrual method followed by the underlying contract.</p>
            <p>This field will provide the link to the table EB.ACCRUAL.PARAM which determines how accruals are performed by the core accrual processing.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION.NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to denote the additional notes to justify the actions taken on the EB.CASHFLOW record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMD.CUR.MON.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the IFRS adjustment amount for the current month.</p>
            <p>Changes to the contractual cash flows triggers IFRS amendment processing. Entries for this amount will be raised during cob.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denotes the customer related to the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.CFLOW.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to denote the date on which the cash flow is expected post impairment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAKEOVER.NPV</field>
<desc>
            <p>Either EIR or NPV would have been inputted in EB.CASHFLOW.CAPTURE. If EIR is given, corresponding NPV is calculated and stored in this field. This NPV would be used to recalculate EIR, during amendment to the contract. </p>
            <p>Otherwise the NPV that was given in EB.CASHFLOW.CAPTURE will be updated in this field directly</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.IAS.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the previous IFRS classification under which this contract was classified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASHFLOW.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the Rate used in the underlying contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.FLOW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be a signed amount from the point of view of the bank. For example a loan disbursement will be a negative amount and a repayment will be a positive amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMD.PRV.YR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the IFRS adjustment amount for the previous year.</p>
            <p>Changes to the contractual cash flows triggers IFRS amendment processing. Entries for this amount will be raised during cob.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALC.COMPLETED</field>
<desc>
            <p>When there is a amendment to the cash flow, system raises adjustment entries through the service IFRS.AMENDMENT.SERVICE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Upon completion of the service, this field will be updated as "YES".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the application that triggered the change to the EB.CASHFLOW record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDIT.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMPAIRMENT.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denotes the IMPAIRMENT LOSS calculated for this contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FEED.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to denote how the collateral value is arrived during impairment calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Options : AUTOMATIC or NOFEED.</p>
            <p />
            <p>AUTOMATIC: Collateral amount will be calculated  automatically each time impairment provisioning is run.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NOFEED: Collateral amount will not be calculated each time and the initial amount will be taken for impairment provisioning.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 audit field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field hold the asset type like AMORTISED and FAIRVALUE.</p>
            <p>This field will only be updated in case of an amendment to cash flow's.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will store the effective rate of interest calculated based on the information supplied to the EB.CASHFLOW.HANDOFF by the applications.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

