<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IA</product>
<table>EB.CASHFLOW.CAPTURE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application EB.CASHFLOW.CAPTURE will take care of updating EB.CASHFLOW capture for existing contracts in the system. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This application will update the EB.CASHFLOW initially and link the contract to update the cash flow and thereafter by updating the fields IAS.CLASSIFICATION and IFRS.SUB.TYPE. On running the service BNK/IFRS.CAPTURE.SERVICE, the EB.CASHFLOW.CAPTURE record will be converted to EB.CASHFLOW record.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>IAS.CLASSIFICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the IAS.CLASSIFICATION id.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will store the effective rate of interest of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Either AMC or EIR must be inputted but not both.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be a signed amount from the point of view of the bank. For example a loan disbursement will be a negative amount and a repayment will be a positive amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Will be updated by system only if the field POPULATE.CASHFLOW is set as "YES"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes any error that occurs during the service IFRS.CAPTURE.SERVICE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXC.FROM.EIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the cash flows which are not considered for EIR calculation or for any IFRS related calculations.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The cash flows which are marked EXLD.FROM.EIR are only for informative purpose.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Will be updated by system only if the field POPULATE.CASHFLOW is set as "YES"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.FIX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the date from which the new rate, in case of a rate fixing contract, will be applicable.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the INTEREST.BASIS of the underlying contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field.</p>
            <p>Will be updated by system only if the field POPULATE.CASHFLOW is set as "YES"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the market rate for the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This can either be a ID in PERIODIC.INTEREST table or the actual rate itself.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POPULATE.CASHFLOW</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this field POPULATE.CASHFLOW is set as ‘YES’, system will get the static, rate and cash flow information and will populate it to EB.CASHFLOW.CAPTURE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>If this field POPULATE.CASHFLOW is set as ‘N’, system expects the user to provide the cash flow information as well as the rate and static information.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the contract currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field. </p>
            <p>Will be updated by system only if the field POPULATE.CASHFLOW is set as "YES"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IAS.SUB.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the key to IFRS.SUB.TYPE file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the Rate of the underlying contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field.</p>
            <p>Will be updated by system only if the field POPULATE.CASHFLOW is set as "YES"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTSTANDING.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the outstanding amount to the bank as on the rate fix date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.HEAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field hold the asset type like AMORTISED, FAIRVALUE or DISCLOSURE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the Amortised cost amount used for the calculation of EIR.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If AMC Balance is inputted then with that and all the future cash flows for the contract, the system will calculate the EIR.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Either AMC or EIR must be inputted but not both.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPTURE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of EB.CASHFLOW.CAPTURE contains two components.</p>
            <p>The first component is the application name.</p>
            <p>The second components is the key to the record in the application.</p>
            <p>Both these components are separated by '*'</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example:</p>
            <p />
            <p>LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS*LD0033500001</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the date of the cash flow.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Will be updated by system only if the field POPULATE.CASHFLOW is set as "YES"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the OPERAND which will be used along with MARKET.MARGIN.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example: +/- </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flexibility is given to the user through the field MARKET.MARGIN to include margin as a percentage of the market rate in to the calculation of the fair value. Both positive and negative margin percentage can be inputted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>For example if the market rate is 10%. With the positive margin of +0.50%, the net rate for the calculation will be 10.50% and with a negative margin of -0.50%, the net rate for the calculation will be 9.50%.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t><field>EXPECTED.END.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
