<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IA</product>
<table>IFRS.ACCT.BALANCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table will store the accrued balances (calculated balances) for different asset types per contract.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LCY.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the previous balance of an asset type in Local Currency for Foreign currency contracts</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.CALC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the last calculated amount for the asset type.</p>
            <p>The summation of this field and the amount in the balance field will give you the current balance of the asset type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.CALC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the date at which the LAST.CALC.AMT was calculated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.CON.CF.FV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the NPV of the contractual cash flow under FairValue method, i.e. at Market Rate</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.EXP.CF.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the NPV of the expected cash flow  under Amortised cost, i.e. at EIR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LST.CAL.LCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the last calculated amount for the asset type in Local currency for foreign currency contracts</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.EXP.COLL.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value of the expected collateral under Amortised cost method</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.EXP.COLL.FV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value of the expected collateral under fairvalue method</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.EXP.CF.FV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the NPV of expected cash flow under fairvalue method, i.e. Market Rate</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.CON.CF.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the NPV of the contractual cash flow under Amortised cost method, i.e at  EIR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.BALANCES.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will be the id of the underlying contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.HEAD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the Asset types namely AMORTISED, FAIRVALUE, DISCLOSURE, IMPAIR.AMORTISED, UNWIND or IMPAIR.AMC.ADJUST.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the previous balance of an asset type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denotes the T24 book value of the contract.</p>
            <p>Once a contract is impaired, this field will also include the balances of the Past due record related to the contract if any.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGED.CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds all the Hedged contract numbers defined under a particular Hedge group relation.</p>
            <p>Denotes the associative set for HEDGED.BOOK.COST and HEDGED.FAIR.VALUE fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGED.BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field holds the book cost of each contract for the Hedged items defined under IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
            <p>Associated with the HEDGED.CONTRACT.ID field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGED.FAIR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field holds the fair value of each contract for the Hedged items defined under IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
            <P>Associated with the HEDGED.CONTRACT.ID field.</P>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGING.CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds all the Hedging contract numbers defined under a particular Hedge group relation.</p>
            <p>Denotes the associative set for HEDGING.BOOK.COST and HEDGING.FAIR.VALUE fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGING.BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field holds the book cost of each contract for the Hedging items defined under IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
            <p>Associated with the HEDGING.CONTRACT.ID field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGING.FAIR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field holds the fair value of each contract for the Hedging items defined under IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
            <p>Associated with the HEDGING.CONTRACT.ID field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denotes the Hedge status for the Hedge relation defined in IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

