<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IA</product>
<table>IFRS.ACCT.METHODS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>IFRS.ACCT.METHODS stores the accounting methods to be applied for different kinds of contracts based on the classification of the assets and liabilities. This is kept as a separate table so that the users can do the setup based on their requirements.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NPV.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>NPV.RATE forms part of a multi-value set to specify the rate type applicable to the calculation, which can be an EIR rate or a MARKET rate. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field will be input only if NPV.METHOD is set to YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.ACCT.METHODS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Meaningful Alpha numeric id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>NPV.METHOD forms part of a multi-value set to specify if the Net Present Value (NPV) calculation is required based on the IAS.CLASSIFICATION and the accounting method specified. If NPV calculation is not required, an option to the user to include an external routine to calculate the amount will be given through the field CALC.RTN.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>POSTING.REQD forms part of a multi-value set to give an option to the bank on whether the values need to be calculated only, or calculated and posted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provides the option to enter a meaningful description for the Accounting Method.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.TO.EXLD</field>
<desc>
        <p>A Valid record from the table AC.BALANCE.TYPE with REPORTING.TYPE as ‘VIRTUAL’. This is to define the balance types to exclude from the T24 balance calculation.
</p>
        <p>Validation:
</p>
        <p>The normal accounting heads AMORTISED, FAIRVALUE and DISCLOSURE will have the same AC.BALANCE.TYPE record attached to the new field BAL.TO.EXLD. All normal accounting heads will uniformly follow a single T24 balance.
</p>
        <p>When the field BAL.TO.EXLD is populated for “AMORTISED” accounting head and left blank for “FAIRVALUE” or “DISCLOSURE”, system will default the BAL.TO.EXLD from AMORTISED to other normal accounting heads. 
</p>
        <p>The impair accounting heads IMPAIR.AMORTISED, UNWIND, IMPAIR.AMC.ADJUST, AMORTISED.UNDER.IMP, IMPAIR.FAIRVALUE, IMPAIR.FV.ADJ.INC, IMPAIR.FV.ADJ.DEC will have a common BAL.TO.EXLD value. Any value which is different will invoke error.
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.HEAD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>ACCT.HEAD.TYPE forms part of a multi-value set to specify the asset types, which can be FAIRVALUE, AMORTISED, DISCLOSURE, IMPAIR.AMORTISED, UNWIND, IMPAIR.AMC.ADJUST, IMPAIR.FAIRVALUE, AMORTISED.UNDER.IMP, IMPAIR.FV.ADJ.INC or IMPAIR.FV.ADJ.DEC.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Also holds the hedge asset types HEDGED.EFFECTIVE, HEDGING.EFFECTIVE, HEDGED.INEFFECTIVE, HEDGING.INEFFECTIVE, HEDGED.CLOSED.RELATION, HEDGING.CLOSED.RELATION</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>For example for Fair value in equity – the idea is to post EIR accrual to PL and the difference between the EIR accruals and the fair value estimation to Equity. </p>
            <p />
            <p>So we need a asset type called AMORTISED – where EIR accrual will be calculated as the NPV at EIR rate and the difference between the contract posting and the calculated posting will need to be posted as an adjustment. </p>
            <p />
            <p>After this we need to have a fair value estimation say FAIRVALUE – the calculation would be the NPV at market rate – and the posting would be the difference between contract posting, EIR posting and the calculated amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>So in order to ensure this happens asset type for AMORTISED needs to be defined before FAIRVALUE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Hedge related asset types are allowed only when 'IH' product is installed in the company.</p>
            <p>If HEDGED.EFFECTIVE is defined, then system validates for HEDGING.EFFECTIVE also to be defined</p>            
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUST.ENTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>ADJUST.ENTRY forms part of a multi-value set to indicate whether the entry to be posted will be an adjustment to what has already been posted for the contract by IFRS. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>It will be input only for contracts which are classified under fairvalue through equity.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

