<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IA</product>
<table>IFRS.SUB.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table will contain the details relating to IFRS.ACCT.METHODS &amp; IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS along with the details relating to the amendments to the cash flows and EIR, if any.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>IFRS.SUB.TYPE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any meaningful alpha numeric id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS table.</p>
            <p>IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS will store the details relating to the way the accounting entries will be generated in order to make the contracts compatible with the IFRS requirements. This is kept as a separate table so that the user can do the setup based on their requirements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALC.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This forms a Multi-value set with EVENT.TYPE. This field denotes the recalculation method to be used in the case of an associated EVENT being triggered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Inputs are CARRY.COST &amp; EIR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TERM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Option for determining calculation of the EIR and amortised cost (i.e. do we calculate up to the next rate fix date if we know it or the maturity date)</p>
            <p>When the field TERM is set as “None” or “Full’, the system will calculate the EIR for the entire term of the contract. This will be applicable mainly in case of the fixed rate contracts, where the contract rate remains unchanged throughout the life of the contract.</p>
            <p>When the field TERM is set as “Short”, the system will calculate the EIR up to the next rate fixing date and income will be amortised over this period. When the next rate is fixed a new EIR will be calculated for the next amortisation period.</p>
            <p>When the field TERM is set as EXPECTED it means this is applicable for contracts with an expected term.</p>
            <p>The Expected term details will be passed to the Cashflow engine. Cashflow engine will consolidate the contractual cashflows to fit into the expected term for a set of cashflows required for the EIR calculation. All contractual cashflows beyond the  expected life end (based on the Expected term and the Start date) will be consolidated under the expected life end.</p>
            <p>The system will calculate the EIR up to the expected life end date, and the Amortised cost will be calculated as the NPV of the cashflows till the Expected life end.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Valid Inputs are SHORT, FULL and EXPECTED.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNTING.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the Key to IFRS.ACCT.METHODS record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>IFRS.ACCT.METHODS will store the accounting methods to be applied for different kinds of contracts based on the classification of the assets and liabilities. This is kept as a separate table so that the user can do the setup based on their requirements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.RECALC.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default recalculation method during cash flow changes for the contracts falling under this sub type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the SUBTYPE record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to IFRS.EVENT.TYPE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

