<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IA</product>
<table>IFRS.ACCOUNTING.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>IFRS.ACCOUNTING.DETAILS holds the details of the various components used for the calculation of IFRS entries.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CURR.NUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the current number of this record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the balance of the corresponding ACCT.HEAD on the date this record was created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.EXP.CF.FV</field>
<desc>
            <p>To hold the NPV of expected cash flow under fairvalue method, i.e. Market Rate</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.EXP.COLL.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>To hold the total value of the collateral under Amortised cost method.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.EXP.CF.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>To hold the NPV of the expected cash flow  under Amortised cost, i.e. at EIR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.LCY.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local equivalent for the field IFRS.BALANCE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.CON.CF.AMORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>To hold the NPV of the contractual cash flow under Amortised cost method, i.e at  EIR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.EXP.COLL.FV</field>
<desc>
            <p>To hold the total value of the collateral under fair value method</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NPV.CON.CF.FV</field>
<desc>
            <p>To hold the NPV of the contractual cash flow under FairValue method, i.e. at Market Rate</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.DTLS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to IFRS.ACCOUNTING.DETAILS contains two components.</p>
            <p>The first component is the contract id.</p>
            <p>The second component is the date on which the record was created.</p>
            <p>The two components are separated by -.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example:</p>
            <p />
            <p>LD0033500001-20001130</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.HEAD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the Asset types namely AMORTISED, FAIRVALUE or DISCLOSURE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASHFLOW.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the version of the EB.CASHFLOW record used for the calculation of the entries or IFRS.BALANCE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total EB.CONTRACT.BALANCES till PERIOD.END excluding IF entries. Once a contract is impaired, this field will also contain the balance of the past due record in ECB related to the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGED.CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds all the Hedged contract numbers defined under a particular Hedge group relation.</p>
            <p>Denotes the associative set for HEDGED.BOOK.COST and HEDGED.FAIR.VALUE fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGED.BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field holds the book cost of each contract for the Hedged items defined under IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
            <p>Associated with the HEDGED.CONTRACT.ID field, in order to represent the book cost for the corresponding contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGED.FAIR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field holds the fair value of each contract for the Hedged items defined under IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
            <P>Associated with the HEDGED.CONTRACT.ID field, in order to represent the fair value for the corresponding contract..</P>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGING.CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds all the Hedging contract numbers defined under a particular Hedge group relation.</p>
            <p>Denotes the associative set for HEDGING.BOOK.COST and HEDGING.FAIR.VALUE fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGING.BOOK.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field holds the book cost of each contract for the Hedging items defined under IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
            <p>Associated with the HEDGING.CONTRACT.ID field, in order to represent the book cost for the corresponding contract</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGING.FAIR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field holds the fair value of each contract for the Hedging items defined under IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
            <p>Associated with the HEDGING.CONTRACT.ID field, in order to represent the fair value for the corresponding contract</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field denotes the Hedge status for the Hedge relation defined in IAS.HEDGE.GROUP table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

