<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>BC.SORT.CODE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application contains details of bank sort codes used in the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>The length and type of the bank sort codes are checked against the input defined on the FT.BC.PARAMETER file. The maximum and minimum length allowed are defined in field SORT.CODE.LEN and the character type is defined in field SORT.CODE.TYPE. </p>
            <p>All sort codes should be loaded, as any sort code entered in the system will be verified against this file. </p>
            <p>Information concerning the bank using the sort code can be specified, as can a link to the CUSTOMER file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains a code that points to the EXPOSURE.CONDITION file record that defines the exposure ladder rules for the sort code in view. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>If entered must be a valid EXPOSURE.CONDITIONS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the financial institution. </p>
            <p>This field will be used as the enrichment of the sort code when input in the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-35 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Local Reference field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TELEPHONE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Telephone number of the financial institution. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-16 alphanumeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SORT.CODE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Alternative sort code number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This may be used as alternative key when referring to the sort code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Address and/or post code of the financial institution. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 alphanumeric characters. (Optional input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SORT.CODE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.DATE.PRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Similar to field VALUE.DATE.PRD for accepting default exposure date.</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 8 characters may be entered.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE.PRD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies for the TELLER, FUNDS TRANSFER and DATA.CAPTURE Application, the Default Value Date which will be assigned to all transactions where this Transaction code has been defined. This Default Value Date can always be overridden by entering the Value Date directly at transaction level. </p>
            <p>If Y, or N(O) are entered the inputs (a) to (f) are not allowed. </p>
            <p>(a), (bb), (c) specify the number of calendar or working days to be added/subtracted to/from the Run Date in order to obtain the Default Value Date as follows: </p>
            <p>(a) + If days are to be added to the Run Date. The '+' sign should normally be used for credit Entries. - If days are to be subtracted from the Run Date. The '-' sign should normally be used for Debit entries. </p>
            <p>(bb) 01-99Indicates the number of days to be added or subtracted. </p>
            <p>(c) C If (bb) are calendar days, W If (bb) are working days. </p>
            <p>If it is necessary to add/subtract any other days to those specified in (bb) before obtaining the Default Value Date then (d), (ee), (f) are used as follows: </p>
            <p>(d) As for (a) previously. </p>
            <p>(ee) As for (bb) previously. </p>
            <p>(f) C If ee are calendar days. W If ee are working days. </p>
            <p>It must be noted that the day type ('C' or 'W') can only be used once in an equation. </p>
            <p>Note: It is important to realise that the conditions defined in this field are only Applicable for the applications named above. All other Applications have their Value Date conditions defined by their own tables. </p>
            <p>This field allows a Default Value Date to be specified for a TELLER , FUNDS.TRANSFER and DATA.CAPTURE transaction either, equal to the Run Date, or the Run Date plus or minus a number of working or calendar days. This prevents the operator from having to key the Value Date on transactions repeatedly, where a default can be applied. It can be overridden at Transaction level when required. For the DATA CAPTURE application field only this default is also used for the exposure date as well as the value date.</p>
            <p>Example: +03W will mean that the default value date is 3 working days forward from the Run Date. </p>
            <p>+01C + 02W will mean that the default value date is 1 calendar day + 2 working days forward from the Run date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Y If the Default Value Date is to be the Run Date. or         N(O) If a Default Value Date is not to be generated         automatically. Value Date must then be input manually         when Transaction Code is used. or (a) (bb) (c) (d) (ee)         (f) As defined in the example below </p>
            <p>Run Date is the date of the data being processed which         may not always be today's date. If different, the Run         Date is displayed next to the User ID on the screen.</p>
            <p>The same day type ('C' or 'W') can only be used once in         an equation ie. +01C + 02C will not be accepted.</p>
            <p>When both working and calendar days are entered, the sign         must be the same i.e. +01C - 02W will not be accepted.</p>
            <p>It is not necessary to enter the '+-' signs. If omitted         it will always default to '+'</p>
            <p>This default overtakes any previous default set up i.e.         takes presidence over the transaction code default.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BC.SORT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sort code of the financial institution in the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>For more details refer to the helptext for FT.BC.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 characters are allowed.  The actual maximum and minimum number of characters allowed are defined on the FT.BC.PARAMETER file in field SORT.CODE.LEN and the type of characters is defined in SORT.CODE.TYPE.  (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQS.COLL.SUSP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will specify the suspense account category to be used in posting the cheque proceeds of those cheques that have been processed through the cheque collection system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>If entered must be a valid category code between the         range 10000-19999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQS.RET.SUSP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will specify the suspense account category to be used in posting the cheque proceeds for those cheques that have been returned within the processing of the cheque collection system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>If entered must be a valid category code between the         range 10000-19999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Customer number within the T24 system of the financial institution. </p>
            <p>This field allows a sort code to be linked to a T24 customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6  numeric customer number                or 3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

