<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>BGC.STATIC</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>A work file holding a record for each customer whose static details or account details have changed since the last outgoing tape was produced. This file is updated by the applications ACCOUNT, CUSTOMER and ACCOUNT.BGC.INFO. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the old country of residence of the customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type SSS(uppercase alpha) Country code characters. Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING.RESTRICT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains posting restriction from the corresponding old account record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 or 2 numeric character Posting Restriction code.  Associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to BLOCK.CODE.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTCODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the old TOWN and COUNTRY field from the customer record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type s (uppercase alpha or numeric characters) Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains an update date specify what changes have happened to the account. </p>
            <p>This code is in the range 1 to 4: </p>
            <p>          1  indicates this is a new account.           2  indicates modifications to an existing account.           3  indicates an account closure.           4  indicates the reopening of an old account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multivalued field up to 1 numeric characters.  Associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to BLOCK.CODE.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id of the customer whose static details have changed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Must be valid ID on the customer file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the second part of the TOWN COUNTRY field from the customer record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains account numbers of the customer whose static details have changed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multivalued field up to 16 numeric characters.  Associated with field range UPDATE.CODE to BLOCK.CODE.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the old street from the customer record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains CPARTY REQUIRED flag from the corresponding old ACCOUNT BGC INFO record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric characters. Associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to WENST.ADRESSEN. Externally updated only.</p>
            <p>2-digit block code as defined on BGC.BLOCK.CODE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRANCH.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the branch number from the corresponding account record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multivalued field up to 5 numeric characters.  Associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to BLOCK.CODE.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the old SHORT.NAME from the customer file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters. Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WENST.ADRESSEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains CPARTY REQUIRED flag from the corresponding old ACCOUNT BGC INFO record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>YES or NO.  Associated with field range ACCOUNT.NUMBER to BLOCK.CODE.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

