<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>CURRENCY.MARKET</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The Markets defined on this table are used to identify the correct exchange and revaluation Rates to be applied to each Currency.  Different Rates are used in instances where specific Currency Markets exists, e.g. Financial and Convertible markets or where pricing considerations require separate Rates, e.g. Normal Market Rates/Notes/Travellers Cheques. </p>
            <p>Up to nine Currency Markets can be created for each Currency but where only one market exists, this should be defined as 1, which is the default used by other Applications, e.g. DATA.CAPTURE, FUNDS.TRANSFER, etc. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the code by which this Currency Market can be identified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)  The code must be in the range 1-99 and represents the ID of the table.  At present only Currency Market 1 is allowed.</p>
            <p>If a market &gt;= 10, the market indicated in the first digit must be already present on the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Currency Market and is used for enrichment of the Code. </p>
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Currency Market in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 character, type A (Alphanumeric).  Multilanguage field.  Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPREAD.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Included in G13.1.02)</p>
            <p />
            <p>The name of a local routine that can be used to determine a customer spread. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The routine m</p>
            <p>ust be defined as a type S program on the PGM.FILE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The name of local routine should be defined on the PGM.FILE as an S type     program</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

