<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>CURRENCY.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains the common details for each individual Currency. These details are the Numeric Currency Code, Currency Name, Number of Decimal Places and the Interest Basis. </p>
            <p>This table is used to ensure that the same numeric code and no of decimals are used on all the different currency files. For in a multi company environment there can be more than one currency file. </p>
            <p>The Currency name and Interest basis maybe changed at an individual Currency file level. </p>
            <p>The numeric currency code can only be changed on this file (CURRENCY.PARAM). </p>
            <p>Once a record has been authorised the number of decimal places cannot be changed. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EQUIVALENT.CCYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a currency that is equivalent to the currency defined in field CURRENCY.CODE. </p>
            <p>A relationship must be established to enable currencies to be used as interest or charge currencies on any accounts set-up for the main currency. </p>
            <p>This field will be used as a default on the CURRENCY table. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters        or 1-3 numeric characters.  Multivalue field. (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>Input must be an ID of a record on the CURRENCY.PARAM file.</p>
            <p>Input must be different from the contents of field CURRENCY.CODE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRECIOUS.METAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency as a precious metal or not. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 - 3 alphabetic characters (YES or NO)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMERIC.CCY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the numeric code which corresponds to the alpha ID.  This code must be unique and provides an alternative means of referencing the Currency details in T24 Applications. </p>
            <p>The code may be set by banks currently using Numeric Currency Codes thus allowing these same codes to continue in use (in effect acting as a translation table).  It could, alternatively, be set to standard codes used in a particular Country for central bank reporting, etc.  Another use is to set these codes according to the frequency of use of the various Currencies.  If, most transactions are, for example, in US dollars, Deutsche Marks and Belgian francs you could the Numeric Currency Codes could be allocated as follows: </p>
            <p>           1 : to US Dollar            2 : to Deutsche Mark            3 : to Belgian Franc </p>
            <p>These short codes can then be used in Transaction Processing Applications to minimise the input required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters, including 0.  This will allow a maximum number of 999 currency codes.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.DECIMALS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Number of Decimal places of the Currency. </p>
            <p>Used to verify that amounts are not entered with decimal places exceeding the number entered in this field. All calculations, e.g. interest, charges, revaluation etc., will be rounded to the Number of Decimal places specified in this field. When the amount fields are displayed, they will also be shown with their corresponding decimals. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character in the range 0 to 4. (Optional input; Default value = 2 decimals.) When the user is creating a new Currency code, this field will already indicate the default value of 2. If the Currency you are creating does not have 2 decimals (e.g. Italian Lira, Japanese Yen), this default value must be changed to the appropriate number of decimals. Once the Currency code has been authorised, the value of this field cannot be changed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECIMAL.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>To define the Description of the decimal places of a Currency. A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. 
Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines for each Currency the <strong>default</strong> calculation basis for interest calculation purposes. This is used <strong>solely</strong> to populate the feld on the actual CURRENCY record. It is then possible to set the interest basis at contract or record level, the absence user input will mean that the value from the appropriate CURRENCY record will be used.</p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>Key</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Days/Denominator</strong>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>A</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>B</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>C</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>D</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>E</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>F</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>For illustrations of all supported </p>
            <p>INTEREST.BASIS</p> types see: <a href="INTEREST.BASIS_data.htm">INTEREST.BASIS</a><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>1 type SSS (Uppercase alpha) character in the range A-F.         (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.CCY.RANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether a currency should always be the base currency for currency conversions, in the event that a base currency has not been supplied. </p>
            <p>Each currency can optionally be assigned a unique base currency rank in the same manner as currency rank. The values are stored in the application RANK.BASE.CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>If two currencies are involved in a conversion and both have a base ccy rank defined then the currency with the lowest rank will take preference. </p>
            <p>N.B. It has been stated that rates to the EURO (EUR) will always be quoted      as the number of other currency units to 1 EUR, even when 1 unit of      the other currency is worth more than 1 EUR. </p>
            <p>For example assuming that 0.71 GBP were worth 1 EUR then the effect of not supplying a base currency or rate to the conversion routine would result in the base currency being set to GBP and the rate  expressed as the inverse of 0.71 i.e 1.408451. </p>
            <p>Setting the EUR to have a base currency rank of 1 would result in the EUR being the base currency and the rate to be 0.71. </p>
            <p>Great care should be taken when setting the currency rank, there are very few instances where a rank needs to be set, for example the EURO as described. </p>
            <p>Another example would be a local currency conversion from a currency where rates are quoted as number of units of foreign to 1 local (even when the rate is less than 1) to the EURO, e.g. IEP to EUR. </p>
            <p>The system will default the base currency  for cross rates to be that currency which has a rate greater than 1, e.g. </p>
            <p>local ccy = EUR      CCY1 = IEP, 0.8 to 1 EUR      CCY2 = GBP, 0.7 to 1 EUR </p>
            <p>If no base currency is supplied then the system will default the base to be GBP and the cross rate to be 0.8 / 0.7 =  1.142857142857. </p>
            <p>If IEP is set to have a base currency rank and GBP is not then the base currency will be set to IEP and the rate to be 0.875. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 character numeric.  Optional input.  If this field is changed then the relevant currency record must be input and authorised for the change to take effect.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the name of the Currency and will be used for on-line enrichments in any field where the Currency alpha or numeric code has been input. </p>
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the Currency code in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table, and will indicate to the user the language in which the description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type AA (Alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters.  Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the country to which the currency defined in field CURRENCY.CODE belongs to. </p>
            <p>If no input is made to this field then the default value will be the first two characters of the contents of field CURRENCY.CODE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters.  (Optional input. See Details for default value.)  If this value is changed then the corresponding currency record should be input and authorised.</p>
            <p>Input must be an ID of a record on the COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the alpha code by which the Currency can be identified in Transaction Processing Applications. </p>
            <p>The ID which can be used in any Application to reference the currency within a transaction, must be in uppercase alpha format. It is recommended to use the standard SWIFT currency codes for the definition of the ID.  In some Applications (e.g. FUNDS.TRANSFER) a Currency code has been hardcoded in the program and the SWIFT currency code has always been used.  e.g. "USD" is hardcoded in some programs.  If you decide not to use the SWIFT Currency codes then modifications will need to be incorporated into some of the programs. </p>
            <p>A NUMERIC.CCY.CODE is also available and can be used as an alternate means to input the Currency code in Transaction Processing Applications. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

