<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>DE.I.FT.TXN.TYPES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to default the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION while processing Inward Swift  messages based on a criteria  for different Message Types which will be used for generating appropriate messages, Transaction Codes etc.</p>
            <p>Different FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION types can be defined here by multivalues and appropriate TXN.TYPE will be taken based on the matching criteria.</p>
            <p>See the user guide for more details.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FT.TXN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION type which has to be used while processing Incoming Swift message through OFS.GLOBUS.MANAGER can be specified here.</p>
            <p>For each message type the criteria may be different.</p>
            <p>For Income MT200, it will create always OT transaction. Hence one FT.TXN.TYPE can  be given here.</p>
            <p>But Incoming MT103 can have different criteria's as below and FT.TXN.TYPE can be given up to 8 Multivalue set and which ever is matching that FT.TXN.TYPE will be used.</p>
            <p />
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Option No-Multivalue</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Acct with bank present (Tag 57)</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Receiver Correspondent (Third party) bank present (Tag 54)</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Receiver Charges present (Tag 71G)</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>8</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>7</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>6</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>5</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>4</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>3</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>1</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>Case 5 is considered as default. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example:</p>
            <p> If inward Swift delivery message has tag 57 and 71G which satisfies the criteria 2 and TXN.TYPE-MV-2 is set as OT02 in </p>
            <p>DE.I.FT.TXN.TYPES, then FT.TXN.TYPE-OT02 will be used as FT.TXN.TYPE in Inward Funds transfer and details pertaining to OT02 like outward delivery message and charge code will be used while creating a Funds Transfer Contract</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>For criteria related to other Inward Message Types MT200, MT205, MT210 refer to User guide.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Incase the Txn.type is not specified for the above combination, error is raised during FT creation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory for this application. </p>
            <p>Multi-value field </p>
            <p>Should be a valid record from FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a Funds.Transfer Contract is created by processing an  Inward swift message, the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION type which has to be used can be specified here for a different message types like100,103,200 etc for different criteria's.</p>
            <p>Basic details from FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION type will be used for Message generation, Transaction code etc.</p>
            <p>The Id of this application is a valid Swift Message Type as defined in DE.MESSAGE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for information only and description about the FT.TXN.TYPE which is to be used for Inward Swift message processing can be given here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3-35 alphanumeric (type 'ANY') characters.</p>
            <p>Multivalue field. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

