<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.APPL.DEFAULT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains Company level Default values which will be used when processing Funds Transfers or Standing Order instructions. These Defaults will be applicable irrespective of the Transaction Type and the User must create one record for each Company on the System. </p>
            <p>The default values defined in this table can be summarised as follows: </p>
            <p><strong>Limit Amounts: </strong>
            </p>
            <p>- Automatic process limit for incoming transactions received direct from delivery. - Less Charges Limit representing the amount below which instructions for outgoing payments will not be accepted on a 'Less Charges' basis. - Minimum Standing Order amount. </p>
            <p><strong>Suspense Accounts: </strong>
            </p>
            <p>- Claim Charge Account which is the Account to be debited when charges are to be claimed from the ordering bank. </p>
            <p><strong>General Information: </strong>
            </p>
            <p>- Telex Charge Type code to be applied for cover and free format telex messages. </p>
            <p>- Centralised Funds Transfer Department indicator. </p>
            <p>- Our own customer number identification. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>USE.STO.ACCT.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies if the ACCT.OFFICER specified in the STANDING ORDER record should always be defaulted into the PROFIT CENTRE DEPT field when processing standing orders. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to Y the content of the ACCT.OFFICER field in the STANDING.ORDER will be defalted into the PROFIT.CENTRE.DEPT field of the Funds Transfer </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Field Valid value is Y</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETRY.END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Give the Standing Order Retry End time.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Expressed in a 24 hour clock format. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is the start time that online standing order retry will stop retrying failed Standing Orders. </p>
            <p />
            <p> Rule 1 Input must be numerical</p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 2 RETRY.END.TIME must be populated in order for record validation to take place</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SO.MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the delivery advice to use for Standing Orders which fail auto-resubmission. When the processing reaches the number of retry days specified in NO.RESUBMSSN.DAYS this advice is produced. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid delivery message</p>
            <p>Less than 1000</p>
            <p>Specified in DE.FORMAT.PRINT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.STO.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Minimum Amount to be transferred when a balance maintenance Standing Order exists. </p>
            <p>This field defines a Minimum transfer Amount below which balance maintenance instructions will not be processed. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>A Customer requests the balance of his Current Account to be maintained at GBP 100.00 to the DR/CR of his Savings Account. </p>
            <p>Where the MIN.STO.AMT equals GBP 5.00, No balance maintenance transfer will take place when the balance is between GBP 95.01 and GBP 104.99. </p>
            <p>Where the Minimum Standing Order Amount does not exist in the Currency of the Account where the Standing Order applies, the System will take the equivalent of the local Currency amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT type characters (Standard Amount Format).  Associated multivalue field.  (Mandatory input if associated Currency is input, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.CR.REV.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.BULK.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE to be used to calculate default charges on bulk standing orders. </p>
            <p>If default charges are to be applied to bulk standing orders, then this field must contain the ID to a valid entry on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE table. </p>
            <p>Note : It is recommended that the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE is UNIT based and has        NO associated links. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input. No default.)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUND.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rounding of Db/Cr transfer amount based on this field.It defines the rounding rule for principle debit and credit amounts.Should have a valid id in EB.ROUNDING.ROULE application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STO.TAX.SEQ.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Tax Sequence Number applicable to Standing Orders. </p>
            <p>This field, together with the Tax Percentage will be used in those countries where some Standing Orders (e.g. those in favour of charity organisations) receive a beneficial tax treatment.  If for example the Standing Order Amount is equal to GBP 10.00 (as defined in Standing Order file) and the tax benefit indicated in these two fields is equal to 30%, the amount which will be eventually transferred will be 7.00 to the charity organisation which in turn can claim the difference ( 3.00) from local authorities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.  Associated multivalue field. (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>This field cannot be validated to any current table, it merely indicates a sequence number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the Dealer Desk in which position to be reported for FT's which are in INO/ANORATE status, when the Rate.Fixing functionality is used.</p>
            <p>When Rate.Fixing is set as "YES" in FT.APPL.DEFAULT, then for FT's which are in INO/ANORATE status, position entries are created with the Dealer.desk as given in FT.APPL.DEFAULT, instead of Dealer.desk given in FT application.  This will help to group the FT's for which the Exchange rate not fixed on a single Dealer.Desk. Once the rates are available for the day,  FT.RATES is run online, then old position entries are reversed and new position entries with current exchange rate and Dealer.Desk as given in FT gets created.</p>
            <p>Rate.fixing is given as Null then it will be always using the FT's Dealer Desk for position entries.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input allowed only when Rate.Fixing is set to "YES" otherwise not allowed</p>
            <p>Should be a Valid record in Dealer.Desk Application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.FIXING</field>
<desc>
            <p>To invoke Fixing Rates functionality give "YES" in this field.</p>
            <p>If Rate.fixing is given as Yes then next field Dealer.Desk in FT.APPL.DEFAULT is mandatory.</p>
            <p>Rate.Fixing in Ft.Appl.Default is given as "YES" then it will be defaulted in RATE.FIXING field in FT and can be changed from Yes to No during Input. But Rate.fixing is Null in FT.Appl.Default then "No" will be defaulted in FT and this can not be changed in FT.</p>
            <p>See FIXING.DATE field in CURRENCY and RATE.FXING in Funds Transfer application for more details.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Values YES or Null.</p>
            <p>If "YES" given, Dealer.Desk Field in FT.APPL.DEFAULT is       mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CENTRALISED.FT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not the Funds Transfer function in the bank is Centralised in one department. </p>
            <p>This field defines whether or not the Funds Transfer function is centralised in one department. </p>
            <p>If input to this field is "N" then the Department code, from the User Profile, will be added to all reference numbers generated.  This will facilitate queries from external parties by providing an easy identification of the department which raised the transaction. </p>
            <p>An alternate extended id format uses the value of the Users processing department to build an id which may be preferable. </p>
            <p>It should be noted that using the option to add the Department code to FT id's which are already set to use the extended id format will result in an id length which would exceed 16 characters and be invalid for use SWIFT messages (where the current restriction of 16 characters applies). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Y = Centralised, N = Not Centralised  (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.STO.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Currency of the amount input in associated field, Minimum Standing Order Amount. </p>
            <p>Any definition of a foreign Currency must be accompanied by a local Currency definition. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character       or 1-3 numeric character Currency code.  Associated multivalue field.  (Mandatory input if associated amount is input otherwise not allowed.  A local Currency must be specified before any foreign Currency)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECONDARY.TLX.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Charge Type to be applied for cover and free format telex messages (i.e. not prime payment cable). </p>
            <p>The Charge Code input in this field will only be used for cover cables and outgoing free format telex messages, (e.g. when the User is making use of the fields Free Text Message To and Message from the Funds Transfer Application). </p>
            <p>These charges are taken in addition to those specifically entered within Funds Transfer. </p>
            <p>If the Bank is to charge for such cables, that this code must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type A (alphanumeric) character Charge Type.  (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>The charge code entered in this field must be a valid code in the Charge Type table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MKT.EXCH.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Definition of the method for calculating local equivalents and deriving marketing exchange profit. </p>
            <p>The option of STANDARD, the default method, will cause marketing exchange profit to be calculated as the difference in local equivalent due to the difference between the CUSTOMER.RATE and the TREASURY.RATE, i.e the CUSTOMER.SPREAD. </p>
            <p>The OPTION of MIDDLE causes marketing exchange profit (or loss) to be booked as the difference between credit and debit amount local equivalents, where the local equivalent of the debit and credit side is calculated independently according to the CURRENCY.MKT.CR or CURRENCY.MKT.DR. The amount for transfer is calculated at the entered rate, which can be defaulted according to the DEAL.MARKET. </p>
            <p>The maketing exchange profit or loss is booked to a P&amp;L category defined in the ACCOUNT.CLASS record FTMKTEXCHCR, FTMKTEXCHDR. Should these records not be defined the category is extracted from MKTEXCHCR, MKTEXCHDR. Should these not be present the category code 53006 will be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p>Only STANDARD of MIDDLE are allowed Default value STANDARD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STO.TAX.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate used to calculate the Tax Amount for Standing Order as a percentage of the entry value. </p>
            <p>This field, together with Tax Number will be used for those countries where some Standing Orders (e.g. those in favour of charity organisations receive a beneficial tax treatment.  If for example the Standing Order Amount is equal to GBP 10.00 (as defined in Standing Order file) and the tax benefit indicated in these two fields is equal to 30%, the amount which will be eventually transferred will be 7.00 to the charity organisation which in turn can claim the difference ( 3.00) from local authorities. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 type R characters plus a decimal point, (Standard rate format) but must less than 100%.  Associated multivalue field.  (Mandatory input if Tax Number is input, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>Rate input must be less than 100%.</p>
            <p>Not more than 2 integers may be entered.</p>
            <p>Not more than 9 decimals may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.RESUBMSSN.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of days for which any standing orders put on hold are to be resubmitted for validation. </p>
            <p>If a standing order, either bulk or normal is put on hold, i.e. it's corresponding FT has a record status of IHLD, then it may be resubmitted for validation for a fixed number of days as entered in this field. Once these number of days have passed, the system will generate the delivery advice specified in SO.MESSAGE.TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric</p>
            <p>1 - 10 days</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETRY.START.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>RETRY.START.TIME</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <DT>Expressed in a 24 hour clock format.</DT>
                <DD>This is the start time that online standing order retry will start retrying failed Standing Orders.</DD>
                <DT>The EB.SO.RETRY.CLEAR phantom must be active and the NO.RESUBMISSION.DAYS is populated.</DT>
                <DD />
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1 Input must be numerical</p>
            <p>Rule 2  RETRY.END.TIME must be populated in order for record validation to take place.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.RATE.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not used and is reserved.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLAIM.CHARGES.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Account to be debited when charges are to be claimed from the ordering bank. </p>
            <p>This field defines the Suspense Account to be debited when charges are to be claimed from the ordering bank. </p>
            <p>Where this Account number is input as the Charge Account number in a Funds Transfer transaction, a Claim Charges advice will automatically be sent to the ordering bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 to 12 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) Account number  or  3 to 10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".") character Account Mnemonic.  (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>The Application will only allow an Account classified as "Internal" and in local currency.  Customer or foreign Currency Accounts will be rejected.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.DB.REV.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Funds Transfer Application, for a specific company, which may be another bank or branch. </p>
            <p>A valid Company code will be used as the ID for this file.  This means that the user must define different Funds Transfer Default values for each Company. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Company ID: CC-GGG-NNNN where CC is alphabetic Country code GGG is numeric Company.Group NNNN is numeric  or  Company Mnemonic 2-5 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') characters  (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.CORR.BANK.CHGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify whether defaulting of Correspondent Bank charges functionality is required or Not.</p>
            <p>To default Correspondent Bank charges in FUNDS.TRANSFER application while processing Outward / Inward MT103 message, this field has to be set as "YES" and charges has to be specified in CORR.BANK.CHARGES application for the Receiver (either Credit Customer if receiver Bank not specified or Receiver Bank Customer No if exists for Outward Message) or Sender (for Inward Message ) MT103 message with an optional Txn.type combination.</p>
            <p>Based on the above setup, correspondent charges will be defaulted as follows:-</p>
            <p>Outward MT103.</p>
            <p>At the Funds.Transfer Applciation level, BEN.OUR.CHARGES is given as "OUR" then based on the charges defined in CORR.BANK.CHARGES application for the Credit Currency, system populates the charge details along with CHARGE.FOR as "RECEIVER" and these details mapped to Tag 71G of Outward MT103 Message. The amount to be remitted (tag 32) is arrived by adding the Credit Amount PLUS Receiver Charges (Tag 71g) in MT103 Message.</p>
            <p>Inward MT103.</p>
            <p>While processing Inward MT103 message, if charges for the Receiver of MT103 is not specified in tag 71G, then Receiver charge details are defaulted from CORR.BANK.CHARGES (as defined for the Sender Customer).</p>
            <p>For more details see the CORR.BANK.CHARGES application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field   </p>
            <p>Valid value "YES" to indicate defaulting of Correspondent     charges or Null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.COM.ON.ERR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify whether the details given in Commission &amp; Charge fields to be Retained or Cleared, when an error encountered in Funds.Transfer Application. </p>
            <p>When an error encountered in Funds.Transfer, details entered in the following fields are cleared irrespective of whether the user has entered the commission / charge details or defaulted by the system.</p>
            <p>45. COMMISSION.CODE 46. COMMISSION.TYPE 47. COMMISSION.AMT 48. COMMISSION.FOR </p>
            <p>49. CHARGE.CODE 50. CHARGE.TYPE 51. CHARGE.AMT 52. CHARGE.FOR</p>
            <p>For example for "OT03" Txn type where Beneficiary is mandatory and user omitted to input the beneficiary details, then system will prompt an error and clear off the details which is already there in Commission/Charge related fields.</p>
            <p>To Retain details given in the above fields specify "RETAIN" or Null to have the existing functionality of clearing Commission/Charge fields.</p>
            <p>Note when it is specified as "RETAIN", system will not calculate the Commission/charges even when there is a change in Transaction Amount or Customer etc and values will be retained as it is.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Valid values "RETAIN" or Null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>When Dealer.Desk is given, the Acct.Officer of the Dealer desk gets defaulted as per DEALER.DESK application setup.</p>
            <p>Identifies the department to which profits/losses will be allocated for this dealer desk during revaluation process.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input</p>
            <p>Defaults the Acct.Officer of Dealer.Desk as given in next field</p>
            <p>Mandatory when Rate.Fixing is set as "YES"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.PROCESS.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the amount, in local currency below which incoming transactions, received direct from Delivery can be processed automatically. </p>
            <p>This field defines the amount below which incoming transactions received direct from Delivery can be processed automatically.  The amount input is treated as local currency.  For transactions involving foreign currency the local currency equivalent of the debit entry is used. </p>
            <p>If the amount of the transaction is greater than the Limit defined in this field, the Funds Transfer Application will automatically place the transaction in a Hold status (i.e. HLD) and the User will need to go through the normal </p>
            <p>Note : Any message received from Delivery in an incomplete state will        always be placed in a Hold status. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT type characters (Standard Amount Format).  (Optional input.)  Authorised.  If the amount of the transaction is less than the Limit defined in this field, the Funds Transfer Application will place it in an unauthorized or in an Authorised status according to the operating conditions defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AWAIT.COVER</field>
<desc>
            <p>AWAIT. COVER functionality can be used where the bank wants to make  payment only after receiving the Cover message. </p>
            <p>When a Swift Payment message is received during Inward processing, if the AWAIT. COVER is set to "YES" then FUNDS. TRANSFER contract will be put on hold. Bank can verify whether cover instruction is received then process the contract manually.</p>
            <p>When AWAIT. COVER is set as NULL, then FUNDS. TRANSFER contract will not be put on Hold because of above reason.</p>
            <p>Above functionality  is applicable only for inward swift messages which are processed through OFS.GLOBUS.MANAGER and when Incoming swift message type has Tag 54 (Receiver's Correspondent).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p>Valid values YES or Null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.TXN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION to be used on the main FT produced by the bulk standing order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 4 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  (Optional input. No default.)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.RATE.DELIVERY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not physical Delivery for outgoing payments can take place before todays Fixing Rates have been loaded. </p>
            <p>This facility can be used in countries where Funds Transfer transactions are processed with exchange rates defined at the "FIXING".  This could mean that when the transaction is entered into the System, the relevant exchange rate may not yet be available.  The value defined in this field will indicate if the Delivery of the actual Payment message, resulting from these transactions, can take place before the final exchange rate is known. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The following values will be accepted: </p>
            <p>  Y : Delivery of the actual payment message will take place before     the Fixing rates are actually loaded in the currency   table - When in Funds Transfer application, Credit Amount &amp;   Commission/Charge Code is given as "Waive" Or "Debit   Plus".</p>
            <p>  N : Payment message will not be delivered before Fixing rates are     loaded on the currency table.  (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.CR.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not used and is reserved.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LESS.CHARGES.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the amount, in local currency, below which instructions for outgoing payments should not be accepted to pay on a Less Charges basis, e.g. where Charges would exceed the amount of the payment. </p>
            <p>Used to highlight remittances or transfers (where the charges are to be deducted from the credit) which results in the charges being greater than, or a disproportionate amount of, the credit entry. </p>
            <p>This checking is not applicable to inward transactions.  Any deviation from this Limit for other transactions can be overridden at transaction level if necessary. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 AMT type characters (Standard Amount Format).  (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT103.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify whether system can generate MT103+ or MT103 when the Funds transfer bank fields does not have "xxA" tag for MT103 message.</p>
            <p>If specified as "System" and in MT103.TYPE in FT is selected as MT103+,  then system will raise an error when the Funds.Transfer contract does not have bank field ( for tags 52,54,55,56 &amp; 57) with valid BIC code ("SW-") or Customer Number who has valid record in DE.ADDRESS with carrier as "SWIFT.1" or without a Ben.Acct.No.</p>
            <p>Incase MT103.CONTROL is null then system raises an override and generates MT103 instead of MT103+ in above case.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Valid value SYSTEM or Null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STO.PROCESS.GAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the date until when standing orders and bulk standing orders will be processed, depending on their frequency next date. </p>
            <p>You can combine 1 or 2 date operations, always based on the data base today's date, each operation being "+" or "-", followed by a number of days, and followed by "C" or "W", meaning calendar or working days. </p>
            <p>"+" and "C" are taken by default. </p>
            <p>Examples:</p>
            <p>"+01W-01C" means "Last day before next working day (will be today if tomorrow is a working day)." </p>
            <p>"+03W-01C" means "Last day before 3rd following working day." </p>
            <p>If nothing is entered here, the system will use unchanged the data base today's date. </p>
            <p>Input into this field will not affect balance maintenance standing orders (BI, BO &amp; BP). Input into this field will not affect standing orders which have any input into the DATE.ADJUSTMENT field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>8 type ANY (alphanumeric) characters. "+" and         "C" are optional, and zeros will be added if         needed. Example: "1-1W" will be taken as         "+01C-01W". Optional input, blank means default         FT calculation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.FIXING.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>A no input field which indicates whether the rate fixing process is running or not.If the vlaue is 'Y' then it indicates that FT.RATES has been started and if null it means that the rate fixing process is completed.Updated by FT.RATES routine</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIS.REV.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a FUNDS.TRANSFER contract which is moved to History is reversed, then the reversal transaction will use this Transaction code.</p>
            <p>If no transaction code is given here, the original transaction codes used in FUNDS.TRANSFER contract will be used during reversal.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>If entered, Must be a valid code from TRANSACTION file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.FIX.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>An user defined subroutine that the user can attach in FT.APPL.DEFAULT application for rate fixing process.Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters can be allowed.The subroutine entered should exist in EB.API record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESUBMIT.OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the list of overrides required for resubmission process on a standing order. This will take the value from EB.LOOKUP record RESUBMIT.RULE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in EB.LOOKUP with ID as RESUBMIT.RULE*OVERRIDE.ID </p>
            <p>If this field has null value then system will process resubmission only for unauthorsied overdraft override.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

