<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.BC.TXN.CODE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table defines the conditions to be applied for incoming local clearing transactions processed from the delivery system or from a tape interface. </p>
            <p>If there are no conditions present for the local transction type, the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION record for the FT Transaction type will apply. </p>
            <p>           Transaction Codes </p>
            <p>           The Transaction codes to be used for the generation of the            entries. Both Debit and Credit transaction codes can be defined            for basic entries, debit charges and cheques. </p>
            <p />
            <p>           Commission Types </p>
            <p>           The default commission types applicable for each local            transaction type. These commission types must first be defined            in the Commission Type table. </p>
            <p />
            <p>           Charge Types </p>
            <p>           The default charge types applicable for each local transaction            type. These charge types must first be defined in the Charge            Type table. </p>
            <p />
            <p>           Maximum Forward and Back Value Date </p>
            <p>           The maximum forward and back value dates applicable for each            local transaction type can be specified, and any excess beyond            these value dates will force an override at the transaction            level. </p>
            <p />
            <p>           Default Value Dates for Accounting Entries </p>
            <p>           The default value date conditions may be held for each local            transaction type. The conditions for both debit and credit            entries are catered for; ie the user can specify for each local            transaction type the value date conditions applicable to the            bank and to the customer. </p>
            <p />
            <p>           Production of Advices </p>
            <p>           For a given local transaction type, the production of debit and            credit advices can be controlled by default. </p>
            <p>The default conditions defined in this table will only be used by incoming local transactions in the Funds Transfer application, during validation of the transaction, if specific values have not been entered manually, or generated by the tape applications. </p>
            <p>Amendments to this table will only take effect after the user has next signed on to the system. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Transaction Code to be used on the Debit entry generated by Funds Transfer. </p>
            <p>This field defines the Transaction Code which will be assigned to the Debit entry, (generated as a result of using this Transaction type) unless a cheque has been received. </p>
            <p>Where a cheque has been received the Transaction code used will be the one specified in DR.CHEQUE.TXN.CODE. </p>
            <p>The Transaction Code of the entry is used to determine the references and narratives to be printed on statements. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>Must be an existing Debit code on the Transaction table applicable to Funds Transfer.</p>
            <p>Data Capture (Field 2) on Transaction table must be blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEARING.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines for which FT Transaction Type and local clearing transaction code, the conditions described in the record apply. </p>
            <p>The key to this file is constructed from the combination of the FT Transaction Type , the local clearing type identifier, and the local clearing transaction code, for example debits received from Telekurs for the Bancomat system should be defined as: </p>
            <p>           BDBMT870 </p>
            <p>where      "BD" is the FT Transaction type for incomimg direct debits </p>
            <p>           "BMT" is the identifier of the Bancomat tape transactions </p>
            <p>           870 is the transaction code from Bancomat for local currency                ATM withdrawals </p>
            <p>The Funds Transfer system will use the contents of the INWARD.PAY.TYPE field to construct the key to the FT.BC.TXN.CODE file. For the above example the contents would be: </p>
            <p>           INWARD.PAY.TYPE   BMT870-LCL </p>
            <p>For local clearing payments the suffix LCL is added. Only the first elements delimited by the "-" will be used. </p>
            <p>The FT.BC.TXN.CODE definitions will only be checked for BI and BD FT transaction types. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-12 alphanumeric characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The first 2 characters must be defined on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.CHEQUE.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the debit Transaction Code to be assigned when a cheque issued by a customer and drawn on ourselves, has been presented to us for payment by the bank who has negotiated it. </p>
            <p>The identification of a specific Transaction Code for this type of transaction will result in the cheque number input being checked against the Stop Payment file and appearing on the statement. </p>
            <p>The Transaction Code of the entry is used to determine the references and narratives to be printed on statements. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>Must be an existing Debit code on the Transaction table.</p>
            <p>Data Capture field on Transaction table must be blank.</p>
            <p>Cheque Indicator field on transaction must be YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STO.TXN.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, system field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.CHARGE.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Transaction code to be used when debiting charges. </p>
            <p>This field defines the Transaction Code which will be assigned to the Charge entry generated by Funds Transfer when charges are to be debited to a separate Account. </p>
            <p>The Transaction Code of the entry is used to determine the references and narratives to be printed on statements. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>Must be an existing Debit code on the Transaction table.</p>
            <p>Data Capture field on Transaction table must be blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.TYPES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines all the default Commission Types applicable to this Transaction Type. </p>
            <p>This field defines all the default Commission Types applicable to this Transaction Type. </p>
            <p>Unless Commission is waived or specifically input on initiating a Funds Transfer payment then the default Commission Types specified in this field will be applied automatically. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type A (alphanumeric) character Commission type.  Multivalue field.  (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>The Commission Type(s) input in this field must exist on the Commission Type table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Type of Payment for which the Value Date conditions defined in the next three fields are applicable. </p>
            <p>If ALL is specified then no other Payment Types may be input.  If either CONV or NOCONV is input, both must be specified, separately as one is not valid without the other. </p>
            <p>Note : This field provides the facility to define whether or not        conversion is involved in the transaction in order to determine if        different Value Date conditions exist: </p>
            <p>ALL    The conditions specified in the next three fields are applicable to        all transactions irrespective of whether the transactions involve        conversion of Currencies or not. </p>
            <p>CONV   The conditions specified in the next three fields are only        applicable to transactions involving conversion of Currencies. </p>
            <p>NOCONV The conditions specified in the next three fields are only        applicable to transactions not involving conversion of currencies. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>ALL     = All transactions CONV    = Only transactions involving conversion of currencies NOCONV  = Transactions not involving conversion of currencies.  Associated multivalue field with fields PAYMENT.VALUE, CUSTOMER.FLOAT and SAME.CUSTOMER.FLOAT.  (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Transaction Code to be used on the Credit entry generated by Funds Transfer. </p>
            <p>This field defines the Transaction Code which will be assigned to the credit entry, generated as a result of using this Transaction type. </p>
            <p>The Transaction Code of the entry is used to determine the references and narratives to be printed on statements.  The Debit/Credit indicators within the Transaction Code table are not used to verify this input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>Must be an existing Credit code on the Transaction table applicable to Funds Transfer.</p>
            <p>Data Capture field on the Transaction table must be blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.ADVICE.REQD.Y.N</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether a credit advice should be produced for this type of transaction by default. </p>
            <p>If no input is specified in this field,  Funds Transfer will not generated a Credit advice. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or N.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.FLOAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the default number of days to be applied for any Customer Value Date applicable to the Payment Type for this type of transaction. </p>
            <p>This field allows the User to define special Customer Value Date conditions at the transaction level by specifying within Payment Type a number of days between the Value Date applied to Customer and the Value Date applicable to the bank.  If zero '0' is input, the Customer will receive the Same day value as the bank itself. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>INCOMING TRANSFER </p>
            <p>DEBIT NOSTRO ACCOUNT (VALUE 15/1) </p>
            <p>CUSTOMER FLOAT = 3 (15 plus 3 = 18) </p>
            <p>CREDIT CUSTOMER ACCOUNT (VALUE 18/1) </p>
            <p>OUTGOING TRANSFER </p>
            <p>CREDIT NOSTRO ACCOUNT (VALUE 15/1) </p>
            <p>CUSTOMER FLOAT = 2 (15 less 2 = 13) </p>
            <p>DEBIT CUSTOMER ACCOUNT (VALUE 13/1) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-9 = Number of working days to be added to the debit Value Date to       make the credit Value Date for inward transfers and deducted       from the credit Value Date to make the debit Value Date for       outward transfers.  or  P   = Processing date irrespective of the other Value Date.  Associated multivalue field.  (Mandatory input if Payment Type field has been input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.ADVICE.REQD.Y.N</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether a debit advice should be produced for this type of transaction by default. </p>
            <p>If no input is specified in this field, and the Funds Transfer is one of the following Transaction Types; OC, OD, OT, OB, BC , a debit advice will be generated by default. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or N  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STO.TXN.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, system field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.VALUE.MAXIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum period of Back Value/Exposure acceptable for this type of transaction without an override being required. </p>
            <p>If Y, N or NO is entered the inputs (a) to (f) are not allowed. </p>
            <p>(a), (bb), (c) specify the number of calendar or working days to be subtracted from the Processing Date in order to obtain the Maximum Back Value Date/Exposure date as follows: </p>
            <p>            (a)   -   If days are to be subtracted from the Run Date.                       Only the '-' sign will be allowed for this field. </p>
            <p>           (bb) 01-99 Indicates the number of days to be subtracted. </p>
            <p>            (c)   C If (bb) are calendar days,                or W If (bb) are working days. </p>
            <p>If it is necessary to subtract any other days to those specified in (bb) before obtaining the Maximum back Value Date/Exposure date then (d), (ee), (f) are used as follows: </p>
            <p>            (d) As for (a) previously.            (ee) As for (bb) previously.             (f)   C  If (c) is 'C'              or   W  If (c) is 'W' </p>
            <p>Note : Processing Date is the date of the data being processed which may        not always be today's date.  If different, the Processing Date is        displayed next to the User ID on the screen. </p>
            <p>This field allows you to specify a Maximum back Value or Exposure Date for this Transaction Type being either the Processing Date, or a number of working or calendar days to be subtracted from the Processing Date.  This prevents the operator from inputting a Value Date or an Exposure Date which exceeds an acceptable period for this type of transaction. </p>
            <p>Any Funds Transfer payment input for the Transaction Type with a Back Value date greater than that specified in this field must be overridden. </p>
            <p>Example:   A Default Value Date of -03W would be 3 working days backwards. </p>
            <p>     or    -01W -02C would be 1 working day plus 2 calendar days            backwards. </p>
            <p>Note : The date specified in this field may not be earlier than the Back        Value Maximum as specified in the Dates file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y       If the Maximum Back Value or Exposure Date is to be the         Processing Date.  N or NO Where no special maximum is required.  The Back Value         minimum as specified in the Dates file will apply.  or      (a) (bb) (c) (d) (ee) (f) As defined below.  (Optional input;  Default = None).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.TXN.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, system field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.TXN.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, system field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.TYPES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines all the default Charge Types which are applicable to this Transaction Type. </p>
            <p>The Charge Type(s) input in this field must exist on the Commission Type table. </p>
            <p>This field defines all the default Charge Types applicable to this Transaction Type. </p>
            <p>Unless Charges are waived or specifically input on initiating a Funds Transfer payment then the default Charge Types specified in this field will be applied automatically. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type A (alphanumeric) character Charge type.  Multivalue field.  (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the default Payment/Transfer Value date applicable to the Payment Type for this type of transaction. </p>
            <p>If 'Y', 'N' or 'No' is entered the inputs (a) to (f) are not allowed. </p>
            <p>(a), (bb), (c) specify the number of calendar or working days to be added to or subtracted from the Processing Date in order to obtain the default Value Date as follows: </p>
            <p>            (a)  +/-  If days are to be added to or, subtracted from, the                       Processing Date. </p>
            <p>           (bb) 01-99 Indicates the number of days to be added/subtracted. </p>
            <p>            (c)   C If (bb) are calendar days,                or W If (bb) are working days. </p>
            <p>If it is necessary to add or subtract any other days to those specified in (bb) before obtaining the default Payment Transfer Value Date then (d), (ee), (f) are used as follows: </p>
            <p>            (d)     As for (a) previously.            (ee)     As for (bb) previously.             (f)   C If (c) is 'C'              or   W If (c) is 'W' </p>
            <p>Note : Processing Date is the date of the data being processed which may        not always be today's date.  If different, the Processing Date is        displayed next to the User ID on the screen. </p>
            <p>This field allows you to specify a default payment transfer Value Date for this Transaction type being either the Processing Date, or a number of working or calendar days to be added to or subtracted from the Processing Date. </p>
            <p>For inward payments the value applies to the debit value date and for all other payments the value applies to the credit value date. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>           A Default Value Date of </p>
            <p>           +03W would be 3 working days forward. or            +01W+02C would be 1 working day plus 2 calendar days forward. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y       If the default value date is to be the Run Date.  N or NO Where no default is applicable, this will allow the User         to input the Value date.  or        (a) (bb) (c) (d) (ee) (f) As defined below.  Associated multivalue field.  (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAME.CUST.FLOAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, system field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Local Transaction Type in an abbreviated format which can be used for reporting where space is limited. </p>
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter a Short Description for the Transaction Type code in various languages. Each expansion will correspond to a new Language as defined in the Language Table and will indicate to the User the Language in which this Short Description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-15 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field.  (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORW.VALUE.MAXIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum period of Forward Value/exposure acceptable for this type of transaction without an override being required. </p>
            <p>If Y, N or No is entered the inputs (a) to (f) are not allowed. </p>
            <p>(a), (bb), (c) specify the number of calendar or working days to be added to the Processing Date in order to obtain the Maximum Forward Value Date/Exposure date  as follows: </p>
            <p>            (a)   +   If days are to be added to the Run Date.                       Only the '+'  sign will be allowed for this field. </p>
            <p>           (bb) 01-99 Indicates the number of days to be added. </p>
            <p>            (c)   C   If (bb) are calendar days.              or   W   If (bb) are working days. </p>
            <p>If it is necessary to add any other days to those specified in (bb) before obtaining the Maximum Forward Value Date/Exposure date then (d), (ee), (f) are used as follows: </p>
            <p>            (d)     As for (a) previously.            (ee)     As for (bb) previously.             (f)   C If (c) is 'C'              or   W If (c) is 'W' </p>
            <p>Note : Processing Date is the date of the data being processed which may        not always be today's date.  If different, the Processing Date is        displayed next to the User ID on the screen. </p>
            <p>This field allows you to specify a Maximum Forward Value or Exposure Date for this Transaction type being either the Processing Date, or a number of working or calendar days to be added to the Processing Date.  This prevents the operator from inputting a Value Date or an Exposure Date which exceeds an acceptable period for this type of transaction. </p>
            <p>Any Funds Transfer payment input for this Transaction Type with a Forward Value Date greater than that specified in this field must be overridden. </p>
            <p>Example:   A Default Value Date of +03W would be 3 working days forward. </p>
            <p>     or    +01W+02C would be 1 working day plus 2 calendar days forward. </p>
            <p>Note : The date specified in this field may not be later than the Forward        Value Maximum as specified in the Dates file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y       If the Maximum Forward Value or Exposure Date is to be the         Run Date.  N or NO Where no special maximum is required.  The Forward Value         minimum as specified in the Dates file will apply.  or      (a) (bb) (c) (d) (ee) (f) As defined in the Details.  (Optional input;  Default = None).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Local Transaction Type. </p>
            <p>This field provides a Description of the Local Transaction Type. </p>
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the Transaction Type in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the Language table, and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field.  (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

