<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.BULK.ITEM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Application used for Bulk upload processing. This can be inputted through generic upload or manual.</p>
            <p>This application hold individual payment details of the Bulk upload. It can be created when the corresponding FT.BULK.MASTER exists.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the status of an item.</p>
            <p>Following are the values updated in this field,</p>
            <p>Values allowed for user input,</p>
            <p>CREATED – When an item is first inputted</p>
            <p>REJECTED – To reject a payment</p>
            <p>System updated status,</p>
            <p>ERROR – If there is any error during validation or during FT/DD item creation</p>
            <p>READY – If there is no error during validation service and ready for payment</p>
            <p>PROCESSED – If FT or DD item is created for this Bulk Item, then gets updated with this status</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.BULK.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tirgger field to update TOTLA.AMOUNT in the BULK.MASTER field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid inputs – YES or NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SORT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the bank sort code. If SORT.CODE entered then account number is treated as other bank account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid sort code in BC.SORT.CODE.</p>
            <p>SORT.CODE when inputted should not be the Bank’s own SORT.CODE.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the account specified is a T24 account or other Bank account. If T24 account it will be updated as INTERNAL else it will be NULL.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Field</p>
            <p>Updated by System. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate the errors that occur during validation and payment process.</p>
            <p>NoInput Field</p>
            <p>Updated by System.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the transaction type applicable to the transaction being processed.</p>
            <p>This will override the transaction type from Bulk Update Type file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid record in TXN.TYPE.CONDITION</p>
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the value date that is going to be used in the entry raised for Credit/Debit.</p>
            <p>Defaulted from Bulk Master Payment Value Date field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>SINGLE type Bulk it should be same as PAYMENT.VALUE.DATE in BULK.MASTER.</p>
            <p>MULTI type bulk it can be greater than or equal to the PAYMENT.VALUE.DATE in the BULK.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.MANUAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the Bulk item record is inputted manually by the user or uploaded from a file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Updated field. Default is NULL and will be updated as Manual if manually inputted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the payment Id. Reference for send / release of payment. </p>
            <p>NoInput Field</p>
            <p>Updated by System.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>NoInput Field</p>
            <p>Updated by System.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the customer of the account to whom the fund is going to be Credit/Debit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Value for this field is defaulted for T24 accounts. For other bank account’s, input is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the currency in which the fund is going to be Debit/Credit. </p>
            <p>Currency should be same as currency given in Bulk Master </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Currency in Currency table.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Hold the Account details that is going to send / release payments.  Should be in the Currency of the Bulk.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid T24 account or if other bank account then SORT.CODE field is mandatory.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This filed hold the payment amount, the amount going to be Credit/Debit.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.ITEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This filed is the id of Bulk Item to be created. The id has two parts separated by a dot. First part is the id of Bulk Master and the second part is sequence number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Bulk Master Id.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the reference of payment. This will override any reference from Bulk Update Type file.</p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p>Upto 35 characters</p>
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

