<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.BGC.TAPE.DATA</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>A work file holding the details of transactions received on the BGC incoming tapes. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>BGC.RUNNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BATCH.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the total value in Guilders of the batch sent via the BGC in block coded 213. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the information provided from the BGC under block coded 240. Payment reason / cheque number. </p>
            <p>If the incoming transaction is of a cheque type this field will contain the cheque number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>32 type S (alpha or numeric) characters.  Input externally only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.CONTRA.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the 5 digit code of dutch bank account numbers which indicates which bank holds the contra account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 5 numeric characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id of the customer whose static details have changed. </p>
            <p>This id is calculated by the system consisting of the following concatenated together separated by '-'. </p>
            <p>          Tape Name           Tape sequence number           BGC run number           BGC processing date           Item on tape </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>38 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BGC.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the transaction code as defined by the BGC which describes the transaction type. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 numeric characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
            <p>This field contains a key to the file FT.BGC.TRANSACTION which contains all the associated starting positions and lengths of any associated narrative payment details which have been sent via the BGC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains all the narrative payment details associated with the particular transaction being processed via the BGC in tape. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multivalued field. Each multivalue containing up to 35 type S (alpha or numeric) characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.AC.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken form the incoming BGC tape and contains the name of the account whose id is in field ACCOUNT.RESIDENT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 24 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the amount in Guilders of the contained transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 12 numeric characters.  Updated externally only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.SEQNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.FT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the id of the Funds Transfer that is generated in order to place the incoming transaction into the T24 system. </p>
            <p>This field may be empty as a Funds Transfer is not always generated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>14 type SS (alpha numeric with first two alpha) characters.  Input externally only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.AC.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the address as according to the BGC in tape of the holder of the contra account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 28 type S (upper case alpha or numeric) characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the enquiry number as sent via the BGC in BLOCK code 213. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 8 characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This contains the reference number sent from the BGC under block type 213. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 12 type S (alpha or numeric) characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.AC.RESIDENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the owner of the account is resident in the Netherlands. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the BGC in coming tape and is the T24 account which the transaction is against. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric characters.)  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming BGC tape and contains the name of the account whose id is in field ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 24 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.RESIDENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the owner of the account is resident in the Netherlands. </p>
            <p>           1 Indicates that the account holder is a resident. </p>
            <p>           2 Indicates that the holder is NOT resident. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALREADY.BOOKED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the bank has already processed the contained transaction prior to receiving these instructions. </p>
            <p>2 indicates the transaction has already been booked and the BGC update is for information purposes only. If this is not equal to 2 a corresponding Funds transfer transaction will be produced. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies whether the incoming transaction is a debit or credit in favour of the account. </p>
            <p>          1 indicates a debit. </p>
            <p>          2 indicates a credit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCEPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 49 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Account number for the other side of the deal, this should not be an account held by the bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 24 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.  Externally updated only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.SYSTEM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the T24 system date on which the tape was processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date format.  Updated externally only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.DATA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 40 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

