<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.LOCAL.CLEARING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application contains the parameters required by Funds Transfer for control of local clearing payments. </p>
            <p>Details specified will be used for BC, BI and BD transaction types within FUNDS.TRANSFER. </p>
            <p>The type of local clearing system in use is defined here. The details of field specifications, and special routines must be present on the file FT.BC.PARAMETER for the clearing system. </p>
            <p>Clearing accounts with their associated sort codes and account officers should be specified for use as defaults for inward messages, and as a verification check for outward messages generated using the Funds Transfer BC transaction. </p>
            <p>The customer numbers of the clearing accounts should be defined to allow messages from all applications to be diverted into the clearing system automatically. </p>
            <p>Details of sort codes for PTT transactions and the maximum amount for PTT payments can also be defined. </p>
            <p>This record must be present to allow local clearing transactions to be used in Funds Transfer. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CLEARING.ID.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.OUT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the associated TXN TYPE is used for inward or outward payments. </p>
            <p>Together with with the fields TXN.TYPE and DEBIT.CREDIT, this field defines which FT transaction type is to be used for Incoming and Outgoing payments, and whether the given type is for debits, credits or both (from the point of view of the customer). </p>
            <p>INWARD denotes that the TXN.TYPE is used to process payments received by the bank, OUTWARD denotes that the TXN.TYPE is used to generate outgoing payments. </p>
            <p>Currently the system can only process BC transactions for outgoing payments, BD transactions for incoming debits to customer accounts, and BI transactions for incoming credits to customer accounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'INWARD' or 'OUTWARD' or any abbreviation thereof.  Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MEM.ACCT.LOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of the LOCAL REFERENCE field used for member account numbers. </p>
            <p>This gives the location of the member account number local reference field. This must be present for the SIC clearing system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQ.LOCREF.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the LOCAL REFERENCE field required by the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>This gives the name of the local reference field required by the local clearing system. This name must be present on the FT.BC.PARAMETER record for the clearing system defined in field CLEARING.SYSTEM. The field that it must be present in on the FT.BC.PARAMETER record is LOCREF.ITEM.REQ. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-20 alphanumeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with REQ.LOCREF.POS.  (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be present in field LOCREF.ITEM.REQ on the FT.BC.PARAMETER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSMISSION.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 05 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTT.NOSTRO.BC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines which NOSTRO account is to be used for the BC transaction type for the associated PTT.ACCT.NO. </p>
            <p>These fields should be used if the bank generates payments directly to the PTT. </p>
            <p>This field together with PTT.ACCT.NO and ACCT.OFF.PTT, defines the NOSTRO account to be debited, when processing outward payments. </p>
            <p>A separate account may be specified for each branch (ACCT.OFF.PTT) of the bank, and or each type of transaction for reconciliation purposes, if required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-16 alphanumeric account number            or 3-10 alphanumeric account mnemonic.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPEC.ACCT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTT.SORT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the BC BANK SORT CODE of the PTT (post office). </p>
            <p>If payments can be sent to the PTT, the relevant sort codes should be entered in this field. Any funds transfer using this sort code will then generate a PTT payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 numeric characters.  (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be an existing record on the BC.SORT.CODE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.CODE.LOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of the LOCAL REFERENCE field used for local payment codes. </p>
            <p>This gives the location of the payment code local reference field. This must be present for the SIC clearing system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTT.MAX.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximum local currency payment amount allowed for PTT transactions. </p>
            <p>If PTT transactions are allowed, there may be a limit to the payment amount. Any amount in excess of this will be rejected by Funds Transfer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-19 Standard Amount  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRNCH.NOSTRO.BD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which NOSTRO account is to be used for the BD transaction type for the associated BC.CODE. </p>
            <p>This field, together with BC.CODE and ACCT.OFFICER, defines the NOSTRO account to be credited, when processing inward debit payments. </p>
            <p>A separate account may be specified for each branch (BC.CODE) of the bank, and or each type of transaction for reconciliation purposes, if required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-16 alphanumeric account number         or 3-10 alphanumeric account mnemonic  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be an existing ACCOUNT record, with LIMIT.REF of NOSTRO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEARING.SYSTEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>The clearing system defined here will customise the funds transfer field specifications for BC transcations, as per the definitions in FT.BC.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-10 alphanumeric characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the FT.BC.PARAMETER file.</p>
            <p>The following clearing systems can only be defined according to the LOCAL.COUNTRY and LOCAL.CURRENCY in the company record:       SIC  - Country must be CH or LI, or Currency CHF.       SCC  - Country must be SK or currency SKK.       BGC  - Country must be NL or currency NLG.       BACS - Country must be GB or currency GBP.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether the associated TXN TYPE processes debits, credits or both to the customer account. </p>
            <p>Together with with the fields TXN TYPE and IN.OUT.TYPE, this field defines which FT transaction type is to be used for Incoming and Outgoing payments, and whether the given type is for debits, credits or both (from the point of view of the customer). </p>
            <p>Entry of DEBIT denotes that the TXN TYPE will debit a customer's account in the banks books. Entry of CREDIT denotes that a customer's account will be credited by the TXN.TYPE. If BOTH is specified accounts may either be debited or credited. </p>
            <p>The contents of this field will be checked when processing inward payments to decide which transaction type should be used for the generated funds transfer. Outward payments do not refer to this field, and is for information use only. </p>
            <p>Currently only outward debits may be generated using the BC transaction type. Inward credit payments must be processed using BI txn type, and inward debits must be processed using the BD transaction type. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'DEBIT', 'CREDIT' or 'BOTH', or any abbreviation thereof.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTT.ACCT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the PTT account number of a branch of the bank, and together with fields PTT.NOSTRO.BI to ACCT.OFF.PTT, defines the PTT clearing accounts for that branch, and the branch (DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER) code. </p>
            <p>These fields should be used if the bank receives payments directly from the PTT, and these are processed directly into the Funds Transfer application (for example PTT BED transaction tape in Switzerland). </p>
            <p>Incoming PTT transactions are treated in a similar way to incoming local clearing payments, and will generate either BI (incoming credit) or BD (direct debit) Funds Transfers. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 numeric characters, leading zeroes allowed.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRNCH.NOSTRO.BI</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which NOSTRO account is to be used for the BI transaction type for the associated BC.CODE. </p>
            <p>This field, together with BC.CODE and ACCT.OFFICER, defines the NOSTRO account to be debited, when processing inward credit payments. </p>
            <p>A separate account may be specified for each branch (BC.CODE) of the bank, and or each type of transaction for reconciliation purposes, if required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-16 alphanumeric account number            or 3-10 alphanumeric account mnemonic  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be an existing ACCOUNT record, with LIMIT.REF of NOSTRO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRNCH.NOSTRO.BC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which NOSTRO account is to be used for the BC transaction type for the associated BC.CODE. </p>
            <p>This field, together with BC.CODE and ACCT.OFFICER, defines the NOSTRO account to be credited, when processing outward payments. </p>
            <p>A separate account may be specified for each branch (BC.CODE) of the bank, and or each type of transaction for reconciliation purposes, if required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-16 alphanumeric account number         or 3-10 alphanumeric account mnemonic (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be an existing ACCOUNT record, with LIMIT.REF of NOSTRO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the FT transaction type used for local clearing. </p>
            <p>Together with with the fields IN.OUT.TYPE and DEBIT.CREDIT, this field defines which FT transaction type is to be used for Incoming and Outgoing payments, and whether the given type is for debits, credits or both (from the point of view of the customer). </p>
            <p>Currently the system can only process BC transactions for outgoing payments, BD transactions for incoming debits to customer accounts, and BI transactions for incoming credits to customer accounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 alphanumeric characters.  Multivalue field.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTT.NOSTRO.BD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines which NOSTRO account is to be used for the BD transaction type for the associated PTT.ACCT.NO. </p>
            <p>These fields should be used if the bank receives payments directly from the PTT, and these are processed directly into the Funds Transfer application (for example PTT BED transaction tape in Switzerland). </p>
            <p>This field together with PTT.ACCT.NO and ACCT.OFF.PTT, defines the NOSTRO account to be credited, when processing inward payments. </p>
            <p>A separate account may be specified for each branch (ACCT.OFF.PTT) of the bank, and or each type of transaction for reconciliation purposes, if required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-16 alphanumeric account number                 or 3-10 alphanumeric account mnemonic.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTT.NOSTRO.BI</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines which NOSTRO account is to be used for the BI transaction type for the associated PTT.ACCT.NO. </p>
            <p>These fields should be used if the bank receives payments directly from the PTT, and these are processed directly into the Funds Transfer application (for example PTT BED transaction tape in Switzerland). </p>
            <p>This field together with PTT.ACCT.NO and ACCT.OFF.PTT, defines the NOSTRO account to be debited, when processing inward payments. </p>
            <p>A separate account may be specified for each branch (ACCT.OFF.PTT) of the bank, and or each type of transaction for reconciliation purposes, if required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-16 alphanumeric account number           or 3-10 alphanumeric account mnemonic.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REV.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard text to be added to reversal messages. </p>
            <p>If any reversal messages can be sent through the clearing system, the reversal text should be entered here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 alphanumeric characters.  Multilanguage field.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.CUST.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the customer number of the clearing system. </p>
            <p>The customer of the clearing system Nostro accounts should be entered to allow the delivery system to divert payments for this customer into the clearing system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric customer number        or 1-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic  (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUTOFF.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 05 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQ.LOCREF.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the position of the LOCAL REFERENCE field specified in REQ.LOCREF.NAME on the LOCAL.REF.TABLE file for Funds Transfer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with REQ.LOCREF.NAME.  (Optional or Mandatory Input if REQ.LOCREF.NAME input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to the Local clearing record. </p>
            <p>Input of a record allows the BC transaction to be used in funds transfer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>SYSTEM  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQ.LOCREF.APP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the position of the LOCAL REFERENCE field specified in REQ.LOCREF.NAME on the LOCAL.REF.TABLE file for Funds Transfer. </p>
            <p>This gives the position of the local reference field defined in field REQ.LOCREF.NAME on the LOCAL.REF.TABLE file defined for the Funds Transfers application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters.  Multivalue field associated with REQ.LOCREF.NAME.  (Optional or Mandatory Input if REQ.LOCREF.NAME input)</p>
            <p>Input mandatory if an input is made to REQ.LOCREF.NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.OFF.PTT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines which branch of the bank corresponds to the associated PTT.ACCT.NO. </p>
            <p>These fields should be used if the bank generates and/or receives payments directly to/from the PTT. </p>
            <p>A separate account may be specified for each branch (ACCT.OFF.PTT) of the bank, and or each type of transaction for reconciliation purposes, if required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER code. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the account/department code for the associated BC.CODE. </p>
            <p>This field allows each branch of the bank (BC.CODE) to be associated with an account officer or department. </p>
            <p>When processing inward payments the appropriate account and acct officer will be used for the BC CODE when generating the funds transfer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric account officer code.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the authentication code of the bank to be sent with the local payment message. </p>
            <p>This code will be sent to the delivery system for SIC payments. If the authenticator is not required on the message generated, the data should not be mapped in the DE.MAPPING table. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 9 alphanumeric characters.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BC.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the BC BANK SORT CODE belonging to the bank. </p>
            <p>Together with fields BRNCH.NOSTRO.BI, BRNCH.NOSTRO.BD, BRNCH.NOSTRO.BC, and ACCT.OFFICER, this field allows the user to define which Nostro account and account officer correspond to the given sort code and transcation type. </p>
            <p>All sort codes belonging to the bank should be specified in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The code must exist on the BC.SORT.CODE file.</p>
            <p>No duplicates allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

