<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.PROV.RATE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used to define the Agent banks which will be required when processing payments in Currencies not quoted locally. </p>
            <p>Any Currency present in this table must not be the subject of a Nostro account.  If it were, then the entry would not be appropriate here (i.e. the presence of a Currency code on either file is mutually exclusive). </p>
            <p>When a Provisional (approximate) Rate is used, the local currency equivalent will be credited to the suspense account defined in the Funds Transfer Application Default table.  The bank defined in this table will be instructed to pay the beneficiary (in the unquoted Currency) and claim reimbursement (in a common Currency, e.g. US Dollars) using the exact rate.  The common Currency equivalent can then be remitted to the Agent bank, to the debit of suspense and any shortfall/excess on the provisional amount can be debited/credited to the Customer. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>AGENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Agent bank to be used when provisional exchange rate transactions are generated for the Currency specified in the key to the record. </p>
            <p>This field defines the Agent bank to whom the instruction will be sent and who in turn will advise the exact rate applicable. </p>
            <p>No autorouting payment details will be taken from the agent record, merely the Name, Address and Telex or Swift codes. </p>
            <p>Note:     Where a remittance has to be made in a            Currency which is not quoted on the local            market a provisional rate must be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric character Customer Code or    3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') character Customer Mnemonic. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the code by which a Currency for which provisional exchange rates are used can be identified. </p>
            <p>This field defines a Currency where provisional exchange rates are used,  i.e. where Currency of remittance is not quoted on local exchange market. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type SSS (Uppercase alpha) characters or    1-3 Numeric characters.  Currency code. (Mandatory Input.)</p>
            <p>It must be an existing code on the Currency table.</p>
            <p>It must not be an existing code on the Nostro Account file as the code is to be mutually exclusive between the two files.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

