<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.SCC.TAPE.DATA</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is an enquiry file which is used to hold details of the incoming transactions on tape from the Slovak Clearing Centre. Comprehensive reports may be produced from the data present on the file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.BNK.SRT.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the benefactor bank's identification code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUR.REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the sequential serial number of the transaction for the receiving bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 6 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID to the record on the enquiry file. </p>
            <p>The ID consists of the following four elements separated by a '-' : </p>
            <p>           Tape Name </p>
            <p>           Tape Sequence Number </p>
            <p>           SCC Process Date </p>
            <p>           Item Number on the Tape. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 33 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSFER.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the currency of the transaction, which will always be in the local currency (SKK). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>SKK  -   This is the only value allowed.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCC.SPECIFIC.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the second specific ("specificky") symbol. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.SEQ.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIMARY.DOC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the date on which the primary document was input to the system of relations of payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 numeric characters. Standard T24 date format.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is used to hold any verbal information for the receiver. </p>
            <p>This field is used to hold any verbal information for the receiver from the sender if the SCC.TXN.CODE is any other than "91" and up to four multivalues are allowed. </p>
            <p>If the SCC.TXN.CODE is "91", which is a free-format message, then up to fifty multivalues are allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  Multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.FT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ID of the Funds Transfer generated by T24 when mapping the incoming transaction on the tape into T24. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>14 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THIRD.BNK.SRT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the identification code of a third bank involved in the transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEARING.REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the serial number of the transaction from the sending bank via the clearing system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 6 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCC.VARIABLE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the first variable ("variabilny") symbol. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCC.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the local transaction code used by the Slovak Clearing Centre. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.SYSTEM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the T24 system date that the incoming tape was processed on. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 numeric characters. Standard T24 date format.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the number of the account being debited, i.e. the benefactor account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>16 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSFER.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the amount involved in the transaction in the local currency (SKK). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 15 numeric characters plus a decimal point '.' character.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.ACCT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the name of the benefactor account holder. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIMARY.DOC.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the primary document identification of the input operation from the sending bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 13 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCC.SPECIFIC.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the first specific ("specificky") symbol. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCC.VARIABLE.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the second variable ("variabilny") symbol. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.MESSAGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to hold any error messages encountered when processing the incoming tape. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCC.CONSTANT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the constant ("konstantny") symbol from the SBCS code book. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the name of the beneficiary account holder. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the number of the T24 account being credited, i.e the beneficiary account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>16 numeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.SORT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is the beneficiary bank's identification code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.TO.BK.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is taken from the incoming SCC tape and is used to hold any information from the sending bank to the receiving bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  Multivalue field. A maximum of four multivalues allowed.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

