<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.TAPE.REFERENCE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application contains various details of the tape being processed. It is updated for both incoming and outgoing tapes. </p>
            <p>For outgoing tapes it is updated when the GENERATE or REGEN action is performed and for incoming tapes it is updated when the LOAD action is performed. </p>
            <p>These details are deleted once the transaction details for the tape are physically downloaded or uploaded and written to the FT.TAPE.HIST file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NO.RECORDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of records present on the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 5 numeric characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the date of the tape being processed from the details held on the tape. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type D characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.EXPIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the expiry date of the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type D characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME.LOAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the date and time on which the tape was processed using one of the following actions, GENERATE or REGEN for outgoing tapes and LOAD for incoming tapes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 type A characters which are displayed in the format YY/MM/DD HH:MM.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHECKSUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the value of the checksum derived from the details on the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 numeric characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.TOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sent total of the credit transactions present on the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 type AMT characters in the local currency format.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.TOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sent total of the debit transactions present on the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 type AMT characters in the local currency format.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the date on which the tape is processed by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type D characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.DB.TOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the calculated total of the debit transactions present on the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 type AMT characters in the local currency format.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.SEQ.NR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sequence number of the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 8 numeric characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.CHECKSUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the value of a checksum calculated by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 numeric characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field refers to the name of the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 6 type A alphanumeric characters.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.CR.TOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the calculated total of the credit transactions present on the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 type AMT characters in the local currency format.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the terminal number and sign-on name of the operator who processed the tape using one of the following actions, GENERATE or REGEN for outgoing tapes and LOAD for incoming tapes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 25 type A alphanumeric characters in the format TNO_USER.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of the tape being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 16 type A alphanumeric characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field details any override messages that may have been encountered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 type A alphanumeric characters.  Associated subvalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains additional information from the tape Header and Trailer records not otherwise contained in this record. </p>
            <p>When using the Generic acconting interface with LOAD.ROUTINE AC.LOAD.INWARD.FILE, it will contain each element mapped from the header in the format </p>
            <p>ITEM.NAME = value </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPROVAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date and time the tape was approved by the APPROVED.BY user. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPROVED.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the name and user number of the person who approved the tape for processing. </p>
            <p>This field will only be filled once a tape has been approved and then only if required, as parameterised on FT.TAPE.PARAMS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A characters.  Associated multivalue field.  Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPROVED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the date and time on which the tape was approved. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 15 characters Date time format. Associated multivalue field. Internal System field - Externally updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

