<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.TAPES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The FT.TAPES application is used to process the tapes received from and sent to the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>The User has to enter the ID of the tape to be entered along with the action which he/she wishes to perform. The tape ID has to be a valid entry on the FT.TAPE.PARAMS file. </p>
            <p>The application must be run with the "V" function. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TAPE.SEQ.NR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the tape sequence number(s) to be processed. </p>
            <p>This field is used to specify which sequence number(s) of the tape defined in the first part of the KEY are to be processed. Depending on the action specified in the second part of the KEY the following input is allowed: </p>
            <p>           (i) LOAD       - Input not allowed. </p>
            <p>          (ii) APPROVE    - Input may be "ALL" which will approve all                             sequence numbers defined for the tape.                          or Input may be one or more specific sequence                             numbers which must have been loaded                             previously. Error messages will be given if                             approval is not required. </p>
            <p>(iii)UPDATE     -   Input may be "ALL" which will update all                     sequence numbers defined for the tape.                 or  Input may be one or more specific sequence                     numbers which must have been loaded                     previously. (iv) CANCEL     -   Input may be "ALL" which will cancel all                     sequence numbers defined for the tape. </p>
            <p>                or  Input may be one or more specific sequence                     numbers which must have been loaded                     previously. </p>
            <p>(v)  GENERATE   -   Input may be "NEW" which will be used the                     first time a tape is downloaded. This will                     then automatically assign a sequence                     number. </p>
            <p>                or  Input may be one specific sequence number                     which must have been downloaded                     previously. </p>
            <p>(vi) CREATE     -   Input may be "ALL" which will create all                     sequence numbers defined for the tape. </p>
            <p>                or  Input may be one or more specific sequence                     numbers which must have been downloaded                     previously. </p>
            <p>(vii)REGEN      -   Input may be one specific sequence number                     which must have been downloaded                     previously. </p>
            <p>(viii)VERIFY    -   As UPDATE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 7 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory input, default or not allowed. See Details).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAN.REASON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Details the reason(s) for the tape being cancelled. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  (Mandatory input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if the action (the second part of the KEY) is "CANCEL".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed for any other action.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the tape which is to be processed and the action which is to be performed upon it. </p>
            <p>The first part of the KEY, which is the name of the tape, must be a valid entry on the FT.TAPE.PARAMS file. The second part of the KEY, separated from the first by a "-", must be the action required. Depending on the direction of the tape, which is defined on the FT.TAPE.PARAMS record, one of six actions must be specified. </p>
            <p>For incoming tapes from the local clearing system one of the following three actions must be entered: </p>
            <p>          (i) LOAD       - This will load the specified tape into the                            work area. </p>
            <p>         (ii) APPROVE    - This approves tapes that require approval and                            results in the APPROVED.BY and APPROVAL.DATE                            fields being filled on FT.TAPE.REFERENCE and                            FT.TAPE.HIST </p>
            <p>        (iii) UPDATE     - This will generate the Funds Transfer entries                            from the details loaded. </p>
            <p>         (iv) CANCEL     - This will cancel the previously loaded tape. </p>
            <p>          (v) VERIFY     - This will run the UPDATE.RTN to create                            reporting records only and not entries. This                            can only be used if VERIFICATION in                            FT.TAPE.PARAMS = YES. </p>
            <p>For outgoing tapes to the local clearing system one of the following three actions must be entered: </p>
            <p>          (i) GENERATE   - This will generate the flat file to be put on                            the outgoing tape. </p>
            <p>         (ii) CREATE     - This will load the flat file onto the outgoing                            tape. </p>
            <p>        (iii) REGEN      - This will regenerate a previously generated                            tape. This action is used if for example an                            outgoing tape could not be read by the                            receiver and therefore has to be sent again. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 15 alphanumeric characters as follows:  - The first part of the KEY identifies the name of the tape to be   processed.  - The second part of the KEY separated from the first by a "-" is   the action to be performed.  (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the tape being processed, which is the same as the first part of the key. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is an internal, NOINPUT system field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

