<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>FT.TAPE.PARAMS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file contains details of the tapes to be used for sending or receiving information from the local clearing system. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the actual value to be used for the data in the corresponding RUN.PARAM field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 alphanumeric type A characters.  (Associated multivalue field).</p>
            <p>Input should only be made if authorised by Temenos Systems.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.CMD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the uniVerse command to be used to load the tape into the work area. </p>
            <p>The load command must copy the incoming tape to a directory called FT.IN.TAPE/XXX.WORK, where XXX is the tape name defined in field 0 KEY. </p>
            <p>If a header file is present then this is copied to FT.IN.TAPE/XXX.HDR. </p>
            <p>If a trailer file is present then this is copied to FT.IN.TAPE/XXX.EOF. </p>
            <p>Each multivalue is to be a separate command and subvalues are provided if the length of a command exceeds the line. In this case spaces should not be unnecessarily put at the end or beginning of a line if the command is split since the subvalues will be concatenated together. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters of type ANY - leading spaces allowed.  Subvalue field.  (Mandatory input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if DIRECTION is "INWARD".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed if DIRECTION is "OUTWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.FILE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of days that records on the enquiry report file created from the incoming tape are to remain on the system. </p>
            <p>An enquiry report file is built for all transactions present on the incoming tape from the local clearing system and this field defines the number of days that records are to remain on the system. The routine defined in field 10 ENQ.PURGE.ROUTINE is used to clear the records from the file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.  (Mandatory input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if DIRECTION is "INWARD".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed if DIRECTION is "OUTWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAD.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the routine to be used in conjunction with the load command to update the FT.TAPE.REFERENCE record. </p>
            <p>The load routine if present is used for validation checks and to extract information which is used to update the FT.TAPE.REFERENCE record. </p>
            <p>If using the GENERIC accounting interface the Load routine AC.LOAD.INWARD.FILE should be used to return header information. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  (Optional input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Input must exist on PGM.FILE as a type S (subroutine) program.</p>
            <p>Optional input if DIRECTION is "INWARD".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed if DIRECTION is "OUTWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.INSTRUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the tape to be used for either sending or receiving information from the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines whether incoming tapes require approval after loading, before they are processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>ALL - indicates that all tapes require approval. OVERRIDE  - tapes that generate overrides when loaded require approval. NO - indictaes that no approval is required.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the routine to be used to generate Funds Transfer transactions from the incoming tape. </p>
            <p>The update routine is used for building the Funds Transfer transactions from the incoming data present on the loaded tape. </p>
            <p>When using the GENERIC accounting interface the routine AC.INWARD.FILE should be specified. This will process the file according to the AC.ENTRY.PARAM definitions. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  (Mandatory input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Input must exist on PGM.FILE as a type S (subroutine) program.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if DIRECTION is "INWARD".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed if DIRECTION is "OUTWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.DAYS.FOR.TAPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the number of days for which the tape file should be left on the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric characters, i.e maximum 99 days. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the tape is to be used for receiving information from or sending information to the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>I(NWARD)     -     Used for receiving information  O(UTWARD)    -     Used for sending information  (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.PURGE.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the routine which is used to clear the records on the enquiry report file built for incoming transactions. </p>
            <p>The enquiry purge routine defined in this field is called by the batch job FT.LOCAL.DATA.PURGE in the start of day process FT.START.OF.DAY. It will clear all records on the enquiry report file after the number of days specifies in field ENQUIRY.FILE.DAYS. </p>
            <p>When using the Generic Accounting interface the routine AC.INWARD.ENTRY.PURGE should be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  (Mandatory input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Input must exist on PGM.FILE as a type S (subroutine) program.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if DIRECTION is "INWARD".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed if DIRECTION is "OUTWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the tape. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 35 alphanumeric characters.  Multilanguage field.  (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTRUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes any instructions purely for informational purposes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. Subvalued multilanguage field. (Optional input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GENERATE.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the routine to be used to create the flat file to be sent to the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>The generate routine is used for building the flat file which is to be put on the tape to be sent to the local clearing system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  (Mandatory input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Input must exist on PGM.FILE as a type S (subroutine) program.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if DIRECTION is "OUTWARD".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed if DIRECTION is "INWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATE.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the routine to be used in conjunction with the create command to create the tape from the flat file generated by the generate routine. </p>
            <p>The create routine is used for building the tape to be sent to the local clearing system from the flat file if the GENERATE.ROUTINE does not already do this. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  (Optional input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Input must exist on PGM.FILE as a type S (subroutine) program.</p>
            <p>Optional input if DIRECTION is "OUTWARD".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed if DIRECTION is "INWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.APPROVAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not an inward tape requires approval. </p>
            <p>This is used by the "APPROVE" action. </p>
            <p>The values allowed are: </p>
            <p>        (1) NO       - no approval of tape required </p>
            <p>        (2) ALL      - approval required for all tapes </p>
            <p>        (3) OVERRIDE - approval required if any overrides encountered                        during the loading of the tape. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input may be "NO", "ALL" or "OVERRIDE".  (Optional or noinput).</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if DIRECTION field contains "INWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERIFICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not the downloaded file can be run in VERIFY mode as well as UPDATE. In VERIFY mode the application file is processed and only reports are generated, no accounting entries are raised. This mode may be used to enquire on the contents of a file, and is also useful when first defining the interace to check that parameters are correctly set. </p>
            <p>When using the generic accounting interface (UPDATE.ROUTINE = AC.INWARD.FILE), this value should be set to YES. </p>
            <p>N.B. If this field is set to yes it is important that the UPDATE.ROUTINE      is capable of processing the inward file only for reporting purposes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must either be Y or NO.</p>
            <p>Optional.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTI.TAPES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines whether more than one tape may be loaded in any one LOAD command for incoming tapes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y(ES) - multiple tapes allowed  N(O)  - multiple tapes not allowed  (Mandatory input if DIRECTION is 'INWARD', otherwise not allowed).</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if DIRECTION is 'INWARD'.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if DIRECTION is 'INWARD'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines optional parameters that may be set up to be used in the mapping program which creates the tape data. </p>
            <p>NOTE : Because the data to be entered in this field will be provided by        Temenos Systems, Users should not make any input without prior        consent. </p>
            <p>The reason for this is that any data entered must correspond to hard-coded values within the mapping program for the relevant interface. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 alphanumeric type A characters.  (Associated multivalue field).</p>
            <p>Input should only be made if authorised by Temenos Systems.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHORISER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHECK.PREV.TAPES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines whether for incoming or outgoing tapes the system should check the FT.TAPE.HIST file for tapes with the same number of records, totals and checksums for possible duplication. </p>
            <p>An input of 'YES' means that the tape, whether incoming or outgoing, will be checked against tapes in the FT.TAPE.HIST file for tapes with the same number of records, totals and checksums within the number of days specified in field NO.DAYS.FOR.TAPE. This is a measure to prevent possible duplication of a tape in case it has been processed before. If a matching tape is found then the user will be given an override message with the matching tape number and the date/time on which it was processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y(ES) - the tape should be checked for possible duplication.  N(O)  - the tape should not be checked.  (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATE.CMD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the unix command to be used to physically copy the transaction details from the work area to the outgoing tape. </p>
            <p>The create command must copy the transaction details to the outgoing tape being sent to the local clearing centre. </p>
            <p>           The main work file is copied from a directory called            FT.IN.TAPE/XXX.WORK. </p>
            <p>           If a header file is present then this is copied from            FT.IN.TAPE/XXX.HDR. </p>
            <p>           If a trailer file is present then this is copied from            FT.IN.TAPE/XXX.EOF. </p>
            <p>In the above examples XXX is the tape name specified in field 0 KEY. Each multivalue is to be a separate command and subvalues are provided if the length of a command exceeds the line. In this case spaces should not be unnecessarily put at the end or beginning of a line if the command is split since the subvalues will be concatenated together. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters of type ANY - leading spaces allowed.  Subvalue field.  (Mandatory input or not allowed).</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if DIRECTION is "OUTWARD".</p>
            <p>Input not allowed if DIRECTION is "INWARD".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

