<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FT</product>
<table>SINGLE.INWARD.BULK</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                SINGLE INWARD BULK </p>
            <p />
            <p>The Single Inward Bulk Standing Orders application is used to run the Inward Bulk Standing Orders application on-line. </p>
            <p>The application allows one or more Inward Bulk Standing Orders to be executed. The User has to enter the ID of the Inward Bulk Standing Order/s which are to be processed. This corresponds to Field 0 ACCOUNT.NO.DATE from the Inward Bulk Standing Order file. The only Inward Bulk Standing Orders which may be run are those which have the date part of Field 0 less than or equal to today's date. Obviously the Inward Bulk Standing Order to be executed must be held on the Live Inward Bulk Standing Order file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the ID of the Inward Bulk Standing Order/s which are to be run on-line. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-12 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the total amount of the Inward Bulk Standing Order defined in the previous field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Internal associated multivalue field.) Details:  The contents of this field correspond to Field 4 TOTAL.CREDIT.AMOUNT of the Inward Bulk Standing Order file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIST.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a sequential number which is updated every time when a history file is generated for the application SINGLE.INWARD.BULK.The history number will be updated in the id of the SINGLE.INWARD.BULK.HIST file.When a SINGLE.INWARD.BULK is verified for the first time the HIST.NO will be updated as 1.Every time it is verified 1 will be added to the HIST.NO field of existing record and this will be updated in the live SINGLE.INWARD.BULK file and the old record will be written to SINGLE.INWARD.BULK.HIST file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.BULK.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies which Inward Bulk Standing Order is to be executed. It must be a valid ID in the Live Inward Bulk Standing Orders file. </p>
            <p>The contents of this field must correspond to a valid entry on the Inward Bulk Standing Order file, this being Field 0 ACCOUNT.NO.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 24 type A (alphanumeric) characters as follows: -                 The first part of the ID identifies the Account Number for which the Inward Bulk Standing Order has been defined. -                 The second part of the ID is separated from the Account Number by a '-' and will be a date. Associated multivalue field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.PAYMENTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the number of payments, i.e. credits, of the Inward Bulk Standing Order defined in field 1. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Internal associated multivalue field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

