<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CR</product>
<table>CR.CUST.OPPOR.HIST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

 
 CR
 CR.CUST.OPPOR.HIST
 CR.CUST.OPPOR.HIST
 
 
 
 This system generated table will monitor all opportunities communicated with the customer. It is necessary in order for the system to know whether a customer is already the target of a campaign on an earlier
 iteration, or has already been approached by the bank regarding a particular product, so that inappropriate opportunities can be prevented.
 
 It can also be used in analysis of campaign/opportunity effectiveness, and also to monitor how many communications have been directed towards a customer over a set period of time.
 
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EVENT.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Phase 2 : Event which caused opportunity to be generated
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 Noinput field. Reserved for later use.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPPORTUNITY.ID</field>
<desc>

 <p>Opportunity record for this product. So the system can reference the original Opportunity record . Contains all current opportunities and all prior opportunities (within a set time period) which were declined by the client)</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPPOR.GEN.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field will indicate which Opportunity Generator record caused the opportunity to be generated 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 System Generated Noinput Field.
 Automatically populated from Opportunity Generator record when the record is generated from an opportunity propensity.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>
First field of multivalue set. Each multivalue set will represent one product / product group / category that we have presented to the customer as an opportunity.
This field will store the product initiated by the opportunity. This is principally for the prevention of duplicate opportunities being generated for the same customer.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 References AA Product Catalog. As with PRODUCT.GRP and CATEGORY, only one of PRODUCT, PRODUCT.GRP and CATEGORY may be populated. 
 
 

</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECTION</field>
<desc>

 <p>Direction of the opportunity generated. It could be either INBOUND or OUTBOUND.</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAMPAIGN.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 This field will indicate exactly which campaign record and iteration caused the opportunity to be generated.
 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 
 System Generated Noinput Field.
 Automatically populated from Campaign Generator record when the record is generated from a campaign. Should also include iteration number of campaign.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CR.COPH.ID</field>
<desc>

 <p>Customer Code. Valid id on customer table.</p>
 
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DATE.CREATED</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Indication of when the opportunity was created. Necessary for calculation of how many outbound opportunities have been created in a set period.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 System Generated Noinput Field.
 Date format.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.REJECTED</field>
<desc>

 <p>Date this opportunity was rejected.</p>
 
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>PRODUCT.GRP</field>
<desc>
        <p>
  Holds the AA.PRODUCT.GROUP Id to represent the product group that we have presented to the customer as an opportunity.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 System Generated Noinput Field.
An opportunity may represent a specific product, a product group or a specific category. If the opportunity is at the specific product level, the PRODUCT field would be populated - however, if the opportunity is at the
higher 'product group' level, then this AA.PRODUCT.GROUP field would be populated. Only one of PRODUCT , AA.PROUCT.GROUP and CATEGORY can be populated.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
        <p>
   Holds CATEGORY if specified in opportunity (in which case, PRODUCT and PRODUCT.GROUP should be null) that we have presented to the customer as an opportunity.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 System Generated Noinput Field.
 As with PRODUCT and PRODUCT.GRP, only one of CATEGORY, PRODUCT and PRODUCT.GRP may be populated.
</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>OPP.STATUS</field>
<desc>
        <p>
    Holds the value as 'PURGED' when this Opportunity has been purged (moved from live file into history) otherwise this field will not hold any value.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 System Generated Noinput Field. 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ORIG.DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
This field will hold the Original direction of the CR.OPPORTUNITY. The system needs to monitor how many outbound opportunities are generated by the bank, to ensure 'over saturation' does not occur where the 
customer is contacted too many times. However, if an opportunity is initially 'INBOUND', i.e reliant on the customer contacting the bank, if it is changed to 'OUTBOUND' following interest from the customer, these 
opportunities should not be included in the overall count - hence over saturation relies on the Original direction, rather than the eventual direction of the opportunity.  
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 System Generated Noinput Field. 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>