<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CR</product>
<table>CR.CONTACT.LOG.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

 
 CR
 CR.CONTACT.LOG.PARAM
 
 
 
 A parameter table which holds information on which field should be the tracking field for a customer or account in any application.
 
 
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.LOG</field>
<desc>

 Valid options 
 
 YES or NO 
 
 If No the log file update will not happen.
 

</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROSPECT.ALLOW</field>
<desc>

 This field determines if a transaction in that applicaiton may be input for a client who has a CUSTOMER.TYPE of PROSPECT on the CUSTOMER file.
 
 This option can be blocked in the COMPANY record.
 
 Valid options 
 
 YES or NO or NULL
 
 
 
 
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.FIELD</field>
<desc>

 Should be a valid field in that application which holds the account number.
 
 Example 
 Application MG.MORTGAGES 
 A valid field within MG.MORTGAGES would be MORTGAGE.ACCOUNT
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTACT.LOG.PARAM</field>
<desc>

 The @id is either SYSTEM, any T24 application with or without a version
 
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.COMPONENT</field>
<desc>

 Specifies the way to extract Customer reference from the field, CUSTOMER.FIELD.
 
 This field is used to specify the exact position or the means to extract the customer reference from the field, CUSTOMER.FIELD. It can be defined in the format x,y.
 
 Example 1:
 If CUSTOMER.FIELD has the value : 10102520070101 (Customer number appended with Date), the field CUST.COMPONENT has to be defined with the value 1,6 to denote that customer number exists from first position until sixth position.
 
 Example 2:
 If CUSTOMER.FIELD has the value : 20070101.101025.01, CUST.COMPONENT should be defined as .,2 where “.” as the delimiter, the second value has to be extracted as the customer number.
 
 This is an Optional Field.
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.FIELD</field>
<desc>

 Should be a valid field in that application which holds the customer code 
 
 Example 
 Application MG.MORTGAGES 
 A valid field within MG.MORTGAGES would be CUSTOMER
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.HIS.INDEX</field>
<desc>

 This field is only used by the CR.CONTACT.LOG.PARAM record SYSTEM. It is used to record how many transaction histories are to be held.
 
 No input field unless the @id is SYSTEM
 
 
</desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

