<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CR</product>
<table>CR.OPPORTUNITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

 
 CR
 CR.OPPORTUNITY
 CR.OPPORTUNITY
 
 
 
 Opportunities can be generated by sources other than direct marketing campaigns, and also adding the new functionality of a ‘Propensity Engine’ to identify products which are likely to be of interest to specific customers.
 The Sales Opportunity Functionality will generate Opportunities, which will interface with existing Workflow functionality to manage both the sales and origination workflows.
 The functionality will make use of the Rules Engine to determine appropriate opportunities for customers from both campaigns and individual customer circumstances.
 It is intended that the opportunities generated through this functionality will for the first phase relate solely to products.
 
 
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OP.GENR.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 If an opportunity has been generated as a result of a propensity calculation, the Opportunity Generator Id that was used to generate it should be stored here.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Noinput field, populated automatically by system. 
 Should be a value from Opportunity Generator table.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARENT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Transaction Reference of the application used for creating opportunities in Real Time.</p> <![CDATA[ 
]]></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANUAL.GENR.COMM</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 If the opportunity has been added manually – either as a result of a customer request, or a staff member’s individual initiative, it will not have arisen through an event, propensity or campaign. Therefore, it must be raised ‘ad hoc’.This field must be populated in this case to indicate the reason for the opportunity to be created.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Mandatory input if previous 3 fields (Event, Opportunity Capaign Ids) are blank, otherwise noinput.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Indication as to whether this opportunity is inbound (can only be communicated by the customer talking to us) or outbound (communicated by us contacting the customer). 
 Copied from Opportunity Template when the record is generated. If the opportunity is Inbound, this can be changed by the user to ‘Outbound’ upon contact with the customer.
 In changing the opportunity to outbound, this will trigger a PW Process(through Service). This id will then be returned to the Opportunity Process Id.
 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Values may be either Inbound or Outbound.
 Can't change the direction from outbound to Inbound
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>

 <p>Customer for whom opportunity is generated.</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPPOR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Phase 2 Enhancement
 
 Populated from running of Amount Rule from Opportunity Template. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 System field, can be overwritten.
 Numeric value.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.REFERENCE </field>
<desc>
        <p>Transaction Reference (Id) of the application which is to be executed in process workflow. </p> <![CDATA[ 
]]></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMUNICATION</field>
<desc>

 <p>Phase 2 Development</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>

 <p>Product that this opportunity relates to. Links to AA.PRODUCT table. Copied from Opportunity Template when the record is generated.</p>

 <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> : 
 Should be a valid record from AA.PRODUCT table if AA product is installed.
 Input allowed only when PRODUCT.GRP or CATEGORY field is null
 
 
</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPPOR.DEF.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Opportunity Template that caused this opportunity to be generated. Copied from Opportunity Template when the record is generated.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Noinput field, populated automatically by system. 
 Should be a value from Opportunity Template table.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Name of the application which is to be executed in process workflow.</p> <![CDATA[ 
]]></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.COMMENTS</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Comments/text that may be written by the user regarding this opportunity. Multivalue set with Comments date.
 Likely to be used either when the opportunity is entered ad-hoc or has been manually updated by the user.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Optional Input.
 Text box.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 End Date of opportunity. Calculated from Opportunity Template Duration or Campaign Generator when the record is generated.
 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Populated automatically by system
 Must be valid Date.
 Must be later than Start Date.
 
 

</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Start Date of opportunity. Calculated from Opportunity Template or Campaign Generator when the record is generated.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Populated automatically by system
 Must be valid Date.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARENT.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p> Name of the application used for creating opportunities in Real Time.</p> <![CDATA[ 
]]></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>

 <p>Phase 2 Enhancement</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPPOR.ORIG.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 If the client chooses to adopt this opportunity, this indicates the origination workflow that is triggered. Copied from Opportunity Template when the record is generated.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Noinput field, populated automatically by system. 
 Populated automatically by system upon generation of opportunity. 
 Should be a value from PW Process table.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPPOR.PROC.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 PW Process Created to handle this Sales Workflow Process, which is defined from Opportunity Template when the record is generated.This field will be prepopulated for all outbound opportunities, and will be updated when an inbound opportunity is changed to be an outbound opportunity.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Noinput field.
 Populated automatically by system upon generation of opportunity. 
 Should be a value from PW_Process table.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPPOR.STATUS</field>
<desc>

 <p>Inputtable or system updated field, to specify where the status currently is. This status field will start with ‘Not Communicated Yet’.
 
 Field is then updated depending on customer actions.</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.OPPOR.ID</field>
<desc>

 <p>Auto generated ID</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROB.SUCCESS</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Phase 2 Enhancement
 
 Populated from running of Probabiliy Rule from Opportunity Template. 
 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 System field, can be overwritten.
 Percentage value.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INBOUND.CHANNELS</field>
<desc>

 <p>If the opportunity is inbound, then this field will list the channels through which the user can be contacted for this opportunity.
 This field will have been validated against both the opportunity template for available channels, and also the customer profile to determine 
 through which channels they can be contacted. This field will be cleared when the opportunity is changed from inbound to outbound.</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITER.NUMBER</field>
<desc>

<p>This field is used to store the Iteration number on Opportunity.</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.COMPANY</field>
<desc>

 <p>Company for which opportunity record is created.
 
 This will be defaulted by the system with current company id.</p>
 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAMPAIGN.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 If the opportunity has been generated by a campaign, this indicates the iteration of the campaign. Copied from the Campaign Generator when the record is generated.
 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> :
 Noinput field, populated automatically by system. 
 Should be a value from Campaign Generator Table.
 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHOSEN.CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Stores the choice the customer makes as to how they would like to be communicated when they indicate they are interested in an inbound opportunity. When they choose a channel,
 this will be checked against the channel field on the opportunity template, and will initiate the appropriate workflow.
 Channel that will be used for outbound communication when the opportunity direction is changed from inbound to outbound.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>:
 This is mandatory for inbound opportunities.
 Input must a value with in INBOUND.CHANNELS.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENTS.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field indicates the date at which Comments/text that may be written by the user regarding this opportunity. This field is to be used along with USER.COMMENTS field. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>Optional Input.  </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>PRODUCT.GRP</field>
<desc>
        <p>Product group that this Opportunity relates to. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>A valid record from AA.PRODUCT.GROUP can be input if AA product is installed. Input allowed only when PRODUCT or CATEGORY field is null</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Category that this Opportunity relates to. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>A valid record from CATEGORY can be input. Input allowed only when PRODUCT or PRODUCT.GRP field is null</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>STATUS.CHG.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Date on which the OPPOR.STATUS value is changed, this date and OPPOR.STATUS values will be compared with Opportunity Parameter's OPPOR.STATUS and DAYS.PAST.EXPIRY fields, </p>
		<p> and when Opportunity's OPPOR.STATUS matches with OPPOR.STATUS defined on Opportunity Parameter and STATUS.CHG.DATE is less than DAYS.PAST.EXPIRY such Opportunity records will be moved to History file (purged).</p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>System field</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>SUPERCED.OPPOR.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field denotes the Opportunity ID which was 'SUPERCEDED' before when new Opportunity is created whose OPPOR.STATUS matches with PROP.PRIOR.OP.STATUS and </p>
		<p> PROP.ACTION defined as 'OVERWRITE' on CR.OPPORTUNITY.PARAMETER table.</p>
		
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>System field</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CREATE.NEW.OPP</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field has the value as 'YES' when the existing Opportunity was 'SUPERCEDED' and SUPERCED.OPPOR.ID field has Superceded Opportunity ID.</p>
		
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>System field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>