<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CL</product>
<table>CL.INCENTIVE.STRATEGY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
       <p>Collectors are given incentives (in form of points which can be transformed to cash) based on their </p>
<p>performance and achievement of predefined targets.</p>
   <p>External agencies are given commission based on amounts recovered and pulled out items against salary assignment.</p>
<p>Incentive calculation for Collectors’ activity will be done only if collection activities exceed more than mentioned for each collector.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TRGT.MAIN.ACT</field>
<desc>
       <p>Number of main actions required as target for the collector.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PTS.MACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of incentive points allocated to collector if the target main actions is reached.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FACTOR.MAIN.ACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of main actions over the target to be considered as an extra unit.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POINTS.MACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of points to allocate to collector per extra unit of main actions.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PROD.MACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of productive outcomes related to main actions required as target for the collector.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PTS.PRO.MACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of incentive points allocated to collector if the target productive outcomes related to main actions is reached.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.MACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of productive outcomes related to main actions over the target to be considered as an extra unit.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.MACT.POINTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of points to allocate to collector per extra unit of productive outcomes related to main actions.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.OTHERS.ACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of other actions (other than main action) required as target for the collector.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PTS.OACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of incentive points allocated to collector if the target other actions is reached.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FACTOR.OTHER.ACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of other actions over the target to be considered as an extra unit.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTS.OTHER.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of points to allocate to collector per extra unit of other actions.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PROD.OACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of productive outcomes related to other actions (other than main action) required as target for the collector.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TTRGT.PTS.PRO.OACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of productive outcomes related to other actions (other than main action) required as target for the collector.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FACTOR.PRO.OACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of productive outcomes related to other actions over the target to be considered as an extra unit.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTS.PROD.OACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of points to allocate to collector per extra unit of productive outcomes related to other actions.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.NO.PTP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of PTP (promise to pay) to be obtained by collector as target.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PTS.PTP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of incentive points allocated to collector if the target number PTP is reached.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FACTOR.PTP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of PTP over the target to be considered as an extra unit.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTS.UNIT.PTP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of points to allocate to collector per extra unit of PTP.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PTP.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total PTP amount (promise to pay amount) to be obtained by collector as target (Not Used)</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PTP.AMT.PTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of incentive points allocated to collector if the target PTP amount is reached. (Not Used).</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FACTOR.PTP.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PTP amount over the target to be considered as an extra unit. (Not Used).</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTS.UNIT.PTP.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of points to allocate to collector per extra unit of PTP amount (Not Used).</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.NO.KPTP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of KPTP (kept promise to pay) to be achieved by collector as target.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.PTS.KPTP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of incentive points allocated to collector if the target number KPTP is reached.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FACTOR.KPTP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of KPTP over the target to be considered as an extra unit.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTS.UNIT.KPTP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of points to allocate to collector per extra unit of KPTP.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.KPTP.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total KPTP amount (kept promise to pay amount) to be achieved by collector as target.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRGT.KPTP.AMT.PTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of incentive points allocated to collector if the target KPTP amount is reached.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FACTOR.KPTP.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>KPTP amount over the target to be considered as an extra unit.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PTS.UNIT.KPTP.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of points to allocate to collector per extra unit of KPTP amount.</p>
                
        </desc>
</t>

</menu>
</t24help>

