<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>CL</product>
<table>CL.ITEM.WEIGHT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
       <p>A record to be created for sorting, this record will have a mandatory record “SYSTEM”, which will be the one by default.  </p>
            <p>A sorting record can be created for each queue.</p>
            <p> Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Must be valid QUEUE Id or "SYSTEM"</p>
            <p />
            <p></p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OUTSTD.AMT.UPTO</field>
<desc>
<p>This field with the next field allows assigning a weight to the OUTSTANING AMOUNT of the COLLECTION ITEM record based on the value of this amount.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTS.WEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The weight to be given to the up to amount defined in the previous field.</p>
           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODUE.AMT.UPTO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field with the next field allows assigning a weight to the OVERDUE AMOUNT of the COLLECTION ITEM record based on the value of this amount.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ODUE.WGT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The weight to be given to the up to amount defined in the previous field.</p>
           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLACK.LIST.WGT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Which weight to be given to items with black-list flag is ‘Y’.</p>

        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BPTP.UPTO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field with the next field allows assigning a weight to the NUMBER OF BPTP (broken promise to pay) of the COLLECTION ITEM record based on the value of this number</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>BPTP.WEIGHT</field>
<desc>
    <p>The weight to be given to the up to number defined in the previous field.</p>
           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PD.DAYS.UPTO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field with the next field allows assigning a weight to the number of days past due of the COLLECTION ITEM record based on the value of this number of days.</p>
           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PD.DAYS.WEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The weight to be given to the up to number of days defined in the previous field.</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DNO.ACT.UPTO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field with the next field allows assigning a weight to the number of days elapsed since last action performed on the COLLECTION ITEM record based on the value of this number of days.</p>
           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DNO.ACT.WGT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The weight to be given to the up to number of days defined in the previous field.</p>
           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UL.LOAN.SECURED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Informs if loan is Secured or or not to be considered in weight calculations.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid option are 'Y' and 'N' </p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.WGT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The weight to be given to the Loan secured based on UL.LOAN.SECURED</p>
            
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.OUTCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should be an entry in the OUTCOME file. (Start of multi-value association). </p>
           
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.OCOME.WGT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The weight to be given for the attribute “last outcome” for each item having an outcome code equal to the value specified in the previous field.</p>
               
        </desc>
</t>

</menu>
</t24help>

