<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>CL</product>
        <title>CL.PARAMETER</title>
        <table>CL.PARAMETER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table will be used for general parameters for Loan Collections.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Record with ID equal to valid company ID is to be created.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>HIST.NOTES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>if there is no movement's or action taken within mentioned in COLL.ITEM.DEL.DAYS field .</p>
                <p>then system will move the collection item to history along with update the Note field</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Free Text Message.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INACTIVES.NOTES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>There is no movement in collection item's based on ACTION.DATE and UPDATE.DATE fields,</p>
                <p>system will update this information into collection.item table field Notes</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Free text message.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>KPTP.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The outcome code to be used for kept promise to pay.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be Id of the CL.OUTCOME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PPTP.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The outcome code to be used for partial kept promise to pay.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be accepted from CL.OUTCOME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PPTPB.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The outcome code to be used for partial kept promise to pay when a partial repayment is done before the PTP end of the grace period.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be Id of the CL.OUTCOME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PTP.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The outcome code to be used for promise to pay.</p>
                <p>This field is used to identify whether only debit, only credit or all entries are to be restricted.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be Id of the CL.OUTCOME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PTP.GRACE.PRD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Grace period (number of days) given to the customer before a promise to pay (PTP) is considered as broken (BPTP).</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PTP.PERCENTAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>What percentage of a promise to pay amount if it is paid is sufficient to consider that a promise to pay is kept.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SPAY.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Outcome code to be populated automatically if customer pays without any promise to pay.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be Id of the CL.OUTCOME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AA.OD.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Virtual Balance type which will be used to calculate the total outstanding overdue amount of AA Loan.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must be a valid ID in AC.BALANCE.TYPE and the field REPORTING.TYPE must be "VIRTUAL".</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AA.OS.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Virtual Balance type which will be used to calculate the total outstanding Loan balance amount of AA Loan.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must be a valid ID in AC.BALANCE.TYPE and the field REPORTING.TYPE must be "VIRTUAL".</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APAY.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Outcome code used for payments obtained by external agencies, it will be used to calculate the commission to pay to external agencies.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be accepted from CL.OUTCOME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ASAL.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Outcome code used for salary assignment obtain by external agencies, it will be used to calculate the commission to pay to external agencies.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be accepted ID of the CL.OUTCOME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BPTP.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The outcome code to be used for broken promise to pay.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be Id of the CL.OUTCOME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CATEGORY.FROM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Products to be handled by debts collection module. (for LD/PD/AA)</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be Id of the CATEGORY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CATEGORY.TO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Products to be handled by debts collection module. (for LD/PD)</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The Value should be accepted Id of the CATEGORY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPTP.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is used to increase the amount of the commitment</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
          <t>
            <field>RPTP.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is used to reduce the amount of the commitment</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPANY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>List of companies mentioned can be parameterised for to capture the collection items.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Valid COMPANY Id.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
