<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FR</product>
<table>FRA.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The FRA Module initiates all confirmations, payments, charges, commissions, advices, accounting entries and updates all relevant positions. The detailed action to be taken by the Module for a particular deal is defined within a series of user controlled tables specifically compiled for Future Rate Agreement.</p>
            <p>Application of good housekeeping within these tables will provide the level of flexibility required.</p>
            <p>The default conditions defined in these tables will only be used by the FRA Application, during validation of the transaction, if specific values have not been manually entered during the transaction input stage.</p>
            <p>Tables which are updated during the on-line day are not reflected within the FRA program until the User has completed the current Input session. This is to ensure that transactions carried during that session are not subjected to different default conditions. When the User initiates the Application the next time, all updates will be available.</p>
            <p>The FRA.PARAMETER table is required to be set-up at installation of the Application to enable Future Rate Agreements to function in an efficient manner.</p>
            <p>Within this table are defined parameters which determine most of the rules by which the system operates. These are as follows:</p>
            <p>1. Determination of the revaluation formula and Frequency.</p>
            <p>2. Definition of acceptable variances of rates.</p>
            <p>3. Definition of the default spot and Fixing date.</p>
            <p>4. Definition of timing and content of revaluation entries.</p>
            <p>5. Definition of the default product category codes for Trade and Hedge transactions.</p>
            <p>6. Definition of rules for the confirmation matching.</p>
            <p>7. Definition of rules for the production of reports.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.FX.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the default FX.TEXT number which is to be used if the user does not enter any settlement instructions and the system does not find any default value for a specific transaction. This text will be printed on the settlement confirmation and will also provide the settlement account if no other default is found by the application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 9 representing the specific text on the FX.TEXT table.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P&amp;L.RL.PFT.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Profit and Loss category code to be used for the </p>
            <p> booking of the Realised profit of FRA Hedge Contracts</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input if field AMORT.HEDGE is set to 'NO' </p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: 50000...50999</p>
            <p>Existing values in this field can only be modified and cannot be cleared.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIRST.LAST.ACCR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies, for HEDGE contracts, if the accrual is to start on the first day or, start on the second day and finish on the last day.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"F"(irst) = Accrual will begin on first day and will not occur on the last day.  "L"(ast)  = Accrual will start on second day and finish on last day.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCOME.ACCR.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Interest income category code to be used for the accrual of the settlement profit on HEDGE deals.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Category code.  5 numeric digits in range 51000 - 51999.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
            <p>Must be existing on the Category code table.</p>
            <p>Must be in range 51000 - 51999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.L.RL.LOSS.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.L.UR.LOSS.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.UR.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the provision on the unrealised loss due to revaluation of FRA positions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10000 - 19999.  Must be existing on the CATEGORY table.  Input in this field is mandatory.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOSS.ACCR.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Interest expense category code to be used for the accrual of the settlement loss on HEDGE deals.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard category code.  5 numeric digits in range 50000 - 50999.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
            <p>Must be existing on the Category code table.</p>
            <p>Must be in range 50000 - 50999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.SET.FORMULA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the position type for which the conditions defined in fields PROD.TRADE to PROD.RL.LOSS are applicable.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 alpha characters.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.  Must exist on FX.POS.TYPE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MKT.EX.PR.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The internal account category code for the market exchange profit/loss has to be entered in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Minimum of 5 Type N (Numeric) Characters.</p>
            <p> The range should be between 10000 and 19999</p>
            <p> This field is mandatory when MKT.EX.PL.CATEG has a value.</p>
            <p>-This becomes a NOCHANGE field after authorisation.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P&amp;L.RL.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       50000...50999</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RATE.VAR.ALLOW</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the interest rate variance allowance above which an override will be required in the transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>01% to 999%.  No decimals are allowed.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.L.UR.PFT.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.RL.PFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the booking, before the value date, of the realised profit due to the closing of FRA positions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10000 - 19999.  Must be existing on the CATEGORY table.  Input in this field is mandatory when REAL.PFT.T.S is equal to Trade date, otherwise not allowed.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SH.POSN.LG.PER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies for SHORT positions, which side of the rate from the PERIODIC.INTEREST note table must be taken by the system for the LONG Period when it calculates the market rate for the revaluation of Trading Short position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values are:             B = Bid Rate            O = Offer Rate            M = Mid Rate  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROK.P.L.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.UR.LOSS.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the </p>
            <p> provision of the unrealised loss due to revaluation of FRA Hedge Contracts</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input if field HEDGE.REVAL is 'YES' and HEDGE.REVAL.METHOD is set to 'BOOK'.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: 10000...19999</p>
            <p>Existing values in this field can only be modified and cannot be cleared.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LG.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       BID      OFFER      MID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MKT.EX.PL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category code to which the market exchange profit/loss is posted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Minimum of 5 Type N (Numeric) Characters.</p>
            <p> The range should be between 50000 and 59999</p>
            <p> This field is mandatory when MKT.EX.PR.CATEG has a value.</p>
            <p>-This becomes a NOCHANGE field after authorisation.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P&amp;L.UR.PFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       51000...51999</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.UR.PFT.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the </p>
            <p> the provision of the unrealised profit due to revaluation of FRA Hedge Contracts</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input if field HEDGE.REVAL is 'YES' and HEDGE.REVAL.METHOD is set to 'BOOK'.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: 10000...19999</p>
            <p>Existing values in this field can only be modified and cannot be cleared.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.L.UR.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Profit and Loss category code to be used for the recognition of the unrealised loss due to revaluation of FRA positions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>50000 - 50999.  Must be existing on the CATEGORY table.  Input in this field is mandatory.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.COM.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if the charges or commissions applied to the counterparty must be booked on the TRADE date or on the settlement (START) date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"T"(rade) = on trade date. "S"(settlement) = on settlement date.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P&amp;L.UR.LOSS.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Profit and Loss category code to be used for the </p>
            <p> recognition of the unrealised loss due to revaluation of FRA Hedge Contracts</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input if field HEDGE.REVAL is 'YES' and HEDGE.REVAL.METHOD is set to 'BOOK'.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: 50000...50999</p>
            <p>Existing values in this field can only be modified and cannot be cleared.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.REVAL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the revaluation entries for FRA Hedge Deals are to be Booked or only Calculated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: BOOK or CALC</p>
            <p>Input allowed only if HEDGE.REVAL is set to 'YES' and is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P&amp;L.REAL.PFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       51000...51999</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SH.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       BID      OFFER      MID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.RL.PFT.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the </p>
            <p> booking of the Realised profit of FRA Hedge Contracts</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input if field AMORT.HEDGE is set to 'NO' </p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: 10000...19999</p>
            <p>Existing values in this field can only be modified and cannot be cleared.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHGXCOM.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       TRADE      SETTLEMENT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.RL.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the booking, before the value date, of the realised loss due to the closing of FRA positions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10000 - 19999.  Must be existing on the CATEGORY table.  Input in this field is mandatory.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.TRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the default product category code for TRADE FRA contracts within the pre-defined position type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>26000 - 26099.  The code must exist on the CATEGORY table.  Input in this field is mandatory.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTL.FORMULA</field>
<desc>
            <p>If required by the local environment, the system allows the user to use different settlement formulas according to the currency of the transaction.</p>
            <p>There are some countries (e.g. Australia) where one formula is used for Local currency transactions and another one for Foreign currency transactions. In this case, this field and the previous will be used to indicate the specific requirement at the currency level.</p>
            <p>If no data is entered in this field and the previous one the general formula will be used for the calculation of the settlement amount irrespective of the currency of the FRA transaction.</p>
            <p>All the currencies not specified in this association of multivalue fields will automatically use the general formula.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 9 representing the settlement amount calculation formula specific to the currency specified in the previous field.  Multivalue field associated with SETTL.CCY.CODE.  Input in this field is optional.</p>
            <p>a)Settlement formula = 1: The discount rate will be same as the Market rate and the discount period will be same as the FRA period.</p>
            <p>b)Settlement formula = 2: No discounting is required.</p>
            <p>c)Settlement Formula = 3:  The discount rate will be the long rate and the discount period will be the one corresponding to the long rate.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.L.REAL.PFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the booking of the realised profit due to the closing of FRA positions or because the settlement date has been reached.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>51000 - 51999.  Must be existing on the CATEGORY table.  Input in this field is mandatory.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P&amp;L.RL.LOSS.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Profit and Loss category code to be used for the </p>
            <p> booking of the Realised loss of FRA Hedge Contracts</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input if field AMORT.HEDGE is set to 'NO' </p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: 50000...50999</p>
            <p>Existing values in this field can only be modified and cannot be cleared.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LG.POSN.LG.PER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies for LONG positions, which side of the rate from the PERIODIC.INTEREST note table must be taken by the system for the LONG Period when it calculates the market rate for the revaluation of Trading Long position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values are:             B = Bid Rate            O = Offer Rate            M = Mid Rate  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.REVAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether FRA Hedge Deals are to be revalued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: YES and null</p>
            <p>Default is null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the company for which the conditions are being defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Company code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTL.CCY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If required by the local environment, the system allows the user to use different settlement formulas according to the currency of the transaction.</p>
            <p>There are some countries (e.g. Australia) where one formula is used for Local currency transactions and another one for Foreign currency transactions. In this case, this field and the next one will be used to indicate the specific requirement at the currency level.</p>
            <p>If no data is entered in this field and the next one, the previous formula will be used for the calculation of the settlement amount irrespective of the currency of the FRA transaction.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard currency code.  Multivalue field associated with SETTL.FORMULA.  Input in this field is optional.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.L.RL.PFT.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SH.POSN.SH.PER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies for SHORT positions, which side of the rate from the PERIODIC.INTEREST note table must be taken by the system for the SHORT Period when it calculates the market rate for the revaluation of Trading Short position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values are:             B = Bid Rate            O = Offer Rate            M = Mid Rate  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORT.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the accrual of the settlement profit/loss on HEDGE deals is required or not. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: NO and null</p>
            <p>Null (Default) - Accrual of  settlement profit/loss from Start.Date</p>
            <p> 'NO' - Accrual of  settlement profit/loss will not take place</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when HEDGE.REVAL is set to 'YES' and HEDGE.REVAL.METHOD is set to 'BOOK'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.UR.PFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if the bank wants to book unrealised profit and recognise them directly as a real income in its Profit and Loss accounts.</p>
            <p>Many regulatory authorities authorise banks to financially recognise the profit only when its is actually realised.</p>
            <p>According to the value of this parameter, unrealised profits (due to revaluation of FRA positions) will be completely disregarded or on the contrary directly recognised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"Yes" or "No".  Input in this field is mandatory.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROK.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if the brokerage charges from the Broker must be booked on the TRADE date or on the settlement (START) date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"T"(rade) = on trade date. "S"(settlement) = on settlement date.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROK.P&amp;L.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       52000...59999</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P&amp;L.UR.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       50000...50999</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.CONFIRM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if the bank wants to use the online confirmation matching facility for the broker confirmations. If "YES" is introduced in this field, all deals done with a broker will appear on the "unconfirmed broker" list up to the time that they have been confirmed on-line by the user or the START date of the contract has been reached.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"Yes" or "NO".  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.FIX.DAYS.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.UR.PFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.RL.LOSS.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the </p>
            <p>booking of the Realised loss of FRA Hedge Contracts</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input if field AMORT.HEDGE is set to 'NO' </p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: 10000...19999</p>
            <p>Existing values in this field can only be modified and cannot be cleared.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LG.POSN.SH.PER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies for LONG positions, which side of the rate from the PERIODIC.INTEREST note table must be taken by the system for the SHORT Period when it calculates the market rate for the revaluation of Trading Long position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values are:             B = Bid Rate            O = Offer Rate            M = Mid Rate  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REAL.PFT.T.S</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTERPY.CONFIRM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if the bank wants to use the online confirmation matching facility for the counterparty confirmations. If "YES" is introduced in this field, all deals will appear on the "unconfirmed counterparty" list up to the time that they have  been confirmed on-line by the user or the START date of the contract has been reached.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"Yes" or "NO".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the default product category code for HEDGE FRA contracts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>26000 - 26099.  The code must exist on the CATEGORY table.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.L.UR.PFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Profit and Loss category code to be used for the recognition of the unrealised profit due to revaluation of FRA positions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>51000 - 51999.  Must be existing on the CATEGORY table.  Input is mandatory if "Book unreal profit" is equal to "YES", otherwise not allowed.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.DEAL.WISE.REVAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether revaluation of Trade deals have to be done deal wise or consolidated.</p>
            <p>When set to yes, FRA deals will have FRA.POSITION individually and also revaluation deal wise.</p>
            <p>When value is not entered,default value of this field is "No", where FRA deals with same POSITION.TYPE, CURRENCY, CCY.MKT, REFERENCE RATE,INT.BASIS, DEALER.DESK,START.DATE And MAT.DATE will be consolidated under a single position key and
     Consolidated positions gets revalued  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.FIXING.REPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.FIX.DAYS.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.PAST.MAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the number of days after final settlement that the contract must be transferred to the History file.</p>
            <p>Final settlement = START date for NON hedge contracts,                           = MATURITY date for HEDGE contracts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>001 to 999 (days).  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOD.MAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether deals using this deal category are to be processed at the start of day or at the end of day.</p>
            <p>Input Yes to make the deal mature or take value during the start of day procedure (</p>
            <p>FRA.START.OF.DAY</p>
            <p>FRA.END.OF.DAY</p>
            <p>Limit exposures for the deal are also updated during the start of day procedure (</p>
            <p>SYSTEM.LIMIT.SOD</p>
            <p>SYSTEM.LIMIT.EOD</p>
            <p>All accounting entries, payments, payment messages and limit updates for deals maturing or taking value are raised during the start of day procedure.</p>
            <p>There is a</p>
            <p>SOD.MAT</p>
            <p>FRA.DEAL</p>
            <p>FRA.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>SOD.MAT</p>
            <p>FRA.DEAL</p>
            <p>SOD.MAT</p>
            <p>FRA.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>SOD.MAT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Y or N (default = N)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P&amp;L.UR.PFT.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Profit and Loss category code to be used for the </p>
            <p> recognition of the unrealised profit due to revaluation of FRA Hedge Contracts</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input if field HEDGE.REVAL is 'YES' and HEDGE.REVAL.METHOD is set to 'BOOK'.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: 50000...50999</p>
            <p>Existing values in this field can only be modified and cannot be cleared.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the reference rate from the PERIODIC.INTEREST table against which the variance allowance will be checked.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>01 to 99.  Input in this field is mandatory.  This reference rate  must exist for at least one currency on the PERIODIC.INTEREST rate table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.L.RL.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Product category code to be used for the booking of the realised loss due to the closing of FRA positions or because the settlement date has been reached.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>50000 - 50999.  Must be existing on the CATEGORY table.  Input in this field is mandatory.  This field is associated with field range POSITION.TYPE to PROD.RL.LOSS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the revaluation frequency for the TRADE contracts. It must be remembered that HEDGE contracts are not revalued.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>B  = each working (Business) day           Wn = Weekly on day "n", i.e.               1  = Monday    2 = Tuesday  3 = Wednesday               4  = Thursday  5 = Friday          Mnn = Monthly on day "nn", i.e               01 ----&gt; 30 = actual day of month               31 = last working day of month.  Input in this field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REF.PRCE.VAR.ALLOW</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALC.MKT.PL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FTT.COLL.CPTY.TAX</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
