<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FR</product>
<table>FRA.HEDGE.POSITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>INTRODUCTION</p>
            <p>A specific Position file will be maintained for the FRA Hedge transactions where revaluation is required. </p>
            <p>In other words, the position file will be maintained for only those FRA Hedge deals that have value BOOK or CALC in their CALC.OR.BOOK field .Unlike Trade deals, where the position is maintained group wise, the FRA.HEDGE.POSITION is maintained deal wise.</p>
            <p> The FRA.HEDGE.POSTION records among other things whether the deal is a BUY deal or a SELL deal, the rate at which the deal was marked to market (market.rate), the deal rate, the notional amount of the deal and the FRA Period. The unrealized or realized PL as the case may be is maintained online, but posted, wherever necessary, as part of the COB run.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.REVAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the various events during the life time of the FRA Hedge Contract.</p>
            <p>The various values of the field HEDGE.REVAL are as below:</p>
            <p>UNFIXED - The deal is yet to be fixed. Fixing Date is yet to cross.</p>
            <p>FIXED - The deal has been fixed.</p>
            <p>FIXED.REAL - The deal has been fixed and P/L has been realised</p>
            <p>UNFIXED.DUE - The deal is yet to be fixed. Fixing Date has been crossed.</p>
            <p>A suffix ".REV" indicates that the deal has been reversed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PURCHASE.OR.SALE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the FRA Hedge deal  is a purchase or a sale contract</p>
            <p>Values: PURCHASE or SALE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.PROFIT.LOSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Until the Fixing Day, this field will hold the un-realised profit/loss amount computed during the COB. </p>
            <p>If the deal remains un-fixed after crossing the Fixing date, the value held by this field is the last un-realized Profit or Loss amount computed on Fixing Date.</p>
            <p> For deals that have been fixed during the day, the field will hold the realized Profit or Loss amount.</p>
            <p>The un-realized Profit/Loss amount represented by this field will not be booked if the field CALC.OR.BOOK is set to CALC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINCIPAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the principal amount of FRA Hedge Deal</p>
            <p>Update online from the field FRA.AMOUNT of FRA.DEAL</p>
            <p>It holds a signed amount. Negative for SALE contracts</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.REVAL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the revaluation amount should be booked or just calculated.</p>
            <p>Values can be BOOK or CALC</p>
            <p>BOOK - Indicates that the revaluation amount will be booked</p>
            <p>CALC - Indicates that the revaluation amount will only be calculated and not booked.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the number of days between the START.DATE and MATURITY.DATE</p>
            <p>Updated from the field NUMBER.OF.DAYS of FRA.DEAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the Start Date of the FRA Hedge Deal</p>
            <p>Updated online when a contract is first input from the field START.DATE from FRA.DEAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the Id of the FRA Hedge Deal</p>
            <p>Should be a valid ID of FRA hedge contract with CALC.OR.BOOK set to either CALC or BOOK</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the rate at which the deal was marked to market.</p>
            <p>Update only during the COB</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the rate used for discounting </p>
            <p> Based on the settlement formula defined in FRA.PARAMETER, DISC.RATE gets updated in FRA.HEDGE.POSITION. </p>
            <p>When settlement formula is 1, discount rate will be same as the market rate. </p>
            <p>When settlement formula is 2, no discounting happens. DISC.RATE is updated as "NA" </p>
            <p>when settlement formula is 3, discounting rate will be the long rate.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the maturity date of the FRA Hedge Deal</p>
            <p>Updated online when a contract is first input from the field MATURITY.DATE from FRA.DEAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the reference price of the FRA Hedge Deal</p>
            <p>Update online when the contract is first input from the field REFERENCE.PRICE of FRA.DEAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the currency of the FRA Hedge Deal</p>
            <p>Updated online from field CURRENCY of FRA.DEAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The interest rate of the FRA Hedge Deal.</p>
            <p>Updated online from field INTEREST.RATE of FRA.DEAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the dealer Id for the FRA Hedge Deal</p>
            <p>Update online from the field DEALER.DESK of FRA.DEAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the settlement formula defined in FRA.PARAMETER, DISC.PERIOD gets updated in FRA.HEDGE.POSITION </p>
            <p>When settlement formula is 1, discount period will be same as the FRA period </p>
            <p>When settlement formula is 2, no discounting happens. DISC.PERIOD is updated as "NA"  </p>
            <p>when settlement formula is 3,  The discount rate will be the long rate and the discount period will be the one corresponding to the long rate.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.LOSS.EQUIV</field>
<desc>
            <p>The local equivalent of the REVAL.PROFIT.LOSS.</p>
            <p>This field will only be activated when the currency of the deal is not equal to the local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

