<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FR</product>
<table>FRA.AGREEMENT.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to store the types of agreements used in FRA contracts. </p>
            <p>Eg. ISDA, FRABBA etc. </p>
            <p>Each contract must be linked to an agreement type. The field </p>
            <p>AGREEMENT.TYPE</p> on the <p>FRA.DEAL</p> contract is validated against the agreement type definitions on this file and enriched with the associated description. </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.AGREEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the master agreement type is entered but no further information is supplied on the FRA contract this field is used to specify the type of master agreement followed by the date on which the agreement was signed and also the version of the agreement. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be a key to a valid full </p>
            <p>FRA.AGREEMENT.TYPE</p>     record.  </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field used to fully define the FRA agreement type. </p>
            <p>The first line of the description is used for field enrichments. E.g. On the </p>
            <p>FRA.DEAL</p> field <p>AGREEMENT.TYPE</p>.   <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>1-25 Alpha-numeric characters. (Mandatory field. Multi-valued field).</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FRA.AGREEMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID defines the type of agreement used in FRA contracts. </p>
            <p>Eg. ISDA, FRABBA etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-22 Alpha-numeric characters (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Input must be either TYPE for master agreement type or TYPE/DATE//VERSION for full     agreement types. For example ISDA is a master agreement type. There can be other agreement     types such as ISDA/19731112//1988.</p>
            <p>TYPE is mandatory and can be up to six alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>If present, DATE must be eight numeric characters in the form YYYYMMDD.</p>
            <p>If present, VERSION must be two numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISDA.DEF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to show the year of the version of the ISDA definitions. The contents of this field are used in field 14C for SWIFT messages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

