<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DD</product>
<table>DD.CODES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Define the various reason codes along with event as applicable for a clearing system.</p>
            <p>For example in Direct Debit, when a claim is sent after the Mandate lodgment can have different reason code compare to the regular direct debit claim. Similarly return or resubmission of an item can have different code.</p>
            <p>In this application the various codes as applicable for the Event can be defined here and it is defaulted during DD.ITEM creation based on the event. These codes can mapped to the outward file format when the Reason.Code field in DD.ITEM is given in DD.OUT.FORMAT.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CLEARING.SYSTEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id is a clearing system for which the clearing codes are defined here for various events.</p>
            <p>The Events as defined in DD.EVENTS &amp; Codes as defined in DD.REASON.CODES are linked here for a clearing system and based on the events appropriate codes are defaulted in DD.ITEM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Id is 1-10 Alpha Character/s</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DD.EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Define the event along with the appropriate reason code, which will be defaulted in DD.ITEM based on the event.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory -Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Should be a valid record in DD.EVENT</p>
            <p>Duplicate events or Null value -Not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REASON.CODES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Give the reason code as applicable for the given event.</p>
            <p>In case more than one reason code is given for an activity, then the reason code given in the first sub- value is populated in DD.ITEM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory -Associated Sub Value field</p>
            <p>Reason code given should be a valid record in DD.REASON.CODES for the clearing system as given in the ID.</p>
            <p>Null value not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

