<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DD</product>
<table>DD.GENERATE.FILES.XREF</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds temporary files for building the final claim file to be generated for Direct Debit clearing Processing. </p>
            <p>It contains details of the records to be claimed for a particular mandate reference, under a specific DD.PARAMETER id for a particular Claim value date.</p>
            <p>While generating the file online using DD.GENERATE.FILES application, in case the 'UPDATE.FILES' field is given as 'N' then the DD.GENERATE.FILES.XREF record is not cleared and if the field is entered as 'Y' then the  final file gets created and the corresponding DD.GENERATE.FILES.XREF  record is immediately cleared. </p>
            <p>If the final file is generated as an EOD batch process then the DD.GENERATE.FILES.XREF record created , is cleared as soon as the final file gets generated.</p>
            <p>All updates to this file are effected automatically by the system and the only functions users are allowed to perform are (L)IST, (S)EE and (P)RINT.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the total amount of all the records  which are to be included in the final file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARAM.DATE.MANDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This holds the ID of the DD.GENERATE.FILES.XREF record and is of the form</p>
            <p>DD.PARAMETER id "-" Value date of underlying  DD.ITEMs"-" DD.DDI mandate reference</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DD.ITEM.LIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the list of DD.ITEMS included in this particular file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.RECORDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the total number  records which are to be included in the final  file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTPUT.RECORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the records as per the format specified in the DD.OUT.FORMAT application for DATA section, which are to to be included in the final Claim file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

