<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DD</product>
<table>DD.HEADER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file contains records for each claim file processed and provides summary information on the production time, item total and amount total for the file.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PARAM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the file is comprised of:</p>
            <p />
            <p>DD.PARAMETER id - Claim Date - Currency</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 1000-20050626-USD</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System created record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the id of the claim record written to the location specified in the DD.PARAMETER record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The system date and time when the process created the claim file and this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The sum total of the amounts for all the DD.ITEM records passed for inclusion in the claim file. Note that where the DD.DDI record has the field COMBINE.DD.ITEMS set to Yes then the amounts of records being combined will be in this total and will reflect on the first DD.ITEM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEARING.SYSTEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Each clearing system is usually based on a Sort Code and will have a unique DD.PARAMETER id to identify it and it's component files. This is the record id of the DD.PARAMETER file which controls the options and settings of this claim file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the firect of the claim file. Since the DD.HEADER is normally produced for outgoing files this would normally be OUTWARD. However, if local devlopments update the file for incoming then the direction would be INWARD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System created value</p>
            <p>Either a value of OUTWARD or INWARD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.RECORDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number or DD.ITEM records included in the claim file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The T24 User id of the person who ran the process which created the file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

