<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DD</product>
<table>DD.ITEM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a live file and has the details related to the Claim.</p>
            <p>The details for this file are taken from the Forward STMT.ENTRY which created this DD.ITEM and along with the underlying DD.DDI/ DD.STANDALONE detail.</p>
            <p>This is the base application for creating outward claim file and the field name can be used in DD.OUT.FORMAT and the details are populated in the outward file. Similarly using the field details available here, other DD application such as DD.STANDALONE or DD.DDI can be referred.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MANDATE.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This contains the underlying Mandate reference. When combining the DD.ITEM claims this field is used as part of the criteria for matching.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLAIM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Claim accounting is generated on the value date and this contains the date on which the claim entry is raised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Our reference as available in the STMT.ENTRY is updated here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESUB.DD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>When an ITEM is returned and resubmitted, the returned DD.ITEM will have the Resubmitted DD.ITEM reference id here for cross reference.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Currency of the Account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the last claim is made, taken from the mandate (DD.DDI) when processing the last item.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Direction of the Claim.</p>
            <p>Defaults from the mandate which relates to this item (DD.DDI)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REASON.CODE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The record id of the DD.REASON.CODES which is used to provide enrichment for the REASON.CODE field since the codes themselves are usually too brief to enable a visual understanding of their meaning.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Uniquely identifies each claim item.</p>
            <p>The reference number is automatically generated with the creation of the DD.ITEM.</p>
            <p>Explanation of Reference Number format: DDYYDDDNNNNN where:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.DD.ITEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a DD.ITEM is resubmitted, the new DD.ITEM created will have the original DD.ITEM reference id recorded here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the forward Statement entry id through which the DD.ITEM was created. Other required details for this file such as Contract reference, Amount,Value date, Booking Date,Our reference, Their reference etc are taken from this Forward.entry.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will have the value as INTERNAL, when a DD.ITEM is created for an internal DD.DDI.</p>
            <p>That is, when the REQUEST.TYPE field in DD.DDI is INTERNAL. No Input field. Update by System.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the date on which the DD.ITEM is created. ie. System.Date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The status related to DD.ITEM which can only be updated by the System.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTPUT.REC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of the claim fiel that this DD.ITEM has been included in.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This contains the value date of the claim or the date on which the amount to be claimed. This is updated from the value date as available in STMT.ENTRY.</p>
            <p>Number of days as given in Claim.Date.Prd is deducted from this value date to determine the file generation date and file is generated on that day with the file date as this Value date. The claim accounting will be raised on this value date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REASON.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reason code as applicable for the Status is updated here.  The reason codes is defaulted from DD.REASON.CODES as applicable for the Status and Clearing system is defaulted here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the status is changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THEIR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Their reference as available in the forward STMT.ENTRY is populated here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSP.FT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID of the FT, which is generated during the suspense processing on CLAIM date. </p>
            <p>No Input field. Update by System.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARAM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of the DD.PARAMETER which was used in the creation process of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS.HIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a Status in DD.ITEM is changed, this field is updated with the old status along with the date on which it is changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Currency market as available in the STMT.ENTRY is updated here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the contract id which is linked to this DD.ITEM.</p>
            <p>The contract reference can be either MG id incase the DD.DDI is linked to MORTGAGE contract or DD.DDI id for standalone DD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the T24 account number for the mandate received and refers to the account where the claim amount to be credited.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account Officer populated in STMT.ENTRY is defaulted here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This has the Direct Debit Claim amount and this has to be mapped to outward claim file for the amount to be claimed.</p>
            <p>This amount is updated from the STMT.ENTRY local currency amount for which the DD.ITEM is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The is the date on which the STMT.ENTRY is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

