<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DD</product>
<table>DD.IN.FORMAT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Each clearing system has their prescribed file format for Outward &amp; Inward claim submission and return.  </p>
            <p>Incoming claims can be processed directly using a local Accounting interface without creating DD.ITEM.</p>
            <p>However for future reference, claim details are required then the using a local interface, which should deconstruct the incoming file with the details as given in DD.IN.FORMAT and map the same to DD.ITEM.</p>
            <p>Hence in this application, the field name related to DD.ITEM along with the field position in incoming file from which the details to be taken can be given . Also routine can be attached to populate the values which is not available in the incoming claim file.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DATA.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>If FIELD.DELIMITER is blank then this field indicates the starting position for the data to be extracted.</p>
            <p>If FIELD.DELIMITER is set then this field indicates the field number for the delimiter.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p>1-5 Numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.DELIMITER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The delimiter used to deconstruct the data from the inward file contents. If the field is blank, then the DATA.LENGTH becomes mandatory. If the delimiter is repesent as &lt;NNN&gt;, then it indicates that the delimiter is specified in ASCII character and the given value inside the bracket is used as CHARX(NNN) during decoding of data.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>1-5 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes a DD Inward  format file and same is used as an enrichment when it is referred in other application.</p>
            <p>Descriptions may be entered in each of the languages defined in the LANGUAGE table.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTI.VAL.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the incoming file has multi values and this field can be used to specify the multi value no to which the data can be mapped.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>1-5 Alphanumeric Characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.VAL.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the incoming file has Sub values and this field can be used to specify the Sub value numer to which the data can be mapped.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>1-5 Alphanumeric Characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEARING.SYSTEM.</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id to this application is a clearing system which is defined in DD.REASON.CODES application.</p>
            <p>This can be linked to DD.PARAMETER in inward file format field. However local interface has to be used to deconstruct the incoming claim file details.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in DD.REASON.CODES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the field name to which this data to be mapped. Currently the details can be mapped to DD.ITEM hence it should contain a valid field name from DD.ITEM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p>Should be a valid field name in DD.ITEM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>If FIELD.DELIMITER is blank, then this field indicates the length of the data to be mapped to DD.ITEM.</p>
            <p>If FIELD.DELIMITER is present, then this field is insignificant.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>1-5 Numeric character</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.MAP.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the routine which should be used to populate the field value in DD.ITEM</p>
            <p>The routine given here should be prefixed with "@".</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Should be a valid record in PGM.FILE</p>
            <p>Routine should be cataloged and VOC pointer should be available.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

