<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DD</product>
<table>DD.PURGE.FILES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to purge the records in DD.DDI, DD.STANDALONE, DD.ITEM, DD.LINKS,  DD.PROCESS.LIST, DD.ACTIVITY DD.STANDALONE.FQU.LIST AND DD.HEADER by specifying criteria, which can accept a valid field name from the respective application along with a value.</p>
            <p>Records in the application can be purged on line by using "V" function or during End of day activities (by use of batch job DD.PURGE.FILES)</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DD.PURGE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name of the main record on the file.</p>
            <p>The single record on this file must always be named 'SYSTEM'.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Can only be 'SYSTEM'. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This contains the name of the Field used for selecting the records to be purged. To be used in combination with fields Appl opr and Appl Value for the purpose of selecting records for purging.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Associated sub value field till Appl. Value</p>
            <p>Must hold valid field name from Application mentioned in Appl.Name.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This holds the name of the Application for which purging is required</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Can only hold one of the following values</p>
            <p>DD.DDI, DD.STANDALONE, DD.ITEM, DD.LINKS,  DD.PROCESS.LIST, DD.ACTIVITY DD.STANDALONE.FQU.LIST AND DD.HEADER</p>
            <p>Associated Multi-value field with fields from Appl.Name to Appl.Value</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.OPR</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is the operand  used to decide the selection criteria for purging records of the Application mentioned in Appl.Name in combination with the value specified in Appl.Value field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>It can hold any of the following values : EQ, GE, GT, LE, LK, LT, NE</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input Field</p>
            <p>It is an Associated Sub-value Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is used to specify the value of the field specified in Appl. Name in combination with field Appl.Opr.  based on which the records will be selected for purging.</p>
            <p>For example.</p>
            <p>To purge records of DD.DDI for mandates which are cancelled  the following can be the set of values :</p>
            <p>1. 1 APPL.NAME...... DD.DDI</p>
            <p>2. 1. 1 APPL.FIELD.. STATUS</p>
            <p>3. 1. 1 APPL.OPR.... EQ</p>
            <p>4. 1. 1 APPL.VALUE.. CANCELLED</p>
            <p>To purge records of DD.STANDALONE  for records which were created before 1st Jan 2003 which are matured the following can be the set of values :</p>
            <p>1. 1 APPL.NAME...... DD.STANDALONE</p>
            <p>2. 1. 1 APPL.FIELD.. STATUS</p>
            <p>3. 1. 1 APPL.OPR.... EQ</p>
            <p>4. 1. 1 APPL.VALUE.. MATURED</p>
            <p>2. 1. 2 APPL.FIELD.. CREATE.DATE</p>
            <p>3. 1. 2 APPL.OPR.... LT</p>
            <p>4. 1. 2 APPL.VALUE.. 20030101</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>It is an Associated Sub-Value Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

