<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>GA</product>
<table>GAC.ACCOUNTS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is available only in a T24 Administration Account.</p>
            <p>Each record is used to control linking / unlinking to a UniVerse / jBASE account representing a business entity.</p>
            <p>The actions LINK and UNLINK may be performed on an account. The action is performed when the record is verified.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows whether the link has been established or not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the UniVerse account / arbitrary name in jBASE, which contains the business entity's data. Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>It must be the name of a Universe account / jBASE account with T24 installed.</p>
            <p>The release of T24 in the business entity must be the same as</p>
            <p>that in the admin. account (Case sensitive)</p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUBLISH.DIRECTORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines the action to be taken when this record is verified.</p>
            <p>LINK : Connect/Re-link the business entity to the admin. account.</p>
            <p>UNLINK : Break the link to the business entity</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Short input of "L" or "U" is permitted.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 6 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted: LINK, UNLINK</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi-valued field. There is an occurrence for each company in the linked entity.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field automatically generated by the system. Contains the entity's Company code.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the business entity.</p>
            <p>This is a multi valued standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 20 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

