<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FD</product>
<table>FD.APPROVE.POOLING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>OVERVIEW</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The selection of the fiduciary orders to be approved and placed may be very tedious for the dealer as each order must be processed individually. In order to reduce the number of manipulations, a new facility is implemented, allowing processing several transactions in one shot.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The approval step must be simplified. It must allow the dealer, in the one hand, selecting the fiduciary orders to be processed according to his own-defined criteria, and, in the other hand, defining the action to be applied on each order by eventually using a bulk process.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Hereafter are the actions that can be applied by the dealer to orders, either individually or by group:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Approval of an open order including principal change and reimbursement of     notice contracts</p>
            <p />
            <p>Cancellation of an already approved order, provided that the pool the     order belongs to is not yet closed</p>
            <p />
            <p />     Change of the number of the pool group automatically assigned by the system<p /><p /></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>POOLING.ORDER.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the reference of the file FD.APPROVE.POOLING. As there is no effective record attached to this application, this reference is virtual and set to the value SYSTEM.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />up to 60 alphanumeric characters <p /><p /><p>Field Properties</p><p /><p /><p /><p />Standard T24 alphanumeric field.<p /><p /><p>A maximum of 60 characters may be entered.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GL.POOLING.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows to globally change the pooling status for each selected orders (GL. POOLING.STATUS is moved to the field POOLING.STATUS of each selected orders).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>APPROVED or CANCEL for new Notice and new Fixed orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>ACCEPTED for principal changes or reimbursements of Notice orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POOLING.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Holds the status of order for pooling purposes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>APPROVED,     ACCEPTED (only for Notice changes) and CANCEL are the only allowable input. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input     of CANCEL is only possible when the previous POOLING.STATUS was APPROVED and     the GROUP.STATUS on FD.POOL.GROUP is not CLOSED, or the previous     POOLING.STATUS was AMENDED</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This     is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GL.POOLED.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows to globally apply a new pool group to each selected orders (GL.POOLED.GROUP is moved to the field POOLED.GROUP of each selected orders). </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The POOLED.GROUP can be amended for MANUAL orders only. An existing group number can be entered, provided the currency, value date and maturity date of the order are the same as those on FD.POOL.GROUP record for the pool group number. If no suitable group exists and the order is to be removed from the allocated group, input of NEW will cause a new group number to be allocated.  </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Once the order has been approved by the dealer, the group number cannot be amended, unless the approval is cancelled.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>10 digit group number comprised of: 5 digit julian date followed by a 5 digit sequence number or NEW.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input allowed when POOLING is AUTO, NONE or SPLIT. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The number entered must exist on the FD.POOL.GROUP file, and the Currency, Value date and Maturity Date on the order must be the same as that on the FD.POOL.GROUP record. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The GROUP.STATUS on FD.POOL.GROUP cannot be CLOSED</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Together with fields CURRENCY, VALUE.DATE, MATURITY.DATE, AMOUNT, POOLED.GROUP, POOLING.STATUS, DEALER.INSTR, FID.TYPE, defines details of the orders for preparing the pooling process.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Multi Selected orders from the enquiry.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>15-18 alphanumeric FID.ORDER ID. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date the order is due to begin, i.e. the date the customer will be debited with the principal.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The end date of FIXED term deposits, and the number of days notice required to be given before reimbursement of a NOTICE contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-8     standard date format or 1-3 number of days notice.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This     is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The principal to be deposited by the customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14     standard amount in the format of the CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>This     is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Identifies the currency of the deposit requested by the customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-3 SWIFT currency     code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a NOINPUT     field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Special instructions regarding the order for the attention of the dealer making the placement.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35     alpha numeric SWIFT characters. Multi valued field. </p>
            <p>This     is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FID.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of Fiduciary deposit requested by the customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"FIXED"     or "NOTICE" or any abbreviation thereof. </p>
            <p>Input     must be defined in field FID.TYPE of FD.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>Input     must be defined on the FD.GROUP.CONDITION record which applies to the     customer in the field FIDUCIARY TYPE</p>
            <p>This     is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POOLED.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The number of the Pool Group assigned by the system or the user to determine the grouping of orders.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>10     digit group number comprised of: 5 digit julian date followed by a 5 digit     sequence number or NEW (Optional Input) </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No     input allowed where POOLING is AUTO, NONE or SPLIT. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The     number entered must exist on the FD.POOL.GROUP file, and the Currency, Value     date and Maturity Date on the order must be the same as that on the     FD.POOL.GROUP record. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The     GROUP.STATUS on FD.POOL.GROUP cannot be CLOSED</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This     is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

