<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FD</product>
<table>FD.CUST.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows details for customers using the Fiduciary system to be recorded. </p>
            <p>A customer can express a preference for banks where the placement should be made, and express banks where the placement should not be made. Any preferred bank defined for the customer of an order will used as the default FID.BANK in the placement, if there is only one order used to generate the Placement. </p>
            <p>Limits can be expressed for particular banks and an overall bank limit, to allow the customer's exposure for the placement to be controlled.  These figures are currently held for information only and do not have any effect on the placement of the Fiduciary. </p>
            <p>Customers with no Mandate should be specified on the FD.CUST.DETAILS table. A customer group number for reporting purposes can also be specified on this table. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MANDATE.HELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies what kind of mandate the customer has signed :</p>
            <p>The control of the signature is done not only on the fact that the mandate is signed or not but also on the nature of the signed contract. The various forms of signature are of three types:</p>
            <p>
                <p>Not signed</p>
            </p>
            <p>Signed within the group</p>
            <p>Signed inside and outside the group</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Optional input)</p>
            <p>A   maximum of two alpha characters may be entered   </p>
            <p>is a specific value meaning that mandate is signed inside and outside the group</p>
            <p>The   following values are permitted :</p>
            <p>   (The blank value means ALL, mandate is signed for both placement inside   and outside the group)</p>
            <p>NO   </p>
            <p>(No mandate signed)</p>
            <p>IN</p>
            <p>(Mandate signed   only for placements inside the group)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.INT.BASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the special interest calculation method for deposits within the group </p> <![CDATA[ ]]><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Input must be       defined in INTEREST.BASIS</p><p>1 alpha character       may be entered</p><p>The following values are permitted :</p><p>A</p>(360/360) <p>B</p>(366/360) <p>E</p>(366/365) <p>F</p>(360/365)</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.GROUP.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to allocate an arbitrary group number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 5 numeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.ACCT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Minimum amount to keep on the current account. This field is used when calculating the amount to be invested, both for new and renewed deposits.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Mandatory input if one the fields of the multi-valued set is populated)</p>
            <p>1 14 standard       amount in the format of the CURRENCY defined in the previous field</p>
            <p>A maximum of 14 characters may be entered</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.DEV.COD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the method of variation to apply to the rate.</p>
            <p>This, will define if the interest rate of inside group notice deposit</p>
            <p> is changed automatically </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be       defined in FD.RATE.DEVIATION</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field, for the Outside group Contract and for inside group FIXED deposit </p>
            <p>4 alpha characters       </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FID.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current amount of funds placed with the associated LIMIT.BANK in local currency. For future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 14 numeric amount in local currency. (System field No input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIDUCIARY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of Fiduciary deposit for which the customer has specificities</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Mandatory input if one the fields of the multi-valued set is populated)</p>
            <p>No duplicate is       allowed</p>
            <p>A maximum of 6 characters may be entered</p>
            <p>Input must be       defined in field FID.TYPE of FD.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>Must be a key of FD.CHARGE.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>Input must be       defined on the FD.GROUP.CONDITION record which applies to the customer in       the field FIDUCIARY TYPE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREF.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>For the associated PREFERRED.CCY this field allows all the banks where the customer prefers the funds to be placed to be specified. </p>
            <p>If the customer makes a Fiduciary deposit and the order is the only in the pooled group used to generate the placement, the first preferred bank in the list will be used as the default FID.BANK when the placement is made, providing it is in the same currency as the PREFERRED.CCY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric customer number    or 3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic. (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>No duplicates allowed within one currency.</p>
            <p>At least one bank is mandatory when the associated PREFERRED.CCY is present.</p>
            <p>Customer must exist on the Customer file and be defined as a BANK on the ACCOUNT.CLASS file.</p>
            <p>Cannot be defined as an EXCLUDED.BANK.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System field no input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of funds currently placed with the associated LIMIT.BANK. For future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-character standard SWIFT currency code.  (This is a NOINPUT, system field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDED.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines any banks where the customer does not wish funds to be placed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric customer code     or 3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the Customer file and be defined as a BANK on the ACCOUNT.CLASS table.</p>
            <p>No duplicates allowed.</p>
            <p>No empty values allowed.</p>
            <p>Cannot be defined as a PREFERRED.BANK.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the margin to be applied to the Standard spread.  It must only be processed for inside group deposits. It cant be used without </p>
            <p>RATE.CATEG</p>
            <p> and must not be populated if </p>
            <p>RATE.CATEG is equal to "MANUAL" </p>
            <p>or</p>"<p>STANDARD"</p><p>. The default value is either taken from the field </p><p>RATE.SPREAD</p><p> in </p><p>FD.CUST.DETAILS</p><p>, if any, or </p> is <p>"0". </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>(Optional field)</p><p>1  10 numeric       rate</p><p>It stands for a       percentage that may be prefixed by a sign (+ or -)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.ACCT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency of the minimum amount to keep on the current account. This field is used when calculating the amount to be invested, both for new and renewed deposits. Fields MIN.ACCT.CCY to MIN.ACCT.AMT form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Mandatory input if one the fields of the multi-valued set is populated)</p>
            <p>3-alpha character       SWIFT standard currency code. </p>
            <p>No duplicate       currencies allowed</p>
            <p>Must exist on the       CURRENCY file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>It defines the way to calculate the interest rate for each currency. </p>
            <p>Used only for inside group contracts</p>
            <p>Existing calculation methods: </p>
            <p>BID : Standard rate or Standard rate +/- Margin on Standard spread</p>
            <p>STANDARD: Standard rate  Standard spread +/- Margin on Standard spread</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>(Optional field)</p>
            <p>10 alpha characters       may be entered       </p>
            <p>Valid       calculation method</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted :</p>
            <p>                     BID , STANDARD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RND.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percent of the standard rounding to apply</p>
            <p>Default is blank i.e. 100%</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1  5 numeric rate</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREFERRED.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The customer can express banks where he would prefer the funds to be placed. The preferred bank can be defined for a specific currency or whatever the currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3-alpha character SWIFT   standard currency code. (Optional field:   is a specific value meaning   that the preferred bank is defined whatever the currency)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No duplicate currencies   allowed</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on the   CURRENCY file</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RNEW.AMT.MET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This information determines the method used for the calculation amount to renew</p> <![CDATA[  ]]><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>(Optional field)</p><p>11 alpha characters may be entered</p><p>The following values are permitted :</p><p>PRINCIPAL</p><p>(principal amount)</p><p>INCOME</p><p>(net at maturity)</p><p> INCOME</p><p>(net at maturity + account balance in value date)</p><p>NET</p><p>(take the smallest of the net at maturity and the maximum renewable)</p><p>PPAL</p><p>(take the smallest of the principal amount and the maximum renewable) </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximum amount of funds in local currency the customer may have placed with the associated LIMIT.BANK. </p>
            <p>This field is currently used for information only and will not be checked by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric customer number       or 3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Mandatory if the associated LIMIT.BANK is present.</p>
            <p>Not allowed if there is no LIMIT.BANK specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current amount of funds placed in the associated OS.CCY with the associated LIMIT.BANK.  For future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric amount.  (This is a NOINPUT, system field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency for which are defined the fields :</p>
            <p>RATE.DEV.CODE</p>
            <p>RATE.MARGIN</p>
            <p>RNEW.AMT.MET</p>
            <p>RND.TYPE</p>
            <p>RND.PERCENT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-alpha characters       SWIFT standard currency code</p>
            <p>No duplicate       currencies allowed  is a       specific value, means that the following fields are defined for all       currency</p>
            <p>Must exist on the       CURRENCY file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.OS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current amount of funds currently placed with the associated LIMIT.BANK in local currency. For future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric amount in local currency.  (This is a NOINPUT, system field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of the customer for which the details are defined. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric customer number     or 3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the customer to specify banks with an individual limit for placement of funds. </p>
            <p>This field is currently used for information only and will not be checked by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric customer number     or 3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the customer file and as a BANK on the ACCOUNT.CLASS table.</p>
            <p>No duplicates allowed.</p>
            <p>No empty values allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RND.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The standard rounding of the amount is parameterized according to the currency in the table FD.FID.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>This field allows the system to use the rounding method used for deposits inside the group even for deposits outside the group.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Optional field)</p>
            <p>6 alpha characters may be entered</p>
            <p>Must be a key of FD.CHARGE.PARAMETER</p> <![CDATA[  ]]></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERALL.BANK.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximum amount of funds the customer may have placed with any one Fiduciary Bank. </p>
            <p>This field is currently used for information only and will not be checked by the system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric amount in local currency. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

