<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FD</product>
<table>FD.FID.CURRENCY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to define details of amounts that are required as a minimum and a multiple of the currency for a Fiiduciary deposit. </p>
            <p>For each currency used for Fiduciary transcations a record should be defined specifying the minimum amount allowed for deposit, and the amount of which the order should be a multiple. When orders are input, any principal or principal change not satisfying these parameters will require an override. When automatic renewals are generated and the new principal is based on income, the new principal will be rounded according to the currency multiple. </p>
            <p>Any category code or type that is to be defined on the FD.GROUP.CONDITION file must be defined in this application first. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>UPTO.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Upper limit of amount level</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-14 standard amount       in the format of the CURRENCY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>multi-valued       field at both its own level and </p>
            <p>FID.TYPE</p>
            <p>       level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The       last level (which may be the unique level) is identified by a blank value       in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTIPLE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the amount that the principal, or principal change amount for an order of the CURRENCY defined must be a multiple of. </p>
            <p>Any principal, or principal chnage amount which is not a multiple of this amount will require an override when input in the FD.FID.ORDER. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric standard amount field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TENOR.EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Event associated with the tenor.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>6       alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>multi-valued       field at both TENOR level and FID.TYPE level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input       not allowed for fixed deposit</p>
            <p />s         <p /><p>The following values are permitted:</p><p /><p /><p>BLANK</p><p /><p /><p>CHANGE</p><p /><p /><p>INIT</p><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the minimum amount allowed in the currency as a deposit amount. </p>
            <p>Any principal amount which is less than this amount when input in the FD.FID.ORDER will require an override. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric standard amount. (Mandatory field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TENOR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Deposit tenor (1M, )</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4       alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p />
            <p>multi-valued       field at both its own level and FID.TYPE level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The       blank value can only be used when there is only one tenor define</p>
            <p>.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input       not allowed for notice deposits       </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Minimal band to invest for a deposit placed at any bank. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-12 standard amount       in the format of the CURRENCY</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>multi-valued       field at both UPTO.AMT level and FID.TYPE level</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the currency for which the rules defined are applied </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 alpha character SWIFT standard currency code. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency code used to format the amounts defined. </p>
            <p>Defaulted from the record id, CURRENCY.CODE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alpha standard SWIFT currency code - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FID.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the fiduciary type or category code for which the minimum and multiple amounts are defined.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 6 characters may be entered</p>
            <p />
            <p> Must be a key of FD.CHARGE.PARAMETER</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>multi-valued field       associated with fields to MIN.AMT</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Minimum amount to invest for a deposit made by any customer and placed at any bank</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1-12       standard amount in the format of the CURRENCY</p>
            <p />
            <p>multi-valued       field at both TENOR level and FID.TYPE level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

