<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FD</product>
<table>FD.GROUP.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds details of commission and charge defaults and calculations for a group of fiduciary deposits or an Portfolio or an individual customer. The type and associated minimum, maximum and percentage of the calculated amount to be taken can be specified. </p>
            <p>A specific set of conditions can be defined for a customer, or a group, defined on the FD.GEN.CONDITION file. The group applicable to the customer is defined on the CUSTOMER.CHARGE file, in the ACTUAL.GROUP field, associated with the FIDUCIARY application. If a seperate customer condition is applicable, a record will be defined with  an id of C-customer no, and this will take precedence over the customer group. </p>
            <p>For a specific commission type, a minimuim and maximum commission can be applied, and also a percentage of the calculated commission can be taken. Fiduciary commission calculations are defined on the FD.COMMISSION.TYPE table. The commission type specified will be used as the default when the FD.FID.ORDER is input. The commission type is associated with either a CATEGORY code or the type (i.e. FIXED or NOTICE). </p>
            <p>Charges are defined on either the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE table, and for each possible charge type, a percentage can be specified. Another percentage to be taken for all other charge types can also be defined. </p>
            <p>ID format for the group condition can be "NNN" ,"C-NNNNNN" or "P-NNNNNN-N"</p>
            <p>If a portfolio level record exists in FD.GROUP.CONDITION, for any transactions involving the portfolio, the Commission and charges defined in the record will apply</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MAX.COMM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum amount of commission that can be applied in one commission period for the associated DEF.COMM.CD. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The maximum commission amount can be specified in any currency. If the currency is not the same as the order currency, it will be converted at the mid rate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric amount. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.PEN.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Defines the percentage of the calculated </p>
            <p>DEF.PEN.COMM.CD</p>
            <p> to be applied to the customer.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The percentage defined is taken after calculating the default penalty commission amount based on the </p>
            <p>FD.COMMISSION.TYPE</p>
            <p> definition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>0-100 numeric percentage. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if </p>
            <p>DEF.PEN.COMM.CD</p>       is populated  <p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The percentage of the calculated OTH.CHRG.CD to be applied to the customer at the associated CHARGE.EVENT of the order. </p>
            <p>The percentage specified will be taken for the associated OTHR.CHRG.CD and CHARGE.EVENT if it exists on the order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-100 numeric percentage (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if associated OTHR.CHRG.CD is present.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.MIN.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency in which the maximum and/or minimum commission amount for the associated DEF.COMM.CD is specified. </p>
            <p>The system will first check for the currency of the deal in this sub-valued field, then look for the local currency. If neither of these is found the first definition currency is used as the default. The amount will be converted to the deal currency at mid-rate where the currency is different. </p>
            <p>A maximum and minimum commission amount for the commission code specified can be defined. The minimum and maximum can be taken at either interest movement, principal movement or both, as specified on the FD.CHARGE.PARAMETER table. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 character standard SWIFT currency code. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Mandatory if MIN.COMM.AMT or MAX.COMM.AMT is defined.</p>
            <p>Duplicate currencies not allowed for each FIDUCIARY type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date and optional frequency for the interest settlement for all linked placement contracts. </p>
            <p>The interest settlement date may be announced by the fiduciary bank as a one off payment date, or on a regular frequency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 character standard date input followed by5 character standard frequency (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be after the LAST.INT.SET.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The last interest rate applied at the LAST.INT.SET.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 11 numeric rate (No input field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REST.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the percentage to be applied to the calculated charges not defined in OTHR.CHRG.CD for the associated Fiduciary Type. </p>
            <p>This percentage will be applied to all other charges which are not defined in the OTHR.CHRG.CD fiedl for the associated Fiduciary Type. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-100 numeric percentage. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.COMM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum amount of commission to be applied for the current group and the associated DEF.COMM.CD. </p>
            <p>The minimum commission amount can be specified in any currency (MIN.MAX.CCY). If the currency is not the same as the order it will be converted at the mid rate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric amount (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the percentage of the calculated DEF.COMM.CD to be applied to the customer. </p>
            <p>The percentage defined is taken after calculating the default commission amount based on the FD.COMMISSION.TYPE definition. No percentage specified implies that the full commission amount will be taken. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-100 numeric percentage (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.CHRG.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The charge types to be used as a default if required for the associated FIDUCIARY.TYPE. </p>
            <p>Charges can be defaulted on the order if specified to do so on the FD.CHARGE.PARAMETER application. If requested, the codes specified here associated with the FIDUCIARY.TYPE and the associated event will be used. This field should also be used if percentages of charge codes are to be defined for the group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-11 alphanumeric charge type (Optional input)</p>
            <p>No duplicates allowed for a given fiduciary type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.PEN.COMM.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the default penalty commission type for the associated category or fiduciary type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2-11 alphanumeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the </p>
            <p>FD.COMMISSION.TYPE</p>       file.  <p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIDUCIARY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The TYPE or CATEGORY code of the order for which the commission defaults apply. </p>
            <p>The type or category code entered must be defined on the FD.CHARGE.PARAMETER file. This holds details of how and when the commission is calculated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>FIXED or NOTICE or 1-3 digit group number (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Must exist on FD.CHARGE.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>No null values allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of the FD.GEN.CONDITION which applies to the customer of the Fid Order, or the number of the customer used as a key to the FD.GROUP.CONDITION file. </p>
            <p>In addition , a Date can be appended with a hyphen in condition that a corresponding CONDITION.PRIORITY record and XX.GEN.CONDITION record exists with this date . </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-3 numeric group number    or "C-" followed by 1 to 6 digit customer number     or 3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic (Mandatory input).   If the ID  'C- CUSTOMER NUMBER'  is defined for an individual   customer, it gets automatically defaulted to the   field ACTUAL.GROUP pertaining to FD application (if defined)  in the   customer's  CUSTOMER.CHARGE  record. </p>
            <p>If a customer number is specified, the customer must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>If a group number is specified, it must exist on the FD.GEN.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will define the time at which the associated charge will be taken. </p>
            <p>The charge can either be taken whenever: </p>
            <p>          - a principal movement takes place;           - the contract matures;           - the drawdown takes place. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The only options are DRAWDOWN, MATURITY or CHANGE. (optional input)</p>
            <p>Default value will be DRAWDOWN.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the last interest settlement. </p>
            <p>When an interest settlement date is reached, the interest are written to the FD.GROUP.PAYEMENT.HIST file with the key, of            Fid Bank . Curreny . Days Notice . Settlement date and the settlement date will be recorded on in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 standard date characters (No input field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>System override messages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 35 alphanumeric characters (No input field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.COMM.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default commission type for the associated Fiduciary type. </p>
            <p>Details of commission calculations are defined for the COMM.CD on the FD.COMMISSION.TYPE table. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-11 alphanumeric FD Commission type. (Mandatory field)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the FD.COMMISSION.TYPE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

