<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FD</product>
<table>FD.GROUP.PAYMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds details of the next interest settlement date, and the interest rates applicable for all notice contracts of a given currency and notice period with a particular fiduciary bank. </p>
            <p>New interest rates in the current interest period can be specified when announced by the Fiduciary bank. The current interest rate, and previous rates for the current period are also stored. </p>
            <p>Interest settlement dates announced by the fiduciary bank can be specified as a single payment date, or a date with an associated frequency. Interest settlement dates with a frequency are cycled forward by the system at the appropriate date. The FD.GROUP.PAYMENT record holds details of interest rates for the current interest period only. At the end of each interest settlement, the details of rates are written to the FD.GROUP.PAYMENT.HIST file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NEW.RATE.EFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The effective date of the associated NEW.INT.RATE. </p>
            <p>Together with NEW.INT.RATE, these fields allow future rate changes to be entered. The fiduciary end of day will automatically cycle the interest rate at the NEW.RATE.EFF date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8-character standard date field (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be in ascending date order.</p>
            <p>No input allowed without associated NEW.INT.RATE.</p>
            <p>Date must be greater than or equal to todays date.</p>
            <p>Cannot be prior to the LAST.INT.SET.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Together with NEW.RATE.EFF defines future rate changes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-11 numeric rate type. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>No input allowed without associated NEW.RATE.EFF.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System override messages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.INT.SET.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date of the last interest settlement. </p>
            <p>When an interest settlement date is reached, the interest are written to the FD.GROUP.PAYMENT.HIST file with the key, of </p>
            <p>           Fid Bank . Currency . Days Notice . Settlement date </p>
            <p>and the settlement date will be recorded on in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 standard date characters</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORWARD.BACKWARD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the method that will be followed if the cycled interest settlement date is a non working day in the relative currency.</p>
            <p>The following provides an explanation of the various input values for this field:</p>
            <p>Null = Calendar  The sysem will use the same date irrespective of whether dates cycled are working days or not.</p>
            <p>1 = Forward  The system will cycle forward to the next available working day.</p>
            <p>2 = Backward  The system will cycle to the previous working day.</p>
            <p>3 = Fwd Same Month  The system will cycle forward unless the next working day unless it falls in the next month.  In this case, it will cycle to the previous working day.</p>
            <p>Validation</p>
            <p>
                <p>A single numeric value in the range 1-3 or Null.</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null = Calendar</p>
            <p>1 = Forward</p>
            <p>2 = Backward</p>
            <p>3 = Forward same month</p>
            <p>Single Value  Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Together with the associated RATE.EFF.DATE, specifies the effective interest rates during the current period, prior to the current system date. </p>
            <p>The interest rates applicable to the current interest period are stored with the associated effective date. For a new record, interest rates prior to the system date can be input. After authorisation, this field cannot be changed. </p>
            <p>When an interest settlement is made the interest rate will be set to the last interest rate of the previous interest period. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-11 numeric rate type. (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days prior to a new interest rate effective date, for a rate change confirmation to be sent. </p>
            <p>The default value of for the number of days is taken from the FD.PARAMETER file in the field DEF.RATE.NOTICE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 to 99 number of days (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.RATE.APPLIED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The last interest rate applied at the LAST.INT.SET.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-11 numeric rate</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The description of the FD.GROUP.PAYMENT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 alphanumeric characters.  Multi language field  (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The effective date of the associated INTEREST.RATE in the current interest period. </p>
            <p>The effective date of the associated INTEREST.RATE can be entered on a new record, and cannot be changed after authorisation.  When an interest settlement date is reached and the FD.GROUP.PAYMENT record is cycled, the previous period interest rate is stored with an effective date of the last settlement date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8-character standard date field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Dates must be in ascending order.</p>
            <p>No input allowed without an associated interest rate.</p>
            <p>Date cannot be greater than todays date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SETTLE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date and optional frequency for the interest settlement for all linked placement contracts. </p>
            <p>The interest settlement date may be announced by the fiduciary bank as a one off payment date, or on a regular frequency. </p>
            <p>When multiple NOTICE orders are pooled onto a single placement, and an order is being reimbursed, the interest for this order will be paid on the date held in this field, regardless of the date on which the order was reduced to zero principal. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>            8-character standard date input followed by 5-character standard frequency (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be after the LAST.INT.SET.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CHG.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Defines if automatic allocation of INTEREST.RATE since END.OF.DAY is used to calculate the new interest rate of Notice Deposit. Only for inside group notice deposit, and by bank</p>
            <p>. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered</p>
            <p />
            <p>The following values       are permitted: YES, NO</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.CCY.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fiduciary Bank, Currency and number of days NOTICE used to identify the record containing the interest details. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 digit customer number         or              3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic followed by "." followed by 3 character standard SWIFT currency code followed by "." followed by 0-999 number of days notice (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The customer element of the key must exist on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>The currency must exist on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current interest rate applicable. </p>
            <p>The current interest rate is held in this field. This must be entered for a new record, and cannot be changed once input.  Interest rate changes should be entered using the NEW.INT.RATE and NEW.RATE.EFF fields. The CURRENT.INT.RATE will be updated at the NEW.RATE.EFF date during the Fiduciary end of day. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-11 numeric rate type. (Mandatory field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.PRIOR.CONF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days prior to a new interest rate effective date, for a rate change confirmation to be sent. </p>
            <p>The default value for the number of days is taken from the FD.PARAMETER file in the field DEF.RATE.NOTICE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-99 number of days  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

