<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FD</product>
<table>FD.MATURITY.DATES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>OVERVIEW</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>FD.MATURITY.DATES</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>FD.MATURITY.DATES is used to define, by year/month, the standard maturity dates. Furthermore, a parameter describes the way the adjustment of the maturity date should be done.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> When a frequency (</p>
            <p>1M, 3M</p>
            <p>, &amp;#8230;) is used to key in the maturity of a contract, the system calculates the resulting date by taking into account the holidays in the country related to the deal currency. It, then, compares this date with the dates stored in the corresponding record of </p>
            <p>FD.MATURITY.DATES (</p>
            <p>these dates will be convert to working dates</p>
            <p>)</p>
            <p> and chooses one according to the adjustment rules defined in the field </p>
            <p>MATDATES</p>
            <p> of </p>
            <p>FD.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field used to store either a Null value that stands for all currencies or a valid currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The field </p>
            <p>CURRENCY</p>
            <p>       must contain either a null value that stands for all currencies or a valid       currency defined in </p>
            <p>CURRENCY</p>
            <p>.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No duplicate is allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Sub-valued field that must stand for a valid day in the corresponding year/month.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The days must be valid for the corresponding       year/month and must be specified in ascending order within the associated       currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When a currency is specified, the system must       check if the input day is a working day in the country related to this       currency (an override is issued if the input day is not a working day).</p>
            <p />
            <p>Sub-valued field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YEAR.MONTH</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Key of FD.MATURITY.DATES file</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The YEARS.MONTH key is an unique identifier to the FD.MATURITY.DATES file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The key of this file is made of a year in the form YYYY and a month in the form MM, </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>both being separated by a dot.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Ex: 2001.01</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

