<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>FD</product>
<table>FD.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is the main parameter file for Fiduciaries and allows the user to specify the different CATEGORY codes (for both deposit and placement) by fiduciary type (FIXED or NOTICE) and eventually fiduciary subtype (IN, OUT or CD) used for each deposit type; i.e. Fixed, Call/Notice and the placement types. The P/L codes and accrual cycles are set in this file. It is possible to set, at this level, whether accruals must be calculated for commissions on Notice contracts. In addition, the default pooling option for notice order contracts may be specified on this file as well as whether pooling to existing placements is allowed. It also allows specifying the length of time the file stays live post maturity and the parameters for automatic renewal of contracts together with the rules to be applied to the definition of standard maturity dates. The usage of a placement profile is also specified, together with the version of FD.FIDUCIARY to be used within the bulk pooling process. It is also used to define whether interest and/or commission accounts may be specified in a currency different from the transactions one.  For inside group deposits, it allows, in the one hand, to define the type of rate used to automatically allocate an interest rate, and, in the other hand, to specify the minimum net income for a fixed order.  Commission calculations can be calculated after taking into account the values of client holdings, you can specify whether to add assets with net or absolute values and whether to exclude and ASSET.TYPE and SUB.ASSET.TYPE entries.   This file has only one record called SYSTEM. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.POOL.DEFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>For notice orders, the default value of the POOLING field is specified here. </p>
            <p>The value in this field corresponds to the standard pooling options available in the FIDUCIARY application. </p>
            <p>This field is only used for defaulting purposes and does not restrict the input of the pooling option on the order contract. </p>
            <p>If input in this field is missing the value of the POOLING field will default to NONE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be one of AUTO, NONE or MANUAL.  Defaults to NONE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FURTHER.POOLING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether an order can be automatically inserted into a partially approved pool group. By default, when one of the orders of a pool group is approved, no additional order can be automatically inserted into this group.</p>
            <p>When the value of this field is Y, an order may be automatically inserted into an existing pool group while this group is not closed, provided that the pooling criteria match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>If populated, Input must either be Y or NO. Defaults to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POOLING.FDP.PRG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Is used to specify the </p>
            <p>FD.FIDUCIARY</p> version used with the placement option in <p>FD.APPROVE.POOLING</p> application and <p>FD.APPROVE.POOLING,NOTICE</p> version. The first multi-value stands for the <p>FD.FIDUCIARY</p> version of <p>FIXED</p> contracts. The second multi-value stands for the <p>FD.FIDUCIARY</p> version of <p>NOTICE</p> contracts. <p>By default, the standard </p><p>FD.FIDUCIARY</p> version is used.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional multi-valued field</p><p>If populated, input must be an existing version of the </p><p>FD.FIDUCIARY</p>       application     <p>Default = </p><p>FD.FIDUCIARY</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.DEF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional single field. Defines the default method for the calculation of the principal amount of a new deposit. If this field is not populated, there is no default for the principal amount of new deposits: a manual input is required.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Possible value : "ACCT" or blank</p>
            <p>11 alphanumeric characters may be entered</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.UPD.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days the dealer is allowed to modify the maturity date by on a fixed placement contract. </p>
            <p>A dealer may need to amend the maturity date on a placement to cater for local holidays. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 number of days (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.CAT.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end of the category code range to be used for fiduciary deposits (orders). </p>
            <p>The category codes available for Fiduciary deposits (orders) are in the range 27000-27099. The category code can be used to define delivery conditions, Limits and charge and commission details. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>5-digit standard product category code (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 27000-27099.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Cannot overlap the range formed by DEP.CAT.STRT and DEP.CAT.END for other multi values.</p>
            <p>Must be greater than or equal the associated DEP.CAT.STRT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RENEW.RPT.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of Working or Calendar Days from today that maturing Fiduciary Orders should be reported to the account officer. </p>
            <p>This parameter will be used when processing the Fiduciary Renewal Report. Any maturing fiduciaries within the specified period will be reported. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>            1-99 number of days followed by "W"orking or "C"alendar day type indicator.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.CAT.STRT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start of the category code range allocated to the deposits of the associated FID.TYPE and FID.SUBTYPE. </p>
            <p>The category codes available for Fiduciary deposits (orders) are in the range 27000-27099. The category code can be used to define delivery conditions, Limits and charge and commission details. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 27000-27099.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Cannot overlap the range formed by DEP.CAT.STRT and DEP.CAT.END for other multi values.</p>
            <p>Must be less than or equal the associated DEP.CAT.END.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ONLINE.DRAWDOWN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field default to YES. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only option possible is YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.RATE.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default number of days before a rate change that the rate change advice should be sent to the customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 or 2 numeric number of days (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.CAT.PLT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default category code to be used in Fiduciary Placement contracts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)   </p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.   </p>
            <p>Must be in the range defined by PLT.CAT.STRT and PLT.CAT.END for the     associated FID.TYPE and FID.SUBTYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.SUBTYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies what is the defaulted subtype for a fiduciary</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>(Mandatory input if the field "SUBTYPE" is populated)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3-alpha characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The   following values are permitted :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>       CD</p>
            <p />(Certificates of   deposit)<p /><p /><p>           IN</p><p /><p>(For placements or deposits done   inside the group)</p><p /><p /><p>       OUT (For placements or deposits done outside the group)</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The profit and loss category to be debited when brokerage is payable. </p>
            <p>Brokerage is taken at the value date on Fiduciary Placements, if specified. The Profit and Loss category specified will be debited and the broker account defined in the BROKER account class record will be credited in the specified currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the category file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-69999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.RENEW.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional single field. Defines the default method for the calculation of the principal amount of a renewed order.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>11 alphanumerics characters or blank value may be entered</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>PRINCIPAL</p>
            <p>INCOME</p>
            <p>INCOME.ACCT</p>
            <p>NET</p>
            <p>PPAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PEN.COMM.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field </p>
            <p>PEN.COMM.CAT</p> is added in order to define the category used for posting the penalty commission.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>5-digit standard internal category (Optional input)</p><p>Must exist on the Category file.</p><p>Must be in the range 10000-19999.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FID.SUBTYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Defines the subtype at fiduciary type level</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3-alpha characters       </p>
            <p />
            <p>If a field of the multi value set is blank, another input in the same multi value set is denied</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The   following values are permitted :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>       CD</p>
            <p />(Certificates of   deposit)<p /><p /><p>           IN</p><p />(For placements or deposits done inside the group)<p /><p /><p>       OUT (For placements or deposits done outside the group)</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields FID.TYPE to RESERVED1 form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.POOL.EXIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies, for notice contracts, whether it is possible to pool an order onto an existing placement. </p>
            <p>When a notice placement is authorised, this parameter record is examined. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to NO, then the pool group is removed from the FD.POOL.GROUP.XREF file, the pool group remains CLOSED and no further orders will be pooled into the group. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to YES, then the pool group is added to the FD.POOL.GROUP.XREF file with a key which has a null in the value date (e.g. USD--3). The pool group record itself is modified such that the group status changes from CLOSED to EXIST. The FURTHER.POOLING indicator on the record is change to YES to indicate that the group has been reopened for pooling. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must either be YES or NO.  Defaults to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.SUB.ASS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field concerns the sub-asset type / types (since the field is multi-valued) that are to be excluded when evaluating the customer in the file, "FD.CUST.VALUE."</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1: Input to this field is optional but should take the form of a valid key to a record on the 'SUB.ASSET.TYPE.' FILE</p>
            <p>Rule 2: Input can take the form of 1 - 3 numerics.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.MTH.ADJ.C</field>
<desc>
            <p>The profit and loss category used for adjustments to FIXED order commissions in previous months in the current year. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-59999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUATION.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input to this field must take the form of a valid program, and hence exist as a VOC file.</p>
            <p>The name of the routine should be an existing Universe program executeable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POOLING.FDP.PROG</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the application (and VERSION) to be used with the drilldown Placement to check the fiduciary record created by the FD.APPROVE.POOLING application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must     refer to an existing application of types H,U,L,T,W in the PGM.FILE. If a     VERSION is specified (id contains ",") the record must exist in     the VERSION application.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must     be blank, FD.FIDUCIARY or any version of FD.FIDUCIARY application.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLT.CAT.STRT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the start of the category range available for placements of the associated FID.TYPE and FID.SUBTYPE</p>
            <p>The category codes available for Fiduciary placements are in the range 27100 to 27199. The category code can be used to define delivery conditions and Limits.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 27100-27199.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Cannot overlap the range formed by PLT.CAT.STRT and PLT.CAT.END for       other multi values.</p>
            <p>Must be less than or equal the associated PLT.CAT.END.       </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RENEWAL.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of days prior to maturity of the existing order, when the renewed order is to be created. </p>
            <p>Renewals can be specified from 1 to 99 "C"alendar or "W"orking days before the maturity of the existing order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>            1 or 2 numeric number of days followed by W or C.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Number of days must be in the range 1-99.</p>
            <p>Either "W"orking or "C"alendar days must be specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The field </p>
            <p>RATE.TYPE</p>
            <p> is a multi-valued optional numeric field. If present, it must contain a valid rate type defined in the first 2 characters of the </p>
            <p>PERIODIC.INTEREST</p>
            <p> key.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>  The order in which the types are defined in this field determines their priority.  </p>
            <p>It defines the market rate for which the interest rate is calculated (for inside group contracts) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid Market Rate       Type</p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of two       characters may be entered</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.DIFF.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The category code of the internal account to be used for posting any difference entry between the placement interest and order interest. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit internal account category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the Category file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 10000-19999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the FD.PARAMETER file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>SYSTEM or any abbreviation thereof. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLCMT.CAT.STRT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the start of the category range available for placements of the associated FID.TYPE. </p>
            <p>The category codes available for Fiduciary placements are in the range 27100 to 27199. The category code can be used to define delivery conditions and Limits. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 27100-27199.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Cannot overlap the range formed by PLCMT.CAT.STRT and PLCMT.CAT.END for other multi values.</p>
            <p>Must be less than or equal the associated PLCMT.CAT.END.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RENEWAL.OVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the level of override to be automatically approved on renewed fiduciary orders. </p>
            <p>When renewals are created with the AUTO or SEMI option, and any override is encountered, the new order will handle the overrides according to this parameter. </p>
            <p>NONE       Specifies that NO overrides are automatically approved and will            cause the new order to be placed on HLD status. </p>
            <p>CONTRACT   Specifies that any override generated from the new order will            be automatically processed. This includes overrides such as non            working days, and minimum Fid currency. It does not include            accounting overrides. </p>
            <p>ACCOUNT    Specifies that all overrides are automatically approved,            including those from Accounting. New orders generated in this            case will be fully processed if no errors are found. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NONE, CONTRACT or ACCOUNT.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.PL.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The new category code to be used for accrual of FIXED order commission. </p>
            <p>When the category code for FIXED accruals of commission is to be changed, the new category should be added to this field. During the end of day, the existing accruals will be removed from the old category, and booked to the new in the CRF. The PL.ACCR.COMM will then be replaced with the new value, and this field will be cleared. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard category code. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-59999.</p>
            <p>Must not be the same as PL.ACCR.COMM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The description of the type of Fiduciary contract selected in the previous field 'FID.TYPE'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3-35 characters.  Language field  (Mandatory field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLCMT.CAT.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end of the range of category codes allocated for fiduciary placements for the associated FID.TYPE. </p>
            <p>The category codes available for Fiduciary placements are in the range 27100-27199. The category code can be used to define delivery conditions and Limits. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard product category code.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 27100-27199.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Cannot overlap the range formed by PLCMT.CAT.STRT and PLCMT.CAT.END for other multi values.</p>
            <p>Must be greater than or equal the associated PLCMT.CAT.STRT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>XRATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies, in the one hand, whether an income account with a currency different from the one of the transaction may be used, and, in the other hand, the type of the exchange rate between the two currencies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>BUY.SELL, MID or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EX.ASSET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field concerns the asset type / types (since this field is multi-valued), that are to be excluded when evaluating the customer in the file, "FD.CUST.VALUE."</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1: Input to this field is optional but should take the form of a valid key to a record on the 'ASSET.TYPE' file.</p>
            <p>Rule 2: Input can take the form of 1 -3 numerics.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies the default settlement market to be used at the time of settlement of a deposit in which an income account in a currency different from the transaction one is used.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field. No       default.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No input allowed if </p>
            <p>XRATE.TYPE</p>
            <p> is not       specified</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FID.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of fiduciary contract allowed to be used. </p>
            <p>If both FIXED and NOTICE fiduciary contracts are to be processed, then they must be defined here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>FIXED or NOTICE or any abbreviation thereof. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>No duplicate values allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.POST.MAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of calender or working days a liquidated contract is to remain on the Live file before being written to History. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>            1-99 number of days followed by "W"orking or "C"alendar day indicator  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.RENEW.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional single field. Defines the default status that a renewed FIXED order is to be created with:</p>
            <p>AUTO The order will be generated fully authorised subject to validation checks.</p>
            <p>SEMI The order will be created unauthorised with NAU status subject to validation checks.</p>
            <p>MANUAL The order will be created with HLD status.</p>
            <p>NONE No renewal will be generated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The following values are permitted :</p>
            <p>        NONE, AUTO, SEMI or MANUAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.INCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Minimal net income for an inside group fixed deposit. </p>Must be a valid amount.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p>1-14 standard amount       in the format of the local currency.</p><p /><p>single-valued optional field</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURE.AT.SOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POOLING.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>By default, the pooling of fiduciary orders to a group of orders is carried out according to three criteria: </p>
            <p>                 - Currency                  - Value Date                  - Maturity Date </p>
            <p>Hence orders which having matching values for these fields will be pooled together. </p>
            <p>This field is used to specify additional fields to pool by. Where orders have the same values in the additional fields, as well as the three mandatory fields, then - and only then - will the orders be pooled together. </p>
            <p>Input to this field must be a valid, single valued field on the FD.FID.ORDER file, but specific instances of the LOCAL.REF field may be referenced. These should be input as LOCAL.REF-n, where n is the number of the local reference being referenced. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must reference a valid, single valued field on the FD.FID.ORDER file, or a specific instance of a local reference field.</p>
            <p>Must be in one of the following forms:  Field number   Valid field numbers are converted to field names                upon input.  Field name     Must be a valid field name  LOCAL.REF-n    Where n is the instance of the multi value field to                be referenced.</p>
            <p>Optional</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System field no input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.ACCR.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the profit and loss category to be used for posting commission accruals on FIXED fiduciary orders. </p>
            <p>Accruals for the month are posted to this category, all crf updates for accruals are posted to an asset type of this category. </p>
            <p>This category cannot be changed directly after the first authorisation, and must be changed by using the field NEW.PL.COMM. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard Profit and Loss category (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the Category file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-59999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.CAT.PLCMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default category code to be used in Fiduciary Placement contracts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range defined by PLCMT.CAT.STRT and PLCMT.CAT.END for the associated FID.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default value for the MARGIN.RATE for the associated FID.SUBTYPE and FID.TYPE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 or 2 digit percentage. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RENEWAL.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of calender or working days after the maturity of the previous order, that the new order will start. </p>
            <p>Renewed orders will normally start (i.e. VALUE.DATE) on the same day as the previous order matures. The default value of this field is 0W, i.e. zero working days. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-9 numeric number of days followed by C or W. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLACEMENT.PROFILE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field specifies whether FD.PLACEMENT.PROFILE must be used to allocate or check the bank of placement within a fiduciary transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional     field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Possible     values are: Y, NO (Null value is allowed (assimilated as     NO))</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the field is set to Y, the value </p>
            <p>FID.BANK</p> must be included in the field <p>POOLING.FIELDS</p> of <p>FD.PARAMETER</p><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLT.CAT.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end of the range of category codes allocated for fiduciary placements for the associated FID.TYPE and FID.SUBTYPE</p>
            <p>The category codes available for Fiduciary placements are in the range 27100-27199. The category code can be used to define delivery conditions and Limits.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)   </p>
            <p>Must be in the range 27100-27199.   </p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.   </p>
            <p>Cannot overlap the range formed by PLT.CAT.STRT and PLT.CAT.END for other     multi values.   </p>
            <p>Must be greater than or equal the associated PLT.CAT.STRT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATDATES</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field defines the adjustment rules for the standard maturity dates.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NULL,</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>FORWARD, </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> BACKWARD,</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>FORWARD IN MONTH, </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>BACKWARD IN MONTH, </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NEAREST FWD, </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NEAREST BWD, </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NEAREST FWD IN MTH, </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>NEAREST BWD IN MTH </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>&amp;#8230;.or any abbreviation thereof. (Mandatory input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.PORTFOLIO.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines if the portfolio valuation uses the absolute or net value of the customer's holdings with the bank. In accordance to this: </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1: Input is optional. Valid input to this field is either "Absolute" or "Net."</p>
            <p>Rule 2: If null, this field will be defaulted to "Net."</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.CAT.DEPOSIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default category code used for fiduciary orders of the associated FID.TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range defined by DEP.CATEG.STRT and DEP.CATEG.END for the associated FID.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.YR.ADJ.C</field>
<desc>
            <p>The profit and loss category used for booking adjustments to FIXED order commission accruals into the previous year. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the category file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-59999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODIFY.COMM.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines if the 'COMM.RATE' field in the file, "FD.FID.ORDER" is to become input capable.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input to this field is either "Yes,"         "No," or null</p>
            <p>If this field is set to "Yes," the commission         rate can then, if desired, be set in         "FD.FID.ORDER."</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.CAT.DEP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default category code used for fiduciary orders of the associated FID.TYPE and FID.SUBTYPE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)   </p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.   </p>
            <p>Must be in the range defined by DEP.CAT.STRT and DEP.CAT.END for the     associated FID.TYPE and FID.SUBTYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System field no input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.CATEG.STRT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start of the category code range allocated to the deposits of the associated FID.TYPE. </p>
            <p>The category codes available for Fiduciary deposits (orders) are in the range 27000-27099. The category code can be used to define delivery conditions, Limits and charge and commission details. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard product category code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 27000-27099.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Cannot overlap the range formed by DEP.CATEG.STRT and DEP.CATEG.END for other multi values.</p>
            <p>Must be less than or equal the associated DEP.CATEG.END.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RENEW.BLOCK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether renewals are to be stopped temporarily for specific account officers. </p>
            <p>From time to time it may be desirable to block the renewal processing for a particular account officer, or ALL account officers. If anything is specified in this field, the orders for the specified account officers will not be proposed for renewal. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>ALL or 4-digit account officer code. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If ALL is specified, no other account officers can be specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.CATEG.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end of the category code range to be used for fiduciary deposits (orders). </p>
            <p>The category codes available for Fiduciary deposits (orders) are in the range 27000-27099. The category code can be used to define delivery conditions, Limits and charge and commission details. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5-digit standard product category code (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 27000-27099.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Cannot overlap the range formed by DEP.CATEG.STRT and DEP.CATEG.END for other multi values.</p>
            <p>Must be greater than or equal the associated DEP.CATEG.STRT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.COMM.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether accruals must be calculated for commission taken in arrears on notice contracts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must either be YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.CYCLE.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date and frequency of the next commission accrual. </p>
            <p>Commissions are accrued for FIXED fiduciary orders on either a daily or monthly basis. Commissions are booked to the Profit and Loss category defined in the field PL.ACCR.COMM. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>            8-digit standard date followed by 5-character standard frequency (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The date must be greater than or equal to today.</p>
            <p>The frequency must be DAILY or M0131.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.CYCLE.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date and frequency for the next accrual of interest. </p>
            <p>Interest can be 'accrued' either on a daily or monthly basis. As interest on Fiduciary contracts is off balance sheet the figures accrued are not posted, but update the FD.BALANCES record so that they can be used for the portfolio valuations. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>            8 numeric standard date characters followed by a standard 5 alphanumeric frequency (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Date must be greater than or equal to today.</p>
            <p>The frequency must be either DAILY or MONTHLY and fall on the last day of the month.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.VALUE.MAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximum back date for a fiduciary order. </p>
            <p>Any order entered with a value date prior to the BACK.VALUE.MAX will require an override. The back value max is cycled during the end of day. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 numeric standard date format (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

