<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IB</product>
<table>IB.USER.PASSWORD</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

 
IB.USER.PASSWORD
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RPT.PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Allows the external user to confirm the new password required.
 This must match the NEW.PASSWORD to allow the password to be successfully changed.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory Field
 Must be 6 to 12 characters
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WEB.USER</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Contains the external user name that the password is to be reset for.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory Input
 Must be a valid WEB.USER in IB.USER
 

</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the new password for the external user.
 The password must be repeated in the RPT.PASSWORD field to be succesfully changed. It cannot be the same as the old password or the IB.USER id.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory Input
 Must be 6 to 12 characters
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Allows the External user to specify their existing password.
 This must match the exsiting password to allow a succesful change to take place. The existing password need not be supplied in special circumstances, this is indicated by the REPEAT.OLD.PWORD field.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory Input if REPEAT.OLD.PWORD is set to Y
 Not allowed if REPEAT.OLD.PWORD is set to NO
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPEAT.OLD.PWORD</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies if the old password must be repeated in order to successfully change the users password.
 The standard option is that the users password must be repeated in order for the password to be changed, as it is envisaged that this application will be executed by the external system via OFS. To provide additional security the external user must repeat his existing password before allowing a change.
 There may be occasions however where the bank is required to reset the password, for example if it is forgotten by the user. This use is denoted by setting this field to NO. This type of use always requires an override approval, it is envisaged that access to this mode of operation will be strictly controlled using VERSION and SMS.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory field
 Valid options Y or NO
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

