<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IB</product>
<table>IB.USER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

 
 IB
 IB.USER
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INFO</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Information pertaining for the particular user can be provided optionally.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 Standard T24 alphanumeric field.
 A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the sign on name to be used by the external user. 
 The sign on name is the name to be supplied when the external user logs into the system.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Minimum 6 characters
 Maximum 16 characters
 Must be alpha numeric characters of type AA
 Cannot be the same as the WEB.USER
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the expiry date of the external user profile.
 When attempting to access T24 from the external system if the T24 system date has passed this date the user will be denied access.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory Input
 Must be after the START.DATE
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the Functions which may be used to access records of the Application entered in the corresponding Field 17. This field is used, together with the associated Fields 16-18 and 20-23 to specify precisely which Functions the User may be used to access which records in which Applications. Valid Function codes are: A 2 C D E H I L P Q R S V If NOT is entered, plus one or more Function codes, the System converts it to a list of all the Functions which are allowed. (See Fields 17, 18 and 20 for examples.) Note: Even if the function 'C' (copy) is not allowed, the user will still be able to transfer the ID (together with its enrichment) of a selected record when using the '!' facility during an input function.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 0-29 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters: 1. Function codes separated by spaces or 2. NOT + one or more Function codes or 3. N (No Functions allowed)or 4. ALL (All Functions allowed). Multi-value field associated with Fields 16-18, 20-23. Mandatory input except if a USER.SMS.GROUP was defined in field 18.1 in which case input is not allowed.No Default Value. If Function 2 (2nd Authorization) is allowed, but not A (1st Authorization) the User is allowed to enter Function Code A, a Security Violation is generated if the record requested is not ready for 2nd Authorization.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 The encrypted password to be supplied by the external user when loggin in to the system.
 The password is initially set to be the same as the SIGN.ON.NAME, the password should be changed by the user on the first use. For security reasons the password cannot be viewed in this field.
 The password is changed using the IB.USER.PASSWORD application.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 System field noinput
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Contains the language code to be used for the external user.
 The ability to provide foreign translations in the external system is dependent upon the operation of that system, this field will indicate the preferred language.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory Field
 Must be a valid entry in the LANGUAGE table
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies a particular Version which may be used to access records for the Application entered in the corresponding APPLICATION (Field 17.) This field is used, together with the associated Fields, 16, 17 and 19-23, to specify precisely which records in which Applications may be accessed by the User, using which Versions and Functions. * and ? can be used in this field , to specify more than one Version. They act as wild card characters ,where * replaces any number of characters including null, numbers, alphabets etc. and ? replaces one character including null, numbers, alphabets etc. The version field in can have the value for eg : ,SAVE* , which allows the user to access Versions of ACCOUNT applications for eg : ACCOUNT,SAVESTUDENT , ACCOUNT,SAVERESIDENT , ACCOUNT,SAVESALARIED, etc The version field can have the value for eg : ,SAVE1000?00,which allows the user to access versions of ACCOUNT application for eg: SAVE1000100, SAVE1000200, SAVE1000300 , etc Note: Versions of Applications may be used to change the screen layout or the rules for Input, Validation and Authorization. Example 1: To allow a User to List and See all Accounts except for those with Account Officer = 1234 using the standard version of Account, and to List and See all Accounts for Account Officer = 1234 only, using a special Version Account,99: Field 17.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 18.1(VERSION) ,0 19.1(FUNCTION) L S 20.1(FIELD NO) 9 21.1(DATA COMPARISON) NE 22.1(DATA FROM) 1234 17.2(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 18.2(VERSION) ,99 19.2(FUNCTION) L S 20.2(FIELD NO) 9 21.2(DATA COMPARISON) EQ 22.2(DATA FROM) 1234 Example 2 : To allow a User to Input and See all Account version with name starting with SAVINGS followed by any character: Field 17.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 18.1(VERSION) ,SAVINGS* 19.1(FUNCTION) I S For more examples of Fields 16-23 see Fields 17 and 20. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 1. 0-50 type A (alphanumeric) characters beginning with ','. or 2. ',0' to allow only the standard version. or 3. No input to allow all Versions. Multi-value field associated with Fields 16, 17 and 19-23. (Optional input except if a USER.SMS.GROUP was defined in field 17.1 in which case input is not allowed. If not entered, access to all Versions is allowed. 
 Special character * will replace any number of characters and ? replaces one character. Also ? after * and two occurances of * are not allowed.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWORD.REVIEW</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies how often and on what date the external User must change his Password. 
 This can be daily, every 1-9 weeks, twice a month (on 15th and last day of each month) or every 1-6 Months. 
 a) Daily Enter D or DAILY 
 If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the System assumes the Next Change Date will be tomorrow. 
 (b) Every 1-9 weeks Enter Wn where n is 1-9 
 If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the System assumes the Next Change Date will be n x 7 days from today. 
 c) Every 1-6 months Enter Mnndd 
 Where nn is the number of months 01-06 and dd is the day in the month on which the password must be changed, (01-31). If this date does not exist (e.g. 30th February) the next day will be assumed (1st March) 
 If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the System assumes day 'dd' in 'nn' months from the current month. 
 Example: 
 If today's date is 26 FEB 1985 and you enter M0215 the System will assume the Next Change Date should be 15 APRIL 1985. 
 d) Twice a month Enter T 
 If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the System assumes the 15th of the current month if today is not after the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month is assumed. 
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 This field is in two parts. 1) Next Change Date: 1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters. Default value calculated by the System depending on change frequency. (Optional input) 2) Change Frequency: 1-5 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters (Mandatory input) 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WEB.USER</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Contains the identifier of the external user the associated record describes.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory Input
 Any valid character
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TO</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the end of a range of values with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 20) are to be compared. 0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. OR Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following way: (i) Up to 30 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by, (ii) A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by, (iii) Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid entry on the multi-value field SYS.FIELD.NAME on the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in (i). Multi-value field associated with Fields 16-22. (Optional input if Field 21 contains EQ or NE, otherwise not allowed.) Note: The values input in this field and the previous one must be in agreement with the Format rules of the element specified in Field 20.1. If, for example, the input in Field 20 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic, a minimum input of 10 characters will be required in this field.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 See Details for format.
 It may only be input if corresponding DATA COMPARISON (Field 21) contains EQ (Equal To) or NE (Not Equal To).
 Must not be less than DATA FROM (Field 22)
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.LAST.USE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Contains the time of the last access by the external user.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 System Field No Input allowed
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the account numbers that the user can access in transactions for debiting.
 In a typical external system the user will have a very limited access to certain accounts related to his own client number. These accounts may be presented to the user in the form of a drop down list in the external application.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Optional Field
 Must be a valid account number or mnemonic existing in the account file for the associated COMPANY.CODE
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.RESTR</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the Company to which the User must be Signed On in order to use the Applications, Versions and Functions specified in the related Fields 17 to 23. This field is used, together with the associated Fields 17-23, to specify for each Company to whose records this User has access, precisely which records in which Applications can be accessed using which Versions and Functions. The group of Fields, 16-23 can be repeated up to 999 times. Refer to APPLICATION (Field 17) for examples. Any files for which standard or special file mnemonics have been specified in the Company record can only be accessed by Users who have Signed On to that Company (or have used the PASSWORD Application to access that Company).
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 Permits "ALL" to allow the functions for all companies listed in the COMPANY.CODE field.
 9 alphanumeric characters 'CCGGGLLLL' where: CC is 2 alpha characters Country code GGG is 3 numeric characters Company Group LLLL is 4 numeric local code. or 2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or '.') Company Mnemonic characters. 
 Multi-value field associated with Fields 17-23. 
 Mandatory input. No Default Value. 
 It must be a Company Code from the COMPANY.CODE field of this record.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERNAL.USER</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Insert text here
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 Rule 1
 Rule 2
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the Portfolios that the user has access to from the external application.
 In external applications involving the use of securities transactions the external user will usually be restricted to particular portfolios when entering transactions. The portfolio will generally belong to the client of the external user.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Optional Input
 Must be a valid entry in the SEC.ACC.MASTER table.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.COMPARISON</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the type of comparison to be made between the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 20) and the values specified in Fields 22 and 23. The meanings of the Inputs are as follows: EQ Equal to GE Greater than or Equal to GT Greater Than LE Less than or Equal to LT Less Than NE Not Equal to LK Like UL Unlike The User may only access records in which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 20) satisfy the conditions specified in Fields 21-23. For examples see FIELD NO (Field 20).
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 EQ, GE, GT, LE, LT, NE, LK, UL or no input. Multi-value field associated with Fields 16-20, 22 and 23. (Mandatory input if FIELD NO (Field 20) is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.)
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the accounts that the user is allowed to credit funds to in external transactions. These accounts will usually be associated with the client of the user.
 In a typical external application the user is not permitted to enter an account number, it is presented as a drop-down list.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Optional Input
 Must be a valid account number or mnemonic in the account file of the associated COMPANY.CODE
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.FROM</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the value, or start of a range of values, with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 20) are to be compared. 1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. OR Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following way: (i) Up to 30 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by, (ii) A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by, (iii) Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid entry on the multi-value field SYS.FIELD.NAME on the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in (i). Multi-value field associated with Fields 16-21 and 23. (Mandatory input if FIELD NO is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.) This field specifies either a single value or the lower limit of a range with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 20) are compared. Note: The values input in this field and the next one must be in agreement with the Format rules of the element specified in Field 20.1. If, for example, the input in Field 20 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic, a minimum input of 3 characters will be required in this field. When defining the enquires a user can run, you can also 'turn off' all SMS checks for a particular enquiry. This is useful when the enquiry presents non sensitive information from sensitive files. I.e you may wish to show customer and account static information (address, account titles etc ) but not show the balances. As the enquiry itself controls the presentation there may be no need for any additional security. To suppress SMS you must append *NOSMS to the name of the enquiry. E.G. Field 17.1 (APPLICATION) ENQUIRY.SELECT Field 19.1(FUNCTION) I Field 20.1(FIELD.NO) 0 Field 21.1(DATA.COMPARISON) EQ Field 22.1(DATA.FROM) CUSTOMER.STATIC*NOSMS This mechanism works only with ENQUIRY.SELECT and must be entered in the format detailed above.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 See Details for format.
 Input must begin and/or end with 3 dots when DATA.COMPARISON = 'LK' or 'UL'.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies, when used together with Fields 21-23, precisely which records may be accessed in the Application specified in the corresponding APPLICATION (Field 17.) A record may only be accessed if the field indicated here has a value allowed in the corresponding Fields 21-23. 0-3 numeric characters. OR Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following way: (i) Up to 30 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by, (ii) A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by, (iii) Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid entry on the multi-value field SYS.FIELD.NAME or USR.FIELD.NAME on the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in (i). Eg: FOREX&gt;COUNTERPARTY It is recommended that field names and not field numbers are specified. If field numbers are specified then when a file layout changes you will be forced to manually change all user profiles affected. Multi-value field associated with Fields 16-19 and 21-23. (Optional input. No input means all records may be accessed, regardless of contents.) For multi-value fields, only the field number may be specified, not the entry number, e.g. 20, not 20.1, all entries in the multi-value field will be checked. The System displays the name of the field indicated. Example 1: To allow a User to See and List all Accounts records, but only Input (or change), Copy or Delete Accounts in pounds sterling. Field 17.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 19.1(FUNCTION) L S 17.2(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 19.2(FUNCTION) I C D 20.2(FIELD NO.) ACCOUNT&gt;CURRENCY (currency) 21.2(DATA COMPARISON) EQ (equal) 22.2(DATA FROM) GBP Example 2: To allow a User access to Account records only if they have Currency equal GBP and Category not in the range 01-001 to 01-099. Field 17.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT19.1(FUNCTION) ALL 20.1(FIELD.NO) ACCOUNT&gt;CURRENCY (Currency) 21.1(DATA.COMPARISON) EQ (equal) 22.1(DATA.FROM) GBP 17.2(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 19.2(FUNCTION) ALL 20.2(FIELD.NO) ACCOUNT&gt;CATEGORY (Category) 21.2(DATA.COMPARISON) NE (not equal) 22.2(DATA.FROM) 01-001 23.2(DATA.TO) 01-099 Example 3: To allow a User to Authorise Data Capture records, but only if they do not contain an override. Field 17.1(APPLICATION) DATA.CAPTURE 19.1(FUNCTION) A 20.1(FIELD.NO) DATA.CAPTURE&gt;OVERRIDE (Override) 21.1(DATA COMPARISON) LT (Less Than) 22.1(DATA.FROM) "" (lowest possible value) Note: It is not possible to prevent a User from entering on override during input, but Authorization can be restricted, as above, to ensure that any overrides are checked by a more senior person. "" is the lowest value a field can have, so specifying LT (Less Than) "" ensures that no override may be present. Example 4: Restricting FOREX transactions to a counterparties that belong to a specific account officer. Field 17.1(APPLICATION) FOREX 19.1(FUNCTION) I20.1(FIELD.NO) CUSTOMER&gt;ACCOUNT.OFFICER 21.1(DATA COMPARISON) EQ22.1(DATA.FROM) 100 Note: As you can see the field specified does not have to belong to the application. If the system can link the APPLICATION to the field then the SMS restriction will be applied. In this example the COUNTERPARTY field on the FOREX file provides the link to the CUSTOMER file. Hence when the transaction is input T24 reads the CUSTOMER file using the COUNTERPARTY as the key and checks that the ACCOUNT.OFFICER is 100. You do not have to define that the COUNTERPARTY as the key to CUSTOMER file this is done automatically based on the RELATED.FILE stored in the STANDARD.SELECTION record for FOREX. Note: If you wish to test a value in a related file a consderable process load can be incurred when the user lists the file. This can be relieved by defining the related field as a J-descriptor user field on the STANDARD.SELECTION record and using that. Thus in the example above define CUST.OFFICER as type J, CUSTOMER&gt;ACCOUNT.OFFICER and then specify the FIELD.NO as FOREX&gt;CUST.OFFICER.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 See Details for format.
 It must not be higher than the number of fields in records of the Application specified in APPLICATION (Field 17.)
 Input in this field will not be allowed when 'N' has been input in 'FUNCTION' (Field 19.1).
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.LAST.USE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Contains the date the external user last accessed the system.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 System field no input allowed
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies that start date of the external user profile.
 When an external user signs into T24 the system date will be compared to this date, if the profile starts before the current date the user will be denied access to T24.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory Input
 Must be a standard date.
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the separators to be used when formatting amounts for enquiry and record display in T24. 
 This field specifies the separators to be used when formatting amounts. Input of ',.' will use commas to separate the thousands and a full stop for the decimal place. 
 Input of '.,' will have the opposite effect. 
 Any combination of 2 from comma, full stop and apostrophe can be used. 
 Data returned to the external system formatted by T24 (e.g. from a typical enquiry) will be formatted according to this option, the display of data by the external system using this format will depend upon the operation of that system.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 (Optional input) 
 Must be either comma, full stop or apostophe. 
 The same character cannot be used twice. 
 The default is ',.'. 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies which Application may be used to access records belonging to the Company specified in the related COMPANY RESTR (Field 16). This field is used, together with the associated Fields 16 and 18-23 to specify precisely which records in which Applications can be accessed by the User using which Versions and Functions. It must be the name of an existing Application, the name of an existing USER.SMS.GROUP preceded by the '@' sign (in which case further input in fields 18.1 to 23.1 will not be allowed), ALL.PG to allow access to all Applications or ALL.PG (program type) to allow access to all Applications of a certain type (see below). The following program types may be used in conjunction with ALL.PG (e.g. ALL.PG.H) to give access to a particular type of program:- Program Type Meaning H Programs for which the standard 3 files exist - Live, Unauthorised and History, e.g. CUSTOMER. U Programs for which Live and Unauthorised files exist, but no History, e.g. VERSION. L Programs for which only a Live file exists (updated automatically by the system) e.g. STMT.ENTRY (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program). M Programs which are designed to do something other than processing the standard T24 functions using a specific file e.g. PASSWORD.ENABLE, End Of Day Batch programs. T Programs which handle automatically updated CONCAT files, e.g. CUSTOMER.ACCOUNT (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program). Note: The following 3 type M programs are available to all users and cannot be restricted:- SIGN.ON SIGN.OFF PASSWORD Example 1: To give a User access to the records of only one Company (GB-001-0000) but allow access to all records for this Company using all Functions (except auditor review) and all Versions of all Applications, enter the following: Field 4.1 (COMPANY) GB-001-0000 Field 16.1(COMPANY CODE) Field 17.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG Field 18.1(VERSION) Field 19.1(FUNCTION) ALL Note: Fields 20-23 are used to specify particular records or types of records which may be accessed within an Application. See FIELD NO (Field 20) for examples. Example 2: To give a User full access (except auditor review) to the records of Company GB-001-0000 and to give limited access to the records of Company GB-001-0001, only allowing the List and Display functions for Customer Application. Field 4.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000 Field 4.2(COMPANY) GB-001-0001 Field 16.1(COMPANY.CODE) GB-001-0000 Field 17.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG Field 18.1(VERSION) Field 19.1(FUNCTION) ALL Field 16.2(COMPANY.CODE) GB-001-0001 Field 17.2(APPLICATION) CUSTOMER Field 18.2(VERSION) Field 19.2(FUNCTION) L S Example 3: To give a User access to the records of only one Company (GB-001-0000), allowing him to List Display, Input and Copy Customer records and to List and Display records for all other Applications: Field 4.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000 Field 17.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG Field 19.1(FUNCTION) L S Field 17.2(APPLICATION) CUSTOMER Field 19.2(FUNCTION) L S I C Example 4: To prevent a USER from using any type M Applications, but allow him to List and Display records in any other Applications: Field 4.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000 Field 16.1(COMPANY CODE) Field 17.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.H Field 19.1(FUNCTION) L S Field 17.2(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.U Field 19.2(FUNCTION) L S Field 17.3(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.L Field 19.3(FUNCTION) L S Field 17.4(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.T Field 19.4(FUNCTION) L S
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 1. 1-30 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters, Application name. 
 or 2. ALL.PG to allow all Applications. 
 or 3. ALL.PG (program type) see details. or 
 4. '@' sign followed by a valid USER.SMS.GROUP 
 Multi-value field associated with Fields 16 and 18-23. (Mandatory input in each set of Fields 16-23.) 
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLIENT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 Specifies the clients (CUSTOMER) associated with this external user.
 External users are generally associated with a client number, and will usually only have acces to a restricted set of enquiries and transactions related to that client.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory input
 Must be a valid CUSTOMER number or MNEMONIC
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>
 The code of the company to which the external user will have access.
 In a multi-company environment the user will be restricted to transactions in their own company which is identitied in this field. The external user will only have access to the company specified in this field.
 </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
 
 
 
 
 Mandatory field
 Must be a valid Company Code or Company Mnemonic
 
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

