<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ABBREVIATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The Abbreviation Table has been developed to allow Applications and functions which are used regularly to be abbreviated thereby reducing keystrokes. </p>
            <p>These are examples of how Applications can be allocated standard Abbreviations </p>
            <p>APPLICATION                   ABBREVIATION </p>
            <p>CUSTOMER                      CU LIST.PROFILE                  LP PREIODIC.INTEREST             PI </p>
            <p>If required, functions can also be included in the Abbreviation table e.g. </p>
            <p>APPLICATION   FUNCTION                    ABBREVIATION </p>
            <p>CUSTOMER      INPUT                       CI CUSTOMER      AUTHORISE                   CA CUSTOMER      DISPLAY INDIVIDUAL RECORD   CS CUSTOMER      DISPLAY LIST                CL </p>
            <p>If you are regularly using a function with only one specific record, this can also be defined in the Abbreviation table e.g. </p>
            <p>APPLICATION     FUNCTION      RECORD ID    ABBREVIATION </p>
            <p>CUSTOMER        DISPLAY       1234         CD </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ABBREVIATION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Abbreviation code by which the original text can be identified. </p>
            <p>This field is used to specify the Abbreviation which will generate the ORIGINAL TEXT specified in Field ORIGINAL.TEXT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-35 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters. No comma will be allowed in the Abbreviation text.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHORISER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGINAL.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the original Application, Function command or record ID from which the Abbreviation was created. </p>
            <p>This field contains the Application and Function commands to be performed and the record to be accessed in response to the Abbreviation being entered. </p>
            <p>It should be ensured that, when entering this field, the correct text is Input as no validation is performed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3-54 type A (alphanumeric) characters (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

