<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ARCHIVES.SPOOL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds the instructions for spooling the contents of the archiving system. Three records only exist on the file to specify spool to the tape drive, printer, or to both simultaneously. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TIME.OUT.MINUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum run time for the spool process. </p>
            <p>The time out minutes defines the maximum run time allowed for the spool. When reached the process will terminate with an appropriate message in the batch como or on the screen. </p>
            <p>Next time the spool is run the process will continue from the last key used in the file being treated when the process timed out. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Minimum entry of 30 minutes. Maximum 99.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAPE.UNIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the tape drive unit number to be assigned to the spool process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESET.LAST.RUN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether further updates will be allowed before the spool run completes after a timeout. </p>
            <p>If "Y" further updates to the archives file are allowed after a timeout on the last spool run. If "NO" the spool run must complete by being rerun before further updates may proceed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>"Y" or "NO".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOOL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the spool type to be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.  Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must be one of the following:  1   Spool to tape only 2   Spool to printer only 3   Spool to both tape and printer</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOGICAL.TAPE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the logical tape number to be assigned to the tape. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DENSITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       800      1600      3200      6250</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 alphanumeric characters. (Multivalue field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the file. </p>
            <p>Keys to archives spool are descriptively named according to the spool type they are related to. </p>
            <p>Examples:   TYPE1 spools to tape only             TYPE2 spools to printer only             TYPE3 spools to both </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the last key and file being processed when the spool timed out on the last run. </p>
            <p>This field will be blank unless the last spool run timed out in which case it will contain the filename and record key which was in progress at the time. This is used to define the point at which to continue in the next spool run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-54 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

