<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ARCHIVES.CANCEL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The archives cancel file holds the instructions for which parameters to apply to which files during the cancel stage of archiving. </p>
            <p>Each record on the file defines the language to be used in printed output and a time out for the process.  Large files may take some time to be archived since the conditions which must be satisfied can be complex. The time out exists to stop the process after a defined length of time in minutes. The next time the same cancel is run the process will continue from the point reached in the file last time out. </p>
            <p>Following these fields begins a multivalue set of keys to the parameter file. This is the list of files which will be considered for archiving by this cancel record. </p>
            <p>The "V" verify function actually invokes the cancel or alternatively cancels may be run from within the end of day batch processing. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TIME.OUT.MINUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum run time for the cancel process. </p>
            <p>The time out minutes defines the maximum run time allowed for the cancel. When reached the process will terminate with an appropriate message in the batch como or on the screen. </p>
            <p>Next time the cancel is run the process will continue from the last key used in the file being treated when the process timed out. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 2 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Minimum entry of 30 minutes. Maximum 99.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 35 alphanumeric characters. (Multivalue field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the file. </p>
            <p>There is only one key on this file called "ALL" which invokes a cancellation of all archived data providing of course that it has first been spooled to tape successfully. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 14 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT.RECORD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether a report of the record ids cancelled will be spooled during the cancellation process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Must be either "Y" to print the report or "NO" to suppress the printing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

