<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ARCHIVES.FIELD</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The archives field file holds the instructions for which parameters to apply to which files during the field removal stage of archiving. </p>
            <p>Each record on the file defines the language to be used in printed output and a time out for the process. </p>
            <p>Large files may take some time to be archived since the conditions which must be satisfied can be complex. The time out exists to stop the process after a defined length of time in minutes. The next time the same field removal is run the process will continue from the point reached in the file last time out. </p>
            <p>Following these fields begins a multivalue set of keys to the parameter file. This is the list of files which will be considered for archiving by this field removal record. </p>
            <p>The "V" verify function actually invokes the field removal or alternatively field removals may be run from within the end of day batch processing. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LAST.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the last key and file being processed when the field removal timed out on the last run. </p>
            <p>This field will be blank unless the last field removal run timed out in which case it will contain the filename and record key which was in progress at the time. This is used to define the point at which to continue in the next field removal run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 54 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.OUT.MINUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum run time for the field removal process. </p>
            <p>The time out minutes defines the maximum run time allowed for the field removal. When reached the process will terminate with an appropriate message in the batch como or on the screen. </p>
            <p>Next time the field removal is run the process will continue from the last key used in the file being treated when the process timed out. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 2 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Minimum entry of 30 minutes. Maximum 99.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 35 alphanumeric characters. (Multivalue field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a list of keys to the parameter file whose conditions will be applied to their files in this field removal run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 - 27 alphanumeric characters. (Multivalue field)</p>
            <p>Each file name entered must exist as a key on the ARCHIVES.PARAMETER file and therefore as a defined routine on the PGM.FILE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the file. </p>
            <p>Keys to archives field are descriptively named according to the application they are related to. </p>
            <p>They are further subdivided between transaction based files and static tables for each application. </p>
            <p>Examples: FX.TRANS contains parameter records for the foreign exchange           transaction files. </p>
            <p>          LD.TABLES contains parameter records for static tables archiving           within the loans and deposits module. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 14 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the language to be used for saved records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.</p>
            <p>Numeric language code e.g. 1 ENGLISH must exist on the language table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

