<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ASSET.REGISTER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
        <p>The debit transaction code for this schedule. If none is entered, then it defaults using the code from ASSET.CLASS. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> It must be a valid TRANSACTION code with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND equal to DEBIT. This field is mandatory if a schedule is defined.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDUAL.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The value of the asset when it reaches the end of it's economic life</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
        <p>
        </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a field for the description of the Asset being set up. Insert text here </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Rule 1 Rule 2</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINAL.SCHED</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the date when the final schedule takes place. It is only allowed if the frequency code is specified.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.PERIOD.START</field>
<desc>
        <p>The start date ofthe current depreciation period. Default DATE.PURCHASED if depreciation is set to 'YES'. This is also a 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ECONOMIC.LIFE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the economic life of the asset expressed as a number of years or months. Input is converted to months.Years is entered by entering the years followed by a 'Y'. For example, two years would be 2Y, three years would be 3Y. It is also mandatory if the 'SL' schedule is defined.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPITAL.ALLOWANCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is to state whether Capital Allowances are allowed for this type of asset. The choices are Yes or No. It will default from Asset Class for this type of asset.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.PURCHASED</field>
<desc>
        <p>The date the asset was purchased. A mandatory field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.AMT.CLAIMED</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the schedule amount of allowances. It is also a 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the current value of the asset, which defaults to Cost of Asset. This field is non inputtable and will be updated by the process of SL, RB, FS or WO schedules with the schedule amount debited.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.CAP.ALLOWANCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the maximum capital alllowance for the asset.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.PERIOD.START</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the start date of the capital allowance period. Default DATE.PURCHASED if CAPITAL.ALLOWANCE is set to 'YES'. It is a 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
        <p>A detailed description of the asset that is being registered. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. Mandatory input. A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPRECIATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>This specifies whether depreciation is allowed for this asset or not. The choices are Yes or No. If no input is made then this will default to the choice made within Asset Class for this type of asset.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARR</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a free format text field, and is optional input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WRITE.OFF.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The write-off value of the asset. This will be updated by the process of the 'WO' schedule with the schedule amount. A noinput field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the end date of the current capital allowance period. Default to the earliest capital allowance schedule date if CAPITAL.ALLOWANCE is set to 'YES'. It is a 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
        <p>The end date of the current depreciation period. Default to the earliest depreciation schedule date if depreciation is set to 'YES'. It is a 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGINAL.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The initial value of the asset expressed in its currency format. A mandatory field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the schedule date of capital allowances in descending chronological order, i.e. the latest comes first.. It is also a 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.STATUS</field>
<desc>
        <p>This ASSET can only be used when the field is 'OPEN'. When a lease contract is linkled to this asset, this field should be changed to 'IN-USE'. This field will be changed to 'CLOSE' after a WO schedule is processed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The value of the provision of an asset. This will be updated by the process of; 'SL', 'RB', 'FS', or 'WO' schedules with the schedule amount credited. A 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.FREQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>The date that the depreciation is to be performed with optional frequency for this schedule. The frequency is invalid for Write Off schedules as a write off would only be performed once. Mandatory when SCHED.TYPE specified.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>The internal account number which holds the balance of the provision of an asset. Defaults to CCY CATEG 0001 where CATE is derived from ASSET.CLASS.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The rate field is used as part of the depreciation amount calculations for certain schedule types only The rate is used as follows : Reducing Balance Schedule = (CURRENT VALUE - RESIDUAL VALUE) * RATE Flexible Schedule = (COST OF ASSET - RESIDUAL VALUE) * RATE Capital Allowance Schedule = (COST OF ASSET - RESIDUAL VALUE) * RATE </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> This is mandatory for RB , FS and CA schedule types only. Cannot be entered for an SL schedule.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Currency in which the asset value is expressed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COST.OF.ASSET</field>
<desc>
        <p>The original value of the asset plus any additional cost incurred. This will default to original value if no input is made.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CLAIMED.TD</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the total capital allowances claimed to date. It is also a 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
        <p>The credit transaction code for this schedule. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> It will default from ASSET.CLASS if one is entered. A mandatory field if a schedule is defined. This must be a valid TRANSACTION code with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND equal to 'CREDIT' .</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.CAP.ALLOW.PCNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This specifies the maximum capital allowances as a percentage of the initial cost of an asset. The total capital allowances claimed must not be greater than this percentage * the total cost of the asset. This field is mandatory if capital allowance is set to 'YES'.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.CONTROL.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>The internal account number which holds the balance of the capital alllowances contra of an asset. Defaults to CCY CATEG 0001 where CATEG is derived from ASSET.CLASS.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTRY.IDS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.CLAIMED.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is an internal account number which holds the balance of capital allowances claimed for an asset. This will default to using the category from ASSET.CLASS as part of the number, if none is chosen.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the customer of he underlying lease if ASSET.STATUS equals 'IN-USE'; otherwise null. It is also a 'NOINPUT' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi-value field that holds the transaction ids of the underlying leases. This is an 'EXTERN' field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CAP.ALLOW</field>
<desc>
        <p>This specifies the maximum total allowances that can be claimed for the asset. This will not be greater than the cost of the asset.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCHED.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>There are five schedule types that can be chosen. They are as follows:- SL Straight Line RB Reducing Balance FS Flexible Schedules CA Capital Allowances WO Write Off Only schedule types 'SL', 'RB', and 'FS' are treated as schedules for depreciation and are also allowed for depreciation if DEPRECIATION is set to 'YES'. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> For schedule types SL, RB, or FS only one schedule type can be specified at any one time, that is to say multiple schedules must be of the same type. For schedule types SL, RB, or FS a frequency code or multiple occurances must be specified. CA schedule type is only allowed if the field Capital Allowance is set to 'YES' If WO schedule is chosen then no frequency or multiple occurance is allowed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WRITE.OFF.ACC.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>The internal account number which holds the write-off value of an asset. Defaults to CCY CATEG 00001 where CATEG is derived from ASSET.CLASS.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>This specifies the category for depreciation. It will be within the range of categories 60000 - 64999, and will default to the category within ASSET.CLASS if none is chosen.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc><p>The schedule amount to be paid on the schedule date as specified in DATE.FREQ.. It will default an amount calculated by type of schedule , schedule time remaining , amount already paid and original cost. </p><p>Validation Rules</p><p> For schedules SL and FS, the amount must be less the COST.OF.ASSET - RESIDUAL.VALUE. For schedule RB, the amount must be less than the CURRENT.VALUE - RESIDUAL.VALUE. For schedule CA, the amount must be less than the MAX.CAP.ALLOWANCE - TOTAL.CLAIMED.TD For schedule WO, the amount must be equal to the CURRENT.VALUE.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>The internal account number which holds the value of the asset. It defaults to CCY CATEG 0001 where CATEG is derived from ASSET.CLASS.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.CLASS</field>
<desc>
        <p>The grouping of various types of assets. Must be a valid id on ASSET.CLASS. A mandatory field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.REGISTER.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>The ASSET.REGISTER contains the information needed by T24 to be able to link the asset to either a STANDING.ORDER (for operating leases) or an LD based Annuity Leasing contract. The debit balance of the asset account would normally be created by the prior use of either FT or DC to pay the cost of the asset.. There are broadly three types of leasing contracts : Finance Leasing Hire Purchase Agreement Operating Leasing There is the option for depreciation on all types of leases and Capital Allowances on Finance Leases and Operating Leases. There are four types of depreciation calculations supported : Straight Line Reducing Balances Annuity Flexible Schedules Depreciation is carried out during the end of day depending on the schedule frequency. An asset must be recorded on the register before any leasing contracts can be made. An ASSET CLASS category for an asset must be defined before an asset can be recorded.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

