<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ASSET.CLASS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Insert text here </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Rule 1 Rule 2</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a field for the description for the type of Asset Class being set up.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPITAL.ALLOWANCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether Capital Allowances are to be allowed for this type of Asset Class. The choices are either Yes or No.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>An existing CATEGORY code in the range 11000 19999.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPRECIATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether depreciation is allowed for this type of class or not.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.TRANS.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
        <p>The credit transaction code for Capital Allowances. It must exist on the TRANSACTION file with DEBIT.CREDIT.INT = CREDIt</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.TRANS.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
        <p>The debit transaction code for Capital Allowances. It must exist on the TRANSACTION file with DEBIT.CREDIT.INT = DEBIT.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.TRANS.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
        <p>The debit transaction code for depreciation . </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> It must exist on the TRANSACTION. File with DEBIT.CREDIT.INT = DEBIt</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>This a category for depreciation entries, which will be an existing category within a predefined range of categories set up by the user. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Within a predefined range of categories 60000 -64999.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.TRANS.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
        <p>The credit transaction code for depreciation. It must exist on the TRANSACTION file with DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = CREDIT.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WRITE.OFF.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>An existing CATEGORY code in the range 1100 - 19999</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.CATEGORY</field>
<desc><p>The new Asset Class being set up will be within a predefined range of categories, 11000 - 19999, in the total list of categories.It will also be in the range of Asset Categories within this list. For example, a category within the Fixed Assets range of categories could be for Cars, Asset Classes of this being Rover or BMW. Categories on this list are set up by users of the system.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.CLASS.KEY</field>
<desc>
        <p>This application allows the setting up of categories under which the various types of Assets are set up, to be used by the different types of lease contracts. The fields include depreciation and capital allowance CATEGORY codes, as well as TRANSACTION code fields for both of these. This then allows the user to define many of the fields that will be applicable for that entire group of assets, this means that when the user inputs a new asset in ASSET.REGISTER, many fields can be defaulted to those applicable to that category of assets. An asset cannot be recorded onto the system unless a category has been defined for it.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.CLAIMED.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>The Capital Allowance claimed category. Must be in the range 11000 - 19999.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CA.CONTROL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Capital Allowances Control category . Must be in the range 11000 - 19999</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

