<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>AUTO.TXN.POPULATE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LOG.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether Log is required or not. 'Y' will turn the LOG on, 'N' or 'NULL' will turn the LOG off.</p>
            <p>NOTE : Turning LOG on will reduce the performance . Hence use it only while analyzing the problems </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Y OR N is accepted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STARTING.JOURNAL</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field accepts valid journal ids. It is used to build OFS strings for a range of journal records. This facility should be used for testing purpose only. </p>
            <p>Input starting journal no. in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>OPTIONAL</p>
            <p>Should be a valid id from journal file (F.JOURNAL) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFS.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name of the source record, which will be used to replay the transactions</p>
            <p>Should be a valid OFS.SOURCE record with SOURCE.TYPE as GLOBUS. This field can be entered only during the RESTORE operation</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Max number of characters allowed 15.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOG.PATH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the path where the log file will be stored. Kindly note the log file name will always be defaulted as ATP.LOG in the LOGPATH immaterial of the operation performed (BUILD/REPLAY).</p>
            <p>The UNIX or NT pathname for the directory can be specified with '/' for unix and '\' for NT.</p>
            <p>example : /dev/bnk/bnk.run/logdir (unix).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Unix/NT path name</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>BUILD operation is used to build the OFS strings by extracting the transaction details from the Journal.</p>
            <p>LOAD operation is used to replay the OFS strings in the test area.</p>
            <p>NOTE : The BUILD operation will always be used in the source/live area and the REPLAY option is used in the test area where the OFS strings formed in the source area will be replayed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Accepts BUILD OR RESTORE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATP.FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>BUILD: </p>
            <p>During Build operation the OFS strings will be stored in the file name specified in the ATP.FILE.NAME. </p>
            <p>REPLAY: </p>
            <p>During the replay operation the ATP tools picks up the OFS strings from the file name specified in the ATP.FILE.NAME and replay the transactions in the destination area.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>MAX SIZE : 35 Characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATP.FILE.PATH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the directory where the OFS file ( Defined in ATP.FILE.NAME) is stored.</p>
            <p>Unix / NT pathname can be specified with '\' (WINDOWS) or '/' (UNIX).</p>
            <p>example : /dev/mbdemo/mbdemo.run/atppath will be the directory under which the ATP file name </p>
            <p>will be stored.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Must be a valide Unix/NT path name.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENDING.JOURNAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts valid journal ids. It is used to build OFS strings for a range of journal records. This facility should be used for testing purpose only. </p>
            <p>Input ending  journal no. in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>OPTIONAL</p>
            <p>Should be a valid id from journal file (F.JOURNAL)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

