<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>BROWSER.PARAMETERS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds details of the system wide parameters that are required to run the Browser interface to T24.</p>
            <p>      It contains one record identified as SYSTEM.</p>
            <p>      This allows the user to define various parameters, such as, which applications require specialised processing when using Browser, the names of the 'skins' supported in Browser, as well as shortcut key definitions.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>HEIGHT.PACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>In order to ensure that windows are opened in the correct place and with the correct size, pack settings are required to take account of the browsers title and border widths.</p>
            <p>     This field defines the height number of pixels of a window border.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LARGE.REPORT.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the size of large reports.  If a report is large than this size then it will be displayed in text format due to memory usage at the web server.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAVE.CHANGES.OVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this is set to YES then when closing a contract screen where changes have been made to the field data, a prompt will be shown indicating that the changes will be lost.  This allows the user to cancel the close operation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.PACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>In order to ensure that windows are opened in the correct place and with the correct size, pack settings are required to take account of the browsers title and border widths.</p>
            <p>     This field defines the top number of pixels of a window border (e.g. title bar).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STACK.DEPTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This defines the number of old tokens stores on a user basis.  The default setting is 5.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESERVE.TOKEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Preserve Token field is used internally by the Browser product to signify whether 'tokens', used between T24 and the Browser client, expire or not.</p>
            <p>      This setting should only be used by System Administrators that are fully aware of the consequences of setting this field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Accepted values:  YES and NO.  (Optional input. No default     value).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELPTEXT.DIRECTORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is no longer used.  The directory where the XML HelpText files are stored is now stored in helpParameters.xml as part of the Browser web application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALID.SKIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the names of the 'skins' allowed for displaying screens in the Browser product.</p>
            <p>      A 'skin' determines the 'look and feel' of the Browser screens in terms of colours, fonts, graphics, etc.  Each Browser installation will be delivered with a number of predefined skins that can be used.  This field defines those that are present.</p>
            <p>      The skin displayed used by Browser screen is defined on a user basis by the application BROWSER.PREFERENCES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Up to 20 (type A) alphanumeric characters.  Multivalue field     (Optional input. Default value = blank.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORTCUT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the shortcut key for the corresponding shortcut button to be used by screens in the Browser product.</p>
            <p>      Together with the corresponding shortcut button selected, these pairs define a 'shortcut' method to access action keys on Browser screens.  A number of pre-defined shortcut buttons are presented in this field that can then be associated with a single character key to be used as a shortcut to the button.</p>
            <p>      For example, selecting a shortcut button of "COMMIT" and a corresponding shortcut key value of "C" will cause the "Commit" button to gain focus on a contract screen when the "Alt" key is pressed in conjunction with the "C" key.  Then pressing the "Enter" key will cause the commit to take place.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Optional input.</p>
            <p>      A maximum of 1 character may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEFT.PACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>In order to ensure that windows are opened in the correct place and with the correct size, pack settings are required to take account of the browsers title and border widths.</p>
            <p>     This field defines the left hand-side number of pixels of a window border.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>There is only 1 record for BROWSER.PARAMETERS called SYSTEM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WIDTH.PACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>In order to ensure that windows are opened in the correct place and with the correct size, pack settings are required to take account of the browsers title and border widths.</p>
            <p>     This field defines the width number of pixels of a window border.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.STD.APPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the non-standard applications that require additional processing when the Browser product is used.</p>
            <p>      The Browser product uses a form of caching when the user requires a new contract screen to be displayed.  If the application is marked as being non-standard then the new contract screen will not be cached, thus ensuring the the application is run every time.  This is important for such applications as TELLER.</p>
            <p>      This setting should only be used by System Administrators that are fully aware of the consequences of setting this field.</p>
            <p>      This field is applicable only till R07.005 and lower releases”</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Up to 35 characters.</p>
            <p>      Must match an application name from the PGM file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTER.KEY.COMMITS</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this field is set to YES then use of the Enter (Return) key will Commit the contract on display.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROWSER.WIDTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the default width of Browser windows when opened outside of a Composite Sreen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USED.TIMEOUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is no longer used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORTCUT.BUTTON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the shortcut button and corresponding shortcut key values to be used by screens in the Browser product.</p>
            <p>      Together with the corresponding shortcut key value, these pairs define a 'shortcut' method to access action keys on Browser screens.  A number of pre-defined shortcut buttons are presented in this field that can then be associated with a single character key to be used as a shortcut to the button.</p>
            <p>      For example, selecting a shortcut button of "COMMIT" and a corresponding shortcut key value of "C" will cause the "Commit" button to gain focus on a contract screen when the "Alt" key is pressed in conjunction with the "C" key.  Then pressing the "Enter" key will cause the commit to take place.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      The following values will be accepted:  AUTHORISE = Authorise     a contract.  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field can be multivalued depending on which attributes are required.  Valid options are :-</p>
            <p />
            <p>  CHECKFILE.ENRICHMENT</p>
            <p>    If this option is selected then checkfile enrichments will be run dynamically. Otherwise enrichments will only be run when a contract is committed or validated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  MAXIMIZE.WINDOWS</p>
            <p>    If this option is selected then windows will be always be displayed in the maximized state when opened.  This does not apply to the main window.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  MULTILINE.VERSION.HEADERS</p>
            <p>    If this option is selected then browser will display both lines of the VERSION header (fields HDR.1.00 to HDR.2...132) in the user's language.</p>
            <p>    If no heading has been defined for the users language, the default language heading will be used.</p>
            <p>    If no heading has been defined at all, the version description will be used.</p>
            <p>    If no description or heading has been defined, the application name and version will be used.</p>
            <p>    This setting is off by default as multiline headers can take up a lot of room in composite screens.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  NO.AUTOCOMPLETE</p>
            <p>    If this option is selected then auto-completion of field values is switched off.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  NO.LANG.IN.VERSION</p>
            <p>    If this option is selected then the language prefix (e.g. "GB") will not be displayed in field labels.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  NO.SELECTION</p>
            <p>    If this option is selected the enquiry selection fields are not displayed on the enquiry result screen.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  NO.SORT.OPTIONS</p>
            <p>    If this option is selected then lists of values will not be sorted in to an alphabetical list, but will be displayed in the order in which they were defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROWSER.HEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the default height of Browser windows when opened outside of a Composite Sreen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROWSER.LEFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the default left screen position of Browser windows when opened outside of a Composite Sreen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROWSER.TOP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the default top screen position of Browser windows when opened outside of a Composite Sreen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

