<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>BROWSER.PREFERENCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file defines a user's preferences for the appearance and behaviour of the Browser product screens.  The application is keyed on the user's Id.</p>
            <p> This allows the user to define various parameters, such as, which 'skin' the user would like to run the Browser with thus determine the 'look and feel' of the Browser windows, as well as a number of optional attributes defining whether they wish to see Hot Fields and Auto Launch Enquiries in their Browser.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SKIN.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the 'skin' to be used for a user's Browser screens.</p>
            <p> A 'skin' determines the 'look and feel' of the Browser screens in terms of colours, fonts, graphics, etc.  Each Browser installation will be delivered with a number of predefined skins that can be used.  This field defines which skin the user prefers..</p>
            <p> The valid skin names are defined in BROWSER.PARAMETERS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Up to 20 (type A) alphanumeric characters.  (Optional input. Default value = blank.)</p>
            <p> Must exist in the BROWSER.PARAMETERS list of valid skin names.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT.LOCATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The destination for any print requests.  Values are :-</p>
            <p>Local - use a printer connected to a user's PC</p>
            <p>Server - use a printer connected to the T24 Application Server</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAVE.WIN.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether or not window positions and size should be saved when a window is closed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to BROWSER.PREFERENCES is the USER record ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define the numeric value of top, left, width and height of a screen delimited by spaces.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines a number of Attributes for the user's Browser session..</p>
            <p> This includes whether the user wants to see any Hot Fields (as defined by VERSION) or Auto Launch Enquiries (as defined by CONTEXT.ENQUIRY) on their contract screens.  A user may be accessing T24 via a slow network link, therefore the time taken to return to the T24 server to validate hot fields or run context enquiries may be unacceptable.  Therefore, these facilities can be disabled here on a per user basis.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Accepted values: NO.HOT.FIELDS = Indicates that the user does not     want to see any Hot Fields on contract screens.  NO.AUTO.LAUNCHES     = Indicates that the user does not want to see any Auto Launch Enquiries     on contract screens.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.WILDCARD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the user to define and add their own wildcard for running enquiries. By default enquiries are run using the '...' match. New enquiry wildcards can be additionally added.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAIN.SCREEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of a Composite Screen (i.e. from EB.COMPOSITE.SCREEN) record that will be loaded when the user signs in.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

