<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>BROWSER.TOOLS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This Application defines Tools to be used on a BROWSER.TOOLBAR record. Tools defined here will be displayed dependent on the definition and then act according dependent on the definition herein</p>
            <p>   Validation Rules</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TOOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This  is the key to the BROWSER.TOOLS application. It is a text description of the tool in question</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the name of an image file to display on the button. The filename should be the name of a file stored in the /plaf/images directory on the web server</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Any text up to 35 chars</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.CONF.PROMPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether a confirmation message should be displayed when the tool is pressed.  The message displayed is that defined by the PROMPT.TEXT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROMPT.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A prompt message to be displayed when a tool is pressed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies what function the tool uses if it is required to perform a commit on the current deal</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A, D, R or I</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the tool.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the text that will be displayed on the button when displayed</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Any Text up to 35 characters in length</p>
            <p>   Language Field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The javascript command for this BROWSER.TOOL.</p>
            <p>  Where a field name in is prefixed by AMFE_ the field will be subtituted by field data from the enquiry selection data.  </p>
            <p>  This can also be the additional data to be sent to T24 with a commit. The contents of ITEM will be set in the OFS$TOOLBAR.TARGET common available. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the type of tool.  For example, whether the tool is a COMMIT button or runs some JAVASCRIPT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the data that will be used in different ways for different button types</p>
            <p>   ACTION: The contents of this field will be passed back to T24 with a commit. This feature is currently unavailable.</p>
            <p>   DO.DEAL: The contents of this field will be used as the basis for a command line operation</p>
            <p>   DO.API: The contents of this field will be used as the parameter to be passed to the API</p>
            <p>Target is the destination frame or window in which the output of the action performed is launched.</p>   
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Any Text up to 35 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the type of tool that is being defined. There are 4 types of tool.</p>
            <p>   ACTION: This type of button does a commit using the function defined in the FUNCTION field for the tool. The value of the ITEM field is also returned to the T24 application and is set in common for the application use.</p>
            <p>   COMMIT: This type of button does a commit using the function  defined in the FUNCTION field for the tool.</p>
            <p>   DO.API: This type of button does a call to the API: the value of TARGET is passed into the API as the parameter</p>
            <p>   DO.DEAL: This type of button runs the command line defined in the TARGET field</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   either ACTION, COMMIT, DO.API or DO.DEAL</p>
            <p>   Mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOLTIP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the text to be displayed as a tool tip when the mouse floats above the tool.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Any Text up to 35 characters</p>
            <p>   Language field</p>
            <p>   Mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORTCUT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies a shortcut to be used on the browser screen</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Any Text, one character</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a currently unused field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.TOOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether the tool should be marked as the default tool on a toolbar.  The use of the Return key will activate the default tool.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines how the tool should be displayed.  The default option is as a button.  The tool can also be displayed as an image, as a text hyperline</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Image</p>
            <p>   Text</p>
            <p>   Text Image - Future Use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENABLED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether the tool is enabled for use. YES or NO</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   YES or NO</p>
            <p>   Mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>STYLE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
