<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>CHANNEL.PROTECTION.LIMIT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ALLOWED.CCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>List of currencys that the protection limit applies to. Null field implies all currencys. A protection limit only applies if all the fields are true.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rule</p>
        <p>3 CCY, must be a valid currency code.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOWED.CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Preferred Channel for which the protection limit applies to. Null field indicates that limit is applied for all channels</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation rules</p>
        <p>Links to EB.CHANNEL</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>List of T24 applications that the protection limit applies to. Null field implies all applications for the associated SYSTEM.ID. A protection limit only applies if all the fields are true.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rule</p>
        <p>20 PG, must be a valid application.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.RISK.RATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>List of Beneficiary risks that the protection limit applies to.</p>
        <p>This is linked to BENEFICIARY field BEN.RISK.TYPE</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rule</p>
        <p>Holds value from 1-9 numbers</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>The currency of LIMIT.AMOUNT field.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rules</p>
        <p>3 CCY, must be a valid currency</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>The actual Limit amount</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rule</p>
        <p>10 numeric</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRO.LIMIT.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Key reference to the application</p>
        <p>The Protection Limit  is used by products which have daily limits on the cumulative amount of transactions that can be done via an external channel.</p>
        <p>By default a limit which is established applies to all transactions. Should a user wish to limit certain transactions while leaving others unrestricted they can do so by limiting the transactions based upon System Id, Application, Transaction Type, Currency and Beneficiary Risk.</p>
        <p>These options are each multi-valued and aggregated with each other. For example should a user choose an 'Application' of Funds Transfer and a 'Beneficiary Risk' of High, then only transactions initiated via Funds Transfer, to a high-risk beneficiary will have the limit applied.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>List of system ids that the protection limit applies to. Null field implies all system ids A protection limit only applies if all the fields are true.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rule</p>
        <p>4 alpha numeric must be a valid product code on EB.PRODUCT.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.OF.DAY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>List of transaction types that the protection limit applies to. Null field implies all transaction types. A protection limit only applies if all the fields are true.</p>
        <p>This is linked to EB.TRANSACTION.TYPE, which is used to group multiple transaction codes together.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rule</p>
        <p>15 Alpha numeric, must be a valid transaction group code on EB.TRANSACTION.TYPE.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

