<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>CHANNEL.PROFILE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Indicates the separators to be used when formatting amounts for input/display purposes</p>
            <p value="2">Enquiries, Repgens &amp;amp; screen input/display</p>
        </p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation rules</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">2 Alphanumeric character</p>
            <p value="2">Decimal separater can be comma or full stop</p>
            <p value="3">Same character cannot be used</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMIT.ACTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Multi-value defining the actions to be performed when committing a record.  Valid values are :-</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Blank – normal commit processing.</p>
            <p value="2">“CONFIRM” – General override to be raised confirming committal of the contract whilst displaying the contract in See mode (using either the same VERSION or an alternative VERSION record).</p>
            <p value="3">“PASSWORD” – User’s password must be supplied for successful committal.</p>
            <p value="4">“ONE.TIME.PASSWORD” – A one-time password must be supplied for successful committal.</p>
            <p value="5">“MEMORABLE.DATA” - User’s memorable data must be supplied for successful committal.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ATTRIB</field>
<desc>
        <p>Attributes to enable / disable the contract features:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">MULTI.VERSION.HEADERS – enables version multi-line version headers to be displayed.</p>
            <p value="2">NO.AUTO.LAUNCHES – restricts auto launch of enquiries.</p>
            <p value="3">NO.CALENDAR  -  Hides the calendar icon for date type fields.</p>
            <p value="4">NO.CHECKFILE.ENRICHMENT – turns off the check file enrichment feature.</p>
            <p value="5">NO.CONTEXT.ENQUIRIES – disables the context enquiries.</p>
            <p value="6">NO.DROPDOWNS – disable the dropdown feature.</p>
            <p value="7">NO.HEADER.TAB  -  won’t display the contract header.</p>
            <p value="8">NO.HOT.FIELDS – disable the hot fields functionality.</p>
            <p value="9">NO.WEB.VALIDATION.FIELDS – disable the web validation.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Description of profile used by External user is defined in this field.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation rules</p>
        <p>Standard T24 language field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.WILDCARD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Wild card characters that will be used by processing enquiry</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">*,% could be defined</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.ATTRIB</field>
<desc>
        <p>Attributes to enable / disable the enquiry features:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">NO.SELECTION -  restricts  enquiry selection screen embeeded on enquiry response window.</p>
            <p value="2">ALL.DATA   - to display all the selected records.</p>
            <p value="3">NO.COLUMN.HEADER –  restricts the column header being displayed on the enquiry results.window.</p>
            <p value="4">NO.TOOLBAR – to disable the enquiry toolbar display.</p>
            <p value="5">ZERORECORD.DISPLAY – blank screen will be displayed when no records are selected.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOW.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>A generic type field specifying the type of flow being defined.  Values allowed are :</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">“FIRST.LOGIN” - action to be performed when a new user logs in for the very first time.</p>
            <p value="2">“EVERY.LOGIN” – action to be performed when a user logs in.</p>
            <p value="3">“INITIAL.SCREEN” – initial composite screen to be displayed after a user logs in.</p>
            <p value="4">“POST.COMMIT” – action to be performed following a successful commit.</p>
            <p value="5">“LOGOUT” - action to be performed when a user logs out.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOW.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>A generic value field specifying what to display at this point in the workflow.  This should either be a EB.COMPOSITE.SCREEN record Id or a URL to a static page.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.ACCESS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Key to CHANNEL.PRODUCT.ACCESS can be defined here.  Standard multi-value field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROTECTION.LMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Key to CHANNEL.PROTECTION.LIMIT can be defined here.  Standard multi-value field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SKIN.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>External user skin to be specified in this field.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rules</p>
        <p>20 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SMS.GROUP</field>
<desc>
        <p>The USER rights can be generically defined for more than one user through a USER.SMS.GROUP. The ID of the USER.SMS.GROUP record can be provided here and the restrictions defined there will be followed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ATTRIB</field>
<desc>
        <p>Attributes to turn off the system level features:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">NO.AUTOCOMPLETE - disable the IE’s auto complete feature.</p>
            <p value="2">SIMPLE.INTERFACE - turns off all the above mentioned contract and enquiry features.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOL.STYLE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Display of  Tool style could be specified:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">TEXT          -  indicates the tools to be displayed as text.</p>
            <p value="2">IMAGE         – Indicates the tools to be displayed as images.</p>
            <p value="3">TEXT.IMAGE – Indicates both text and image could be displayed on tools.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOLBAR</field>
<desc>
        <p>Browser toolbar to be associated with TOOLBAR.TYPE. Should be valid record in BROWSER.TOOLBAR.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOLBAR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicates the pre-defined list of toolbar types as referred from EB.LOOKUP  TOOLBAR.</p>
        <p>Predefined values:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">APPLICATION</p>
            <p value="2">ENQUIRY</p>
            <p value="3">ENQUIRY.SELECTION</p>
            <p value="4">CONTRACT</p>
            <p value="5">SIGN.ON</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

