<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>CONTEXT.ENQUIRY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used only in conjunction with the T24 GUI. </p>
            <p>Records on this file are used to define enquiries that are linked either to applications, versions or specific felds within applications or versions. </p>
            <p>Where the key refers to either an application, these records are used to list the enquiries that may be run on any field that has that related file. In addition, contract enquiries may be specified by application and version, e.g. the record LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS on this file will hold a list of enquiries that may be run from the LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS application. Enquiries defined in a version record will appear in addition to any defined for the application. </p>
            <p>Where a file name (and optionally version) and a field is specified, then this record pertains to the context sensitive enquiries that are available for the field. These enquiries are grouped together on the Enquiry Menu by application, or application and version. </p>
            <p>All of the enquiries available may be launched from both the Enquiry Menu, and also from the pop-up menu in the contract input screen. The pop-up menu appears whenever the mouse is right clicked on a field. </p>
            <p>In addition, enquiries may be set to autolaunch either at field level, or at validation of a function. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RES.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RES.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>An enquiry / version which references the file or field is defined here, that will appear on the Enquiry and contract Popup menus as a context sensitive enquiry. </p>
            <p>Associated with this field is the field SEL.FIELD which is used to define the selection field on the enquiry / version which references the file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must reference a valid record on the ENQUIRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.ENQ.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields ENQUIRY.NAME to AUTO.LAUNCH form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.0</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PGM.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The description entered here will appear on the drop-down menu according to the user's language. The GB description is required as a default.</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value language field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This Functionality will only execute from Desktop 2</p>
            <p>Text</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies in which order sorting needs to be performed. </p>
            <p>A - Ascending Order</p>
            <p>D - Descending Order</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines for the associated SEL.FIELD, which operands are allowed for the enquiry.  </p>
            <p>This field allows the selection operands to be limited for a particular enquiry. This may be required where the enquiry is based on one particular selection value, for example an enquiry based on Account movements may wish to restrict the BOOKING.DATE selection to RG or EQ. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The following are the operands provided for selection : Null, EQ, NE, GT, GE, LT, LE, RG, NR, CT, NC, LK or UL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the application, application and version, application and field or application, version and field to which the record relates. The type of key depends on the type of the record defined. </p>
            <p>Where a field is specified, the record is a field level record, and the only auto launch options available are YES or NO. </p>
            <p>Where no field is specified, the record if a file level record and the auto launch options are set according to the function that will trigger the launch once the function has been completed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Either the name of an application, e.g. SWAP Or the name of an application and version, e.g. SWAP,IRS Or the name of an application and a field, e.g. SWAP-SWAP.TYPE. The field must be a valid field on the file, but may be entered as either a field name or a field number. Or the name of an appication, version and field, e.g. SWAP,IRS-SWAP.TYPE. Again, the field must be a valid field on the file, but may be entered as either a field name or a field number. </p>
            <p>Field length:  The maximum length of this field has been set at 70 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.FRAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field TARGET.FRAME is changed to the reserved field MV.RES.0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This fields defines the selection field which references the key to the file which is defining this record, e.g. the CUSTOMER record may define the ENQUIRY record LIAB to be one of the related context sensitive enquiries. The selection field of the enquiry which references the customer file is the LIABILITY.NUMBER selection field. This information should be defined here. </p>
            <p>For enquiries that are set to auto-launch at F5, additional functionality allows further specification, in the form. </p>
            <p>Selection field name Selection field name OPERAND data Selection field name OPERAND record field name </p>
            <p>e.g. </p>
            <p>LIABILITY.NUMBER </p>
            <p>CURRENCY EQ "USD" </p>
            <p>LIABILITY.NUMBER EQ CUSTOMER.NO </p>
            <p>The first syntax supplies the key to the record as the data, and EQ as the OPERAND. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a SELECTION.FLD as defined on the related ENQUIRY record.  or</p>
            <p>For enquiries that are to be auto launched at F5;  A valid SELECTION FLD        followed by A valid OPERAND              followed by A valid field name, or data in quotes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RES.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The application or VERSION named here will be available for launch on the drop-down menu in the same way as the enquiries. If this is specified on a VERSION used for input then the user will probably need multiple sessions specified in the USER record as the new application will displace the existing one for a single session user.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This Functionality will only execute from Desktop 2</p>
            <p>A name of a VERSION or an application</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCRIPT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The SCRIPT named here will be available for launch on the drop-down menu in the same way as the enquiries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This Functionality will only execute from Desktop 2</p>
            <p>Script must exist on SCRIPT.DESIGNER file</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RES.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VER.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The description entered here will appear on the drop-down menu according to the user's language. The GB description is required as a default.</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value language field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This Functionality will only execute from Desktop 2</p>
            <p>Text</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Input of up to 35 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Either a field name or a corresponding value associated with the field name entered in the field - SEL.FIELD is allowed. This field is used, to enable the Context Enquiry to be run using multiple selection fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p>Upto 35 alphanumeric characters is accepted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.LAUNCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where the record refers to a specific field, that is a field name has been set in the key, this field determines whether the associated enquiry will automatically be launched once input to this field is complete. </p>
            <p>Where the record refers to a file, the functions that will trigger the automatic launch of the enquiry are defined here.The launch occurs once any of the functions defined are completed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>For field level records, only input of YES or NO is allowed.</p>
            <p>Records that refer to applications, or applications and versions allow the definition of functions. Valid Function codes are:               A 2 C D E H I L P Q R S V  If NOT is entered, plus one or more Function codes, the System converts it to a list of all the functions that are allowed. 0-29 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters:                  1.    Function codes separated by spaces           or    2.    NOT + one or more Function codes           or    3.    NO (No trigger produced)           or    4.    ALL (All Functions produce the trigger).</p>
            <p>Autolauching of enquiries is possible when the record is put on HOLD by   specifying "O" Function on AUTO.LAUNCH.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTEXT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value updated in this field is either ENQUIRY / VERSION depending on whether an Enquiry Name / Version Name is input in the field ENQUIRY.NAME.</p>
            <p>For example: If CUSTOMER-LIST is input in ENQUIRY.NAME, then CONTEXT.TYPE is updated as "ENQUIRY"</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NoInput field. </p>
            <p>A maximum of 7 characters is allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A description of the record is held in this field, and should be something meaningful as it is this description that appears in the Enquiry and contract pop-up menus in the GUI. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of up to 35 alphanumeric characters.  Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

