<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>CONVERSION.PGMS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>When a customer receives a release of T24, there are usually conversion programs which need to be run, due to changes in file layouts of files used by T24.  If a customer is operating in a multi-company environment, some programs will have to be run in each company, thus resulting in a lot of manual input which can produce errors. </p>
            <p>CONVERSION.PGMS is designed to automate the running of the conversion programs.  One record will be released to CONVERSION.PGMS for each major release.  The record will detail all the conversion programs to be run for the release, along with the level of each program.  When the record is released as part of GLOBUS.RELEASE, the release procedure will determine in which companies each of the programs has to be run, depending on the application and level of the program.  After the record has been checked and authorised by the user, RUN.CONVERSION.PGMS can be run to actually run the conversion programs.  Once the conversion programs have been run successfully, the user should reverse the record on CONVERSION.PGMS. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Holds the T24 status of the record, e.g. INAU, IHLD etc.,</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up   to 3 alphanumneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No   input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically   generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HALT.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The message to be displayed if the run conversion utility is to halt after running this program.  As this field cannot hold much information, it will normally refer to the section in the release documentation for a fuller explanation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-50 type A (any) characters.  PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Notes as to why a conversion program was not run.  It is recommended that if it is decided that a conversion program is not to be run (i.e. run program flag is set to 0), the notes field should be updated with the reason why the program was not run.</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.SELECTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Company codes the conversion program is to be run in. </p>
            <p>This field contains all the companies in which the conversion program is to be run.  It is updated when either the program name or program level is entered.  The conversion program will be run in companies depending on the level and application of the conversion program.  For example, if a securities conversion program is defined as being of FINancial level, the company file will be accessed to determine all financial non-consolidation, non-reporting companies in which securities is installed. </p>
            <p>When a conversion record is released, the companies field will be updated by the release procedures, according to the companies and applications installed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-90 type A (any) characters. PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Displays the number of Transactions generated by theSystem in order to effect the Transfer. I.e., how many authorised version of this record exist.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up   to 4 numneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No   input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically   generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is an audit dictionary field used to keep track of on what date and time the record was transacted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up       to 15 numneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No       input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically       generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELEASE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the release number. </p>
            <p>If being run at Temenos London, the release number must reference a record on the PIF.RELEASE.NO file or, if only the major release number is entered (e.g. 14.1), it must reference a record on the PIF.RELEASE.NO file when suffixed by .0 (e.g. 14.1.0). </p>
            <p>If being run at other sites, the release number must reference an existing record or must begin with a non-numeric character. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-20 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is an audit dictionary field that shows the department code of the user who created/updated the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up       to 4 numneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No       input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically       generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies whether the program was: </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 - run successfully 0 - did not run successfully null - has not been run </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field is updated by RUN.CONVERSION.PGMS when the conversion program is run.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 numeric   character.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This     is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROGRAM.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the level at which the conversion program should run. </p>
            <p>When this field is entered, the sub-value set from companies selected to run information is expanded with the company code of all the companies in which the conversion program should be run, depending on the level and application of the conversion program. For example, if a securities conversion program is defined as being of FINancial level, the company file will be accessed to determine all financial non-consolidation, non-reporting companies in which securities is installed.  The sub-valued set will then be expanded to contain these companies, with the run pgm flag set to 1, i.e. the program is to be run.  If there are no companies in which the conversion program is to be run (e.g. securities has not been installed in any company), the sub-value set will be null. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Values are:          INT (Installation)         CUS (Customer)         FIN (Financial)         FTF (Financial table - financial information)         FTD (Financial table - non-financial)         CCY (Currency)         NOS (Nostro)         CST (Customer table)  PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.</p>
            <p>Optional input.  Default value INT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the user who ran the conversion and the time the conversion was run are detailed in this field.  </p>
            <p>This field is updated by RUN.CONVERSION.PGMS when the conversion program is run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-50 type A (any) characters. </p>
            <p>PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the reason why the conversion program did not run successfully.</p>
            <p>This field is updated by RUN.CONVERSION.PGMS when the conversion program is run.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-50 type A (any) characters. </p>
            <p>PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is an audit dictionary field used to keep track of who inputted the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up       to 35 alphanumneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No       input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically       generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDES</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains all the override messages, which the user agreed during input. Stores the full text of the override message for reference purpose.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up       to 35 alphanumneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No       input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically       generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROGRAM.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the conversion program to be run. </p>
            <p>Must reference a record on PGM.FILE or CONVERSION.DETAILS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-30 type A (any) characters.  PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.PGM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the conversion program is to be run or has already been run for the company named in companies selected. </p>
            <p>When the conversion program record is released as part of the release procedures, the run program flag for all programs will be set to 1, i.e. the conversion program is to be run in the company specified.  If there are no companies (e.g. a securities conversion program is to be run but securities has not been installed in any company), the conversion program will not be run.  If the user decides that the program is not be run, the run program flag can be set to 0, i.e. the program is not to be run.  It is recommended that if the program flag is set to 1, the notes field is updated with the reason why the conversion program was not run.  If the run program flag is set to 0, it can be reset to 1.  When the conversion program is run by RUN.CONVERSION.PGMS, the run flag is set to 2 (program has been run) when the program completes successfully.  The run program flag can be set to 1 if it is currently 2, but an override message is given. Care should be taken if resetting a program flag of a program that has already been run, as most conversion programs should not be rerun. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 numeric character:        0  -  conversion program is not to be run in this company       1  -  conversion program is to be run in this company       2  -  conversion program has already been run in this company.   PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.</p>
            <p>Optional input.  Default value 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HALT.AFTER.PGM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the run conversion programs utility should halt after running this conversion program. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character.        0  -  run conversion programs utility does not halt after             running this program       1  -  run conversion programs utility does halt after             running this program  PROGRAM.NAME through to RUN.INFO form a multivalue set describing each conversion program to be run.</p>
            <p>Optional input.  Default value 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDIT.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is an audit dictionary field used to keep track of date and time of the record been audited.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up       to 15 numneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No       input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically       generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDITOR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is an audit dictionary field, which holds the name of the user, who audited the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up       to 16 alphanumneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No       input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically       generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHORISER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is an audit dictionary field used to keep track of the person who authorised the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up       to 20 alphanumneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No       input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically       generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is an audit dictionary field which holds the company code of the record where created in.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up       to 11 alphanumneric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No       input field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Automatically       generated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

