<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>CUS.POS.ENQ.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines which amount is to be displayed for a given Category/System id/ enquiry type. The CUSTOMER.POSITION file contains a DEAL.AMOUNT, the full amount of the deal in DEAL.CCY, and PERC.AMOUNT which is the margin, or percentage value of the deal amount which is used to update the limits system, or in the case of securities is the total margin value of the seecuties held. For certain types of application (e.g FX deals, IRS) the full value does not reflect the true risk, and the percentage value should be displayed. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional input. Input must be PERC or FULL.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Contains the key to the STMT.NARR.FORMAT record used to define the format of narrative to be displayed with details relevant to a CUSTOMER.POSITION record. The details of the format narrative should be defined using the application STMT.NARR.FORMAT, the id of which is identified by this field. Narrative details should be based on the CUSTOMER.POSITION file. CONVERSION @ E.CUS.NARRATIVE ---------------------------- The conversion @ E.CUS.NARRATIVE can be used to build the narrative defined by the NARR.TYPE. The value passed to the conversion should be the NARR.TYPE extracted from the CPEP.RECORD I-descriptor. The conversion will populate field DISPLAY.NARRATIVE in the work record used by ENQUIRY. This can then be extracted and displayed as any other enquiry field, using another field name. The narrative built may be multi-valued. Example: 1) Build the narrative 10.20 FIELD.NAME..... NARRATIVE 11.20. 1 OPERATION... FIELD CPEP.RECORD 13.20 LENGTH.MASK.... 30L 14.20. 1 CONVERSION.. FIELD &gt;,3,1 14.20. 2 CONVERSION.. @ E.CUS.NARRATIVE 15.20. 1 COMMENTS.... This should not be displayed 15.20. 2 COMMENTS.... directly, but should extracted 15.20. 3 COMMENTS.... from the field DISPLAY.NARR... 15.20. 4 COMMENTS.... to ensure multi vlaues are 15.20. 5 COMMENTS.... preserved 18.20 SINGLE.MULTI... M 2) Display the result 10.21 FIELD.NAME..... DISPLAY.NARRATIVE 11.21. 1 OPERATION... DISPLAY.NARRATIVE 12.21 COLUMN......... 26 16.21 TYPE........... L 18.21 SINGLE.MULTI... M </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional input. Input must exist in STMT.NARR.FORMAT.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.SELECT.RTN</field>
<desc>
        <p>The name of a local api routine to return a list of local application contract ids and application file ids.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.FILE.RET.DAYS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Contains the description of the customer position parameters defined. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional Input</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SORT.POSITION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines a value to be used when sorting the display order of customer position records. This allows a value to be attached to a CUSTOMER.POSITION record which can be used to sort information into a required order. I-Descriptor SORT.POSITION -------------------------- The I-Descriptor SORT.POSITION in the CUSTOMER.POSITION Standard Selection record is intended to provide a means of sorting Customer Position records into a designated Category code order. Where a SORT.POSITION is defined in this field, this value will be used, otherwise the CATEGORY.CODE is used. In this way items such as Commitments (category code 21095-99) can be allocated a Sort Position of 40000 to ensure they appear at the end of deal processing. Similarly items without a category code (e.g CO, LI, SC applications) can be assigned a value. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional input. Up to 5 alpha numeric characters allowed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the application (and VERSION) to be used as the drilldown for a deal with details contained in CUSTOMER.POSITION linked to this parameter record. When individual deal details are displayed in an enquiry based on the customer position file, the details of the application to view should be defined in this field. An existing application, or Version of an application should be defined. Applications can be identified by the I-descriptor EB.SYSTEM.ID which extracts element 3 of the CUSTOMER.POSITION key. Alternatively the CATEGORY.CODE could also be used to identify the application. CONVERSION @ E.CUS.POS.NEXT.LEVEL --------------------------------- Within CUSTOMER.POSITION enquiries the conversion routine @ E.CUS.POS.NEXT.LEVEL can be used to define the next level for drilldown. This performs the following processing: The element DETAIL.NEXT.LEVEL should be defined either as a SELECTION field or as an element in the ENQUIRY record. IF the value associated with this is not "NO" then: - For system id = AC the enquiry STMT.ENT.BOOK will be used. This will show the entries accross the account for the last 7 working days, unless a number of days is defined in the SELECTION AC.NO.DAYS, in which case this number of days will be shown. - For system id = SC the enquiry SC.SEC.ACC.HOLD.SUM will be used. This shows all securities held for the portfolio. - For all other applications the underlying application record will be displayed according to the defininition of this field. If no relevant record applies, the APPLICATION defined in the EB.SYSTEM.ID record will be used if present. If the DETAIL.NEXT.LEVEL value is NO: - If the Limit referenc in the CUSTOMER.POSITION key is SCPORT, the enquiry SC.PORT.HOLD.SUM will be run for the customer. - A limit reference beginning CURR will run the enquiry ACCT.BAL.LAST to display the accounts held for the customer. - A limit reference of COLL will run enquiry CO.001 for the customer to display collateral details. - A limit reference of COMMIT will run the enquiry LD.COMMITMENTS to show commitment contracts held by the customer. - A limit refernce of type FX will run FX.ENQ.SUMMARY to show FX deals held by the customer. - A global limit reference will run the enquiry LIAB showing all limits. - All other limit reference values will run LIM.TXN to show limit details. Details are returned to the enquiry in the following format: Next application / enquiry "&gt;" Selection 1 "&gt;" Selection 2 "&gt;" Selection 3 Where Application / Enquiry contains either: Application Name S id (E.g FOREX S FX9501212345) for an application or STMT.ENT.BOOK Selection 1 to 3 contains the required selection criteria for the next level enquiry, and is null for application drilldown. </p><p>Validation Rules</p><p> Must refer to an existing application of types H,U,L,T,W in the PGM.FILE. If a VERSION is specified (id contains ",") the record must exist in the VERSION application.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.LIAB</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether the Customer Position record should be displayed as an Asset or Liability item. When CUSTOMER.POSITION records are created, each item is designated as an ASSET or LIABILITY according to the sign of the DEAL.AMOUNT. A positive value is defined as an ASSET, a -ve value as an asset. The field ASSET.LIAB.MARKER is updated with an A or L respectively. Should this value wish to be reversed for a given record type, this field should be defined to contain the correct marker, which can then be referred to as required in the enquiry. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional input. A or L only allowed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEG.APPL.ENQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>The key to the customer position enquiry parameter record. Records may be defined at the level of: - Category and Enquiry Type (Separated by a '*') - System id and Enquiry Type (Separated by a '*') - Category - System id Enquiry Type is an arbitrary value assigned to an enquiry or group of enquiries, identified by the FIELD.NAME "CPE.TYPE" with a constant value in the Enquiry records. Category may be any category code which may or may not be specified in the system, and is not validated. The system will check the CATEGORY field in the CUSTOMER.POSITION record when attempting to extract the record. System Id is the system id held in the 3rd element of the CUSTOMER.POSITION record key. The I-descriptor CPEP.RECORD contains the most relevant record, the order for checking the most relevent record is described above. Examples of keys: 21095*CP1 - Category code 21095 for enquiry type CP1 LD*CP1 - LD application id for enquiry type CP1 21096 - Category 21096 LD - LD application Examples of records applied: 1) Enquiry type CP1, CUSTOMER.POSITION for LD commitment (cat code 21095). This will use 21095*CP1 as both elements are defined. 2) Enquiry type CP1, CUSTOMER.POSITION for LD commitment (cat code 21096). This will use LD*CP1 as there is no specific record for the category and type. The record 21096 is NOT used as there is a specific record for the application and enquiry type. 3) Enquiry type CP2, CUSTOMER.POSITION for LD commitment (cat code 21095). This will use LD, no records exist for the enquiry type. 4) Enquiry type CP1, CUSTOMER.POSITINO for MD commitment (cat code 21096). This will use 21096 as there is no match on category or application for the record. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Mandatory input. Elements category and system id must be separated by a "*". Any valid alphanumeric character is allowed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUS.EXT.RTN</field>
<desc>
        <p>The name of a local api routine to return a populated CUSTOMER.POSITION record.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

