<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>DATES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>A Date record exists for each company.  This record contains the run dates for the previous, the current and the next working.</p>
            <p>Once it is loaded the date record is automatically updated by the Batch (overnight) processing system.</p>
            <p>User Input to an existing record has not been inhibited at present, this is so that the date records can be updated in a testing environment without the need to run the batch system.</p>
            <p>The standard T24 functions can be used in this file.</p>
            <p>By use of the User Profile limited access to this record should be maintained.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Company for which the Dates information is applicable.</p>
            <p>The standard format of Company Code is:</p>
            <p>CCGGGLLLL where:            CC   is Country Code            GGG  is Company Group Code            LLLL is Local Code</p>
            <p>a) Country Code - Capital letters in the range A-Z.  Must be the ID of an    existing record in the COUNTRY table.</p>
            <p>b) Company Group Code - 3 numeric characters in the range 001-999. Must be    the ID of an existing record in the COMPANY.GROUP table.</p>
            <p>c) Local Code - 4 numeric characters in the range 0001-9999.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-9 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Standard format:  CCGGGLLLL                        or  2-3 type MNE (uppercase alpha) or '.' characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TODAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the date of business being processed in this Company.</p>
            <p>This is normally, but not necessarily, equal to the actual date. Sometimes the System may be being used to process work for another date. For example, finishing Friday's work on Saturday.</p>
            <p>This field will be set automatically with the date from NEXT.WORKING.DAY by the Batch (overnight) processing system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. (Mandatory input)  It is checked against the HOLIDAY table and Overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)   If it is not a working day in the HOLIDAY Table. b)   If it was not the date entered in NEXT.WORKING.DAY of the      previous day's Dates Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.WORKING.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the state of the next business day which will be processed in this Company.</p>
            <p>The next working day is calculated by the Batch (overnight) processing system from the date previously held by this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>It has to be the next business date after that entered in TODAY.</p>
            <p>It is checked against the HOLIDAY table and overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)  If it is not a working day in the HOLIDAY table. b)  It is not the next working date from the date entered in TODAY. c)  If it is five or more working days after the date entered in     TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORW.VALUE.MINIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This date is the furthest forward that the value date entered on a transaction can be before an override is required.</p>
            <p>This date is automatically cycled one working day every time the batch (overnight) processing system is run for this Company.</p>
            <p>If on a DATA.CAPTURE transaction a value date between this date and the one in FORW.VALUE.MAXIMUM is entered than an override is required.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. (Mandatory input)  It is checked against the Holiday Table and overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)   If it is not a working day in the HOLIDAY Table. b)   If it is less than the date entered in TODAY. c)   If it is more than five working days greater than the date      previously entered in TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORW.VALUE.MAXIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Maximum Forward Value Date permitted to be entered on a transaction.</p>
            <p>This date is automatically cycled one working day every time the batch (overnight) processing system is run for this Company.</p>
            <p>If the same date is entered in this Field and in FORW.VALUE.MINIMUM this would not allow any overrides for forward value beyond Minimum.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. (Mandatory input)  It is checked against the Holiday Table and overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)   If it is not a working day in the HOLIDAY Table. b)   If it is less than the date entered in TODAY. c)   If it is less than the date entered in FORW.VALUE.MINIMUM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.DISPO.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>This date is automatically cycled one working day every time the end batch (overnight) processing system is run for this Company.</p>
            <p>This field is only for reference at present.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. (Mandatory input)  It is checked against the HOLIDAY table and overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)   If it is not a working day in the HOLIDAY table. b)   If it is not greater than the date entered in      NEXT.WORKING.DAY. c)   If it is more than five working days after date entered in      TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.BATCH.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used.</p>
            <p>This field has been reserved for possible use at a later date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.WORKING.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date of the last business day processed for this Company.</p>
            <p>This field will be set with the date from TODAY by the batch (overnight) processing system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>This date must be the same date which was previously in TODAY.</p>
            <p>It has to be less than the date in TODAY.</p>
            <p>It is checked against the Holiday Table and overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)  If it is not a working day in the HOLIDAY Table. b)  If it is five working days or more previous to TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of business day. For example, if the country official working week is Monday to Friday, with the bank open for business on Saturday and closed on a Sunday the values of this field would be as follows.</p>
            <p>Monday to Friday - NORMAL</p>
            <p>Saturday - RESTRICTED</p>
            <p>Sunday - CLOSED</p>
            <p>The Holiday tables involved are defined on the company record, in the OFFICIAL.HOLIDAY and BRANCH.HOLIDAY fields. If both the official and branch holiday tables have the same day defined as a working day then the CURRENT.DAY will be set as NORMAL, if the official holiday table defines a day as a holiday and the branch holiday defines it as working then the CURRENT.DAY will be defined as RESTRICTED and if both tables define the day as a holiday then the CURRENT.DAY value will be defined as closed. In addition it is possible to define ad hoc holidays for a company in the BRANCH.CLOSED field. This allows a small number of branch holiday tables to be defined with holidays particular to a branch defined on the compant recoed for the branch.</p>
            <p>It is possible at VERSION level in the BUSINESS.DAY field to determine whether the version can be run based on the type of business day, so that a limited number of business activities can be permitted on a restricted working day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation rules</p>
            <p>Noinput field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field indicates the type of business day and indicates differences between the official holiday table and the branch holiday table as defined on the COMPANY record.</p>
            <p>NORMAL  the branch (company) is open on an official working day</p>
            <p>RESTRICTED  the branch is open on an official holiday, e.g. a weekend or public holiday</p>
            <p>CLOSED  the branch is closed i.e. the holiday table for the branch indicates a non working day, or the day corresponds to a value on the BRNACH.CLOSED field for the company</p>
            <p>It is possible to determine whether a VERSION can be run based on the value of the CURRENT.DAY, so that business activities can be restricted when a branch is open on an official holiday.</p>
            <p>If the BRANCH.HOLIDAY is different to the OFFICIAL.HOLIDAY then the LOCAL.COUNTRY will be blank and the BRANCH.HOLIDAY will be used to populate the LOCAL.REGION field.</p>
            <p>If they are the same then the first two characters of the OFFICIAL.HOLIDAY field will be used to populate the LOCAL.COUNTRY field and the LOCAL.REGION.FIELD will be blank.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No input system updated      field when the business dates on the DATES record are recycled in the      batch</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.PAYMENT.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>The date is automatically cycled one working day every time the end batch (overnight) processing system is run for this Company.</p>
            <p>This field is only for reference at present.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. (Mandatory input)  It is checked against the HOLIDAY Table and overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)   If it is not a working day in the HOLIDAY Table. b)   If it is not greater than the date entered in      NEXT.WORKING.DAY. c)   If it is more than five working days after date entered in      TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JULIAN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the date in TODAY held in the Julian format.</p>
            <p>The Julian format consists of the four digit year followed by the day in the year.  For example, the Julian value for 27th March 1986 is 1986086.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>7 numeric characters in the format YYYYDDD.  (Internal field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the period end date of the EOD section of the previous COB.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Close of business date.</p>
            <p>Either the next working day minus one calendar day or the end of month whichever is earlier.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Date.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNTING.STAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the status of the company regarding processing of accounting entries. This field is automatically updated by the system to manage the control of accounting updates.</p>
            <p>The field can have the following values:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Null - The system is in standard online or application or start of day batch mode.</p>
            <p>UPDATED - The system has applied the days accounting movements to the accounts, account history and CRB base. This covers the system wide stage of the batch processing where special processes may be required to raise further accounting entries.</p>
            <p>CLOSED - All accounting for the day is processed, further entries should not be raised.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>System field noinput</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.VALUE.MAXIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the furthest date back that is allowed to be entered on a back-valued transaction.</p>
            <p>This date will be automatically updated once entries, rates and conditions are dropped. Otherwise, it remains the same date. Therefore the period for back valuation on DATA.CAPTURE entries increases.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces.  (Mandatory input)  It is checked against the Holiday Table and overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)   If it is not a working day on the HOLIDAY Table. b)   If it is greater than the date entered in BACK.VALUE.MINIMUM. c)   If it is greater than the date entered in TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.VALUE.MINIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date furthest back that can be entered on a back valued transaction before an override is required.</p>
            <p>This date is automatically cycled one working day every time the batch (overnight) processing system is run for this Company.</p>
            <p>If on a data capture transaction a 'value' date between this date and the one in BACK.VALUE.MAXIMUM is entered then an override is required.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The date entered cannot be greater than but could be equal to the date entered in TODAY.</p>
            <p>It is checked against the HOLIDAY table and overrides will be required in the following conditions:  a)  If it is not a working day in the HOLIDAY Table. b)  If it is less than five working days before the date entered in     TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.BAL.DATE.START</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

