<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>EB</product>
        <title>DFE Frame Work - Real-Time Parameter</title>
        <table>DFE.REALTIME.PARAMETER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This is a parameter table for Real-time inward messages posted via ofs source type TELNET.</p>
			<p>This table is used to get the appropriate DFE interface ID from the received inward messages to proceed the interface mapping based on the mapping definition given in DFE.PARAMETER and in DFE.MAPPING.</p>
			<p>Table holds the @id as T24 OFS.SOURCE reference as record key.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>	DESCRIPTION </field>
            <desc>
               <p>Free text field to give the record description.</p> 
			   <p>Validation Rules</p>
			    <p>35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
            <field>	ROUTINE </field>
            <desc>
               <p>User can attach a routine to do a business logic to derive the external key by attaching a routine in this field.</p>
			   <p>The routine has one single argument while triggering the routine the argument will sends with inward raw message. User needs to send back with external reference in the same argument as output.</p>
			   <p>System will locate the received data from the routine in field EXTERNAL.CODE and get the appropriate DFE ID from field DFE.PARAM.ID.</p>
			   <p>Validation Rules</p>
			   <p>The routine should prefixed with @ and should have EB.API entry for that routine.</p>
			   <p>Example @T24ROUTINE.NAME</p>
		    </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	FIELD.DELIMITER </field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field should entered with a symbol or a group of character in-case if the receiving raw message is a delimiter data.</p>
		    </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>	FIELD.POSITION </field>
            <desc>
                <p>Configure the field delimited position to get the external identifier from the inward data.</p>
				<p>In-case if the received data is a position based string mention the start position of the external reference.</p>			
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>	FIELD.LENGTH </field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field should enter with length of id position if the receiving message is a position based string.</p>
		    </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>	EXTERNAL.CODE </field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field should configured with exact message identifier for each data.</p>
				<p>This is a associated multi value field with DFE.PARAM.ID, this is used to map the DFE id for the each external identifier.</p>
			</desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>	DFE.PARAM.ID </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This is associated multi value field with above.</p>
				<p>This should entered with appropriate DFE ID for each external identifier.</p>
				<p>Validation Routine</p>
				<p>This should be a valid DFE.PARAMETER ID.</p>
			</desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	DEFAULT.PARAM.ID </field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field should hold the default DFE id for this OFS.SOURCE type system will default load this interface ID to process the message.</p>
			</desc>
        </t>
	<t><field>DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ROUTINE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>FIELD.DELIMITER</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>FIELD.POSITION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>FIELD.LENGTH</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>EXTERNAL.CODE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DFE.PARAM.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DEFAULT.PARAM.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
