<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>DISPO.ITEMS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CURR.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Customer to whom the transferring Account belongs.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPROVED.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The T24 User Profile name for the DISPO Officer who APPROVED the Dispo Item</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Comments can be made to the DISPO Item record in this field.</p>
            <p>When this field is committed, the contents are relocated into the General Comments field (GEN.COMMENTS), and the contents of the COMMENTS field removed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The level of the override. This is used in the creation of the DISPO record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the amount associated with the override message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System generated</p>
            <p />
            <p>No input allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The text of the override displayed at contract input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System generated</p>
            <p>No input allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The officer who entered the associated comments</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid dispo officer.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WORKFLOW.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that the override was raised</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Dispo Status</p>
            <p>
                <DT>The Dispo Officer enters the status of the Dispo Item in this field.</DT>
            </p>
            <p>Available options for this field are:</p>
            <p />
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>NEW</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Default option</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>APPROVED</p>
                    </td>
                    <td />
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>REJECTED</p>
                    </td>
                    <td />
                </tr>
            </table>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The reference id which is updated for the external DDA system to process the FORCE overrides</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> It can hold strings up to 60 characters in length</p>
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.HIST.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.DISPO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where the dispo officer is changed when the item is passed on for further approval then the previous officer code is recorded here.</p>
            <p>This field is maintained by the system and accepts no input.</p>
            <p>If the DISPO.OFFICER record has been reversed then it must be recalled to allow processing of the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid entry on the DISPO.OFFICER table</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PEND.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Each Dispo Item record will have a Pending Status.  This will be used by T24 to determine which items are to be re-routed back to the officer that last had the item during the end of day process.  If an item is held overnight, without this flag being set, the item must be brought into the system manually and would then take the default officer as specified in the parameters, account, etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>YES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>When the item is brought back into the system manually, the Dispo Item will NOT be reset.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>NO / Empty Field</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>When the item is brought back into the system manually, the Dispo Item IS reset to the first Dispo Officer as per parameters, account, etc.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds locally defined field(s).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time the override was raised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.COMMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains a list of all COMMENTS that have been added through the COMMENTS field.</p>
            <p>As each new comment is added by completing the COMMENTS field and committing the record, the entry made to the COMMENTS field is appended to the end of the GEN.COMMENT field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Read-only field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The dispo officer that the dispo item is currently routed to. Change this field to route the items for another officer's approval.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid ID on the DISPO.OFFICER table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Override Id</p>
            <p>This no-input field contains the key to the Override record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account to whom the override belongs.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The account officer for this dispo item. Obtained from the ACCOUNT record associated with the override message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System genetated</p>
            <p>No input allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount associated with the override message. The local currency of this amount is compared with the amount the officer is allowed to approve as specified in the DISPO.OFFICER record</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System generated</p>
            <p>No input allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The T24 application which generated the override message(s)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System generated</p>
            <p>No input allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

