<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>DL.DEFINE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>T24 Data Library - Shareware for T24 </p>
            <p>The T24 Data Library has been created to enable data to be copied between different sites easily.  When a user or implementor of T24 has created data which he feels may be of use to other sites, he can save the data to the Data Library.  Data should be saved into logical units, for example, Dutch Bank Returns, which may include report control records, enquiries, repgens and even programs.  To save the unit, a record is created in DL.DEFINE, listing all the items which make up the unit.  The data is then saved into the unit by using the V function in DL.DEFINE, with the operation set to S. </p>
            <p>NOTE : As with all shareware, the distributor, in this case, Temenos, does        not accept any liability for the data or programs contained in the        Data Library - it is the users responsibility to ensure that all        data and programs being installed through the Data Library are        checked and tested thoroughly before being used. </p>
            <p>When saving records, sensitive data (e.g. the name of your bank or your VAT registration number) can be replaced by specifying the characters to be replaced and the characters they are to be replaced with, on the data library parameter file, DL.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>Once units have been saved, the Data Library should be sent to Temenos Development, where it will be merged into one central library.  This should be done by using the save operation in DL.PARAMETER (using the "V"erify mode in DL.PARAMETER with the OPERATION set to "S" - save). </p>
            <p>Should you wish to restore data from another site, you should restore the data library from tape into an area on disk (e.g. /globus/DLrestore). Examine this file to determine which units you wish to copy into your data library, or whether you wish to copy all units, or only those units which have been created in the "from" data library more recently than yours. Once you have decided which units you want copied onto your data library, enter the requirements in the data library parameter file (DL.PARAMETER). You must enter an OPERATION of "R" to restore, then enter the UNIX pathname of the file from which units are to be copied (e.g. /globus/ DLrestore/F.DL.DATA should be entered in FROM.FILE), the names of the units to be restored or blank to restore all units (RESTORE.UNITS) and whether you wish to overwrite existing units (OVERWRITING = "Y" or "N") or only if the units on the from file are later ("L").  Then run DL.PARAMETER in "V"erify mode to copy the units. </p>
            <p>Similarly if you wish to copy units from a data library in a different T24 account, you can follow the above procedure.  If the file is on the same machine you do not need to restore - just simply enter the pathname of the from data library (e.g. /globus/test/F.DL.DATA). </p>
            <p>When you upgrade your T24 database by running GLOBUS.RELEASE, your data library will be populated with the latest units available.  Existing units will not be overwritten if there were saved after the ones on the data library on the upgrade tape. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The language or country the unit is primarily used for. </p>
            <p>This field will be used for selection purposes only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid country code as defined on the COUNTRY file.</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAVE.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type in which data will stored.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Value can be XML or Null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNIT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the unit identifying the records to be grouped together.  When entered, the unit name will be prefixed by "xxxxnnn-" where "xxxxnnn" is the site name (the last seven digits from the license code on the SPF). </p>
            <p>The full unit name (xxxxnnn-yyyyyyyyyy) can be entered when restoring units saved from other sites.  However, when creating new units, only the site name as specified on the SPF can be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>If the bank code is not entered, a maximum of 22 characters can be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the record to be copied.  The record must exist on the file specified in FILE.NAME. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "ANY" (any) character</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Multi-value field</p>
            <p>Fields FILE.NAME, RECORD.NAME and RECORD.DESC form a multi-value associated set.</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if operation is "S"</p>
            <p>The record must exist on the file specified in FILE.NAME</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTORED.USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the user who restored the data unit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>Internal field</p>
            <p>Populated each time the unit is restored</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Fields RESTORED.USER to RESTD.DATE form a multi-value associated set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.LEVEL.ITEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>TOP.LEVEL.ITEM is used to create a list of all data items associated with a particular record.  When the TOP.LEVEL.TYPE and TOP.LEVEL.ITEM are entered, the fields FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be cleared, then populated with the names of all the associated data items; then TOP.LEVEL.TYPE and TOP.LEVEL.ITEM will be cleared. </p>
            <p>For DELIVERY, TOP.LEVEL.TYPE should the message type (the id of the record on DE.MESSAGE).  FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be populated with all DE.MAPPING, DE.FORMAT.SWIFT and DE.FORMAT.PRINT records for this message type, as well as the DE.MESSAGE record. </p>
            <p>For ENQUIRY, FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be populated with any routines used by the enquiry, as well as the ENQUIRY record. </p>
            <p>For REPGEN, FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be populated with the REPGEN.SORT, REPGEN.CREATE and REPGEN.OUTPUT records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) character</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if operation is "S"</p>
            <p>Must reference a record on the corresponding TOP.LEVEL.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAVED.RELEASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The release level of T24 when the data unit was saved. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>Internal field</p>
            <p>Populated each time the unit is saved</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Fields SAVED.FROM to SAVED.DATE form a multi-value associated set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the record to be copied.  This field should be used so that each record which has been saved has a meaningful description of what the record is for.  Although it may be apparent to the user when they saved the record, other users who may wish to restore units need to know precisely what each record in the unit is for. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "ANY" (any) character</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Sub-value field</p>
            <p>Fields FILE.NAME, RECORD.NAME and RECORD.DESC form a multi-value associated set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether data is to be "S" (saved) or "R" (restored).  This field is only used when the record is "V"erified. </p>
            <p>When the program is run in "V"erify mode, if the operation is set to "S" (save), a unit is created in the data library, with an id as specified in UNIT.NAME.  The records specified in fields FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME are copied from the live files into the unit in the data library.  The fields SAVED.FROM, SAVED.RELEASE and SAVED.DATE on the DL.DEFINE record are updated with details of when the data was saved. </p>
            <p>When the program is run in "V"erify mode with the operation set to "R" (restore), the following actions are performed: </p>
            <p>  i)  Any new files (specified by releasing the FILE.CONTROL record) are       created </p>
            <p> ii) Records contained in the unit are copied into the unauthorised file,      with a status of "IHLD" </p>
            <p>iii) Programs are copied into DL.BP, but are not compiled (use EB.COMPILE      to do this when required) </p>
            <p> iv) The fields RESTORED.USER, RESTD.COMPANY, RESTD.RELEASE and      RESTD.DATE on the DL.DEFINE record are updated with details of when      the data was restored. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Defaulted to "R" if the data unit has previously been saved (i.e. if there is a date in SAVED.DATE); defaults to "S" otherwise. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"S" (save) or "R" (restore)</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Defaults to "R" if the data has previously been saved.  Defaults to "S" otherwise.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.LEVEL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>TOP.LEVEL.TYPE is used to create a list of all data items associated with a particular record.  Valid types are DELIVERY, ENQUIRY, MENU, REPGEN and VERSION. When the TOP.LEVEL.TYPE and TOP.LEVEL.ITEM are entered, the fields FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be cleared, then populated with the names of all the associated data items; then TOP.LEVEL.TYPE and TOP.LEVEL.ITEM will be cleared. </p>
            <p>For DELIVERY, TOP.LEVEL.TYPE should the message type (the id of the record on DE.MESSAGE).  FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be populated with all DE.MAPPING, DE.FORMAT.SWIFT and DE.FORMAT.PRINT records for this message type, as well as the DE.MESSAGE record. </p>
            <p>For ENQUIRY, FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be populated with any routines used by the enquiry, as well as the ENQUIRY record. </p>
            <p>For REPGEN, FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be populated with the REPGEN.SORT, REPGEN.CREATE and REPGEN.OUTPUT records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) character</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if operation is "S"</p>
            <p>Must be one of the following:   DELIVERY  ENQUIRY  MENU  REPGEN  VERSION</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTD.RELEASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The release of T24 when the data unit was restored. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-9 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Internal field</p>
            <p>Populated each time the unit is restored</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Fields RESTORED.USER to RESTD.DATE form a multi-value associated set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date when the data unit was restored. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"D"ate field</p>
            <p>Internal field</p>
            <p>Populated each time the unit is restored</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Fields RESTORED.USER to RESTD.DATE form a multi-value associated set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAVED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date when the data unit was saved. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"D"ate field</p>
            <p>Internal field</p>
            <p>Populated each time the unit is saved</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Fields SAVED.FROM to SAVED.DATE form a multi-value associated set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.DESCRIPTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAVED.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of where the data unit was saved. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) character</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Multi-value field</p>
            <p>Fields SAVED.FROM to SAVED.DATE form a multi-value associated set.</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if operation is "S"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDICES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can contain keywords (specified as seperate values which may be used for searching (for example, to search for all units to relate to central bank reporting). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTD.COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of the company into which the data unit was restored. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-9 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Internal field</p>
            <p>Populated each time the unit is restored</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Fields RESTORED.USER to RESTD.DATE form a multi-value associated set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMP.TO.RESTORE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the unit. </p>
            <p>This should be as meaningful as possible, so that other sites who wish to restore a unit understand what the unit contains. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Multi-language field</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DL.DEFINE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the unit identifying the records to be grouped together.  When entered, the unit name will be prefixed by "xxxxnnn-" where "xxxxnnn" is the site name (the last seven digits from the license code on the SPF). </p>
            <p>The full unit name (xxxxnnn-yyyyyyyyyy) can be entered when restoring units saved from other sites.  However, when creating new units, only the site name as specified on the SPF can be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the file containing records to be copied. </p>
            <p>The file name should be entered without the "F." prefix (if the "F." prefix is entered, it will be removed) and must reference a record on STANDARD.SELECTION.  Alternatively, if a program is to be copied, FILE.NAME can be BP1, BP2 or BP.  When the programs are restored, they will always be restored into DL.BP, regardless of where they were originally saved from.  On the restore, programs are not compiled and cataloged - use EB.COMPILE to do this. </p>
            <p>If FILE.NAME is left blank and RECORD.NAME is entered, the FILE.NAME is defaulted to the FILE.NAME in the previous multivalue (multivalue 2 onwards). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) character</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Multi-value field</p>
            <p>Fields FILE.NAME, RECORD.NAME and RECORD.DESC form a multi-value associated set.</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if operation is "S"</p>
            <p>Must reference a record on STANDARD.SELECTION, or can be BP1, BP2 or BP (if a program is to be copied).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.LIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the select list containing the names of records which make up the unit.  Record names should be entered as filename&gt;recordname, e.g. ENQUIRY&gt;MG.CLOSING.BALANCES.  After the select list has been entered, the fields FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME will be cleared, then populated with the contents of the select list; the select list name will be removed from SELECT.LIST. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) character</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>If entered, must be the name of a select list in &amp;SAVEDLISTS&amp;</p>
            <p>Can only be entered if operation is "S"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Short description describing what the unit contains. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-20 Type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>Multi-language field</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

