<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.ALTERNATE.KEY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext">
            <p>OVERVIEW</p>
            <p />
            <p>This application is used to define an alternate key for an application (e.g. CUSTOMER, ACCOUNT etc.). Using this utility any field in an application (both system fields and local ref fields) can be set as an alternate key. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The alternate key can be used for field inputs as well as id inputs. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>For example, </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If a local ref field say, CUST.ALT.INDEX in CUSTOMER is defined as an alternate key field. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Id input:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>In CUSTOMER application if the value in CUST.ALT.INDEX is used as id input, the corresponding customer record is displayed. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Field input:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>CUSTOMER fields in applications like MM, FX (e.g. field CUSTOMER.ID in MM) will accept alternate keys.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>K.UNIQUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Please refer to the helptext of UNIQUE field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENRI.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>On inputting a duplicate alternate key (multiple keys with the same alternate key) a drop down list with all the real keys that corresponds to that alternate key appears along with an enrichment for each key.  This field specifies the field to be used for enrichment if the DEFAULT.ENRI field in STANDARD.SELECTION record is null.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 to 35 type A (alphanumeric) character field.</p>
            <p>The value entered, must be a valid field on the STANDARD.SELECTION record.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNIQUE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The following are the options: SYSTEM  or blank alternate keys are unique within the current T24 account COMPANY  alternate keys are unique within a company but non unique within the system. NONE  Duplicates are allowed When set to 'COMPANY'or 'NONE' it will become a nochange field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>SYSTEM or COMPANY oR NONE or NULL (i.e. blank). </p>
            <p />
            <p>Null will default to SYSTEM.       </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONCAT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field decides if a concat file should be created for an alternate key. If 'SYSTEM' is specified, the concat file is created. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>  SYSTEM or NONE allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALIDATION.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>A routine to validate the alternate key can be attached here.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUILD.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field to define a routine to build the concat file for the existing records. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCESS.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>If READ is specified then the concat file maintained for the alternate key will be read to get the real key for an alternate key input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If SELECT is specified, concat file will be selected if there is one for this alternate key otherwise a direct select on the application file will be made to get the real key</p>
            <p>  . </p>
            <p />
            <p>The 'SELECT' option may have some performance implications. It is recommended to use the 'READ' option for better performance. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If a routine is defined then it will be executed to get the real key.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>READ,       SELECT or @ROUTINE allowed</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>SELECT is allowed only if the field UNIQUE is set       as SYSTEM or </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.KEY.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid field name on the Standard selection record for the application can be specified here.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The       field specified must be defined as a SYS.FIELD.NAME or USR.FIELD.NAME on       the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the APPLICATION.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.KEY.MAX.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is a no input field that indicates the maximum length of all possible key fields. This can be of any length irrespective of the current key field length defined in the application program.This will allow the actual alternate value input to be accepted by the lowest level validation routines.</p>
            <p />
            <p> ACCOUNT, CUSTOMER fields in applications will be resized to the length specified here. </p>
            <p />
            <p> For SECTOR, INDUSTRY fields, length specified in MAX.LENGTH field in EB.OBJECT will be used for resizing. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The name of the file to which the alternate key or keys defined in the record are to be applied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is a dummy field. For future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

