<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.ADVICES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file controls the output of delivery messages, the format of the messages and deal slip formats for an EB.ACTIVITY.</p>
            <p>By defining the records on this file the users will have total control of the type and format of the eventual output. Users are also able to use their own mapping records instead of the standard ones supplied within T24, which in some cases, may not cater for particular elements of business (i.e. optional fields or sequences on a S.W.I.F.T. message).</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>USER.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to call a user defined routine to map additional data which is not normally available for the message type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid Routine</p>
            <p>Maximum of 30 characters allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the S.W.I.F.T. or T24 message type to be produced.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be a valid ID from the DE.MESSAGE file</p>
            <p>Maximum of 4 numeric characters is allowed</p>
            <p>If this field is blank, no message will be produced</p>
            <p>No duplicate allowed in the same record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies which delivery format is to be used by the activity. This field allows the user to define different formats of the same basic message type for different activities. </p>
            <p>The element defined will become the second element of the resultant DE.FORMAT.PRINT record key.</p>
            <p>The value in this field will be mapped into field 3 of record 8 of the DE.O.HANDOFF information.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 6 characters allowed </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>SUB.CLASS</p>
            <p>This the ID of an existing record in this file, which allows the user to produce an additional subset of messages for this activity.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid ADVICE.CODE</p>
            <p>Maximum of 20 characters may be entered</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This subvalue field specifies the classifications of the associated message type. E.g. CONFIRMATION, ADVICE, PAYMENT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input must be a key to the EB.MESSAGE.CLASS</p>
            <p>All message classes in EB.MESSAGE.CLASS will be         considered if none is specified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAPPING.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to the DE.MAPPING record associated with the message type. Normally, this will be the key to the standard mapping record supplied by Temenos Systems, but users have the ability to use their own mapping records.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be a record existing in DE.MAPPING file.</p>
            <p>The first string, before "-", must reference         the MESSAGE.TYPE field</p>
            <p>Must be blank if MESSAGE.TYPE field is blank</p>
            <p>A maximum of 13 characters may be entered</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The EB.ADVICES id to identify the advice type.</p>
            <p>The id is keyed by EB.ACTIVITY-Type (the latter being optional).</p>
            <p>E.g. RP-0100 (REPO contract initiation)</p>
            <p>RP-0100-RESO (Reverse REPO contract initiation)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be of the format <strong>Activity.Code-Type</strong>         where:</p>
            <p><strong>Activity.Code</strong> is a valid ID in file         EB.ACTIVITY and </p>
            <p><strong>Type</strong> is an optional 12 character         identifier</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.SLIP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID of an existing record in the DEAL.SLIP.PARAMETER file and defines the optional deal slips to produce.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the ID of an existing record in DEAL.SLIP.PARAMETER     </p>
            <p>Maximum of 25 characters allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The description of the advice code</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Free text</p>
            <p>Maximum of 35 characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTRA.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID of an existing record on this file. It allows the user to produce an additional subset of messages for this activity.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum 20 characters</p>
            <p>Must be a valid existing EB.ADVICES Id</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>LOCAL REFERENCE</p>
            <p>Local reference field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.RECORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the EB.ADVICES record to use instead.</p>
            <p>This is useful when the required output is similar to an existing record and it eliminates the need to duplicate EB.ADVICES records of similar details.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid EB.ADVICES record</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

