<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.ALERT.REQUEST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Subscription to an event is done using application EB.ALERT.REQUEST. </p>
            <p>An event is the occurrence happening at a pre-determinable condition or time. Events can be categorized into (1) happening  based on a pre-determined condition (like an account is overdrawn, a customer address is changed) or (2) happening based on a predetermined time ( Like A loan approaching maturity in nn days ) ) </p>
            <p>The events can either be user initiated or system initiated.</p>
            <p>As a consequence of an event, it is possible to send Alerts through SMS, Email and Secure Message to a Customer or a Department Account Officer for an Account , an Arrangement or a Portfolio.</p>
            <p>The alerts can be classified as Activity alerts, Transaction alerts, Balance alerts,  Transfer alerts and Portfolio related alerts.</p>
            <p>T24 supports events and alerts processing using the T24 Enterprise Console (TEC).</p>
            <p>TEC allows detection, capture and recording of an event arising out of an activity, based on a pre-determined condition or time. </p>
            <p>The delivery module in t24 supports the delivery of messages to customer  via SMS or EMAIL  or Secure messages, based on their preferences.</p>
            <p>EB.ALERT.REQUEST application allows the customer to subscribe to or unsubscribe from alerts. Subscription can be availed for an Account, an Arrangement or a Portfolio. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the event from TEC.ITEMS.A valid event from TEC.ITEMS should be specified in this field. These TEC.ITEMS are designed to define the conditions to trigger alerts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This is a NOCHANGE field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field along with FIELD and VALUE, helps the user to set the conditions for the Alert to be triggered. System defaults the value based on the chosen event from TEC.ITEMS.The field values get defaulted automatically from the corresponding TEC.ITEMS record on entering the EVENT field and validating the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This is a NOINPUT field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field along with OPERAND and VALUE, helps the user to set the conditions for the Alert to be triggered. Eg FIELD=Online Cleared Balance, OPERAND=goes below and VALUE=5000 would trigger an Account Available Balance alert. System defaults this value based on the chosen event from TEC.ITEMS.The field values get defaulted automatically from the corresponding TEC.ITEMS record on entering the EVENT field and validating the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This is a NOINPUT field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GB FIELD.DES</field>
<desc>
            <p>System defaults the value based on the chosen event from TEC.ITEMS. The field values get defaulted automatically from the corresponding TEC.ITEMS record on entering the EVENT field and validating the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This is a NOINPUT field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Field position. System defaults the value based on the chosen event from TEC.ITEMS. The field values get defaulted automatically from the corresponding TEC.ITEMS record on entering the EVENT field and validating the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This is a NOINPUT field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies a valid DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALERT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the  Account number,arrangement id or Portfolio No, subscribing to the alerts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid customer number gets defaulted from the Account, Arrangement or Portfolio Id specified in the field Contract Ref.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field along with FIELD and OPERAND, helps the user to set the conditions for the Alert to be triggered. Holds the actual value of the field on which the criteria is based. If a value is provided at the event definition level, then that value is defaulted here. If not, the user can provide the value at the time of Subscribing.</p>
            <p>The fields from FIELD to VALUE are displayed in this subscription screen only when INHERIT is set to Yes in the corresponding TEC.ITEMS record. These set of fields define the criteria for alerts. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUBSCRIBE</field>
<desc>
            <p>An alert is subscribed based on the value in this field.  This field can be set to YES/NO  Whether the customer/account officer  has subscribed to or wants to unsubscribe from the event. By default set as YES. It is a mandatory field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Accepted values to this field are YES/NO </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

