<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.CUSTOMER.ONBOARDING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This Process Workflow helps the user to create portfolio from the scratch i.e. from prospect. However, user has got four options to select from such as Activate Prospect, Existing Customer, New Customer and Prospect. As per the each option selected, the system automatically populates the respective screens for completing the activity like Customer Creation, Account Creation, Capturing KYC Details, Cheque Book Issue, Cash Deposit etc., one after the another.  </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.SERVICES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether account needs to be opend or not. Option 'Yes' allows creating account, otherwise not.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Customer. If the user selects the option Existing Customer in the Customer Prospect Field, it is mandatory to mention the Customer Type whether Corporate or Retail.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10 numeric character Customer Code or 3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') character Customer Mnemonic. (Mandatory input for Customer Accounts not allowed for Internal Accounts). </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.PROSPECT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is decision field on the customer status. User has four options to select from i.e., Activate Prospect, Existing Customer, New Customer, Prospect.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If 'Activate Prospect' option is used, user needs to input certain other mandatory values like Customer Type, Customer Number and Account Services.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>'Existing Customer' indicates that the customer record is already exists, and user has to provide the Customer Number and the Customer Type.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>'New Customer' option is used for creating a new customer. User needs to mention the Customer Type as to whether the new customer is going to be a Corporate or Retail Customer.</p>
            <p />
            <p>'Prospect' option is used for creating the prospect. Mentioning of Customer Type is not mandatory.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of customer to be created like Corporate or Retail. If the user selects the option New Customer in CUSTOMER.PROSPECT field, then it is mandatory to mention the Customer Type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>