<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.COMPILE.TEXT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Defines rules for compiling T24 server programs.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PREV.CHAR.LIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with SEARCH.TEXT, if specified then the character preceding the defined text in the code must be in this list inorder for the warning or error message to be produced.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any alpha-numeric input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WARNINGS.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying the list of warnings that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STANDARDS.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This specifies the message to be produced when coding standards are breached for the programs listed in STANDARDS.CHECK</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any alpha-numeric input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IGN.NO.ICOMMON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with SEARCH.TEXT, if the program being searched does not contain the insert file I_COMMON then no warning or error message will be produced if the text specified is found.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WARN.ITEM.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying each warning that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STANDARDS.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying the list of programming standards failures that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with SEARCH.TEXT, defines the message type if the associated text is found and all the criteria are met. If set the WARNING or CODE.REVIEW then program compilation will be allowed, if set to ERROR then program compilation will not be allowed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Either WARNING, CODE.REVIEW or ERROR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTIPLE.STD.RPTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The setting for this field determines whether all failures to meet the required standards for the same STANDARDS.CHECK are displayed or only the first such occurrence is displayed plus a counter for each additional occurrence.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>YES     - All standards messages for the same     STANDARDS.CHECK are displayed</p>
            <p>NO      - Only the first standards message is     displayed plus a counter for any additional occurrences of STANDARDS.CHECK</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The file tag to be used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and       !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STANDARDS.CHECK</field>
<desc>
            <p>A list of T24 programs for which certain coding standards are expected. The checks are defined in the EB.COMPILE routine and will produce a warning message if the checks are not passed. The message is defined in STANDARDS.MSG. Program compilation will be allowed. The checks are performed whenever one of these programs is called in the program being compiled.</p>
            <p>The checks are only for variable prefixes. File variables must be prefixed with F. and record variables must be prefixed with R.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A predefined list of T24 programs.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTIPLE.REV.RPTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The setting for this field determines whether all code review items are displayed or only the first such occurrence is displayed plus a counter for each additional occurrence.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>YES     - All code review messages for the same     SEARCH.TEXT are displayed</p>
            <p>NO      - Only the first code review message is     displayed plus a counter for any additional occurrences of SEARCH.TEXT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IGNORE.PROG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with SEARCH.TEXT, if specified then if the program being checked is in this list no warning or error message will be produced if the specified text is found.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any alpha-numeric input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINE.NO.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying the line number at which the warning/error occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and       !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVIEW.REASON.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying the reason the code should be reviewed, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STD.ITEM.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying each breach of programming standards that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVIEW.ITEM.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying each code review that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEARCH.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The text to be searched for before compiling the program. If present in the code then the associated fields DEPENDENT.TEXT, IGNORE.PROG, IGN.NO.ICOMMON and PREV.CHAR.LIST will be checked and if all criteria are met then either a warning or an error message will be produced based on the field MSG.TYPE associated to this SEARCH.TEXT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>1)Define SEARCH.TEXT field as 'FBNK... to imply text scanning starting with ‘FBNK followed by   </p>
            <p>    any  character, but preceding with either null or space (before ‘FBNK). </p>
            <p />
            <p>2) Similarly ...FBNK could be defined to imply text scanning ending with FBNK,but end of string </p>
            <p>    should  be either null or space.</p>
            <p />
            <p>3)Define SEARCH.TEXT field as ...FBNK... to imply text scanning of the string FBNK in any part  </p>
            <p>    of the program/ subroutine</p>
            <p />
            <p>CORR.ACTION.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any alpha-numeric input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HTML.ERROR.RPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the messages produced by EB.COMPILE are to be in HTML format. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Either YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying each warning or error message that occurred, only used when generating HTML output. Will contain the program name and the text found.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key for the record controlling warning and error messages produced by EB.COMPILE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Will be SYSTEM</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERRORS.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying the list of errors that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CODE.REVIEWS.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying the list of code reviews that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORR.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The corrective action to be taken is a particular error/warning is seen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECT.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying the corrective action required for the errors that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPENDENT.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with SEARCH.TEXT, if specified then this text must also be present in the line of code to produce the desired warning or error message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any alpha-numeric input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTIPLE.WARN.RPTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The setting for this field determines whether all warning messages for the same SEARCH.TEXT are displayed or only the first such occurrence is displayed plus a counter for each additional occurrence.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>YES     - All warning messages for the same       SEARCH.TEXT are displayed</p>
            <p>NO      - Only the first warning message is       displayed plus a counter for any additional occurrences of SEARCH.TEXT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.ITEM.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying each error that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WARN.TYPE.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tag to be used when identifying the potential problems for the warning that occurred, only used when generating HTML output.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any character A to Z, a to z, 0 to 9, space and     !"#$%&amp;'()*+,-./:;&lt;=&gt;?@[\]^</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

