<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.COMPOSITE.SCREEN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The Composite screen application EB.COMPOSITE.SCREEN is used to define composite screens. This application comprises of a title for the composite screen and a large linked multi value set for defining the contents of each frame and makeup of the frames of the composite screen.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FRAME.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This can be used to specify specific attributes to the frame.  Currently it can be used to specify the following:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  'REPLACE.ALL' - if a frame or fragment has a REPLACE.ALL attribute then the parent composite screen will be replaced when you run an action in that frame such as a drilldown.  If you have nested composite screens then the immediate parent composite screen will be replaced.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTENT.ARGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>     If a CONTENT.TYPE is UTILITY then this will define the args for the called utility will be defined here</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Gives a name for the Frame. All content defining items (i.e. telling you what is in a frame) must have a name</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROWS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This defines the number and width of the Rows. It is done in the same format as the frameset tag in html. For reference and instructions on this see http://www.w3schools.com/html/html_frames.asp. For a given OPEN.FRAME item you must have either the ROWS or the COLS field set. You cannot however have both.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not used in standard Browser.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi purpose field that defines the content of the frame. Either a URL, the name of an Application and version, an enquiry etc. Also used to define the name of the utility to be called.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEMS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This sub-valued field is used to define what requests should be sent to this frame. It can be specific requests of application and version or enquiry, or it can be set to take all unassigned enquiries by setting it to ENQ or all unassigned requests by setting it as ALL. Furthermore it can be set to take everything except enquiries by setting it to NOENQ.  The request is assigned to a window by running through each item until a valid match is found for the request. If none are found a new window is launched.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TITLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The title that will appear on the composite screen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCROLLING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Set to NO to disallow scrolling within the frame.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This can be used to specify specific attributes to the screen definition.  Currently it can be used to specifiy the following:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  'NO.FRAMES' - If this is set then T24 Browser will render the composite screen without the use of HTML Framesets.</p>
            <p>  Please Note: A supporting version of T24 Browser must be used in conjunction with this attribute.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BORDER.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Only used CONTENT.TYPE IS OPEN.FRAME.</p>
            <p>   This field defines what the border of the frame set will be. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLS</field>
<desc>
            <p>     This defines the number and width of the columns. It is done in the same format as the frameset tag in html. For reference and instructions on this see http://www.w3schools.com/html/html_frames.asp. For a given OPEN.FRAME item you must have either the ROWS or the COLS field set. You cannot however have both.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPOSITE.SCREEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A unique name for the composite screen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field states what the item you are trying to define is. it can be one of the following values</p>
            <p>   BLANK: This item starts blank. </p>
            <p>   CLOSE.FRAME: Closes the frameset.</p>
            <p>   COS: This item is a composite screen.</p>
            <p>   ENQ: This item is an Enquiry.</p>
            <p>   MENU: This item is a menu.</p>
            <p>   OPEN.FRAME: Create a frame set. Tells you are splitting this frame into further frames. </p>
            <p>   PW: This item is a PW process.</p>
            <p>   TAB: This item is a tabbed screen.</p>
            <p>   TOOL: This item is a tool (button).</p>
            <p>   TOOLBAR: This item is a toolbar (set of tools).</p>
            <p>   TXN: This item is a contract screen.</p>
            <p>   URL: This item is a URL.</p>
            <p>   UTILITY: This allows you to call a browser routine. Not sure on the entire scope of this.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

