<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.COMPONENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file provides a framework to define independent components or subroutine which can be tested individually. Number of arguments in the routine, each argument's position, its direction can be defined in this application. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>        This field describes the component and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the description of the component in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory Field.</p>
            <p>  Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the T24 product the component belongs to.</p>
            <p>Should be a valid T24 product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMON.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the actual name of the subroutine to be tested, whose details are defined in EB.COMPONENT record. Should be valid subroutine in T24</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUBLISHED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes whether the component has been published. </p>
            <p>Allowed values are Y or null</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUM.PASS.ARGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes total number of arguments of the component (routine) . </p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>T24.SERVER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether this component is a T24 server component or not (as opposed to a front-end UI component such as Browser, etc).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPONENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of this component.  All components start with the 2 character Product code followed by "_" and then a name (E.g. EB_Enquiry).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.PLATFORMS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether or not this component is platform specific or not.  For example T24 server code must be compile on different platforms (i.e. types of Unix operating systems) whereas other components are Java based so are platform independent (e.g. Browser).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WRAP.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the name of the wrapper routine. </p>
            <p>If some common variables, which are not part of the argument list needs to be passed to the component , a wrapper routine needs to be defined. </p>
            <p />
            <p>   The wrapper routine contains three arguments,</p>
            <p />
            <p>   COMPONENT.ID - name of the component</p>
            <p>   ARG.LIST - List of arguments passed to the component</p>
            <p>   COM.LIST - List of common arguments to be used by the routine</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARG.DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    This field denotes the direction of each argument, whether the argument is incoming, outgoing or modifIed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Allowed values are</p>
            <p>INCOMING - Value of the argument is fed to the routine</p>
            <p>OUTGOING - Value of the argument is fed from the routine</p>
            <p>MODIFIED - Value of the argument is fed to the routine and the routine alters its value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The fields starting from ARGUMENT.NAME to ARG.DIRECTION form associated multivalue set.</p>
            <p>   Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARGU.DES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field describes each of the argument. This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the description of the argument in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The fields starting from ARGUMENT.NAME to ARG.DIRECTION form associated multivalue set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARGUMENT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the name of the argument to be passed to the component.</p>
            <p>The fields starting from ARGUMENT.NAME to ARG.DIRECTION form associated multivalue set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Some common variables which the component needs can be defined  here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Mandatory Field.</p>
            <p>  Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARGUMENT.NUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the position of the argument in the component. The argument value is passed at the mentioned position when the component is test. It is mandatory to define the arguments in ascending order. The arguments are shuffled according to the position defined when the routine is called.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Argument number should not be defined for common variables</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The fields starting from ARGUMENT.NAME to ARG.DIRECTION form associated multivalue set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

