<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.DICTIONARY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>EB.DICTIONARY table is T24 glossary which supplies Translation to Fields and Headers defined in Version/Enquiry.</p>
            <p>It enables easy Translation and maintenance of the translated terms.</p>
            <p>Dictionary mechanism need to be enabled in SPF to supply translations.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>HDR.2.118..132</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates text to be displayed as header in second line for columns 118 to 132 of the Version /Enquiry to be specified. This field is mapped to HDR.2.118...132 fields in Version when Dictionary key has Version name in it.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to HDR.2.118…132 field in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 1-39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.1.001..039</field>
<desc>
            <p> Indicates text to be displayed as header in first line for columns 01 to 39 of the Version /Enquiry to be specified. This field is mapped to HDR.1.001...039 fields in Version when Dictionary key has Version name in it.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to HDR.1.001…039 field in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 1-39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.2.079..117</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates text to be displayed as header in second line for columns 79 to 117 of the Version /Enquiry to be specified. This field is mapped to HDR.2.079...117 fields in Version when Dictionary key has Version name in it.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to HDR.2.079…117 field in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 1-39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXT.040..078</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Text that the User wants to define across the screen or page from column 40 to 78 in Version Output. It is mapped to Field labels which are used in Version headers provided fieldname is specified in Dictionary Key. Field characteristics are similar to TXT.040...078 field in Version.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1) Up to 39 characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds description about the Enquiry/Version or field name. When Version name/Enquiry name is specified in Dictionary key, text defined here is mapped to short description of corresponding Enquiry or Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Mandatory Input when Text is not entered.</p>
            <p>2)Up to 35 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.2.040..078</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates text to be displayed as header in second line for columns 40 to 78 of the Version to be specified. This field is mapped to HDR.2.040...078 fields in Version when Dictionary key has Version name in it.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to HDR.2.040…078 field in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 1-39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the text that appears to the left of the field when displayed in Version or Enquiry. This field is mapped to field label of Version and enquiry when corresponding field name is specified in Dictionary key.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics of this field are similar to TEXT in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Mandatory Input </p>
            <p>2)Up to 39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXT.OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Static Text to be displayed while launching the Enquiry is held in this field. Text defined here will be mapped to Operation field in Enquiry for Fields acting as header in Enquiry. Mapping will occur when Dictionary key is set with Fieldname.</p>
            <p>Field Characteristics and Functionality is similar to Operation in enquiry</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 35 A characteristics.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.1.040..078</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates text to be displayed as header in first line for columns 01 to 39 of the Version to be specified. This field is mapped to HDR.1.001...039 fields in Version when Dictionary key has Version name in it.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to HDR.1.001…039 field in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 1-39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROMPT.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Text entered here appears as a prompt to the user, replacing the T24 field name. Field characteristics are similar to PROMPT.TEXT in Version. Text Mapping will happen when Field name is specified in dictionary Key.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1) Up to 1-70 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOL.TIP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Text entered here is displayed near the mouse pointer when it is at rest pointing to the associated field when fieldname is specified along with Version name in Dictionary Key. </p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1) Up to 1-80 characters</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to field TOOL.TIP in Version.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXT.118..132</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Text that the User wants to define across the screen or page from column 118 to 132 in Version Output. It is mapped to Field labels which are used in Version headers provided fieldname is specified in Dictionary Key. Field characteristics are similar to TXT.118...132 field in Version.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 39 characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.TOOL.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Text to be displayed on Browser Tool on the Toolbar can be specified in this field. When Tool Id is specified along with Enquiry name in dictionary Key, text defined in this field will be appear on corresponding Tool of Enquiry Output. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> - </p>
            <p>Up to 35 ‘A’ alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXT.079..117</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Text that the User wants to define across the screen or page from column 79 to 117 in Version Output. It is mapped to Field labels which are used in Version headers provided fieldname is specified in Dictionary Key. Field characteristics are similar to TXT.079...117 field in Version.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 15 characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.1.118..132</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates text to be displayed as header in first line for columns 118 to 132 of the Version to be specified. This field is mapped to HDR.1.118…132 fields in Version when Dictionary key has Version name in it.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to HDR.1.118…132 field in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 1-39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.2.001..039</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates text to be displayed as header in second line for columns 01 to 39 of the Version to be specified. This field is mapped to HDR.2.001...039 fields in Version when Dictionary key has Version name in it.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to HDR.2.001…039 field in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 1-39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies details about Version/Enquiry or field name. When Version name is set in Dictionary Key, Text held in this field is mapped to Description of Version or Enquiry.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Mandatory input when TEXT is not entered.</p>
            <p>2)Multivalue field and it can have text up to 70 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DICT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Key of Dictionary.</p>
            <p>For Headers Translation,Key must contain Version/Enquiry name and Language Mnemonic.</p>
            <p>Format:</p>
            <p>&lt;Version/enquiryname&gt;-&lt;languagemnemonic&gt;</p>
            <p>For Fields Translation of Version and Enquiry,Key must contain fieldnames defined in Version/Enquiry and language Mnemonic.</p>
            <p>Format:</p>
            <p>&lt;Version/enquiryname&gt;-&lt;fieldname&gt;-&lt;languageMnemonic&gt;</p>
            <p>Default language Mnemonic is English.</p>
            <p>Eg:</p>
            <p>To supply french translation for field CUST.NO in CUSTOMER,INPUT version. </p>
            <p>Dictionary key must be given in following way </p>
            <p>CUSTOMER,TEST-CUST.NO-FR</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Any text up to 50 chars</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.HEADER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the static header details that need to be displayed at the Start of the Enquiry. Text defined here is mapped to Enquiry header when Enquiry name is defined in dictionary Key.</p>
            <p>Field Characteristics is almost similar to HEADER field in ENQUIRY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1.Optional Input of up to 42 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.SEL.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the text for Selection field name in Enquiry. Text defined here is mapped to Selection field in Enquiry Selection window when Selection field name is specified in Dictionary Key.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 20 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.1.079..117</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates text to be displayed as header in first line for columns 79 to 117 of the Version to be specified. This field is mapped to HDR.1.079...117 fields in Version when Dictionary key has Version name in it.</p>
            <p>Field characteristics are similar to HDR.1.079…117 field in Version.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1)Up to 1-39 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>VERSION.ADDL.HDR</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>VERSION.ADDL.FTR</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
