<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.EOD.ERROR</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to hold the details of any non fatal errors which occurred during the T24 batch phase and the status of these errors after the batch phase has been completed. </p>
            <p>There are two types of errors which will be reported to this file : critical errors and non critical errors.  Currently only non critical errors are reported. </p>
            <p>Each record on the file represents a single batch run for each company. The status of each record is held in the idescriptor "UNRESOLVED" which will contain one of the following values: </p>
            <p>     OK           - Used to indicate that all errors on the record have                     been resolved. </p>
            <p>     UNRESOLVED   - This value indicates that the record contains at least                     one non critical error which has yet to be resolved. </p>
            <p>     CRITICAL     - When at least one critical error is left unresolved on                     the file this value is used. </p>
            <p>The status of each record on this file is checked each time the BATCH.CONTROL application is invoked and the status of the errors checked. If the errors on the file are UNRESOLVED then an override is required before the BATCH.CONTROL application is invoked. </p>
            <p>If the errors on the file are CRITICAL the BATCH.CONTROL application may not be invoked until these errors are resolved. </p>
            <p>Once an error has been resolved, the date on which the error was resolved should be input in the DATE.RESOLVED field. This resolves the individual error but may not modify the overall status. This will only occur if the last critical error on the record has been resolved, or if the last non critical error on the file has been resolved and there are no critical errors. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FIX.REQUIRED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field details whether the error is considered to be a critical error or not. If the value in this field is set to YES, then the error is considered to be a critical error and the BATCH.CONTROL application will not be able to be invoked until this error has been resolved. </p>
            <p>When this field contains the value NO then the error is not considered to be a critical error, and as such the BATCH.CONTROL application may be invoked when this error is unresolved - but an override will be required. </p>
            <p>Fields TIME.DATE to FIX.REQUIRED form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNRESOLVED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This value indicates that the record contains at least one non critical error which has yet to be resolved.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time and date on which the error occurred is held in this field. Note that the information in this field will hold the machine date and time, not the system date. </p>
            <p>Fields TIME.DATE to FIX.REQUIRED form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>If any records were saved at the time the error was reported then these records are saved to the EB.EOD.ERROR.DETAIL file. The keys to these records are held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields TIME.DATE to FIX.REQUIRED form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.EOD.ERROR.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the unique key to the records on this file and is comprised of two parts. The first part of the key is the company code of the company in which the error took place, and the second part is the system date on which the batch run began. </p>
            <p>Input onto this file is only allowed for records which already exist - users may not create new records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The key to records on this file must consist of a valid company code or a valid company mnemonic.  Followed by a '.' character.  Then followed by a valid date in the format YYYMMDD.</p>
            <p>The record must already exist on the file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the routine in which the error occured is held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields TIME.DATE to FIX.REQUIRED form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>If any specific records were related to the error then the keys to these records will be held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields TIME.DATE to FIX.REQUIRED form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The application identifier which created the error is stored in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields TIME.DATE to FIX.REQUIRED form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.RESOLVED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the only field which is open for input on the EB.EOD.ERROR records. When an error has been resolved, the date on which this resolution occurred should be entered into this field. </p>
            <p>This will then resolve the error in the eyes of this application, and if this error was blocking access to the BATCH.CONTROL application then the BATCH.CONTROL application will no longer be blocked. </p>
            <p>Fields TIME.DATE to FIX.REQUIRED form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to eleven date characters.  Must be a valid date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A description of the error is held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields TIME.DATE to FIX.REQUIRED form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

