<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.EXTERNAL.USER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>EB.EXTERNAL.USER is an application holding details about users of the system who are not staff of the bank. Examples include Internet banking users.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ALLOWED.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
        <p>Allowed customer associated with the channel permission.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation</p>
        <p>Should be defined only if associated  channel permission is defined.</p>
        <p>Should be a valid record in CUSTOMER application.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
        <p>DATE.FORMAT field is used for deciding in which format the dates are to be displayed for a user.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rules</p>
        <p>Valid values are  1, 2, 3 and 4.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">(dd) (month)(year)</p>
            <p value="2">(DD)/(MM)/(YYYY)</p>
            <p value="3">(YYYY)/(MM)/(DD</p>
            <p value="4">YYYYMMDD</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANNEL.PERMISSION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Define the group from which the permissions shall be inherited for the external user</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rules</p>
        <p>Should be a valid record in CHANNEL.PERMISSION</p>
        <p>Should be allowed for all kind of users</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicates the Language in which the System should communicate with this User.  All messages, instructions, Help Text etc. will be displayed when possible in the Language indicated by this definition.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.RTN</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field specifies the routines that needs to be triggered when the user successfully logs in.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">Validation Rules</p>
        <p>The routines entered should have a record on the EB.API application</p>
        <p>Standard multi-value field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Access status of the user</p>
            <p>   ACTIVE: User can use the system, provided they try to access the system within their access start and end dates.</p>
            <p>   INACTIVE: User has not yet been activated.</p>
            <p>   BARRED: The user has barred from using the system.</p>
            <p>   INITIATED : User can activate their access.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time on the first day (START.DATE) that the user can use the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUT.UPD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds a numeric value between 0 to 4 indicating the status of the user record creation in Authentication Server</p>
            <p>0 - user record created successfully in Authentication server</p>
            <p>1 - user record not created in Authentication Server</p>
            <p>2 - Communication does not exist between Authentication server and T24</p>
            <p>3 - Internal Error </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The AA product line for this arrangement</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Last day the user can use the system. If they try after this, they will get a security violation and a message will be logged in the PROTOCOL file detailing why they could not log in.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.AUTH.PW</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reset the Password of the EXTERNAL user in Authentication Server</p>
            <p>Move the PASSWORD status in the Authentication Server to PENDING</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.CUST.DATA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updates the customer information  in Authentication server when any change is made to the existing customer records.</p>
            <p>E.g. NAME,ADDRESS,CITY,COUNTRY,POSTCODE</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.SIGN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the Type of Transaction Signing.</p>
            <p>Valid settings in this field are;</p>
            <p>SMS : One Time Password (OTP) will be sent to the Mail or Mobile as configured in the Authentication server</p>
            <p>Token : User will  use the token given to generate One Time Password(OTP)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOGIN.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of login method.  Valid values from EB.LOOKUP. Ex: Password/MemWord/PIN/OTP etc.</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>T.C.ACCEPTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether the user has accepted the Terms and Conditions first displayed when the user logs in to the system for the very first time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSW.CHANGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date when the password was changed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWORD.REVIEW</field>
<desc>
            <p>The duration in which the password is to be reviewed by the user</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Type of the user.  Valid values are :-</p>
            <p>CORPORATE</p>
            <p>INTERMEDIARY</p>
            <p>PERSONAL</p>
            <p>The USER.TYPE can be manually changed (or automatically defaulted in the Version)from Intermediary to Corporate, if a Corporate user is being created</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time on the last day (END.DATE) that the user can use the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The companies the user can access</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The user's name</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any overrides raised when this record was authorised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHENTICATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of authentication for this external user.  Valid values are :-</p>
            <p>External - External authentication via an authentication services such as 4Tress.</p>
            <p>User Maintained - Maintained by the user with a simpla user name and password.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.AUTH.PIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reset the PIN of the EXTERNAL user in the Authentication Server.</p>
            <p>Move the PIN status in the Authentication Server to PENDING.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field takes the EB.LDAP.PARAMETER record id  as the value</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUT.UPD.SERVER</field>
<desc>
            <p>When selected, will create a user record in the Authentication server</p>
            <p>User id will be same as EB.EXTERNAL.USER  id in the Authentication Server.</p>
            <p>Eg.: 4TRESS</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SALT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MEMORABLE.DATA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Encrypted memorable data of the user</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>A defined channel for communication for this external user (e.g. INTERNET)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAP.DN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field takes any value .</p>
            <p>Value should be prefixed with CN= &lt;anyname&gt;</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.DURATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The duration that the user last used the system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.USER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of this external user.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>First day the user can use the system. If they try before this, they will get a security violation and a message will be logged in the PROTOCOL file detailing why they could not log in.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The password set for the user's login</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.LAST.USE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Last date and time the user last logged in</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customer the user can access. This is a NOCHANGE field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.LAST.USE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Last time the system was used by the user</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The AA.ARRANGEMENT record that the user on which an arrangement has been arrived at between the bank and the user. For example, the INTERNET SERVICES arrangement</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTEMPTS.SINCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Counter of the number of consecutive incorrect passwords the user has actually entered, since last entering a correct password.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field to determine the attributes that are associated with a particular user.</p>
            <p>Valid settings in this field are;</p>
            <p>PREAUTHENTICATED: When selected will skip the password validation in T24 for the respective  EXTERNAL user.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUT.UPD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field will be updated by T24 on creation of a external user in T24.</p>
            <p>Field will hold T24 date as the value.</p>
            <p>It is a no input field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS.CHANGE.REASON</field>
<desc>
            <p>The reason for changing the status of the external user</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTH.SERV.USER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Change the USER.ID of the EXTERNAL user with this value in Authentication Server</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

