<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.EOD.ERROR.DETAIL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>When a non fatal error is reported in the batch it is possible to save certain records which may be of use in tracking down the cause of the problem. </p>
            <p>The records which are saved when a non fatal error is reported in the batch are saved to this file. Each saved record has a record on this file, the keys to which are held on the EB.EOD.ERROR file. </p>
            <p>This is a live file and hence input is not allowed. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RE.POSITION.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a mismatch occurs between the CRB and the position files during the end of day revaluation processing a record is created on this file which uses the fields RE.CCY.MKT to RE.CRF.AMT, which form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>This field holds the amount with which the position files have been updated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The description of the record held in the ADDITIONAL field is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RE.CCY.MKT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a mismatch occurs between the CRB and the position files during the end of day revaluation processing a record is created on this file which uses the fields RE.CCY.MKT to RE.CRF.AMT, which form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>This field holds the currency market in which the mismatch has occurred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The error code used in the call to the EXCEPTION.LOG.FILE is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the module from which the error originated is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RE.POS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a mismatch occurs between the CRB and the position files during the end of day revaluation processing a record is created on this file which uses the fields RE.CCY.MKT to RE.CRF.AMT, which form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>This field details the position type in which the mismatch occurred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the routine from which the error originated is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RE.CRF.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a mismatch occurs between the CRB and the position files during the end of day revaluation processing a record is created on this file which uses the fields RE.CCY.MKT to RE.CRF.AMT, which form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>This fields holds the amount with which the CRB has been updated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDITIONAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to actually hold the record. Each field is represented by a multi value and each multivalue is represented by a sub value. Sub value fields are included on the same line as their related multi values. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLIC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The application identifier from which the error originated is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.AND.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The machine date and time at which the error occurred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>A unique key by which the Entry may be identified.  It is generated by the system, based on the date and time (in hundredths of a second) at which the record was generated and a sequence number. </p>
            <p>The key is made up as follows: </p>
            <p>(a)        4 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st            December 1967. </p>
            <p>(b)        Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers and            (usually) 2 decimals.  If the time is an exact number of            seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted. </p>
            <p>(c)        Sequence number. </p>
            <p>If several records are generated at the same time, all the Entries have parts (a) and (b) the same and are distinguished from each other by their Sequence numbers. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>13 numeric characters            or 16 characters consisting of 15 numeric characters with a decimal    point after the 9th.</p>
            <p>Internal file.  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a mismatch occurs between the CRB and the position files during the end of day revaluation processing a record is created on this file which uses the fields RE.CCY.MKT to RE.CRF.AMT, which form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>This field details the currency in which the mismatch occurred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

