<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.ENQUIRY.GRAPH</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to define graphs based on enquries.</p>
            <p>   Based on a enquiry ( id) this app provides a way of choosing which columns of the enquiry should be used for plotting a desired graph. </p>
            <p>   The list of graphs that are possible to display are provided in the GRAPH.TYPE field. When a graph type is choosen the system then asks the user to fill in which columns to use from the enquiry. Note some graph types require more then 2 columns from the enquiry i.e Bar Line Chart.</p>
            <p>   Some of the attributes only apply to graphs displayed as SVG objects, and have no effect when graphs are displayed as .png images. In general with png images, the margin, legend, title and graph are sized and positioned dynamically by the system to fit inside the specified total area for the graph, and the user does not need to be concerned with tweaking the graph to size these elements.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ENQ.COL.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The column name as specified in the ENQUIRY application. This only accepts coumns which are set to be displayed, non-displayable coulmns will not work. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RIGHT.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The specifies how much space should the graph have on the right side. In pixels. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEGEND.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The source axis for which to display the legend. Can only  be one of the DATA.ITEMS for this record. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEGEND.Y</field>
<desc>
            <p>The y coordinate for where the legend shoud be displayed. In pixels.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LABEL.Y</field>
<desc>
            <p>The y coordinate for where the label shoud be displayed. In pixels. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WIDTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The overrall width of the graph. In pixels.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The specifies how much space should the graph have at the top. In pixels. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRID.Y</field>
<desc>
            <p>If checked, will display a grid along the Y axis. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEFT.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The specifies how much space should the graph have on the left side. In pixels. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRID.X</field>
<desc>
            <p>If checked, will display a grid along the X axis. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCALE.X</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field has no effect on categorical / ordinal graphs and anticipates graphs with a linear X axis. The graphing mechanism automatically calculates a scale for the graph. </p>
            <p> If this field is specified with scale then then the automatic scaling will be overriden if this scale is appropriate. This field is used for the X axis.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LABEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>A title for the graph. In SVG mode, text specified in this field will be displayed coordinally as spcified by the user. In png image mode, the title will appear centered at the top of the graph if enabled.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LABEL.X</field>
<desc>
            <p>The x coordinate for where the label shoud be displayed. In pixels. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEGEND.X</field>
<desc>
            <p>The x coordinate for where the legend shoud be displayed. In pixels. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRAPH.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The graph type specifies the type of graph that will be displayed for the enquiry choosen. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERTICAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>If checked, the label will be displayed in a vertical manner, otherwise horisontally. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images - the title is always horizontal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.ENQUIRY.GRAPH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of an enquiry which is an 'ALLDATA' enquiry. Page enquries don't work with graphs.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEGEND</field>
<desc>
            <p>If checked, will display a legend for the graph. In SVG mode the legend can be chosen from the category labels. In png mode, the enquiry column headings for each series of data will be used for the legend.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOTTOM.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The specifies how much space should the graph have at the bottom. In pixels. Has no effect if graphs are displayed as png images.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.BREAK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to break on a column from the enquiry. This functionality only works with enquiries that use the break change mechanism of grouping result sets together.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.ITEM.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a noinput field used by the system technically.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a noinput field used by the system technically. Note that the data type should match the type of data the enquiry produces. I.e. if the data type is specified as 'Number' then the enquiry data for this column should numbers only, without applied formatting.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCALE.Y</field>
<desc>
            <p>The graphing mechanism automatically calculates a scale for the graph. </p>
            <p> If this field is specified with scale then then the automatic scaling will be overriden if this scale is appropriate. This field is used for the Y axis.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The overrall height of the graph. In pixels.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

