<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.ERROR</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ERROR.SOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This filed is only visible in Desktop and has no presence in Classic.</p>
            <p>This field contains possible solutions to the error.</p>
            <p>The Field can multi value to allow multi language</p>
            <p> Note: When Multi valuing language fields the fields appear in a pre set order, so in order to use a set language you will need to have the languages preceding it multi valued as well.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>50 characters long</p>
            <p>Can accept alpha, numeric and symbol data</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This multi-language field contains the message that will be displayed in the event of an application triggering this error.</p>
            <p>On selecting and validating a second multi language field, a mirror record for the multi language text will be created in DYNAMIC.TEXT with the GB version of the Error message as the key.  All spaces in the DYNAMIC.TEXT record Key are replaced by the "." character.</p>
            <p>Note: When Multi valuing language fields the fields appear in a pre set order, so in order to use a set language you will need to have the languages preceding it multi valued as well. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>50 characters in length.</p>
            <p>Alpha, Numeric and symbol input accepted</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMERIC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the key identification number for error message.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System generated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.ERROR.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Alternative Error Code (ALT.ERROR.CD)</p>
            <p>The field ALT.ERROR.CD has been created to:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Save duplication of same error messages in the same application</p>
            <p>Save duplication of same error messages in different applications</p>
            <p>Reduce maintenance of duplicated error messages in one, or more applications.  Only the "Alternative" Error record has to be updated.  The ALT.ERROR.CD field acts as a link.</p>
            <p />
            <p>On entry of a valid error code, the Description of the Error message is extracted from the Alternative Error Code record and displayed in this fields associated enrichment field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>When linking this Error record to an Alternative Error record, there are only two fields that need to be defined; this field, and the record ID.  Whenever this Error record is referenced by T24 the Message, Information, and Solution fields will be extracted from the Alternative Error record.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>To prevent a potential hanging situation where one record references an alternative record, and the alternative record references the original record, and so ononly the ID of the original record is reported. The Error message, Error Info, Error Solution fields are not reported.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>35 alphanumeric characters in length</p>
            <p>Cannot be linked to itself</p>
            <p>Must be a valid ID to a record on the EB.ERROR table.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
            <p> Used to define channel specific messages. Every OFS.SOURCE record can be set to a specific channel</p>
            <p> If there is a channel specified, the channel specific message will be displayed as en error</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 20 characters long</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.ERROR.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the record that would be used to identify the error message required.</p>
            <p>The field is comprised of two parts:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Part 1: The PRODUCT code. Eg: OF for Universal Interface</p>
            <p>Part 2: An abbreviated description of the error message.</p>
            <p>Eg: For the error message "Mandatory for IB User" that is produced by the OFS.SOURCE application.  OFS.SOURCE application appears in the OF Product class.  An example key would be:  OF.SRC.MAND.IB.USER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is only visible in Desktop and has no presence in Classic.</p>
            <p>This field contains an explanation of the error in more detail.</p>
            <p>This Field can multi value to allow multi language.</p>
            <p> Note: When Multi valuing language fields the fields appear in a pre set order, so in order to use a set language you will need to have the languages preceding it multi valued as well.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>50 characters long</p>
            <p>Can accept alpha, numeric and symbol data</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

