<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.ENC.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>A main parameter template to house-in the encrypt &amp; decrypt routines and list of T24 applications on which the encryption &amp; decryption need to be done.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ENCRYPT.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>EB.API Hook routine to be called for encrypting the fields (Arguments: File name, RecordId and the Record, a dynamic Array) before committing the record to the disk.</p>
            <p />
            <p> For more information on the routine format, please refer to the USER guide.</p>
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. The routine should have an entry defined in EB.API</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENCRYPT.APPL</field>
<desc>
            <p>M/v field ENCRYPT.APPL, to accept the T24 applications and other t24 files, where the encryption and decryption routines will be called only for these entries.  </p>
            <p />
            <p> Validations: </p>
            <p />
            <p> 1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. Allows T24 Applications of PGM.TYPE "HUWD"</p>
            <p> 3. Also accepts valid record from FILE.CONTROL if F.LOCKING record DATA.ENCRYPT is present </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.DECRYPT.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>EB.API HOOK routine for decrypting the field’s data from an Enquiry.</p>
            <p />
            <p> To be called per field at Conversion level</p>
            <p />
            <p> Syntax:</p>
            <p> DECRYPT &lt;&lt;Field Name&gt;&gt;</p>
            <p />
            <p> DECRYPT is a standard text to inform T24 that this field is sensitive and the routine attached in the main parameter table to be called.</p>
            <p />
            <p> DECRYPT is a standard text to inform T24 that this field is sensitive and the routine attached in the main parameter table to be called.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Field Name must be a valid field name in the enquiry</p>
            <p />
            <p> For more information on the routine format, please refer to the USER guide.</p>
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. The routine should have an entry defined in EB.API</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENC.DEC.HOOK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the @ID of this template. The Id is the standard parameter file ID : ‘SYSTEM’</p>
            <p />
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. Value allowed is "SYSTEM"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.ENC.FLD.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p> A EB.API Hook routine to be called for returning the list of fields per application which are encrypted. </p>
            <p>Note: The applications list returned by this routine should match the APPLICATIONS mentioned in the m/v ENCRYPT.APPL. If specified then the field APPL.MSK.CHARS becomes mandatory. </p>
            <p />
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p />
            <p> 1. Non-mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. The routine should have an entry defined in EB.API</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.MSK.CHARS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value to be used for masking the encrypted characters for a non-privileged user.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Note: NULL or Blank values will not be replaced. If this field is left NULL then the actual encrypted data will be displayed.</p>
            <p />
            <p> For more information on the routine format, please refer to the USER guide.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Non-mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. Max length of 35 characters</p>
            <p> 3. If the field APPL.ENC.FLD.RTN is specified then the field APPL.MSK.CHARS becomes mandatory.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECRYPT.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>EB.API Hook routine to be called for decrypting the fields (Arguments: File name, RecordId and the Record, a dynamic Array) before displaying the record on the screen.</p>
            <p />
            <p> For more information on the routine format, please refer to the USER guide.</p>
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. The routine should have an entry defined in EB.API</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DE.ENCRYPT.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>EB.API hook routine to be invoked for encrypting sensitive tags in swift delivery message towards the end of formatting process.  Arguments passed will be the Delivery reference and message contents (F.DE.O.MSG.SWIFT contents).</p>
            <p />
            <p> For more information on the routine format, please refer to the USER guide.</p>
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Non Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. The routine should have an entry defined in EB.API</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DE.DECRYPT.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>EB.API hook routine to be invoked for decrypting swift delivery message before starting formatting process.  Arguments passed will be the Delivery reference and message contents (F.DE.O.MSG or F.DE.I.MSG contents).</p>
            <p />
            <p> For more information on the routine format, please refer to the USER guide.</p>
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Non Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. The routine should have an entry defined in EB.API</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to store meaningful description of the record</p>
            <p />
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. Multivalue Language field.</p>
            <p> 3. Max length of 35 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.MSK.CHARS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value to be used for masking the encrypted field’s value (for a non-privileged user)</p>
            <p />
            <p> Note: This is for the local API routine mentioned in ENQ.DECRYPT.RTN to make use of. CORE does not handle this for ENQUIRY.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Non-mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. Max length of 35 characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.ENRI.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>EB.API hook routine to be invoked for processing the enrichment if the field to be used to return an enrichment value is categorised as sensitive field. </p>
            <p />
            <p> This API will be invoked only if the field used to return an enrichment value is sensitive.</p>
            <p> Accepts two Parameter; 1. Flag to decide User permission 2. Enrichment Value   </p>
            <p> This API is responsible to check whether the user is allowed to view the enrichment as plain text. Based on user permission API should return decrypted enrichment or the Flag to mask the enrichment</p>
            <p> Validations:</p>
            <p> 1. Non Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. The routine should have an entry defined in EB.API</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

