<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.FREE.MESSAGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The EB.FREE.MESSAGE Application is used to store both outward and inward messages.  Messages can be sent to either Customers or SWIFT addresses.  Consult the Delivery User Guide on the use of EB.ACTIVITY and EB.ADVICES.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EB.MSG.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the free-form message request/receipt</p>
            <p>The format is FMyydddnnnn.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACER.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts Standard date format . This field is defaulted from LETTER.OF.CREDIT or DRAWINGS which have TRACER.DATE field set. </p>
            <p>This can also be manually changed which will in turn update the file &amp;#145;EB.SCHEDULE.TRACER&amp;#146; which keeps track of the tracers and when they are scheduled to be sent.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory if TRACER.STAT is &amp;#145;SCHED&amp;#146;.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAFT.PRINT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Set this field to "Y" to preview the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACER.STAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the current Status of the Tracer and accepts the following values :</p>
            <p>&amp;#145; &amp;#145; &amp;#150; If the field is left blank it indicates the non-tracer type.</p>
            <p>SCHED &amp;#150; Indicates that the Tracer is Scheduled to be sent on a future date. If it is set as &amp;#145;SCHED&amp;#146; then the TRACER.DATE becomes mandatory.</p>
            <p>STOP - Indicates that the tracer which was Scheduled is Stopped for some reason. Once the Status is set as STOP, this message record is removed and written to the History file during the End of Day process.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input for tracer</p>
            <p>Allowed values &amp;#150; SCHED , STOP.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVER.CUSTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The T24 ID of the customer who sent/receives the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid ID on the CUSTOMER file or a valid customer mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format multivalue field to be mapped directly to tag 79 of the message types MT499, MT799.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Accepts Swift characters.</p>
            <p>A multivalue set can hold 35 lines with 50 characters each.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACER.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts valid number of days. This gets defaulted from LETTER.OF.CREDIT which has TRACER.DAYS set. If left blank, it gets the<strong></strong>default value from COUNTRY file or from the EB.FREE.PARAMETERS file. This indicates the period after which the tracer message should be recycled and sent again. Tracer messages are generated during the End of Day process.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p>Tracer days should be like &amp;#145;+nW&amp;#146; or &amp;#145;         nW&amp;#146; where &amp;#145;n&amp;#146; stands for the number of         days and &amp;#145;W&amp;#146; stands for Working days.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECV.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The text version of the customer address or the S.W.I.F.T BIC Code prefixed with SW-.</p>
            <p>The customer address will be automatically completed when the customer ID is entered.</p>
            <p>In the absence of the customer number this field should be completed only by the valid swift address prefixed with  SW-</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The S.W.I.F.T address should exist in DE.SWIFT.BOOK and the validations are done only when the customer number field is null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The message text</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid S.W.I.F.T. characters and can be mandatory depending on the message type and the settings in DE.MESSAGE.</p>
            <p>This is a mandatory field when sending N99 Swift messages other than MT499, MT799.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAPPING.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Populated by the T24 delivery mechenism with the Mapping reference that  request for stop payment of a cheque has generated.</p>
            <p>.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
 Fields ACTIVITY.CODE to DELIVERY.REF form a related multi value set.Standard GLOBUS numeric field.A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.This is a NOINPUT field       </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GENERATED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Date on which the message is generated, usually the date when the transaction is authorised.</p>
            <p>  NOINPUT field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REMARK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free-form remarks. This is not intended to be sent as part of the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Free Form</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.ADVICE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to EB.ACTIVITY and EB.ADVICES which determines the message type(s) to be sent and the mappings to be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid record ID in EB.ADVICES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THEIR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The other party's reference information</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If you want to include information from a T24 application specified in APPLICATION.NAME then you enter the ID of the transaction in this field. Input can be the ID of a record from the history file.</p>
            <p>.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The transaction is an existing record in the application entered in APPLICATION.NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.DEL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the reference number allocated by Delivery for incoming SWIFT messages received Inward Delivery.</p>
            <p>The original Inward Swift message details along with header and Block 4 details as received can be viewed by launching the Context Enquiry.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Internal Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Our reference information. This field is defaulted with the ID of the transaction from which it is populated (LETTER.OF.CREDIT or </p>
            <p>DRAWINGS) or the OLD.LC.NUMBER field in LETTER.OF.CREDIT. This will form as the ID for the file EB.TXN.TRACER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACER.COUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field cannot be Input. It keeps count of the number of times a tracer message has been sent for a particular transaction. This field is </p>
            <p>updated during  the End of Day process which increments this field as and when a tracer is sent for a particular transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identify the name of the application where a related T24 transaction is held. This field will be used in conjunction with TXN.REFERENCE field. The content of the corresponding record will be stored in HANDOFF#3.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid program ID registered in PGM.FILE, where the TYPE must be 'H' or 'U'</p>
            <p>Up to 32 alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input must either be an existing CUSTOMER.</p>
            <p>If a Swift BIC address in entered in RECV.ADDR field then NO INPUT</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1 Must be an existing CUSTOMER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Confirmation that MT111 - request for stop payment of a cheque have been sent to the T24 delivery system for onward transmission to ordering institution.</p>
            <p>.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
 21 type A (alphanumeric) characters in the form: AYYYYMMDDUUUUUCCCCCC where A = (D)ELIVERED (R)ECEIVED YYYY = YEAR MM = MONTH DD = SEQUENCE NO UUUUU = SYSTEM USER NUMBER CCCCC = TIME STAMP (System generated.).This is a NOINPUT field </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the direction of delivery message, which is either OUTWARD or INWARD.  OUTWARD denotes the message is generated by the system to be sent to other party.  INWARD denotes an incoming message from 'n' 99 series like MT199, MT299.</p>
            <p> NOINPUT field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

