<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.FILE.UPLOAD.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The EB.FILE.UPLOAD.TYPE application allows parameters for a type of upload to be defined. These include the upload directory, optional maximum file size limit, and optional extension.</p>
            <p>Warning! Changing the UPLOAD.DIR will require any existing uploaded files to be moved manually to the new directory.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>HEADER.POSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the position of the header in the uploaded file.</p>
            <p>Value should be numeric.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEMS.UPD.APPL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must contain a valid application name. </p>
            <p>PGM.FILE type must “H”,”U”and”L”.</p>
            <p>This field indicates the application to be used in the uploaded file for ITEMS.</p>
            <p>It is a Mandatory field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEMS.ID.INCLUDED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the id is specified in the uploaded for ITEMS file or not.</p>
            <p>If the field specified to YES then first column of the uploaded file contains the id of the transaction.</p>
            <p>Optional field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>YES or NO field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEPARATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value of the field delimiter that used in the uploaded file.</p>
            <p>The delimiter may be any single character.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFORMAT.PLUGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid plug-in to reformat the file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be an ID in EB.API </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This routine should process  and Modify the line STRING  specified for the HEADER &amp; LINES application in run time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The format plug-in routine should have 4 arguments</p>
            <p>ARG 1: to specify  the processing string is a HEADER string or ITEMS strings</p>
            <p>ARG 2: to specify a line number</p>
            <p>ARG 3:  to specify an EB.FILE.UPLOAD id</p>
            <p>ARG 4: to specify the line string to process</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.ID.INCLUDED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the id is specified in the uploaded file for HEADER or not.</p>
            <p>If the field specified to YES then first column of the uploaded file contains the id of the transaction.</p>
            <p>Optional field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>YES or NO field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.DIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Warning! Changing the value of this field will require any existing uploaded files to be moved manually to the new directory.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field. This specifies which directory files will be uploaded to.</p>
            <p>This directory will be relative to the directory specified in the EB.FILE.UPLOAD.PARAM / SYSTEM / TC.UPLOAD.DIR field.</p>
            <p>The TC server process must have permissions to write to the directory specified in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>T24.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether the Uploaded file via EB.FILE.UPLOAD is of Standard T24 File to be processed via Service or the corresponding EB.FILE.UPLOAD is for uploading file like PDF.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Possible values: “YES” , “NO” or “NULL”</p>
            <p />
            <p>NULL value or Y denotes that it is a T24.FILE to be picked up the service and also force values for fields HDR.UPD.APPL, HDR.UPD.VERSION, ITEMS.UPD.APPL, ITEMS.UPD.VERSION, SEPARATER and HEADER.POSITION etc and if the value is “N” then these fields cannot be input and this type of EB.FILE.UPLOAD records will not be picked up by the service.  </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>An override will be generated if changing the location of uploaded files as the system will not automatically move any existing files.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field. If set, then specifies a maximum size (in bytes) to be uploaded. If not set, then the system will not place any artificial limits on the upload file size.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEMS.UPD.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains a valid version belonging to the application mentioned in  ITEMS.UPD.APPL</p>
            <p>This field indicates the version to be used to create records in ITEMS APPLICATION</p>
            <p>It is a Mandatory field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.UPD.APPL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field must contain a valid application name. </p>
            <p>PGM.FILE type must be “H”,”U”,”L”.</p>
            <p>This field indicates the application to be used in the uploaded file for HEADER.</p>
            <p>It is a Mandatory field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDR.UPD.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains a valid version belonging to the application mentioned in HDR.UPD.APPL.</p>
            <p>This field indicates the version to be used to create records in HEADER APPLICATION</p>
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field describing the purpose of the EB.FILE.UPLOAD.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.FILE.UPLOAD.TYPE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id of the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTENSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field. If set, then only files with that extension will be uploaded. The system generated filename will also be given the extension provided. </p>
            <p>If this field is not set, then any file type can be uploaded, and the system generated name will be the SIGN.ON.NAME plus a time stamp.</p>
            <p>A leading period character to delimit the extension will be added automatically if none is specified.</p>
            <p>This field is not case sensitive. An extension of 'csv' will allow 'CSV' files to be uploaded.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIXED.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

