<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.FILE.UPLOAD</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>EB.FILE.UPLOAD allows files to be uploaded to the T24 server through Browser and the Temenos Connector.</p>
            <p>The minimum fields required to successfully upload a field are the FILE.NAME field (the file to be uploaded), and the UPLOAD.TYPE field (which specifies an EB.FILE.UPLOAD.TYPE record).</p>
            <p>Files are uploaded to the server by clicking the upload button. To complete the process, the record must then be committed.</p>
            <p>Files that exist on the file system but do not have a corresponding EB.FILE.UPLOAD record should be ignored and considered that the upload process has not been completed.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Mandatory, NOCHANGE field. Can be specified in AUT.NEW.CONTENT in a VERSION. The upload type specifies the upload directory, and optionally a maximum upload size limit and file extension.</p>
            <p>Field is NOCHANGE because the system does not have the ability to move the file if the new UPLOAD.TYPE specifies a different location.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the status of the service T24.UPLOAD.PROCESS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Possible values “PROCESSED”, “ “ , PROCESSING” , ‘ERROR.IN,PROCESSING” </p>
            <p />
            <p>NULL: If the field values is NULL then those record are selected by the service T24.UPLOAD.PROCESS</p>
            <p />
            <p>PROCESSING: once the uploaded record picked by the service then the record status changed from NULL to PROCESSING</p>
            <p />
            <p>PROCESSED:  once the uploaded record are processed then the field status changed from “PROCESSING” to “PROCESSED” </p>
            <p />
            <p>ERROR.IN.PROCESSING: if any error in the service then the field updated with the value as “ERROR.IN.PROCESSING”</p>
            <p />
            <p>Noinputable field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field. The SIGN.ON.NAME of the user uploading the file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>T24.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether the uploaded file via EB.FILE.UPLOAD is a Standard T24 File OR a file like PDF.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field value updated from the field T24.FILE in EB.FILE.UPLOAD.TYPE</p>
            <p />
            <p>Possible values: “YES”, “NO” or “NULL”</p>
            <p />
            <p>Noinputable field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEADER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Id used in the upload process whose file is specified in the corresponding EB.FILE.UPLOAD.TYPE application in the field HDR.UPD.APPL</p>
            <p />
            <p>No inputable field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field. Allows the system to track the processed status of the file once it has been uploaded. After initial upload, this field will be set to 'Uploaded'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the upload to be assigned to a company.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field. Will be set to the size of the upload (in bytes) after validate / commit.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The system will generate a new filename for the uploaded file. The filename will be made up of the SIGN.ON.NAME, a date time stamp (number of milli-seconds since January 1st 1970), and a file extension specified in the EB.FILE.UPLOAD.TYPE record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free form field for describing the upload.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.FILE.UPLOAD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field. If the file is uploaded by an EB.EXTERNAL.USER, then this field will be set to the EB.EXTERNAL.USER ID on validate / commit. Otherwise will be blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOCHANGE field. Allows a file to be uploaded. Select the required file and click the upload button.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

