<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.GC.ACTIVE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Global Constraints Application definitions</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Defines behaviour of Global Constraints at application level.  Maps constraint key fields to application fields.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Key to record is the T24 APPLICATION which is being defined.</p>
            <p>   Will not allow a record to be created for an application which is specified in the EXCLUDE.APPS field of EB.GC.PARAMETER record for either the current company or the SYSTEM record.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key (or field in the application which contains the key) to the record which contains details of the account number related to this application.  See PORTFOLIO.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a field in the application being defined here or a valid key on the application specified in ACCOUNT.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.FLD.ASSOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where there is more than one CUSTOMER.FLD specified and the PORTFOLIO.FLD is linked to the CUSTOMER.FLD within the same multivalue set on the source application, this field should be set to 'CUSTOMER'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maps location of Customer field in application.  Can specify more than one customer where there are two sides of a transaction involving two separate customers, both of which may have constraints which apply to them.  Usually should only specify one.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field used to identify the customer for which this transaction is taking place (and therefore the customer for which the constraint processing should be performed).</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.  Mandatory if CUSTOMER.KEY specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi valued field that specifies the groups in EB.GC.GROUP of which this application is a member.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  System generated fields, maintained by EB.GC.GROUP.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>File which contains details of the account number related to this application.  See CURRENCY.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid T24 application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid API or local subroutine.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Routine overrides the default method of selection of constraint keys, therefore settings of METHOD, field associations, and PRECEDENCE fields (in EB.GC.PARAMETER) may not have the desired result when a selection routine is used, as they will not have any effect on processing of constraints when a SELECTION.ROUTINE is specified here beyond those explicitly coded within the SELECTION.ROUTINE itself.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.FLD.ASSOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where there is more than one CUSTOMER.FLD specified and the CURRENCY.FLD is linked to the CUSTOMER.FLD within the same multivalue set on the source application, this field should be set to 'CUSTOMER'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If set to 'CUSTOMER', both ACCT.FLD.ASSOC and PORT.FLD.ASSOC must also be set to 'CUSTOMER'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.DIAG.LIFE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sets diagnostic life at application level.  EB.GC.DIAGNOSTIC record produced when constraint breached will then be removed from system after this number of days has elapsed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Overrides setting of DIAG.LIFE at System or Company level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maps location of Portfolio field in application.  Can specify more than one Portfolio where necessary.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field used to identify the Portfolio in which this transaction is taking place (and therefore the Portfolio for which the constraint processing should be performed).</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.  Mandatory if PORTFOLIO.KEY specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VSET.LOOKUP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define lookup against a value pair.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This is the name of the index as recorded against a particular multivalue in the field 'Vset Data Field'.  This can then be referenced in the relevant EB.GC.CONSTRAINTS record by prefixing with 'V*'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the application contains two related fields, "CURRENCY" and "CCY.OVRAMT", and CURRENCY contains a list of currency codes and CCY.OVRAMT contains a list of amounts against each of those currencies and we want to get the value for USD, we would set VSET.LOOKUP.ID to "USD".  Using the argument V*CURRENCY within constraints setup (e.g. within EB.GC.GLOBAL and EB.GC.CONSTRAINTS) will return the instance of CCY.OVRAMT which corresponds to USD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.DATE.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maps location of transaction date field in application.  Used by constraints processing to determine date of transaction and therefore whether a particular constraint applies or not based upon validity dates of the constraint.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds details of any override messages previously generated against this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSTRAINT.COUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>System generated field showing the number of constraints which exist against this application for information purposes only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>File which contains details of the account number related to this application.  See PORTFOLIO.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid T24 application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.DIAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Controls diagnostics recording at application level.  If set to 'ON' and diagnostics recording is also enabled at company or system level and a constraint is breached, a record is created in EB.GC.DIAGNOSTIC giving details of constraint breach.  If set to 'OFF', no diagnostics recording will occur.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.PROCESSING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Controls Global Constraints processing at application level.  If set to 'YES' and also enabled at company or system level, record validation for this application will include Global Constraints processing.  If set to 'NO', constraints processing will not occur.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether only the most specific valid constraint (EB.GC.CONSTRAINT) found is processed or if all constraints are processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Constraints processing attempts to read constraints in a specific order as determined by the PRECEDENCE of the key fields, if COM.METHOD is 'SINGLE', the constraints processing ends when a valid constraint is found;  if COM.METHOD is 'CUMULATIVE', the constraints processing ends when all existing constraints have been processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If set to SINGLE, the constraints processing picks up the most specific constraint with respect to the record and application being processed, and if it is valid (in terms of FIRST.VALID.DATE and LAST.VALID.DATE), tests the record against the rules specified in the constraint, and does not process any further constraints.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If set to CUMULATIVE, all constraints which are valid are processed in turn, in each case testing the record against the rules specified in the constraint.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Overrides setting of METHOD at System or Company level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maps location of Currency field in application.  Can specify more than one currency where necessary.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field used to identify the currency in which this transaction is taking place (and therefore the currency for which the constraint processing should be performed).</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.  Mandatory if CURRENCY.KEY specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VSET.DATA.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define lookup against a value pair.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This defines the field on the application defined in EB.GC.ACTIVE which holds the lookup data for the value pair.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the application contains two related fields, "CURRENCY" and "CCY.OVRAMT", and CURRENCY contains a list of currency codes and CCY.OVRAMT contains a list of amounts against each of those currencies and we want to get the value for USD, we would set VSET.DATA.FIELD to "CCY.OVRAMT".  Using the argument V*CURRENCY within constraints setup (e.g. within EB.GC.GLOBAL and EB.GC.CONSTRAINTS) will return the instance of CCY.OVRAMT which corresponds to USD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VSET.LOOKUP.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define lookup against a value pair.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This defines the field on the application defined in EB.GC.ACTIVE which holds the lookup index for the value pair.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the application contains two related fields, "CURRENCY" and "CCY.OVRAMT", and CURRENCY contains a list of currency codes and CCY.OVRAMT contains a list of amounts against each of those currencies and we want to get the value for USD, we would set VSET.LOOKUP.FIELD to "CURRENCY".  Using the argument V*CURRENCY within constraints setup (e.g. within EB.GC.GLOBAL and EB.GC.CONSTRAINTS) will return the instance of CCY.OVRAMT which corresponds to USD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key (or field in the application which contains the key) to the record which contains details of the account number related to this application.  See CURRENCY.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a field in the application being defined here or a valid key on the application specified in ACCOUNT.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key (or field in the application which contains the key) to the record which contains details of the account number related to this application.  See CUSTOMER.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a field in the application being defined here or a valid key on the application specified in ACCOUNT.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>File which contains details of the account number related to this application.  See CUSTOMER.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid T24 application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>File which contains details of the account number related to this application.  See ACCOUNT.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid T24 application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maps location of Account field in application.  Can specify more than one Account where necessary.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field used to identify the Account for which this transaction is taking place (and therefore the Account for which the constraint processing should be performed).</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.  Mandatory if ACCOUNT.KEY specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key (or field in the application which contains the key) to the record which contains details of the account number related to this application.  See ACCOUNT.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a field in the application being defined here or a valid key on the application specified in ACCOUNT.FLD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.FLD.ASSOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where there is more than one CUSTOMER.FLD specified and the ACCOUNT.FLD is linked to the CUSTOMER.FLD within the same multivalue set on the source application, this field should be set to 'CUSTOMER'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If set to 'CUSTOMER', PORT.FLD.ASSOC must also be set to 'CUSTOMER'</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

