<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.GC.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Global Constraints Parameters.</p>
            <p />
            <p> These control the behaviour of Global Constraints processing across a whole company or when read at SYSTEM level, for all of T24.  Some settings within EB.GC.ACTIVE override these settings at application level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRECEDENCE.PORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Precedence order for portfolio restrictions. If precedence set to 1, portfolio type constraint records will take precedence over all those which are not portfolio-specific.  Takes precedence over other 'key fields' with lower precedence.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRECEDENCE.USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Precedence order for the current user. If precedence set to 1, user type constraint records will take precedence over all those which are not user-specific.  Takes precedence over other 'key fields' with lower precedence.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRECEDENCE.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Precedence order for account restrictions. If precedence set to 1, account type constraint records will take precedence over all those which are not account-specific.  Takes precedence over other 'key fields' with lower precedence.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.APPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>A Multi-Valued list of Applications to be excluded from constraints processing.</p>
            <p> Does not allow an EB.GC.ACTIVE record to be created for the specified application.</p>
            <p> If entered in the SYSTEM parameter record it applies to all companies.</p>
            <p> If entered into a Company specific parameter record it applies only to that company.</p>
            <p> Will not allow an application to be added if an EB.GC.ACTIVE record already exists for this application in a affected company.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRECEDENCE.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Precedence order for customer restrictions. If precedence set to 1, customer type constraint records will take precedence over all those which are not customer-specific.  Takes precedence over other 'key fields' with lower precedence.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRECEDENCE.CURR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Precedence order for currency restrictions. If precedence set to 1, currency type constraint records will take precedence over all those which are not currency-specific.  Takes precedence over other 'key fields' with lower precedence.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.DIAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Controls diagnostic recording at company or system level.  If set to 'YES', wherever diagnostics recording is also enabled at application level and a constraint is breached, a record is created in EB.GC.DIAGNOSTIC giving details of constraint breach.  If set to 'NO', no diagnostics recording will occur.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.DIAG.LIFE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sets diagnostic life at company or system level.  EB.GC.DIAGNOSTIC record produced when constraint breached will then be removed from system after this number of days has elapsed.</p>
            <p />
            <p> DIAG.LIFE can be overridden at application level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether only the most specific valid constraint (EB.GC.CONSTRAINT) found is processed or if all constraints are processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Constraints processing attempts to read constraints in a specific order as determined by the PRECEDENCE of the key fields, if COM.METHOD is 'SINGLE', the constraints processing ends when a valid constraint is found;  if COM.METHOD is 'CUMULATIVE', the constraints processing ends when all existing constraints have been processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p> If set to SINGLE, the constraints processing picks up the most specific constraint with respect to the record and application being processed, and if it is valid (in terms of FIRST.VALID.DATE and LAST.VALID.DATE), tests the record against the rules specified in the constraint, and does not process any further constraints.</p>
            <p />
            <p> If set to CUMULATIVE, all constraints which are valid are processed in turn, in each case testing the record against the rules specified in the constraint.</p>
            <p />
            <p> METHOD can be overridden at application level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.PROCESSING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Controls Global Constraints processing at company or system level.  If set to 'YES', whenever Global Constraints processing is also enabled at application level, validation of records will include Global Constraints processing.  If set to 'NO', no Global Constraints processing will occur.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

