<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.INTERNAL.SCORE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Loan origination process involves a step for calculating internal score. Generation of internal score for a applicant is optional. This table is used to store the information on the above mentioned transaction. The option for generating internal score, score being satisfactory or not, value of internal score, customer id and application form id gets stored here. The information on whether the user has opted to generate an internal score for a particular applicant can be retrived from this table.  </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INT.SCORE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value of the Internal score generated for a customer gets stored in this field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field. No Input field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>@ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>A unique reference number (starting with the letters ISA) which identifies a particular transaciton record. The id is auto-generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory input) </p>
            <p />
            <p>Once the transaction is authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.FORM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the Application form id of the loans (personal loan or mortgage loan or auto loan). It is any valid @ID of the the table EB.MORTGAGE.FORM1. A no input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the customer for whom scoring is done. No input field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be a valid record in CUSTOMER table.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.SCORE.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The option to generate internal score is to be given here. If selected as "Yes" the internal score card is generated.</p>
            <p>The field is also used to select the option as "Yes" or "No" on score being satisfactory. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only allowed values are YES and NO</p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>