<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.LENDING.HP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The Process Workflow for Limit enables the Credit Officer to start a process for Limit creation. After clicking on SETUP LIMIT the user has to input the basic details like customer number, secured limit (Y/N) etc in the initial screen. After creating the Limit, the process will move to the Credit Manager to authorize the Limit. Hence a pending activity for authorization of Limit will fall in the Manager's queue. Once the limit is authorized by the Credit Officer, the Workflow for the Officer will show the Create Collateral Right activity. This has to be input by the officer and then authorized by the Manager. Once the collateral right is authorized, the workflow queue of the Credit Officer will display "Create Collateral". This is then authorized by the Credit Manager and the Limit is thus created through Process Workflow. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OD.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Choose OD Limit Yes or No.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LD.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field  displays the type of loan contract which is to be entered into with the Customer.The various loan products available are Commitment, Loan(Corporate Loan), Drawdown of Commitment, Overdraft and Discounted Loan. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field "Limit Reference" displays the Limit Reference relevant to the product chosen by the user in the field Product. As there is no validation provided for this field, the user has to input the Limit Reference which is applicable for the product; for eg. if a Commitment Contract is chosen in the field "Product", then this field should have either the value of 6100 or 2100 only. This is a mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field "Customer" displays Customer Number which can be inputted by the user or chosen from the dropdown enquiry.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which limit will be effective.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>If Limit is required choose Yes, otherwise No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURED.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field "Secured Limit?" enables to user to choose either a Secured or an Unsecured Limit. This is a mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.TITLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Helptext not Available.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Helptext not Available.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AA.PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Helptext not Available.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AA.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Helptext not Available.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field "Account Number" is used to input the account number for which the Overdraft limit to be attached to. It is assumed that this account already exists in the system; hence the user cannot create a account using this single window. This is a mandatroy field if the Overdraft product is chosen and a noinput fields for all other products. The attach limit to account is an auto activity in the process workflow.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field "Currency" displays the currency of the loan contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>