<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.MESSAGE.CLASS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to classify S.W.I.F.T. message types into different message classes, e.g. CONFIRMATION, ADVICE and PAYMENT.</p>
            <p>The idea is to allow the users the flexibility to classify S.W.I.F.T. message types on the EB.ADVICES file and to control the production of the eventual messages on the main contract.</p>
            <p>For example, a contract amendment activity has been defined to produce a confirmation and a payment advice. If, for some reason, the production of the payment advice for a particular contract is to be suppressed, a user could say NO to send advice on that contract instead of changing the EB.ADVICES record to stop the payment advice and to change back afterward.</p>
            <p />
            <p><strong>NOTE</strong>
            </p>
            <p>Care must be taken when defining new message classes as record reversal is not allowed once authorised.</p>
            <p>T24 is released with 3 predefined message classes: CONFIRMATION, ADVICE and PAYMENT.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CLASS.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a system generated field and its value will be incremental. Its value is obtained, at authorisation, by adding one to the number of existing records.</p>
            <p>EB.MSG.CLASS.CONCAT file will be updated accordingly to allow applications using Soft Delivery (eg REPO) to determine the expansion of the multi-values of their SEND.NOTICE field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the description for this message class</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Freetext</p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID that uniquely identifies the message class. It is normally the name of a message that will be produced. (ie Confirmation, Advice, Payment)</p>
            <p>Care must be taken in defining a message class. Because once it is defined it cannot be removed from the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Freetext</p>
            <p>Up to 15 upper case characters (A-Z)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

