<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.MANDATE.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>EB.MANDATE.PARAMETER contain information on the location of amount field, customer field to be looked up 

for every application.  While processing the mandates, the customer /account/date for the processing will be taken from 

these fields in the application.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field name in this field indicates which value date field in that particular transaction  is used for 

ascertaining which mandate is to</p>
            <p> be processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1. Cannot be a LOCAL reference field.</p>
            <p> 2. Field to be Date field. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field name in this field indicates which currency  field in that particular transaction  is used for 

ascertaining which mandate is </p>
            <p> to be processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1. Cannot be a LOCAL reference field.</p>
            <p> 2. Field to be Currency field. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field name in this field indicates which amount  field in that particular transaction  is used for 

ascertaining which mandate is to</p>
            <p> be processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1. Cannot be a LOCAL reference field.</p>
            <p> 2. Field  to be amount field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the description of the EB.MANDATE.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> 2. Upto 35 characters.</p>
            <p> 3. Language Multi value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANDATE.PARAM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any T24 Application.</p>
            <p>  Mandate processing can be linked to any financial or non-financial applications.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MANDATE.FIELD</field>
<desc>
<p>Hard-Coded set of identifiers used across all applications to retrieve appropriate field name location from ID 

application</p>
<p>Validation Rules:</p>
<p> Allowed Values: ACCOUNT, AMOUNT, CURRENCY, CUSTOMER and VALUE.DATE </p>
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>APPL.FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the field location for the field identifier.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
            <p>
                 <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1. Should be a valid field name in the application for which the Mandate record is created.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
	
<t>
<field>EXTRACT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the way to extract value  reference for MANDATE.FIELD from the application</p>
            <p>It holds 3 formats: 1. An API name where the values can be returned from transaction during run time 

transaction processing and a field cannot be defined upfront </p>
            <p> 2. Parameter 1 can be a character for a field delimiter, with the second parameter being the field number. 

E.g - *,1</p>
            <p> 3. Parameter 1 can be numeric for the character start position, with the second parameter being the number 

of characters to return. E.g - 1,2 </p>
            <p />
            <p>
            <p>
                 <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1. Only a valid API defined in EB.API application can be attached here.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MANDATE.RULE.API</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MANDATE.RULE.GATEWAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RAISE.ALERT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if alerts should be raised to pending Signatories using Business events.</p>       
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p> Defaulted to YES, if required can be set to NO</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

</menu>
</t24help>

