<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.MANDATE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>EB.MANDATE will contain information on the signatory groups required for</p>
            <p>     authorisation of transactions within a given range. This will also specify the minimum signatories required for a particular transaction for the specified amount and currency involving  the same customer. </p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>UP.TO.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount formatted for the currency specified. This field defines the mandate processing based on Financial transaction.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGNATORY.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid Signatory Group belonging to this Customer.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1. Mandatory field when UP.TO.AMOUNT is present</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the Mandate.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     1. Multi value language field.</p>
            <p>     2. Mandatory.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency used in this mandate for amounts.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Need not be same as related account currency(s). </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1. Mandatory field when UP.TO.AMOUNT is defined.</p>
            <p>      2. Should be valid currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANDATE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid T24 Customer followed by a valid bank date. Date cannot be backdated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.NO.SIGNATORIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Minimum number of signatories required for the SIGNATORY.GROUP</p>
            <p />
            <p>     A valid number that can be 1 to 9</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1. Mandatory field when SIGNATORY.GROUP is defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MANDATE.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to provide the rule for non-financial transaction, for identified related signatory groups and Minimum number of signatories </p>
            <p>Currently allowed value is DEFAULT</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1. Mandatory when UP.TO.AMOUNT is not defined and used to process the non-financial transactions.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RULE.SIGN.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid Signatory Group belonging to this Customer for the rule defined in MANDATE.RULE field</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>            
            <p />
            <p>     1. Mandatory when MANDATE.RULE is defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RULE.MIN.NO.SIGN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Minimum number of signatories required for the rule defined in MANDATE.RULE field</p>
            <p />
            <p>     A valid number that can be 1 to 9</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1. Mandatory when RULE.SIGN.GROUP is defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>BNK.APPR.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to attach local hook routine to the mandates to check additional conditions or otherwise banks approval. When the hook routine is successful, then the transaction remains in INAO and an override message is thrown. The AUTHORISER field of such transaction will be appended with a key word '_SIGCOMPLETED' to identify such records. These transactions can be authorized by a T24 user with appropriate rights for that override.</p>
            <p>The hook routine should contain one single return argument and should return value as 2, if the bank's approval is required. </p>
            <p />
            <p> A valid local routine </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1. Should be a valid record in EB.API application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>RULE.RESERVED.2</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>RULE.RESERVED.1</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
