<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is new generalized and enhanced mapping mechanism and this uses EB.FORMAT.ENTRY to do the actual mapping. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    This mapping technique can do the following types of mapping:</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Universal ID &amp; field mapping – mapping ID’s to fields, fields to record ID’s and ID’s across to other ID fields</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Wider manipulation of data – the ability to concatenate  field data , use of literals to define fixed mapping data in the set up tables, and added mapping commands to map, company ID’s Reference ID’s, today’s data and Time. </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Ability to map field data in to the first PW.ACTIVITY in the workflow and ability to map all symbol characters. (e.g.!,”,$,%,^,&amp;,*)</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Using routines- routines can be attached to the workflow to define data that can be mapped</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Local reference mapping - to local reference fields, from reference fields and to other reference fields</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Mathematical operator’s can be used to perform calculations and map the results directly in to fields (addition, subtraction, multiplication, division)</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Mapping from $NAU files</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ID.EB.FMT.ENT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>           EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>           ID.EB.FMT.ENT</p>
            <p />
            <p>           This field holds the link to EB.FORMAT.ENTRY which does the actual ID mapping.</p>
            <p>             Validations</p>
            <p>           1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>           2. A valid key of EB.FORMAT.ENTRY.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.SRC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>           EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>           ID.SRC.TYPE</p>
            <p />
            <p>           This field specifies from where we should get the source data for ID mapping.</p>
            <p />
            <p>           Validations</p>
            <p>           1. Mandatory field</p>
            <p>           2. Valid values are:</p>
            <p>           1. PW.ACTIVITY </p>
            <p>           Uses the common variable PW$ACTIVITY.TXN and reads the source record based on the values in TARGET &amp; TRANS.REF in PW.ACTIVITY.TXN. The name of the PW.ACTIVITY is specified in the field ID.DATA.SRC.</p>
            <p>           2. ROUTINE</p>
            <p>           This means that a user routine is attached to the field ID.DATA.SRC and the routine will return the source data for mapping.</p>
            <p>           3. NONE</p>
            <p>           This denotes that there is no source data for mapping and we are going to map only constants and literals into the Target application.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAPPING.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>            EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>            MAPPING.NAME</p>
            <p />
            <p>            This is the @ID of this template. </p>
            <p />
            <p>            This should be a meaning-full name which should indicate the mapping it is going to do</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Validations</p>
            <p />
            <p>            1.A maximum of 35 alpha-numeric characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TABLE.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>           EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>           TABLE.TO </p>
            <p>           This field holds the target application name i.e. the application to which the fields need to be mapped.</p>
            <p>           The  field.no of the fields mentioned in EB.FORMAT.ENTRY is obtained based on the Application name specified in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>           Validations</p>
            <p>           1. Mandatory field</p>
            <p>           2. A valid T24 application name</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>            EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>            SHORT.DESC</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Descriptive information on the mapping to be done</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Validations</p>
            <p>            1.  Mandatory field</p>
            <p>            2. A maximum of 35 characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOG.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>          EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>          LOG.LEVEL</p>
            <p />
            <p>          This field specifies how the SYSTEM should proceed on encountering a mapping error.</p>
            <p />
            <p>          Validations</p>
            <p>          This field can take the following values:</p>
            <p>          1. LOG – Raise an EXCEPTION &amp; proceed.</p>
            <p>          2. BLOCK – Raise an EXCEPTION and stop the SYSTEM from proceeding by throwing the error message.</p>
            <p>          3. No value or NULL – Do not log an exception nor stop the transaction. Just proceed.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLD.DATA.SRC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>          EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>          FLD.DATA.SRC</p>
            <p>          This field holds data according to the value specified in the FLD.SRC.TYPE. </p>
            <p>          The field FLD.SRC.TYPE provides the source data type for FIELD mapping and this field has the exact source based on the source type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Validations</p>
            <p>          This field can take the following values:</p>
            <p>          1. If FLD.SRC.TYPE is ‘PW.ACTIVITY’ then this field can hold a PW.ACTIVITY ID or literal ‘CUSTOMER’. If the value ‘CUSTOMER’ is specified then the FIELD mapping source data is obtained from the Customer.no mentioned in the field CUSTOMER in PW.PROCESS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Also this field can hold a PW.ACTIVITY ID along with UNIQUE.NAME (for ex., CREATE.CUSTOMER.MYUNIQ where CREATE.CUSTOMER denotes the PW.ACTIVITY id and MYUNIQ denotes the UNIQUE.NAME attached to the PW.ACTIVITY). This way of definition is to enable the process at runtime to refer to the latest instance of the PW.ACTIVITY. This is required since there can be multiple instances of the PW.ACTIVITY due to the implementation of iteration patterns like Structured &amp; arbitrary loops.</p>
            <p>          2. If FLD.SRC.TYPE is ‘ROUTINE’ then @ROUTINE will be attached here.</p>
            <p>          (Need to define an EB.API record for the @ROUTINE)</p>
            <p>          4.If FLD.SRC.TYPE is ‘NONE’ then this field is left NULL</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLD.EB.FMT.ENT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>          EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>          FLD.EB.FMT.ENT</p>
            <p />
            <p>          This field holds the link to EB.FORMAT.ENTRY which does the actual FIELD mapping.</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Validations</p>
            <p>          1. Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>          2. A valid key of EB.FORMAT.ENTRY</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLD.SRC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>          EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>          FLD.SRC.TYPE</p>
            <p />
            <p>          This field is similar to ID.SRC.TYPE except that this field specifies from where we should get the source data for FIELD mapping.</p>
            <p />
            <p>          Validations</p>
            <p>          1. Mandatory field</p>
            <p>          2. Valid values are:</p>
            <p>          1. PW.ACTIVITY </p>
            <p>          Uses the common variable PW$ACTIVITY.TXN and reads the source record based on the values in TARGET &amp; TRANS.REF in PW.ACTIVITY.TXN. The name of the PW.ACTIVITY is specified in the field FLD.DATA.SRC.</p>
            <p>          2. ROUTINE</p>
            <p>          This means that a user routine is attached to the field FLD.DATA.SRC and the routine will return the source data for mapping.</p>
            <p>          3. NONE</p>
            <p>          This denotes that there is no source data for mapping and we are going to map only constants and literals into the Target application.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.DATA.SRC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>           EB.MAPPING.SOURCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>           ID.DATA.SRC</p>
            <p>           This field holds data according to the value specified in the ID.SRC.TYPE. </p>
            <p>           The field ID.SRC.TYPE says the source data type for ID mapping and this field has the exact source based on the source type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>             Validations</p>
            <p>           This field can take the following values:</p>
            <p>           1. If ID.SRC.TYPE is ‘PW.ACTIVITY’ then this field can hold a PW.ACTIVITY ID or literal ‘CUSTOMER’.This field can hold a PW.ACTIVITY ID with unique name if that activity is repeated in process. If the value ‘CUSTOMER’ is specified then the ID mapping source data is obtained from the Customer.no mentioned in the field CUSTOMER in PW.PROCESS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Also this field can hold a PW.ACTIVITY ID along with UNIQUE.NAME (for ex., CREATE.CUSTOMER.MYUNIQ where CREATE.CUSTOMER denotes the PW.ACTIVITY id and MYUNIQ denotes the UNIQUE.NAME attached to the PW.ACTIVITY). This way of definition is to enable the process at runtime to refer to the latest instance of the PW.ACTIVITY. This is required since there can be multiple instances of the PW.ACTIVITY due to the implementation of iteration patterns like Structured &amp; arbitrary loops.</p>
            <p>           2. If ID.SRC.TYPE is ‘ROUTINE’ then @ROUTINE will be attached here.</p>
            <p>           (Need to define an EB.API record for the @ROUTINE)</p>
            <p>           3. If ID.SRC.TYPE is ‘NONE’ then this field is left NULL</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

