<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.MODEL.DATA</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The application sets up model data input for any </p>
            <p>T24</p> application. This prevents repeating input that does not vary from record to record or saves standard input that is required periodically. It is associated with VERSION by means of subroutines.  <p>The sequence of events is.</p><p /><p>Have the administrator set up a VERSION record that will         use EB.MODEL.DATA.</p><p>Start input to a new record in the application in which         you want to use the automatic inputs</p><p>Key only into the fields you want filled         automatically</p><p>Hold the record</p><p>Go to the EB.MODEL.DATA application and input a record         indicating the application and version you will be using.         Supply the record key of the record you just put on hold.         When you set REFRESH.DATA to "Y" then the field         names and values from the Held record will be         recorded the EB.MODEL.DATA record.</p><p>Authorise the EB.MODEL.DATA record.</p><p>You can now Delete the Held record.</p><p>The automatic input from the EB.MODEL.DATA record will be         applied when you input a new record to the         application via the VERSION.</p><p>There are two routines that can be attached to a VERSION to incorporate data. One uses the data it finds in the EB.MODEL.DATA with the same ID as the VERSION. The other routine prompts the user for the name of an EB.MODEL.DATA record containing the input.</p><p /><p /></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The VERSION record you intend to be used when this model data is to be copied into the record.</p>
            <p>It may be left blank to permit use with any VERSION in the target application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid VERSION record ID for the target application or         blank</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTI.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Occurence of the field within the target application. The field must be generated via GET.SOURCE. Any input will be ignored.</p>
            <p>There may be fields in the source record which contain data which you do not want copied into each input record. This may be unavoidable when fields such as the current date are completed automatically by the target application. EB.MODEL.DATA allows you to delete copied data fields but not to make any other changes to them.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any input will be ignored.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GET.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When "Y" is entered in this field then the data contents are generated from the source record. The field is then set back to "N".</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Y is the only valid input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub-occurrence sub-valued field in target application. The field must be generated via GET.SOURCE. Any input will be ignored.</p>
            <p>There may be fields in the source record which contain data which you do not want copied into each input record. This may be unavoidable when fields such as the current date are completed automatically by the target application. EB.MODEL.DATA allows you to delete copied data fields but not to make any other changes to them.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any input will be ignored.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODEL.SOURCE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key of a <strong>Held</strong> record in the target application. It is from this record that the model data will be generated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The key of a record on HOLD in the target application.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field name for data within the target application. The field must be generated via GET.SOURCE. Any input will be ignored.</p>
            <p>There may be fields in the source record which contain data which you do not want copied into each input record. This may be unavoidable when fields such as the current date are completed automatically by the target application. EB.MODEL.DATA allows you to delete copied data fields but not to make any other changes to them.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any input will be ignored.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.MULTI.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is application in which you intend to use model data</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid T24 application</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTENTS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field name for data within the target application. The field must be generated via GET.SOURCE. Any input will be ignored.</p>
            <p>There may be fields in the source record which contain data which you do not want copied into each input record. This may be unavoidable when fields such as the current date are completed automatically by the target application. EB.MODEL.DATA allows you to delete copied data fields but not to make any other changes to them.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any input will be ignored.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A multi-language field for description.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Text</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.MODEL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>To use the model data automatically with a particular VERSION then enter the ID of the VERSION record which will use it. (Use @EB.MODEL.FILL in the VERSION record). The application and version fields in the record will be completed automatically in this case.</p>
            <p>For model data that you can select at input of a new record use any name which is not a VERSION record. (In this case use @EB.MODEL.SELECT in the VERSION record)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

