<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.OBJECT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>IN2.LIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>This field holds a list of all IN2 routines related to the Application (e.g. ACCOUNT, CUSTOMER). </p>
                <p>This acts as a link field to get the id for EB.ALTERNATE.KEY, while an alternate key is used as a field input.</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Multi-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Input is the maximum number of Characters to be used as an ACCOUNT ID. </p>
            <p>This field is also used for Alternate Key processing for SECTOR and INDUSTRY applications.</p>
            <p>Maximum length of alternate key for SECTOR, INDUSTRY should be specified here.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The SECTOR and INDUSTRY fields in applications will get resized to the length specified here.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This can be of any length irrespective of the current key field length defined in the application program.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This will allow the actual alternate value input to be accepted by the lowest level validation routines.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Alternate key max length for ACCOUNT, CUSTOMER will be referred from ALT.KEY.MAX.LENGTH field in EB.ALTERNATE.KEY.</p>
            <p>Used for formatting purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None, but should be less than 26.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OBJECT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of the EB.OBJECT record. </p>
            <p>Validation Rule:</p>
            <p>Any alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>VAL.ROUTINE</p>
            <p />
            <p>Locally developed routine to perform additional validation &amp; to apply particular</p>
            <p>format to the key structure.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must exist on the PGM.FILE as a type S program</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.KEY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to get the EB.ALTERNATE.KEY id during field input of alternate keys. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHECKFILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The checkfile to be used for this object. This field is for future development.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 to 35 type A (alphanumeric) character field</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the FILE.CONTROL table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the EB.OBJECT code and is used to provide the enrichment of the code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 to 35 type A (Alphanumeric) character field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENRI.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the field to be used as the enrichment field. This is for future development.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 to 35 type A (alphanumeric) character field</p>
            <p>The value entered, must be a valid field on the STANDARD.SELECTION record of the checkfile</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

