<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.PHANTOM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>A generic application program within T24 which controls all phantom and interactive jobs including the T24 Transaction Server and ATM interface. </p>
            <p>This program sets up all common logic required for all phantom/interactive jobs. Processing is handled by the RUN.ROUTINE, which may be a standard product for example: </p>
            <p>GTS.CLIENT         - required to run GTS ATM.CONTROL.USW    - U/Switchware ATM interface </p>
            <p>or may be a regional/site specific routine. </p>
            <p>The RUN.ROUTINE must handle the starting and stopping correctly whether run interactively or as a background process. A Phantom process is stopped by entering STOP in the PHANT.STOP.REQ field. </p>
            <p>The application allows information to be passed to the run routine via the fields RUN.PARAM and RUN.VALUE. RUN.PARAM allows an indicator recognised by the RUN.ROUTINE to be supplied, the associated value is passed in the RUN.VALUE. Product documentation should identify valid options. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the logic that will be invoked when the phantom is spawned. This could be a 'site-specific' routine that will be performed as background job when run in PHANTOM mode, or online when run in INTERACTIVE mode. </p>
            <p>GTS === For GTS system processing the routine specified should be GTS.CLIENT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-30 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIMEOUT.SECS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the time that will elapse before terminating a read from an input file. If no data is read from the an elected input file in the specified time frame the process will stop, reporting that it encountered a time out. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Input is mandatory if an IN.FILE or OUT.FILE is used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SLEEP.SECS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the amount of time that the process will sleep.  Once the input directory has been cleared the process will sleep for a specified number of seconds before polling for input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the mode that will be used to invoke the process. </p>
            <p>'I'nteractive - Process will run from the current terminal session. </p>
            <p>'P'hantom - Process will run as a background phantom. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 type A (alpha) character of the form : I or P.         (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.OUT.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the UNIX path name of the output directory. </p>
            <p>This directory will contain the files that have been processed by the PHANTOM process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.OUT.PIPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the UNIX character special file that will be used to send data from the phantom process executed by T24. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>../bnk.data/gtconfig/pipes/out </p>
            <p>N.B. It is strongly recommended that a naming convention is established      for both Pipes and Directories before starting system configuration. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.IN.DIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 43 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the activity status of the process. </p>
            <p>'Active'  - Process running.             A phantom process can be halted by entering 'S' in the field             PHANT.STOP.REQ. </p>
            <p>'Closed'  - Process inactive. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Display only)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.OUT.DIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 43 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.RES2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the run status of the phantom process. </p>
            <p>This field will identify error conditions encountered during processing. </p>
            <p>During routine phantom execution this field will contain the text 'Running' and may also contain additional information such as the number of records processed. Further details should be available in the user guide for the RUN.ROUTINE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field. (Display only)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines a fixed value associated with a value in the RUN.VALUE field. </p>
            <p>These associated fields are used to supply values and constants used by the RUN.ROUTINE in order to control processing options. </p>
            <p>The application user guide should provide a list of valid options for that RUN.ROUTINE. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.IN.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the UNIX path name of the input directory. All files in this directory will be elected for input. </p>
            <p>Input directories are only required when the process to be run as a phantom uses a directory to handle incoming information. </p>
            <p>GTS === Files will ONLY be processed by the GTS module if the final record in a file contains the letter 'T' indicating that the file is complete. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional  input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.RES1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PHANT.STOP.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that a request to halt the phantom or interactive process is required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid input : 'STOP' - Stop phantom  (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Stop is only allowed in INPUT mode when the status is ACTIVE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFS.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is applicable to only OFS processing.</p>
            <p>The key of a record in OFS.SOURCE which defines the required OFS processing parameters is entered here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The key of an OFS.SOURCE record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBUS.IN.PIPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the UNIX character special file that will be used to transmit data to the phantom process executed by T24. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>../bnk.data/gtconfig/pipes/in </p>
            <p>N.B. It is strongly recommended that a naming convention is established      for both Pipes and Directories before starting system configuration. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PHANTOM.PID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the UNIX process identifier assigned by the operating system when the background process is spawned. </p>
            <p>The number stored here can be used to investigate the process status from UNIX. </p>
            <p>Defines the port number of the phantom process if database is jBASE , The number can be used to check the the process status by executing the command WHERE &lt;PORT&gt; from jshell. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p />
            <p>jsh jGLOBUS </p>
            <p> --&gt;WHERE 10000</p>
            <p>output</p>
            <p> Port      Device    Account      PID       Command</p>
            <p>10000      tty       jGLOBUS     79582     jsh -Jb -c EX EB.PHANTOM.PH GTUSER OFS.TEST</p>
            <p>                                       184870   EX EB.PHANTOM.PH GTUSER OFS.TEST</p>
            <p>                                       105598   EB.PHANTOM.PH OFS.TEST</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Display only)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Together with RUN.PARAM, this field identifies options and constant values used to control the operation of the RUN.ROUTINE. The value in this field is associated with the RUN.PARAM. </p>
            <p>Documentation for the specific function of the RUN.ROUTINE should explain valid RUN.PARAM options and possible settings. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GTS.USER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the T24 user used to complete audit fields when running GTS. </p>
            <p>This code is written for audit trail purposes in all records which are Input, Changed or Authorised by this process. </p>
            <p>The T24 user this id refers to should be set-up exclusively for this process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-16 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters.  Must exist in the USER application (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.SHUTDOWN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the system should attempt to automatically shut down the EB.PHANTOM process prior to running the batch.</p>
            <p>If this field is set to Y the system will try to close the phantom process if the STATUS is ACTIVE. If the process cannot be closed the system cannot run the end of day. In order to correct this situation the operator should determine whether the process is actually ACTIVE, if not the STATUS flag should be reset manually.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field, valid value Y.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.STARTUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the process should be automatically started on completion of the batch process.</p>
            <p>Any process with this field set to Y and RUN.MODE set to INTERACTIVE will be restarted when the system is set back to on-line status. All processes can also be restarted by running RESTART.EB.PHANTOM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input, valid input Y</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the function of this phantom process. </p>
            <p>Descriptions may be entered in each of the languages defined in the LANGUAGE table. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.PHANT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique identifier for the EB.PHANTOM record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-30 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

