<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.PRODUCT.INFO</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application records common characteristics of Loan Product Types. The basic conditions to be eligible for a particular loan is defined here. </p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LTV</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the minimum Loan to Value ratio for mortgage loan.  The ratio is calculated as  Loan Amount/Property Value*100. No input field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LTV.SECOND.AUTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>A certain LTV percentage beyond which the process has to go for the second approval can be defined here. Validation rules:Max 5 digits allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LTV.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Upper LTV limit for the particular product can be mentioned here. Validation rules:Max 5 digits allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of product, which can be listed as drop down. (Ex: PERSONAL.LOAN, ,MORTGAGE, VEHICLE.LOAN)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the minimum GDS value required for a loan product. The description on GDS is given in EB.MORTGAGE.FORM1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUATION.FEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the valuation fee to be colleced for the property valuation, should be in amount format Validation rules:Max 10 digits allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum permissible amount for the loan. Loan amount cannot be more than the maximum amount specified. Validation rules:Max 10 digits allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIN.DOCS.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the documents to be printed for Final approval</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.TERM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the minimum permissible term for the loan. Loan term cannot be lesser than the minimum term specified. Validation rules:Max 5 digits allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the minimum permissible amount for the loan. Loan amount cannot be less than the minimum amount specified. Validation rules:Max 10 digits allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the minimum TDS value required for a loan product. The description on TDS is given in EB.MORTGAGE.FORM1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.TERM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum permissible term for the loan. Loan term cannot be more than the maximum term specified. Validation rules:Max 5 digits allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>@ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference for each type of product in free format text.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Alphanumeric characters. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AIP.DOCS.REQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the documents to be printed for inprinciple approval</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT.FEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the arrangement fee for a loan disbursal, should be in amount format Validation rules:Max 10 digits allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This contains the description of the Product that is getting created</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>