<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.RULES.VERSION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the text of the rule that is passed across.  This will be written out by the Gui and passed to the rules engine for compilation.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
  Text box within T24.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
  This will be encoded when saved to the database.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.VAR.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description about the rule Variables used in this version of the rule</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the version, so the user would be able to explain the reason why a new version is required.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NESTED.RULES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rules used to determine this rule. Will be a valid existing rule.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>XML</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rule as understood by the Rule processor and engine. Used in the Rule engine to process a rule.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.VARS</field>
<desc>
            <p>T24 System variables populated when T24 is running.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.VAR.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the T24 System variables.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains details of any overrides</p>
            <p>Maximum of 35 characters allowed</p>
            <p>System updated field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.VARS</field>
<desc>
            <p>User defined variables within each rule, to be used solely for that rule.  Simplifies rule definition.  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.USED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rules that are used for this record.  Written to this record when a rule is referenced from the GUI.  Must be a valid rule Id.  If a date suffix is applied, this indicates that this specific version of the rule must always be applied.  No suffix indicates that the latest rule must always be applied.  No alphanumeric (testing purposes) suffixes may be applied.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the contexts which are required for this rule to work</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTEXT.VARS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Primary table fields used on this rule.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTXT.VAR.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Descriptions of the fields from the Primary table that the context is based on.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.RULES.VERSION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique identifier of rule version.  ID consists of an EB.RULE followed by a date.  Once this record has been committed (through the Rules Gui) this will update EB.RULES with this new version.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
   There is also the option of entering an alphanumeric working suffix.  This is for rule testing purposes only rules with correct suffixes (a date/numeric counter) will be copied into the EB.RULES table</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

