<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.ROUNDING.RULE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows a rounding rule to be set at application level instead of the currency level.  This rounding rule ignores the one defined at the currency level provided a rounding rule has been defined for the calling application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The rounding rule id  in the application record is the key to the EB.ROUNDING.RULE   to be used. i.e.Any transaction from an application  which  has a defined rounding rule, will use the rounding as set up here, irrespective of the currency of the transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Note only the two settings below will overrule the rounding definition at the currency level are:</p>
            <p>ROUNDING.TYPE :   this will ignore the definition in the fields MIN.ROUND.TYPE and CASH.ROUND.TYPE in the  Currency record.</p>
            <p>USE.MIN.UNIT: It will indicate whether the MIN.ROUND.AMOUNT defined in the currency will be used.</p>
            <p>Otherwise the rest of the rounding definition is used from the Currency record</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This defines the types of rounding that are used by the rounding rule.</p>
            <p>This overrules the setting under MIN.ROUND.TYPE and CASH.ROUND.TYPE in the Currency record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The possible values are: 1, 2, 3, CURRENCY and NONE</p>
            <p />
            <p>Depending on how USE.MIN.UNIT is set, either the NO.OF.DECIMAL.PLACES or MIN.ROUND.AMOUNT from the Currency record is used for the following round types:</p>
            <p>If set to ‘1’, then the natural rounding applies</p>
            <p>If set to ‘2’, then rounding down applies</p>
            <p>If set to ‘3’, then rounding up applies</p>
            <p>However if set  to ‘NONE’ , then a natural rounding to decimal places is applied.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If  set to ‘CURRENCY’ then, the rounding rule as defined at the Currency level is applied and the rest of the definition in the rounding rule is ignored.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.MIN.UNIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This defines whether the minimum amount, or the lowest unit of currency, is to be used when rounding is in effect for the currency.</p>
            <p>This field is intended for use when the minimum rounding amount is not always the same as the lowest unit of currency defined by NO.OF.DECIMALS.</p>
            <p>Rounding of amounts to this minimum unit is performed according to whatever choice dictated in the ROUNDING.TYPE</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>·   The Possible values are (blank, ‘Y’ or ‘NO)</p>
            <p>·   If  this field is  blank or set to ‘NO’, then the number of decimals set at Currency level will be used.</p>
            <p>If set to ‘Y’, then  if a MIN.ROUND.AMOUNT is set at the Currency level , this is used, otherwise the number of decimals at the Currency level is used</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.TO.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Setup to do a pre rounding of 6 Decimal points before applying actual rounding rule.  Setting this field to NO will make the system to apply rounding for the Actual amount without applying any pre rounding.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p> Valid inputs are NO or Blank. </p>
            <p> Default is Blank which will apply the initial rounding of 6 Decimal points. </p>
            </p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This describes the Rounding rule.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>·  Mandatory field</p>
            <p />
            <p>·  Minimum of 3 characters and Up to  20 characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>An alphanumeric value of minimum 3 characters and maximum of  35 characters for the ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

