<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.SECURE.MESSAGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is developed to establish a secure messaging system in a bank.</p>
            <p>   It helps to post messages between bank user to customer. It provides a facility to define messages </p>
            <p>   and updated with a status for each messages that has been posted.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies Message from / to the customer.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   TEXT field. This field contains body of the messge. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.SENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies time when the message is sent.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Noinput field. This field will be updated when the message is authorised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies status of the message. Default is UNREAD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      It has two options. They are UNREAD and READ.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARENT.MESSAGE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the record ID of parent message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUBJECT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the subject of the message to be sent or received.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.DAO</field>
<desc>
            <p>  Must be a valid record id on department account officer table. Account Offcier to which  the message to be sent.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    For external user, list of allowed DAO for messageing will be populated in this field.Otherwise, it is noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>It holds the record key of EB.SECURE.MESSAGE. System generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must be a valid record id on customer table. Customer to which the message to be sent.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Noinput field if the message is triggered from external user.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies status of the received message. Default is SENT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      It has two options. They are SENT and UNSENT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.READ</field>
<desc>
            <p>It holds date when the message is read.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Noinput field. This field will be updated when the message is read by the receiver.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.SENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the date when the message is sent.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Noinput field. This field will be updated when the message is authorised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input must be a valid record id on customer table. Customer from which the message is triggered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Noinput field. External customer id will be populated for external users.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.DAO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must be a valid record id on department account officer table. Account Offcier from which the message is triggered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      DEPARTMENT.CODE on USER record will be populated if the message is triggered from internal users.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the Image id when the upload attachment is required.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      NoInput field. The record id of the IM.DOCUMENT.IMAGE record which the file being uploaded will be linked to.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.UPLOAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field uses a file browser to locate and display the file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      The field uses a file browser to locate and display the file.When the link button is clicked the file is both renamed and then downloaded to the storage path specified in the IM.DOCUMENT.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

