<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
	<header>
		<product>EB</product>
		<table>EB.SWITCH.PARAMETER</table>
	</header>
	<overview>
		<ovdesc>
			<p>This table is used to enable dynamic switching of a Version, Enquiry, Composite Screen, Tabbed Screen or user Menu
				based on some predefined criteria </p>
			<p />
			<p> The ID format should be a valid ID from one of the following applications:</p>
			<p> - VERSION </p>
			<p> - ENQUIRY </p>
			<p> - EB.TABBED.SCREEN </p>
			<p> - EB.COMPOSITE.SCREEN </p>
			<p> - HELPTEXT.MENU</p>
			<p />
			<p>The ID may also have an optional valid Region or Country code appended, separated with a hyphen character to
				determine if the switch is specific to that region or country.</p>
			<p />
			<p>As the ID determines whether the switching is for a Version, Enquiry, Tabbed Screen, Composite Screen or user
				Menu, only the corresponding switch field can be used for that record.
			</p>
			<p />
			<p>Using the contents of this table, T24 will determine whether to switch a given Version, Enquiry, Composite Screen,
				Tabbed Screen or user Menu with another.</p>
			<p />
			<p>NOTE - The switching defined in this parameter table is only triggered if there is NOT a routine defined in
				EB.DYNAMIC.ATTRIBUTES for the respective element.</p>
		</ovdesc>
		<ovimage></ovimage>
	</overview>
	<menu>
		<t>
			<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
			<desc>
				<p>Mandatory field that holds a description of the switch rule.</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>SWITCH.VERSION</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The name of the VERSION to be used instead of the one requested if the criteria are met. This MUST be a version
					of the same base application.</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>SWITCH.TAB</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The name of the EB.TABBED.SCREEN to be used instead of the one requested if the criteria are met.</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>SWITCH.MENU</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The name of the HELPTEXT.MENU to be used instead of the one requested if the criteria are met.</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>SWITCH.COS</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The name of the EB.COMPOSITE.SCREEN to be used instead of the one requested if the criteria are met.</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>SWITCH.ENQUIRY</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The name of the ENQUIRY to be used instead of the one requested if the criteria are met.</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>TABLE</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The table to use for defining criteria for switching. The available options are:</p>
				<p> - COMPANY</p>
				<p> - SPF</p>
				<p> - USER</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>FIELD</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The field to use for defining criteria for switching. The field must be a valid field in the TABLE chosen</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>OPERAND</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The operand to use for defining criteria for switching. The available options are:</p>
				<p> - EQ (Equal to)</p>
				<p> - NE (Not equal to)</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>DATA</field>
			<desc>
				<p>A value to be used for comparison in the criteria being defined for switching</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
		<t>
			<field>JOIN</field>
			<desc>
				<p>The join to use for joining multiple criteria for switching. The available options are:</p>
				<p> - AND</p>
				<p> - OR</p>
			</desc>
		</t>
	</menu>
</t24help>

