<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.STP.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used for defining the conditions to set up the automatic authorization that is required for selected transactions, based upon the amount or the (debit or credit) account, ETC. to allow STP. This is a new enhancement that is used for defining the various conditions based on which the transactions are allowed for STP (Straight Through Processing or automatic authorization). The ID for this Application should be a valid VERSION record or a VERSION.CONTROL record. If the original Application other than a version (like CUSTOMER, ACCOUNT, ETC.) should be entered as ID, it should have a VERSION.CONTROL record.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PGM.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the FIELD.NAME in the VERSION for which condition has to be set. The value entered here should be valid field name contained in the version record. Alternatively, a routine name can be specified here. The routine should have an entry in PGM.FILE and should have been compiled properly. The format of specifying a routine name is @ROUTIINE.NAME. The routine should have 1 variable name as the outgoing parameter. The value of this variable should be set to ‘1’ if the condition being checked in the routine is satisfied. The value should be NULL if the condition is not satisfied. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONDITION.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Start of the multi-value set, this is a no-input field. This field (after committing) shows the index number of conditions specified for a particular VERSION or VERSION.CONTROL record.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the OPERAND value (EQ, NE, LK, GT, GE, LE, LT, RG) which is applied to the mentioned in FIELD.NAME. Based on the value entered in this field, the condition check for the data will happen. If a routine name has been specified in the FIELD.NAME field, then the user will not be allowed to input any value in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value with which the field mentioned in FIELD.NAME is compared using the operand specified in the field DATA.COMP. If a routine name has been specified in the FIELD.NAME field, then the user will not be allowed to input any value in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> If RG (range) operand is specified in the DATA.COMP field, then value should be entered in this field. If specified, then the value entered in the field FIELD.NAME in version would be compared with values in the range DATA.FROM to DATA.TO. If a routine name has been specified in the FIELD.NAME field, then the user will not be allowed to input any value in this field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

