<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.TABLE.DEFINITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Application used to create dynamic templates</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FILE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the type of the file. The allowed values are FIN, CUS and INT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLD.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the product name of the T24.When this field contains any product value then the corresponding field will allowed to input only when the specified product being installed in the company which the user logged in.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1.Having the check file validation of EB.PRODUCT</p>
            <p>2.Non –Mandatory field </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VIRTUAL.TABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Virtual table that is used for EB.LOOKUP</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 alphanumeric characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Not a mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if VETTING.TABLE and APPLICATION.VET is not present.</p>
            <p>Field MAX.CHAR is mandatory when VIRTUAL.TABLE is present.</p>
            <p>If VIRTUAL.TABLE value is not present in any of the EB.LOOKUP record then this field will be the NOINPUT field </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.TO.WFL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using this field the user can define whether the application should be linked to the workflow. If the value of this field is set to NO, then the record in the application cannot be kept on HOLD after first input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default value that has to be chosen for this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the field that will be created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSERT.LAYOUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>We can specify the location of the insert file. Insert file for the dynamic template will be created under the directory name specified here.</p>
            <p>If there is no mentioned directory present then T24 will automatically create that directory and place the insert file under the directory.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1.Non –Mandatory field </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLD.PROPERTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether the field in the m/t set is NOINPUT/NOCHANGE can be specified in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.ACT.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the field defined in the activity</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.ENRICH.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field in the referred application that has to be used an enrichment for the current field in the m/v set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.CHAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum number of characters that can be allowed in the field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi valued field. Field name that contains the actual name of the fields that will be used to create the dynamic template. Should be unique within this record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VETTING.TABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Vetting table that is used for this field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NS.OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>NS.OPERATION field will determine if this application will allow entry / modification during the close of business</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field should allow only three input ALL,NEW and NOD</p>
            <p />
            <p>ALL - Application alows NS operation</p>
            <p>NEW - Application allows NS operation for NEW id’s only </p>
            <p>NOD - Can be run Non Stop without the NS module installed  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REL.CURRENCY.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to refer the currency field of the dynamic application, based on the currency MATURITY.DATE field forward the DATE from VALUE.DATE according to the holiday table of that country.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1.This field will accept the value only if the data type of the corresponding application having the value “MATURITY.DATE”</p>
            <p>2.Entered value should be present in the FIELD.NAME multi value set </p>
            <p>3.APPL.VET field of the corresponding field entered here should have a value “CURRENCY”</p>
            <p>4.Mandatory field if DATA.TYPE is “MATURITY.DATE”</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid product code. The template created will belong to this product and the template name will be prefixed with this product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds any one of the field name from the multi value set which field become an ID of the dynamic template. properties of that specified field is becomes the properties of the ID for dynamic template.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1.Corresponding field should accept the ALPHA, DATE, ALPHANUMERIC,NUMERIC and TEXT data types.</p>
            <p>2.should be valid name from the FIELD.NAME multi value set </p>
            <p>3.Non –Mandatory field </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.CHAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximum number of characters that can be allowed in the field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MASKING.FMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The data format of the field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ASSOC.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This specifies whether this field forms a single field/multi value field/sub value field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the field should be a CURRENCY type field, then the corresponding EB.TABLE.DEFINITION record should be mentioned here. The value in this field will be accepted only if APPL.VET is defined as CURRENCY and DATA.TYPE is set as AMOUNT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REL.DATE.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field used to relate the current field with other DATE field.(e.g; if the current field name is MATURITY.DATE then MATURITY.DATE field can relate with the other DATE type field VALUE.DATE in the same record ). When you enter (2M ,3W) etc in MATURITY.DATE of the dynamic application which will forward the date (2months or 3 weeks )which is specified in VALUE.DATE field. Date forwarding uses the field REL.CURRENCY.FIELD to refer the holiday table.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1.This field will accept the value only if the data type of the corresponding application having the value “MATURITY.DATE”</p>
            <p>2.Entered value should be present in the FIELD.NAME multi value set </p>
            <p>3.DATA.TYPE field of the corresponding field entered here should have a value “DATE”</p>
            <p>4.Mandatory field if DATA.TYPE is “MATURITY.DATE”</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREFIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The prefix needed to address all the fields defined in the dynamic application. Value entered here will become the prefix for this dynamic application with product. (e.g: if name given here is TEST and product is EB then prefix of the dynamic application becomes EB.TEST.fieldname).</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1.Field can accept alpha numeric values </p>
            <p>2.NOCHANGE field - can’t change the prefix of the insert file once the record being authorized </p>
            <p>3.Mandatory field </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.VET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Vetting application</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the relevant data type of this field. Valid values can be DATE TIME RATE ALPHA ALPHANUMERIC NUMERIC TEXT AMOUNT FREQUENCY </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This contains the description of the template that is getting created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field of the corresponding activity record whose attributes have to be copied to the current m/v set of this record. This field is located in the activity specified in the previous field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Activity code in EB.DYN.ACTIVITY. This field is used to specify that the current field in the m/v set should get its attributes from another field of a different activity. If this facility is used, the the current m/v set will not accept fresh attributes. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.SPECIAL.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>We can add the special fields like STMT.NO and DELIVERY.REF for the dynamic template</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1.Non –Mandatory field </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

