<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.TABBED.SCREEN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application defines the tabs that are displayed on a tabbed screen.</p>
            <p>A tabbed screen may be used to simply display separate enquiries/contracts in separate tabs as a way of saving space on a T24 Browser screen.</p>
            <p>However, tabbed screens can be used to link enquiries and contracts together as a form of workflow between tabs.  Data from one tab can be used in the next tab.  For example, once a user has selected a Customer in one tab they can look at the accounts for that Customer in the next tab.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TAB.TITLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The title of the current tab.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TABBED.SCREEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the Tabbed Screen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TITLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The title of the Tabbed Screen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>What is run to display the content.</p>
            <p>For example, an enquiry ACCOUNT-LIST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ARGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any arguments for the value defined in SOURCE.</p>
            <p>For example, if the CONTENT.TYPE is a UTILITY then the SOURCE field contains the routine name (e.g. OS.NEW.USER) and the SOURCE.ARGS field contains the argumaents to the routine (e.g. MENU).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of content in the current tab.</p>
            <p>This may be :-</p>
            <p>COS - a Composite Screen defined by EB.COMPSOITE.SCREEN</p>
            <p>ENQ - an Enquiry defined by ENQUIRY</p>
            <p>MENU - a Menu defined by HELPTEXT.MAINMENU</p>
            <p>TXN - an Contract screen of a T24 Application</p>
            <p>URL - a URL to an internal/external web site</p>
            <p>UTILITY - a T24 Utility Routine that returns XMl in a certain format</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of a field on the current tabs enquiry/contract whose contents will be copied over to the SELECT.TO field of another tab.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The destination field of an enquiry/contract used when copying content from the SELECT.FROM field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

