<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.USER.PROFILE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p> Security Management System uses the <b>EB.USER.PROFILE</b>application to control the access to T24.</p>
        <p> A User record must be created, for every person who is allowed to use T24, this contains:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> identification details and specifies precisely what information and facilities are available, </p>
            <p value="2">dates and times at which the system can be accessed and other information required for Security Management.  </p>
        </p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;">        Identification</p>
        <p> Identifying details for each User includes: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">a unique Sign           On Name</p>
            <p value="2">Secret Password </p>
            <p value="3">Name</p>
            <p value="4">Classification           (External customer or Internal employee of the           bank)</p>
            <p value="5">Company or Branch</p>
            <p value="6">Department</p>
        </p>
        <p> In addition, User preferences such as the Language in           which messages are displayed, can be           specified.</p>
        <p style="color: #000000;font-weight: bold;">    Permitted Times of Use</p>
        <p> Details specifying when each User can access the           system includes: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Start Date</p>
            <p value="2">End Date</p>
            <p value="3">Start Time</p>
            <p value="4">End           Time</p>
            <p value="5">the maximum time, during which the User can be           inactive without being Signed Off automatically.</p>
            <p value="6">the           number of unsuccessful attempts to Sign On allowed           before the Password is disabled.</p>
            <p value="7">the frequency with           which the Password must be changed and dates           between which the Password should be deactivated.</p>
        </p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;">        Permitted Activity</p>
        <p> For External Users, the customer(s) whose records           can be accessed, must specify the account           numbers.           The information and facilities that can           be accessed are specified at 4 levels: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">COMPANY           APPLICATION </p>
            <p value="2">(and VERSION)</p>
            <p value="3">FUNCTION</p>
            <p value="4">FIELD </p>
        </p>
        <p>     These levels enables to specify which record           belongs to which company and their access rights.</p>
        <p> Up to 999 combinations of Company, Application,           Function and Field are allowed.</p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;">     Activity Logging</p>
        <p> Security Violations are always recorded in the           PROTOCOL file. </p>
        <p>In addition, it is possible to record some or all permitted activities, in the user record, by           the selected Users.</p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;">  Local Elements</p>
        <p>  Additional data elements can be defined to suit the local           requirements  by using <b>LOCAL.TABLE</b>           and <b>LOCAL.REF.TABLE</b> as explained in the Utilities           Help Text.</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.OFF.LOG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether the record is written to the <b>PROTOCOL</b> file recording or not, every time the user <b>SIGNS.ON</b> or <b>SIGNS.OFF</b></p>
        <p><b>Note:</b>     Unsuccessful attempts to <b>SIGN.ON</b> are always logged,           regardless of the value in this field.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Y (Yes) or    N (NO)</p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAP.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the reference ID of an entry, in the <b>LDAP.PARAMETER</b>, that directs to the external identity store.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAP.DN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the external distinguish name (DN) of the external identity, that maps T24 user.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.ITEM</field>
<desc>
        <p>Consists of any commands, that are entered at the Desktop COMMAND line.</p>
        <p>A Multi-valued field checked during SIGN ON.</p>
        <p> Any command(s) that are found in this field during SIGN.ON are invoked one at a time.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.CLASS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the override class, the user can approve.</p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Format; 4 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p value="2"> Multi-valued field. </p>
            <p value="3">Optional input; default value = none.</p>
            <p value="4"> T24 override messages can be classified by means of <b>OVERRIDE.CLASS</b> table. </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEAD.PREF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is made obsolete and is not in use anymore.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.BOOK.BLOCK</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the list of companies, the user CANNOT access, for inter company accounting, in a multi branch system.</p>
        <p> Multi branch indicates that, MB product is installed and the term Multi Book can be used.</p>
        <p>Allows financial level data to store in the same database table of all the companies, but opposed to Multi Company, where the data is stored in a separate table for each company.</p>
        <p> Input to this field is disallowed when the field <b>OTH.BOOK.ACCESS</b> is input.</p>
        <p>Unlike multi company, a user, without signing in to the branches, can transact business with other branches, in a multi branch system.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">
                <p> First multi-valued field must      contain a valid company code or a valid <b>COMPANY.SMS.GROUP</b> key.</p>
            </p>
            <p value="2"> If the first field contains      a <b>COMPANY.SMS.GROUP</b> key, no further input can take place.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK</field>
<desc>
        <p>Identifies the dealer desk code applicable to the user being entered.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 2 alphanumeric characters in the range A-Z, a-z, plus 0-9</p>
            <p value="2"> Optional Input</p>
            <p value="3"> Must be an existing code on the <b>DEALER.DESK</b> table.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies in which format the dates are displayed for a user /       language. It takes inputs 1, 2, 3 and 4.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> (dd) (month) (year) </p>
            <p value="2">(DD)/(MM)/(YYYY) </p>
            <p value="3">(YYYY)/(MM)/(DD)</p>
            <p value="4">YYYYMMDD</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.OFF.ITEM</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the name of any BASIC subroutine that are entered.</p>
        <p> During the SIGN OFF process, any subroutines that are defined in this field is CALLED with one parameter. </p>
        <p>If the parameter returns with the values N, or NO, the SIGN OFF processes will be halted.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Any BASIC subroutine that must contain one parameter.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.ST.TIME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start of period or the log in time, the user can access the system, on a specific day, in the <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b> field.</p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;"> Note: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">
                <p>Always displayed with the format : .</p>
            </p>
            <p value="2">Can be two or more separate periods each day, for the user to access the system, e.g. morning and afternoon, but not during lunch time. </p>
            <p value="3">If 1 or 2 digit is entered, they correspond to minutes between midnight and 1 o clock in the morning.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  1-4       numeric characters with optional : , i.e. HHMM or HH:MM </p>
            <p value="2">
                <p> Input can be 0-2359 or 0000-2359 or 00:00-23:59</p>
            </p>
            <p value="3">Sub-valued field       associated with <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b> and <b>DAY.END.TIME</b> (Optional input)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SALT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.BOOK.ACCESS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the list of companies, the user CAN access, for inter company accounting, in a multi branch system.</p>
        <p> Multi branch indicates that, MB product is installed and the term Multi Book can be used.</p>
        <p>Allows financial level data to store the same database table of all the companies, but opposed to Multi Company, where the data is stored in a separate table for each company.</p>
        <p> Input to this field is disallowed when the field <b>OTH.BOOK.BLOCK</b> is input.</p>
        <p>Unlike multi company, a user, without signing in to the branches, can transact business with other branches, in a multi branch system.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> First multi-valued field must      contain a valid company code or a valid <b>COMPANY.SMS.GROUP</b> key.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.COMPARISON</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the type of comparison made between the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) and the values indicated in Fields 23 and 24.</p>
        <p> The meaning of the Inputs are as follows:           </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">EQ   Equal to           GE   Greater than or </p>
            <p value="2">Equal to           GT   Greater Than           LE   Less than or </p>
            <p value="3">Equal to           LT   Less Than           NE   Not Equal to           LK   Like           UL   Unlike</p>
        </p>
        <p> User can access the records, only if the contents of the field, indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) ,satisfies the conditions specified in Fields 22-24. </p>
        <p>For example see FIELD NO (Field 21).</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> EQ, GE, GT, LE, LT, NE, LK, UL or no input. </p>
            <p value="2">Multi-valued field associated with Fields 17-21, 23 and 24.</p>
            <p value="3">Mandatory input if FIELD NO (Field 21) is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.OUT.MINUTES</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the maximum time in minutes, the user can be inactive, without being Signed Off automatically.</p>
        <p> If <b>TIMEOUT.MODE</b> in SPF is not defined as <b>ACTIVE</b>, and if the user has signed on to the system, and is being inactive for longer time specified in this field,  the system will automatically SIGN.OFF. The  user needs to SIGN.ON again before continuing. </p>
        <p>The time count will be effective at all levels within T24. (In Classic - WAITING APPLICATION, AWAITING FUNCTION, AWAITING ID and AWAITING PAGE INSTRUCTIONS, and whenever the cursor is located in the ACTION line).</p>
        <p>During an input session, when the cursor is within the Data Section of the screen, the time count will not be initiated.</p>
        <p> If <b>TIMEOUT.MODE</b> is set to <b>ACTIVE</b> and when the transaction is not in the authorisation/validation phase, the system automatically signs off as an inactive user after this time. In the authorisation/validation phase the <b>AUTOLOG.TIME.MINS</b> period defined in SPF is used as the inactivity period.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-3 numeric characters. </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TO</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the end-range of values, with which the contents indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) are compared.</p>
        <p> 0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        <p> or        Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the           following way:</p>
        <p style="list-style-type: lower-roman;">
            <p value="1">      up to 30 characters (type ANY) must be a valid           entry on the <b>FILE.CONTROL</b> file, followed by,</p>
            <p value="2">      a (greater than) sign, followed by,</p>
            <p value="3">   up to 18 characters (type A) must be a valid           entry on the multi-value field <b>SYS.FIELD.NAME</b> on the           <b>STANDARD.SELECTION</b> record for the file specified in           (i).</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[  ]]><b>Note:</b>     The values input in this field and the previous field,          must be in agreement with the Format rules of the           element specified in Field 21.1. </p>
        <p> E.g. the           input in Field 21 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic -   a minimum input of 10 characters will be required in           this field.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> See details for format.</p>
            <p value="2"> Can input, only if the corresponding DATA COMPARISON (Field 22) contains EQ (Equal To) or NE (Not Equal To).</p>
            <p value="3">Must not be less than DATA FROM (Field 23)</p>
            <p value="4">
                <p>Multi-valued field associated with fields 17-23.</p>
            </p>
            <p value="5">
                <p> Optional input if Field 22 contains EQ or NE, otherwise not allowed.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.RTN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the routines, that are triggered, when the user successfully logs in.</p>
        <p>Specifies the name of any BASIC subroutine or a java class to input. </p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">The routines entered must have a record on the EB.API application.</p>
            <p value="2">
                <p>Multi-valued field.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies (when used together with Fields 22-24) precisely, which record can be accessed, that are specified in the corresponding <b>APPLICATION</b> (Field 18.)  </p>
        <p>A record can be accessed, only if the field indicated, has a value allowed in the corresponding Fields 22-24.</p>
        <p> 0-3 numeric characters.</p>
        <p> Or Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following way:</p>
        <p style="list-style-type: lower-roman;">
            <p value="1">Up to 30 characters (type ANY) must be a valid entry on the <b>FILE.CONTROL</b> file, followed by,</p>
            <p value="2"> A gt (greater than) sign, followed by,</p>
            <p value="3">Up to 18 characters (type A) must be a valid entry in the multi-value field <b>SYS.FIELD.NAME</b> or <b>USER.FIELD.NAME</b> on the <b>STANDARD.SELECTION</b> record for the file specified in (i).</p>
        </p>
        <p>E.g. FOREX COUNTERPARTY</p>
        <p> It is recommended that field names and not field numbers are specified. If field numbers are specified then when a file layout changes you will be forced to manually change all user profiles affected.</p>
        <p style="font-weight: normal;">E.g.1: </p>
        <p>To allow a User to See and List all Accounts records, but only Input (or change), Copy or Delete Accounts in pounds sterling.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 18.1 (APPLICATION) ACCOUNT</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 20.1 (FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 18.2 (APPLICATION) ACCOUNT</p>
            <p value="4">Field 20.2 (FUNCTION) I C D</p>
            <p value="5"> Field 21.2 (FIELD NO.) ACCOUNT&gt;CURRENCY (currency)</p>
            <p value="6"> Field 22.2 (DATA COMPARISON) EQ (equal)</p>
            <p value="7"> Field 23.2 (DATA FROM) GBP</p>
        </p>
        <p style="font-weight: normal;"> E.g.2:</p>
        <p>To allow a User access to Account records only if they have Currency equal GBP and Category not in the range 01-001 to 01-099.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 18.1 (APPLICATION) ACCOUNT</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 20.1 (FUNCTION) ALL</p>
            <p value="3">Field  21.1 (FIELD.NO) ACCOUNT&gt;CURRENCY (Currency)</p>
            <p value="4">Field  22.1 (DATA.COMPARISON) EQ (equal)</p>
            <p value="5">Field  23.1 (DATA.FROM) GBP</p>
            <p value="6">Field  18.2 (APPLICATION) ACCOUNT</p>
            <p value="7"> Field 20.2 (FUNCTION) ALL</p>
            <p value="8">Field  21.2 (FIELD.NO) ACCOUNT&gt;CATEGORY (Category)</p>
            <p value="9">Field  22.2 (DATA.COMPARISON) NE (not equal)</p>
            <p value="10">Field 23.2 (DATA.FROM) 01-001</p>
            <p value="11">Field  24.2 (DATA.TO) 01-099</p>
        </p>
        <p> E.g.3:</p>
        <p>To allow a User to Authorise Data Capture records, but only if they do not contain an override.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 18.1 (APPLICATION) DATA.CAPTURE</p>
            <p value="2">Field  20.1 (FUNCTION) A</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 21.1 (FIELD.NO) DATA.CAPTURE&gt;OVERRIDE (Override)</p>
            <p value="4"> Field 22.1 (DATA COMPARISON) LT (Less Than)</p>
            <p value="5">Field  23.1 (DATA.FROM) (lowest possible value)</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b> It is not possible to prevent a user from entering on override during input, but Authorization can be restricted, as above, to ensure that any overrides are checked by a more senior person is the lowest value a field can have, so specifying LT (Less Than)ensures that no override may be present.</p>
        <p> E.g.4:</p>
        <p>Restricting FOREX transactions to a counterparties that belong to a specific account officer.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 18.1 (APPLICATION) FOREX</p>
            <p value="2">Field  20.1 (FUNCTION) I</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 21.1 (FIELD.NO) CUSTOMER&gt;ACCOUNT.OFFICER</p>
            <p value="4"> Field 22.1 (DATA COMPARISON) EQ</p>
            <p value="5"> Field 23.1 (DATA.FROM) 100</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b> The field specified does not need to belong to the application. If the system links the APPLICATION to the field, then the SMS restriction will be applied. </p>
        <p>In this example the COUNTERPARTY field on the FOREX file provides the link to the CUSTOMER file. Hence when the transaction is input, T24 reads the CUSTOMER file using the COUNTERPARTY as the key and checks that the ACCOUNT.OFFICER is 100. You do not have to define COUNTERPARTY as the key to CUSTOMER file. It is done automatically based on the RELATED.FILE stored in the STANDARD.SELECTION record for FOREX.</p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b> If the user wants to test a value in a related file, a consderable process load can be incurred, when the user lists the file. This can be relieved by defining the related field as a J-descriptor user field on the STANDARD.SELECTION record.</p>
        <p>Thus in the example above, define CUST.OFFICER as type J, CUSTOMER,ACCOUNT.OFFICER and then specify the FIELD.NO as FOREXCUST.OFFICER.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">See Details for format.</p>
            <p value="2"> It must not be higher than the number of fields specified in APPLICATION         (Field 2.)</p>
            <p value="3"> Input in this field will not be allowed when N has been         input in FUNCTION (Field 4.1).</p>
            <p value="4">
                <p>Multi-valued field associated with Fields 17-20 and 22-24.</p>
            </p>
            <p value="5">
                <p> (Optional input. No input means all records can be accessed, regardless of contents.)</p>
            </p>
            <p value="6">
                <p> For multi-valued fields, only the field number can be specified, and not the entry number, e.g. 21 and not 21.1, all entries in the multi-valued field will be checked. The System displays the name of the field indicated.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASSIFICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether the user is Internal i.e. an employee of the bank using T24., or External i.e. a customer.</p>
        <p> If the user is defined as EXT (external):</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">enter valid customer and account numbers in the fields <b>CUSTOMER</b> and <b>ACCOUNT</b>. </p>
            <p value="2">setup the table <b>USER.EXTERNAL.FILED</b> to indicate, which fields in the applications constitute a CUSTOMER and/or an ACCOUNT field.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-3 uppercase alpha characters.</p>
            <p value="2"> I, IN or INT for an employee of the bank. </p>
            <p value="3">E, EX or EXT for a customer. </p>
            <p value="4">Mandatory input.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION.ID.LOG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether  the details of every Application, Function and record ID can be accessed by the user or not.</p>
        <p> Recorded in the <b>PROTOCOL</b> file.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Y (Yes) or    N or NO.</p>
            <p value="2"> Mandatory input.</p>
            <p value="3"> It must be NO if APPLICATION LOG (Field 27) is NO.</p>
            <p value="4"> Security Violations are always logged, regardless of this field.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.MGMT.L</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether the record is written to the <b>PROTOCOL</b> file or not, everytime the user accesses, any of the Security Management Application.</p>
        <p> If Y is input, a record is written to the PROTOCOL file, everytime the User accesses any of the following Applications:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> PASSWORD           </p>
            <p value="2">PASSWORD.ENABLE           </p>
            <p value="3">PASSWORD.RESET           </p>
            <p value="4">USER           PASSWORD.RESET</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b>     Security Violations are always logged, regardless of the           values in Fields 25-28.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  Y (Yes) or    N(NO)</p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.END.TIME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the end of period or log out time, at which the user cannot access the system, on a specific day, in the <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b>field.</p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;"> Note: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Always displayed with the format :</p>
            <p value="2">For whole day/night login, start must be 00:00 and end must be 24:00 (ie. 24 hours). </p>
            <p value="3">Can be two or more separate periods each day, for the user to access the system, e.g. morning and afternoon, but not during lunchtime. </p>
            <p value="4">If 1 or 2 digit is entered, they correspond to minutes between midnight and 1 o clock in the morning.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-4       numeric characters with optional, i.e. HHMM or HH:MM </p>
            <p value="2">
                <p> Input can be 0-2359 or 0000-2359 or 00:00-23:59</p>
            </p>
            <p value="3">Sub-valued field       associated with <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b> and <b>DAY.ST.TIME</b> (Optional input)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUT.DAY.MONTH</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether the user enters days or months for the first time, while entering the dates.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> If  DDMM is input - the system interprets as 0102 i.e. 1st February and 0419 as an invalid date.  </p>
            <p value="2">If  MMDD is input - the system interprets as 0102 i.e. January 2nd and 0419 as April 19th.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> DDMM or MMDD</p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINTER.FOR.RPTS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Use Printer when reports are spooled. </p>
        <p> Must be a valid entry on the <b>PRINTER.ID</b> file. If the <b>PRINTER.ID</b> is left blank, the system uses the system printer. </p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 30 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.DEPT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field is marked as NOINPUT Field. No longer used. Made Obsolete.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.SCREEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether the screen must be cleared or not, everytime the user completes, processing a record.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Y (Yes) or    N (NO)</p>
            <p value="2">(Mandatory input)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSW.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Not used at present.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> (Internal field.  NOINPUT.)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWORD.VALIDITY</field>
<desc>
        <p>PASSWORD.VALIDITY</p>
        <p>Specifies how often or when, the user can change the password.</p>
        <p><b>Next Change Date</b> - If entered, must be greater than today's date. </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">It must be entered in the format DDMMYY or MMDDYY depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH (Field 29) format of the User record. </p>
            <p value="2"> Spaces between days, months and years are optional.  </p>
            <p value="3">Alternatively, the date may be entered in any of the standard formats permitted by the system. </p>
            <p value="4">If you do not enter the year and/or the month, the system takes today's date.  </p>
            <p value="5">Every time the Password is changed, the system recalculates the date depending on the change frequency.</p>
        </p>
        <p><b>Change Frequency</b>- Can be daily, every 1-9 weeks, twice a month (on 15th and last day of each month) or every 1-6 Months. </p>
        <p class="Indent5Percent">
            <p>
                <p value="1">Daily Enter D or DAILY.  If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the system takes the Next Change Date as tomorrows date.</p>
                <p value="2">
                    <p>Every 1-9 weeks - enter Wn. where n is 1-9.  If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the system takes the Next Change Date as n x 7 days from today.</p>
                </p>
                <p value="3">
                    <p>Every 1-6 months - enter Mnndd, where nn is the number of months 01-06 and dd is the day in the month on which the password must be changed, </p>
                </p>
                <p value="4">(01-31).  If this date does not exist (e.g. 30th February) the next day will be assumed (1st March). If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the system assumes day dd in nn months from the current month.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
        <p>E.g.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> If todays date is 26 FEB 1985 and you enter M0215 the system will assume the Next Change Date should be 15 APRIL 1985.</p>
            <p value="2"> Twice a month Enter T</p>
            <p value="3"> If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the system assumes the 15th of the current month if today is not after the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month is assumed.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validation Rules:</p>
        <p> This field is in two parts. </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> <![CDATA[   ]]><b>Next Change Date:</b> 1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters.  </p>
            <p value="2">Default value is calculated by the system depending on the change frequency. (Optional input).</p>
            <p value="3">   Change Frequency: 1-5 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters (Mandatory input)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
        <p>Assigned to the user, if  they have authorisation to approve dispo items.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Must be a valid dispo officer defined in the <b>DISPO.OFFICER</b> file.</p>
            <p value="2">Optional field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the <b>SIGN.ON</b> name entered by the User.  It is used by the system as an alternative key to access the User details.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 6-16 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input.</p>
            <p value="3"> It must be different from the USER ID (Field 0) of this record.</p>
            <p value="4"> It must be different from the SIGN ON NAME (Field 2) of any other User record.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE.PROFILE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the earliest date, on which the user represented by this record, can have access to the system.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Input may be all numeric DDMMYY or MMDDYY depending on the <b>INPUT DAY MONTH</b> format in Field 29 of the User record.</p>
            <p value="2">Alphanumeric, DDMMMYYYY where the day and year are numeric and the month is the first 3 letters of the month, in capitals.</p>
            <p value="3"> If you omit the year and/or the month, the system takes today's date.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input - It must not be less than today's date.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ADDR</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the address, that is printed on the report banner page.  </p>
        <p>Each multi-valued represents, a minimum of one line  and a maximum of three lines on the banner.</p>
        <p> If the field is left blank, the delivery point from the <b>DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER</b> file will be used.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-22 Any character.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REACTIVATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the end date of the deactivation period and can be entered or changed only by the User via the <b>PASSWORD</b> Application.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Standard Date format</p>
            <p value="2"> Input only via PASSWORD Application.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies a Version, which is used to access the records, that are entered in the corresponding <b>APPLICATION</b> (Field 2.1).</p>
        <p> This field is used, together with the associated Fields, 17, 18 and 20-24, to specify precisely, which record is accessed by the user and in which Application , using which Versions and Functions.  </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> *  and  ?  - specifies more than one Version. They act as wild card characters.</p>
            <p value="2"> * - replaces any number of characters including null, numbers, alphabets etc. </p>
            <p value="3"> ? - replaces one character including null, numbers, alphabets etc.</p>
        </p>
        <p> The version field can have the values for e.g. <b>,SAVE*</b> - which allows the user to access Versions of <b>ACCOUNT</b> applications for eg :<b>ACCOUNT,SAVESTUDENT, ACCOUNT,SAVERESIDENT, ACCOUNT,SAVESALARIED</b>, etc </p>
        <p>The version field can have the values for e.g.: <b>,SAVE1000?00</b>- which allows the user to access versions of <b>ACCOUNT</b> application for e.g. <b>SAVE1000100, SAVE1000200, SAVE1000300</b> , etc</p>
        <p><![CDATA[  ]]><b>Note:</b> Versions of Application, changes the screen layout or the rules for Input, Validation and Authorization. </p>
        <p>E.g. 1:</p>
        <p> To allow a User to List and See all Accounts except for those with Account Officer = 1234 using the standard version of Account, and to List and See all Accounts for Account Officer = 1234 only, using a special Version Account,99:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT </p>
            <p value="2">Field 19.1(VERSION) ,0 </p>
            <p value="3">Field 20.1(FUNCTION) L S </p>
            <p value="4">Field 21.1(FIELD NO) 9 </p>
            <p value="5">Field 22.1(DATA COMPARISON) NE </p>
            <p value="6">Field 23.1(DATA FROM) 1234 </p>
            <p value="7">Field 18.2(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT </p>
            <p value="8">Field 19.2(VERSION) ,99 </p>
            <p value="9">Field 20.2(FUNCTION) L S </p>
            <p value="10">Field 21.2(FIELD NO) 9 </p>
            <p value="11">Field 22.2(DATA COMPARISON) EQ </p>
            <p value="12">Field 23.2(DATA FROM) 1234</p>
        </p>
        <p>E.g. 2:</p>
        <p> To allow a User to Input and See all Account version with name starting with SAVINGS followed by any character:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT </p>
            <p value="2">Field 19.1(VERSION) ,SAVINGS* </p>
            <p value="3">Field 20.1(FUNCTION) I S</p>
        </p>
        <p>For more examples of Fields 17-24 see Fields 18 and 21.</p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 0-50 type A (alphanumeric) characters beginning with , or </p>
            <p value="2">0 to allow only the standard version. or </p>
            <p value="3">Disallows all Versions. </p>
            <p value="4">Multi-valued field associated with Fields 17, 18 and 20-24. (Optional input except if a <b>USER.SMS.GROUP</b> is defined in field 18.1 in which case the input is not allowed. If not entered, access to all Versions is allowed.</p>
            <p value="5"> Special character  *  will replace any number of characters and  ?  replaces one character. </p>
            <p value="6">Also  ?  after  *  and two occurrences of  *  are not allowed.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specify the functions, that are used to access the records of the Application, entered in the corresponding Field 18.</p>
        <p> This field is used, together with the associated Fields 17-19 and 21-24 to specify precisely, which function, the user uses to access which record and application.</p>
        <p>Valid function codes are:           A 2 C D E H I L P Q R S V</p>
        <p> If NOT is entered, plus one or more Function codes, the system converts the code into a list of all the Functions which are allowed.  (See Fields 18, 19 and 21 for examples.)</p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b>During an input function, even if the function C (copy) is not allowed, the user           will still be able to transfer the ID (together with its           enrichment) of a selected record using the !           facility.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 0-29 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.</p>
            <p value="2">Function codes separated by spaces.   </p>
            <p value="3">   NOT + one or more Function codes.</p>
            <p value="4">      N (No Functions allowed).   </p>
            <p value="5">   ALL (All Functions allowed). </p>
            <p value="6">Multi-valued field associated with Fields 17-19, 21-24.</p>
            <p value="7">Mandatory input except if a <b>USER.SMS.GROUP</b> is defined in field 18.1, the input will not be allowed. </p>
            <p value="8">No Default Value. </p>
            <p value="9">If Function 2 (2nd Authorization) is allowed, but not A (1st Authorization), the User is allowed to enter Function Code A - a Security Violation is generated if the record requested is not ready for 2nd Authorization.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.FROM</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies a value, or start of a range of values, with which the contents indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) are  compared.</p>
        <p> 1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        <p> Or Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following way:</p>
        <p style="list-style-type: lower-roman;">
            <p value="1">up to 30 characters (type ANY), must be a valid entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by,</p>
            <p value="2">a gt (greater than) sign, followed by,</p>
            <p value="3">up to 18 characters (type A) must be a valid entry in the multi-valued field <b>SYS.FIELD.NAME</b> on the <b>STANDARD.SELECTION</b> record for a file specified in (i).</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[  ]]><b>Note:</b> The values input in this field and the next field, must be in agreement with the Format rules of the element, specified in Field 21.1. </p>
        <p>E.g., the input in Field 21 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic - a minimum input of 3 characters is required in this field.</p>
        <p> When defining the enquires a user can run, and also turn off all SMS checks for a particular enquiry. This is useful when the enquiry presents non sensitive information from sensitive files. </p>
        <p>i.e. the user may wish to show customer and account static information (address, account titles etc ) but not the balances. </p>
        <p>As the enquiry by itself controls the presentation, there may be no need for any additional security. To suppress SMS you must append *NOSMS to the name of the enquiry.</p>
        <p>E.g.1:</p>
        <p> Field 18.1 (APPLICATION) ENQUIRY.SELECT</p>
        <p> Field 20.1 (FUNCTION) I</p>
        <p> Field 21.1 (FIELD.NO) 0</p>
        <p> Field 22.1 (DATA.COMPARISON) EQ</p>
        <p> Field 23.1 (DATA.FROM) CUSTOMER.STATIC*NOSMS</p>
        <p> This mechanism works only with ENQUIRY.SELECT and must be entered in the format detailed above.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> See Details for format.</p>
            <p value="2"> Input must begin and/or end with 3 dots when         DATA.COMPARISON = LK or &amp; UL</p>
            <p value="3">
                <p>Multi-valued field associated with Fields 17-22 and 24.</p>
            </p>
            <p value="4">
                <p>Mandatory input if FIELD NO is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Allows the user to access and update DISPO items, with the approval of the other dispo officers. This facilitates a higher-ranking officer to take over the duty of a lower level, as and when required.</p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Multi-valued field (Optional      input)</p>
            <p value="2">  Must be a valid dispo officer      as defined in the <b>DISPO.OFFICER</b> file.</p>
            <p value="3"> The <b>DISPO.RIGHTS</b> must not be      the same as the <b>DISPO.OFFICER</b>.</p>
            <p value="4"> Duplicates not allowed.</p>
            <p value="5"><b>DISPO.RIGHTS</b> cannot be      entered when <b>DISPO.OFFICER</b> is empty.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTEMPTS.SINCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of unsuccessful attempts, since the last successful <b>SIGN.ON</b></p>
        <p>If the number in this field is not less than the number allowed in <b>ATTEMPTS</b> (Field 13), the password will be disabled. The password can be reset using the <b>PASSWORD.RESET</b> application.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Numeric. </p>
            <p value="2">Internal field.  NOINPUT</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the Customer records, the external users can access.</p>
        <p> If <b>CLASSIFICATION</b> (Field 3) is <b>EXT</b>, at least one entry will be in this field.</p>
        <p> The external users cannot access the financial information of any Customer, except those specified in this field. </p>
        <p>Input must be Customer Code or Mnemonic of an existing Customer record. If Mnemonic is entered, the system will convert it to the corresponding Customer Code.</p>
        <p> Set up the table <b>USER.EXTERNAL.FIELD</b> to indicate, which field that is specified constitutes to the CUSTOMER and/or an ACCOUNT field.</p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b> For external customers, avoid duplicating this restriction for each Application in field 17 to 24.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">1-10 numeric characters Customer Code. </p>
            <p value="2">3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or) Customer Mnemonic characters. </p>
            <p value="3">Multi-valued field.</p>
            <p value="4">Mandatory input for External Users; otherwise not allowed. </p>
            <p value="5">No default value.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSW.CHANGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Not used at present.</p>
        <p>Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> (Internal field.  NOINPUT.)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION.LOG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether the records of  all the applications, accessed by the user, must be written to the <b>PROTOCOL</b> file.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Y (Yes) or    N (NO)</p>
            <p value="2">
                <p> If Y is input, a record is written to the PROTOCOL file, every time a different Application is accessed.</p>
            </p>
            <p value="3">Mandatory input</p>
            <p value="4"> Security Violations are always logged, regardless of this field.</p>
            <p value="5"> It must be NO, if SECURITY MGMT LOG (Field 26) is NO.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RPT.TO.RECEIVE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the name(s) of the report, the user receives, from the over-night batch run.  </p>
        <p>Must be a valid entry on the <b>REPORT.CONTROL</b> file.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-30 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.TIME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start period of each day, at which the user is allowed access the system.</p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;"> Note: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  Always displayed with the format : </p>
            <p value="2">Can be two or more separate periods                 each day, for the user to access                 the system, e.g. morning and afternoon, but                 not during lunch time.</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[  ]]><b>Note:</b>     If 1 or 2 digit is entered, they correspond to           minutes between midnight and 1 o clock in the morning.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  1-4 numeric characters with optional : i.e.  HHMM or HH:MM </p>
            <p value="2">Multi-valued field associated with END TIME (Field 11) </p>
            <p value="3">Mandatory input.</p>
            <p value="4">
                <p> Input can be 0-2359                  or 0000-2359                  or 00:00-23:59</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the language, in which the system communicates with the user.  </p>
        <p>All messages, instructions, help text etc. will be displayed in the language, indicated by this code.</p>
        <p> All information displayed by the system will be in the language specified, provided if the translation is entered into the system.  </p>
        <p>Any information for which the translation is not entered into the system, is displayed in whichever language it is defined,  in the <b>LANGUAGE</b> table (ref: General Tables).</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-2 numeric characters. </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input.</p>
            <p value="3">The number entered must be the ID of an existing record in the <b>LANGUAGE</b> table.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.SPOOL.TIME</field>
<desc>
        <p> Specifies the time, when the report was last spooled.</p>
        <p>Associated with RPT TO RECEIVE (Field 45.1). </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> HHMM </p>
            <p value="2">NOINPUT field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.SPOOL.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the date, when the report was last spooled.</p>
        <p>Associated with RPT TO RECEIVE (Field 45.1).  </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> YYYYMMDD</p>
            <p value="2">NOINPUT field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies company or companies records, the user can access. </p>
        <p>When a user signs in - access is given to the records of the Company, specified in this field.  </p>
        <p>If more than one Company is specified - the User can access the records of another Company, by using the <b>PASSWORD</b> Application or via Tools/Change Company, in an environment, using T24 Administration Company.</p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;">  Note:     </p>
        <p style="list-style-type: lower-roman;">
            <p value="1">  Always displayed reformatted, with the dashes.</p>
            <p value="2"> Any file  in the COMPANY record, for which standard or special file mnemonics are specified, are only accessed by the users signed on to that Company.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">   Company ID: <b>CCGGGLLLL</b> where CC is alphabetic Country code, GGG  is numeric Company group and LLLL is Local code.</p>
            <p value="2">     Company Mnemonic: 2-3 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or) characters.</p>
            <p value="3"> Multi-valued field</p>
            <p value="4">Mandatory input</p>
            <p value="5">It must be ID or Mnemonic of an existing COMPANY record. The company may be in linked business entity where T24 Administration Company is active.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPARTMENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the bank department, in which the user works.</p>
        <p> Used as default in <b>DATA.CAPTURE</b> batch numbers and reporting purposes.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-4 numeric characters.</p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input</p>
            <p value="3"> It must be the ID of an existing Department/Account Officer (DEPT.ACCT. OFFICER) record.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Stores the User's secret Password.  </p>
        <p>It can be changed only by the user, either when system prompts, on password expiry, or whenever the user wishes to change, using the <b>PASSWORD</b> Application.</p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b>     If a user forgets the secret password, it can be           reset using the <b>PASSWORD.RESET</b> application, which enables           the user to start again with a new password.</p>
        <p> Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> (6-16 characters.  Encrypted.  Never displayed.)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.RESTR</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the Company, to which the user must be signed on, in order to use the Applications, Versions and Functions, specified in the related Fields 18 to 24.</p>
        <p> Used, together with the associated fields 18-24, to specify for each Company, whose record a user can access, precisely which record and application, using which version and function.</p>
        <p> The group of fields, 17-24 can be repeated up to 999 times.  Refer to APPLICATION (Field 18) for examples.</p>
        <p>  A user can access only those Companies (or have used the PASSWORD Application to access that Company) which has files or any standards or special file mnemonics specified.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Permits ALL - to allow functions to all the companies listed in the <b>COMPANY.CODE</b> field. </p>
            <p value="2">In a Multi Book company set up, if the field is defined as ALL - it allows the functions for Lead company and all book companies under that Lead company.</p>
            <p value="3"> 9 alphanumeric characters CCGGGLLLL where: CC   is 2 alpha characters, Country code GGG  is 3 numeric characters, Company Group LLLL is 4 numeric local code. </p>
            <p value="4">or    2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or ) Company Mnemonic characters. </p>
            <p value="5">Multi-valued field associated with Fields 18-24. </p>
            <p value="6">Mandatory input if Role based SMS restriction is not given.</p>
            <p value="7">No Default Value. </p>
            <p value="8">It must be a Company Code from the <b>COMPANY.CODE</b> field of this record.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.LAST.SIGN.ON</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the actual date (system date) , the user last signed on successfully.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Display in the format DD MMM YYYY e.g 18 JAN 1985 </p>
            <p value="2">Internal field.  </p>
            <p value="3">NOINPUT.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the name, by which the user is known and can be used for reporting purposes.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the channel through which the user logs in. This field is updated during sign in and is cleared while signing off.</p>
        <p>When a user logs in through a <b>OFS.SOURCE</b> enabled Interface, the CHANNEL will be updated in this field. </p>
        <p>When there is no channel specified in the <b>OFS.SOURCE</b>, the <b>OFS.SOURCE ID</b> will be updated in this field.</p>
        <p>When a user logs in through service, this field will be updated with the name of the service.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Alphanumeric Field</p>
            <p value="2">NOINPUT Field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE.PROFILE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the latest date, on which the user is represented by this record and had access to the system.</p>
        <p>The Input can be:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">all numeric DDMMYY or MMDDYY, depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH format in Field 29 of the User record, or </p>
            <p value="2">alphanumeric, DDMMMYYYY where the day and year are numeric and the month is the first three letters of the month, in capitals.</p>
        </p>
        <p> If you omit the year and/or the month, the system takes the today's date.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input</p>
            <p value="3">It must not be less than today's date or less than START DATE PROFILE (Field 8).</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINTER.FOR.P.FUNC</field>
<desc>
        <p>Use Printer when 'P function' is used.  </p>
        <p>Must be a valid entry on the <b>PRINTER.ID</b> file.  If the <b>PRINTER.ID</b> is left blank, the system uses the system printer.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 30 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOGIN.STATUS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the login status of the user. </p>
        <p>When a user logs in to T24, this field will be defaulted to <b>ACTIVE</b>.</p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Alphanumeric field</p>
            <p value="2">NOINPUT field.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.SESSIONS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the maximum number of sessions, the user can own.</p>
        <p>With T24 Desktop version 1.1.00, it is possible for every user to run multiple applications concurrently, or multiple instances of each application.</p>
        <p> Each session is a distinct UniVerse session and requires a separate UniVerse licence. </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the attributes that are associated with a particular user.</p>
        <p> Valid settings in this field are:</p>
        <p><b>COMMAND.LINE</b> - Allows the user to use the command line in T24 Desktop.</p>
        <p><b>EXPLORER</b> - Allows the user to use the Application explorers.</p>
        <p><b>ENQUIRY.INDEX</b> - Allows the user to access the enquiry index.</p>
        <p><b>REALTIMEENQUIRY</b> - Allows the user to use the real time enquiries. When signing into T24, desktop creates another session for real time enquiries. This uses an additional database license, but not an additional T24 license.</p>
        <p><b>LOCK.PREFERENCES</b> - Prevents the user from accessing the 'User Preferences'  option that includes various Desktop settings, file locations and system administrative functions, under the 'Tools' menu on the Desktop toolbar. </p>
        <p><b>SUPER.USER</b> - Allows the user to access all the features detailed above, and for all future functionality except <b>REALTIMEENQUIRY</b>.</p>
        <p><b>LOCK.DEACTIVATION</b> - Allows the user to disable the "Deactivation profile" menu  on the desktop.</p>
        <p><b>LOCK.DESIGNERS</b> - Allows the user to disable the "Designer menu" items on the desktop.</p>
        <p><b>LOCK.MISC.ITEMS</b> - Prevents the user from accessing the user toolbar, list of enquiries and list of reports on the desktop.</p>
        <p><b>COMMIT.DETAILS</b> - Allows the user to set the attribute as diagnostic and displays the filenames, when a transaction is updated.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INIT.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Whenever the user signs in from the Classic interface, the system routes the user to the  same application immediately, without entering the application name.</p>
        <p> Not to be viewed as a security measure, as the user can still switch to another permitted application.</p>
        <p> If this field is not used, the system will request the user to enter an application name as soon as <b>SIGN.ON</b> is complete.</p>
        <p> Input to this field is free format. It may be used in the same way as the <b>ACTION</b> line, to enter an Application (or Abbreviation or Version) name and, optionally, a Function Code and a Record ID.</p>
        <p>  If a Menu is required as the initial Application, <i>?n</i> is entered for a Main Menu - where <b>n</b> is the Id of the Main Menu , </p>
        <p>or <b style="font-style: italic;">?xx</b> for a System Menu - where <b>xx</b> is the Id of the Menu. </p>
        <p>Whenever a menu is specified in the User Profile, the system returns to this menu at the Top level.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 0-42 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p value="2">Optional input. </p>
            <p value="3">No         default value.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.LAST.SIGN.ON</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the last sign on time,  on the <b>SIGN.ON</b> screen.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Displayed in format HH:MM, 00:00 - 23:59. </p>
            <p value="2">Internal field.  </p>
            <p value="3">NOINPUT</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RPT.COPIES</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of copies, the user can receive.</p>
        <p>Associated with RPT TO RECEIVE (Field 45.1). </p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 2 numeric characters.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.TIME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the end period of each day, at which the user is allowed to access the system.</p>
        <p style="font-weight: bold;"> Note: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Always displayed with the format : </p>
            <p value="2">      For whole day/night login, start must be 00:00 and end           must be 24:00 (ie. 24 hours).        </p>
            <p value="3">Can be two or more separate periods each day, for the user to access the system, e.g.           morning and afternoon, but not during lunchtime. </p>
            <p value="4">If 1 or 2 digit is entered, they correspond to           minutes between midnight and 1 o clock in the morning.</p>
        </p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1-4 numeric characters with optional : i.e.  HHMM or HH:MM </p>
            <p value="2">
                <p> Input can be 0-2359                  or 0000-2359                  or 00:00-23:59</p>
            </p>
            <p value="3">Multi-valued field associated with START TIME (Field 10) (Mandatory input)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFLINE.SMS.PROFILE</field>
<desc>
        <p>A valid <b>USER.SMS.PROFILE</b> record.</p>
        <p> The properties of this profile is applied, when the Branch is offline and overwriting the main USER properties. </p>
        <p>Gives one set of properties for normal use and another smaller set for use, when the branch is offline.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Input is only allowed if the BR product is installed.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEACTIVATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start date of the deactivation period, that can only be entered or changed by the user via <b>PASSWORD</b> application.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Standard Date format</p>
            <p value="2"> Input only via <b>PASSWORD</b> Application.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTEMPTS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of unsuccessful attempts, allowed to <b>SIGN.ON</b>, using the <b>SIGN ON NAME</b> (Field 2) of this record, before the password is disabled.</p>
        <p> The system stores the number of unsuccessful attempts to <b>SIGN.ON</b>, since the last successful <b>SIGN.ON</b>.  </p>
        <p>When the number of unsuccessful attempts is greater than or equal to the number specified in this field, the Password will be DISABLED and all further attempts will result in SECURITY VIOLATION. </p>
        <p>User records DISABLED are shown in the <b>PASSWORD.EXCEPTION</b> list.</p>
        <p>    The <b>PASSWORD.RESET</b> application allows the user (who has forgotten the Password) to reset the password.</p>
        <p>Following are the reasons for the failure to SIGN.ON:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">   Incorrect Password</p>
            <p value="2">   Today's date less than <b>START DATE PROFILE</b> (Field 8)</p>
            <p value="3">   Today's date later than <b>END DATE PROFILE</b> (Field 9)</p>
            <p value="4">   Time is earlier than <b>START TIME</b> (Field 10)</p>
            <p value="5">   Time is later than <b>END TIME</b> (Field 11)</p>
            <p value="6">   The Password has been deactivated (for further details see PASSWORD Application)</p>
            <p value="7">   The Password has been disabled after too many unsuccessful attempts.</p>
            <p value="8">  The User record is not in Live status i.e new input or change is not yet authorised.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1 numeric character. </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the  details of the user.</p>
        <p> This code is written for audit trail purposes of all the records, which are input, changed or authorised by the user.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 3-16 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters. </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the accounts, that can be accessed by the external users. </p>
        <p>It is not used at the present time.</p>
        <p> If there is an entry in this field, the external users will not have access to the financial information of any accounts, except those which are specified in this field.</p>
        <p> Setup a table <b>USER.EXTERNAL.FILED</b> to indicate, which fields in the application, constitutes a CUSTOMER and/or an ACCOUNT field.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 2-14 numeric Account Number characters or 3-10         type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or ) Account         Mnemonic characters. </p>
            <p value="2">Multi-valued field only allowed for         External Users.</p>
            <p value="3"> Field cannot be input unless the CUSTOMER (Field 15) is entered.      </p>
            <p value="4"> Up to 999 accounts can be entered in each group of fields,         corresponding to an entry in Field 15.</p>
            <p value="5"> Each input must be an Account Number or Mnemonic of an         existing Account record.</p>
            <p value="6"> Each Account entered must have a Customer code (Field 1)        that is equal to the Customer code in the corresponding Field 15         of this record.</p>
            <p value="7">  No duplicates are allowed.</p>
            <p value="8"> If Mnemonic is entered, the system converts it to the         corresponding Account Number.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOWED.DAYS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of days a user can access the system. </p>
        <p>Taken from the associated fields <b>DAY.ST.TIME</b> and <b>DAY.END.TIME</b>. </p>
        <p> The period set in the fields <b>START.TIME</b> and <b>END.TIME</b> (fields 10 11) are applicable for all the days of the week.</p>
        <p> The access time for a particular day is taken from the fields <b>DAY.ST.TIME</b> and <b>DAY.END.TIME</b> if defined, otherwise the common <b>START.TIME</b> and <b>END.TIME</b> is used.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">
                <p>The values allowed are 1 to 7 meaning 1  MONDAY, 2  TUESDAY and 7  SUNDAY.</p>
            </p>
            <p value="2">Multi-valued field associated with <b>DAY.ST.TIME</b> and <p><![CDATA[      ]]><b>DAY.END.TIME</b></p><p value="3"> Optional input</p></p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the separators, that are used when formatting the amounts of Enquiries, Reports and screen input/display.</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> the million thousands separator can be a comma, full stop or apostrophe.</p>
            <p value="2"> the decimal separator can only be either a comma or full stop.</p>
            <p value="3"> the format is entered as a 2 character pair. </p>
        </p>
        <p>For e.g. The first value is used as a separator for millions and thousands. The second value is used as a decimal separator.</p>
        <p>E.g.</p>
        <table class="TableStyle-MasterTable" style="mc-table-style: url('../../../Resources/TableStyles/MasterTable.css');" cellspacing="0">
            <col style="width: 171px;" class="Column-Column1" />
            <col style="width: 145px;" class="Column-Column1" />
            <tbody>
                <tr class="Body-Body1">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="16%" </p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">Setting</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body2">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="84%" </p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">Enter and displayed as</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body1">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="16%"</p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">,.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body2">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="84%"</p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">1,234,567.89</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body1">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="16%"</p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">.,</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body2">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="84%"</p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">1.234.567,89</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body1">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="16%"'</p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">,</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body2">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="84%"</p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">1'234'567,89</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body1">
                    <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="16%"'</p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: center;">.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr class="Body-Body2">
                    <td class="BodyB-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">
                        <p style="text-align: center;">width="84%"</p>
                    </td>
                    <td class="BodyA-Column1-Body2" style="text-align: center;">1'234'567.89</td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Optional field  - system will use, if field is left blank.</p>
            <p value="2"> Any valid combination of 2 can be used.</p>
            <p value="3"> Decimal separator must be either comma or full stop.</p>
            <p value="4"> Thousands separator must be either a comma, full stop or apostrophe.</p>
            <p value="5"> The same character cannot be used twice.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies which Application can be used to access the company records. The company details are specified in the <b>COMPANY RESTR</b> (Field 17).</p>
        <p> This field is used, together with the associated Fields 17 and 19-24 to specify precisely, which record and Application the user can access, using which Version and Function. It must be:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> the name of an existing application, </p>
            <p value="2">the name of an existing <b>USER.SMS.GROUP</b> preceded by the @ sign (in which further input in fields 19.1 to 24.1 will not be allowed), </p>
            <p value="3">ALL.PG to allow access to all the Applications or </p>
            <p value="4">ALL.PG (program type) to allow access to all the Applications of a certain type (see below).</p>
        </p>
        <p> The following program types may be used in conjunction with ALL.PG (e.g. ALL.PG.H) to give access to a particular type of program:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Program Type Meaning.</p>
            <p value="2"> <![CDATA[ ]]><b>H Programs</b> - the 3 standard files exist - Live, Unauthorised and History, e.g. CUSTOMER</p>
            <p value="3"> <![CDATA[ ]]><b>U Programs</b> - Live and Unauthorised files exist, but no History, e.g. VERSION.</p>
            <p value="4"> <![CDATA[ ]]><b>L Programs</b> - only a Live file exist (updated automatically by the system) e.g. STMT.ENTRY (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program).</p>
            <p value="5"> <![CDATA[ ]]><b>M Programs</b> - are designed to do other than processing the standard T24 functions, using a specific file e.g. PASSWORD.ENABLE, End Of Day Batch programs.</p>
            <p value="6"> <![CDATA[ ]]><b>T Programs</b> - handles automatically updated CONCAT files, e.g. CUSTOMER.ACCOUNT (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program). </p>
        </p>
        <p><b>Note:</b> The following 3 type M programs are available to all the users and cannot be restricted:- SIGN.ON SIGN.OFF PASSWORD</p>
        <p> E.g. 1:</p>
        <p> To allow the user, to access the records of only one Company (GB-001-0000), but allow access to all records for this Company using all Functions (except auditor review) and Versions of all Applications.</p>
        <p>Enter the following:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 5.1 (COMPANY) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 17.1(COMPANY CODE)</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG</p>
            <p value="4"> Field 19.1(VERSION)</p>
            <p value="5">Field 20.1(FUNCTION) ALL</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b> Fields 21-24 are used to specify particular records or types of records which may be accessed within an Application. See FIELD NO (Field 21) for examples.</p>
        <p> E.g. 2:</p>
        <p> To allow the user to fully access (except auditor review) the records of Company GB-001-0000 and to give limited access to the records of Company GB-001-0001, only allowing the List and Display functions for Customer Application.</p>
        <p>Enter the following:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 5.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 5.2(COMPANY) GB-001-0001</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 17.1(COMPANY.CODE) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p value="4"> Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG</p>
            <p value="5"> Field 19.1(VERSION)</p>
            <p value="6"> Field 20.1(FUNCTION) ALL</p>
            <p value="7"> Field 17.2(COMPANY.CODE) GB-001-0001</p>
            <p value="8"> Field 18.2(APPLICATION) CUSTOMER</p>
            <p value="9"> Field 19.2(VERSION)</p>
            <p value="10"> Field 20.2(FUNCTION) L S</p>
        </p>
        <p> E.g. 3:</p>
        <p> To allow the user, to access the records of only one Company (GB-001-0000),  to List Display, Input and Copy Customer records and to List and Display records for all other Applications:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 5.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 20.1(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="4"> Field 18.2(APPLICATION) CUSTOMER</p>
            <p value="5"> Field 20.2(FUNCTION) L S I C</p>
        </p>
        <p> E.g. 4:</p>
        <p> To prevent the user, from using any type M Applications, but allow him to List and Display records in any other Applications:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 5.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 17.1(COMPANY CODE)</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.H</p>
            <p value="4"> Field 20.1(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="5">Field 18.2(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.U</p>
            <p value="6">Field 20.2(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="7"> Field 18.3(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.L</p>
            <p value="8"> Field 20.3(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="9"> Field 18.4(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.T</p>
            <p value="10"> Field 20.4(FUNCTION) L S</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">1-30 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters, Application name.</p>
            <p value="2"> ALL.PG to allow all Applications.</p>
            <p value="3"> ALL.PG (program type) see details.</p>
            <p value="4"> @ sign followed by a valid USER.SMS.GROUP</p>
            <p value="5"> Multi-valued field associated with Fields 17 and 19-24. </p>
            <p value="6">Mandatory input in each set of Fields 17-24.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>