<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EB.USER.SMS.GROUP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p>Allows the user to group together various T24 Applications.  </p>
        <p>Enables the creation of logical groups, which can be specified under user roles [<b>EB.USER.ROLES</b>], to avoid repetition of related applications in different user profiles. </p>
        <p>  When a modification is made, it automatically impacts all the profiles which contains this group.</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies a comprehensive description of SMS group.</p>
        <p>Used for free form narrative. Enter a meaningful description, such as the name of the Module/Group, to facilitate the recognition of the facilities contained in the group. </p>
        <p>  Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. </p>
            <p value="2">Multi-valued field. </p>
            <p value="3">Mandatory input.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the date, till which the user can have access to the additional functions in <b>TEMP.FUNCTION</b>.</p>
        <p>  Allowed Input are:
</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">all numeric DDMMYY or MMDDY, depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH format in Field 29 of the User record, or 
</p>
            <p value="2">alphanumeric, DDMMMYYYY where the day and year are numeric and the month is the first 3 letters of the month, in capitals.</p>
        </p>
        <p>  If you omit the year and/or the month, the system assumes they are the same as today.</p>
        <p class="Heading5">  Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  1-9 type D (date     format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces.     </p>
            <p value="2">  Cannot be greater than     <b>END.DATE</b> <![CDATA[     ]]></p>
            <p value="3">  Mandatory if     <b>TEMP.FUNCTION</b> or <b>END.DATE</b> is present. </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies (when used together with Fields 6.1 - 8.1) precisely, which record can be accessed, that are specified in the corresponding <b>APPLICATION</b> (Field 2.)  </p>
        <p>A record can be accessed, only if the field indicated, has a value allowed in the corresponding Fields 6.1 - 8.1. </p>
        <p>  0-3 numeric characters. </p>
        <p>  or       up to 43 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following            way: </p>
        <p style="list-style-type: lower-roman;">
            <p value="1">   Up to 24 characters (type ANY) must be a valid            entry on the <b>FILE.CONTROL</b> file, followed by,</p>
            <p value="2"> <![CDATA[  ]]>A gt (greater than) sign, followed by, </p>
            <p value="3">       Up to 18 characters (type A) must be a valid entry            on the multi-valued field <b>SYS.FIELD.NAME</b> on the            <b>STANDARD.SELECTION</b> record for a file specified in            (i). </p>
        </p>
        <p>For multi-valued fields, only the field number can be specified, and not the entry number, e.g. 21, not 21.1, all entries in the multi-valued field will be checked.  The system displays the name of the field indicated. </p>
        <p>  E.g. 1:</p>
        <p>  To create a group which allows the User, to See and List all Accounts records, but only Input (or change), Copy or Delete Accounts in pounds sterling. </p>
        <p>Enter the following:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  Field  2.1 (APPLICATION)      ACCOUNT </p>
            <p value="2">Field       4.1 (FUNCTION)         L S </p>
            <p value="3">       Field 2.2 (APPLICATION)      ACCOUNT        </p>
            <p value="4">Field 4.2 (FUNCTION)         I C D </p>
            <p value="5">Field        5.2 (FIELD NO.)        8       (currency)        </p>
            <p value="6">Field 6.2 (DATA COMPARISON)  EQ      (equal)        </p>
            <p value="7">Field 7.2 (DATA FROM)        GBP </p>
        </p>
        <p>  E.g. 2: </p>
        <p>  To create a group which allows the User, to access Account records only if they have Currency equal GBP and Category not in the range 01-001 to 01-099. </p>
        <p>Enter the following:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  Field 2.1  (APPLICATION)      ACCOUNT </p>
            <p value="2">Field       4.1  (FUNCTION)         ALL       </p>
            <p value="3">Field 5.1  (FIELD.NO)         8       (Currency) </p>
            <p value="4">Field       6.1  (DATA.COMPARISON)  EQ      (equal)       </p>
            <p value="5">Field 7.1  (DATA.FROM)        GBP       </p>
            <p value="6">Field 2.2  (APPLICATION)      ACCOUNT       </p>
            <p value="7">Field 4.2  (FUNCTION)         ALL </p>
            <p value="8">Field       5.2  (FIELD.NO)         2       (Category) </p>
            <p value="9">Field       6.2  (DATA.COMPARISON)  NE      (not equal)       </p>
            <p value="10">Field 7.2  (DATA.FROM)        01-001       </p>
            <p value="11">Field 8.2  (DATA.TO)          01-099 </p>
        </p>
        <p>  E.g. 3:</p>
        <p>  To allow a User to Authorise Data Capture records, but only if they do not contain an override. </p>
        <p>Enter the following:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  Field 2.1  (APPLICATION)      DATA.CAPTURE       </p>
            <p value="2">Field 4.1  (FUNCTION)         A       </p>
            <p value="3">Field 5.1  (FIELD.NO)         </p>
            <p value="4">Field 24 (Override) </p>
            <p value="5">Field       6.1  (DATA COMPARISON)  LT (Less Than)       </p>
            <p value="6">Field 7.1  (DATA.FROM)  (lowest possible value) </p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[  ]]><b>Note:</b>      It is not possible to prevent a User from entering on an           override, during input, but Authorisation can be            restricted, as above, to ensure that any overrides are            checked by a more senior person  is the lowest value            a field can have, so specifying LT (Less Than), ensures            that no override may be present. </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  See details for format.</p>
            <p value="2">  It must not be higher than the number of fields specified in APPLICATION (Field 2.)</p>
            <p value="3">  Input in this field will not be allowed when N has been input in FUNCTION (Field 4.1).</p>
            <p value="4">
                <p>  Multi-valued field associated with Fields 2.1 to 4.1 and 6.1 to 8.1. </p>
            </p>
            <p value="5">
                <p>  Optional input.  No input means all records can be accessed, regardless of contents.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.ST.TIME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start of period or the log in time, at which the user is allowed to access the system, on a specific day, in the <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b> field. </p>
        <p>If the same field in USER record is empty, then the value in this field will be used. </p>
        <p><b>Note:</b> <![CDATA[ ]]></p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">
                <p>Always displayed with the format : .</p>
            </p>
            <p value="2">
                <p>Can be two or more separate periods each day, for the User to access the system, e.g. morning and afternoon, but not during lunch time. </p>
            </p>
            <p value="3">If only 1 or 2 digits are entered, they correspond to minutes between midnight and 1 o clock in the morning.</p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">1-4 numeric characters with optional : i.e. HHMM or HH:MM </p>
            <p value="2">
                <p>Sub-value field       associated with <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b> and <b>DAY.END.TIME</b> (Optional input)</p>
            </p>
            <p value="3">Input can be 0-2359 or 0000-2359 or 00:00-23:59</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
        <p> Specifies a Version, which is used to access the records, that are entered in the corresponding <b>APPLICATION</b> (Field 2.1).</p>
        <p>    This field is used, together with the associated Fields, 2.1 and 4.1 - 8.1, to specify precisely, which record is accessed by the user and in which Application , using which Versions and Functions.  </p>
        <p><![CDATA[  ]]><b>Note:</b> Versions of Application, changes the screen layout or the rules for Input, Validation and Authorization. </p>
        <p>  E.g. 1</p>
        <p>  To create a group which allows the User, to List and See all Accounts, except for those with Account Officer = 1234 using the standard version of Account, and to List and See all Accounts for Account Officer = 1234 only, using a special Version Account,99: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  Field 2.1 (APPLICATION) ACCOUNT </p>
            <p value="2">Field 3.1 (VERSION) ,0 </p>
            <p value="3">Field 4.1 (FUNCTION) L S </p>
            <p value="4">Field 5.1 (FIELD NO) 9 </p>
            <p value="5">Field 6.1 (DATA COMPARISON) NE </p>
            <p value="6">Field 7.1 (DATA FROM) 1234 </p>
            <p value="7">Field 2.2 (APPLICATION) ACCOUNT </p>
            <p value="8">Field 3.2 (VERSION) ,99 </p>
            <p value="9">Field 4.2 (FUNCTION) L S </p>
            <p value="10">Field 5.2 (FIELD NO) 9 </p>
            <p value="11">Field 6.2 (DATA COMPARISON) EQ </p>
            <p value="12">Field 7.2 (DATA FROM) 1234 </p>
        </p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">   0-23 type A (alphanumeric)     characters beginning with , or </p>
            <p value="2">Allow only the standard     version. </p>
            <p value="3">No input to allow all Versions. </p>
            <p value="4">Multi-valued field associated     with Fields 2.1 and 4.1 to 8.1. </p>
            <p value="5">Optional input. If not entered, access to     all Versions is allowed.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the date, till which the user can have access to the additional functions in <b>TEMP.FUNCTION</b>.</p>
        <p>  Allowed Input are:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">
                <p>all numeric DDMMYY or MMDDYY, depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH format in Field 29 of the User record.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
        <p>  If you omit the year and/or the month, the system takes today's date.</p>
        <p>  Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  1-9     type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. </p>
            <p value="2">  Must     not be less than todays date or START.DATE. </p>
            <p value="3">  Mandatory if TEMP.FUNCTION or START.DATE is present.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TO</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the end-range of values, with which the contents indicated in FIELD NO (Field 5.1) are compared.</p>
        <p> 0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        <p> Or        Up to 43 characters (type ANY) formatted in the           following way:</p>
        <p style="list-style-type: lower-roman;">
            <p value="1">      Up to 24 characters (type ANY) must be a valid           entry on the <b>FILE.CONTROL</b> file, followed by,</p>
            <p value="2">      A (greater than) sign, followed by,</p>
            <p value="3">    Up to 18 characters (type A) must be a valid           entry on the multi-value field <b>SYS.FIELD.NAME</b> on the           <b>STANDARD.SELECTION</b> record for the file specified in           (i).</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b>     The values input in this field and the previous field,           must be in agreement with the Format rules of the           element indicated in Field 5.1. </p>
        <p>E.g., the           input in Field 5.1 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic,           a minimum input of 10 characters will be required in           this field.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> See Details for format.</p>
            <p value="2"> It may only be input if corresponding DATA COMPARISON (Field 6) contains EQ (Equal To) or NE (Not Equal To).</p>
            <p value="3"> Must not be less than DATA FROM (Field 7.1)</p>
            <p value="4">
                <p> Multi-valued field associated with Fields 2.1-7.1</p>
            </p>
            <p value="5">
                <p> (Optional input if Field 6 contains EQ or NE, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SMS.GROUP.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Uniquely identifies the <b>SMS</b> group being created.</p>
        <p>  Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  1 to 14 alphanumeric characters. </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory input.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.END.TIME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the end of period or the log out time, at which the user is stopped from accessing the system, on a specific day, in the <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b>field.</p>
        <p>If the same field in USER record is empty, then the value in this field will be used. </p>
        <p><b>Note:</b> <![CDATA[ ]]></p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">
                <p>Always displayed with the format : </p>
            </p>
            <p value="2">For whole day/night login, start should be 00:00, end should be 24:00 (ie. 24 hours). </p>
        </p>
        <p data-mc-continue="true">
            <p value="3">Can be two or more separate periods each day, for the User to access the System, e.g. morning and afternoon, but not during lunchtime. </p>
        </p>
        <p data-mc-continue="true">
            <p value="4">If only 1 or 2 digits are entered, they correspond to minutes between midnight and 1 o clock in the morning.</p>
        </p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">1-4 numeric characters with optional : i.e. HHMM or HH:MM </p>
            <p value="2">Sub-value field associated with <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b> and <b>DAY.ST.TIME (</b>Optional input)</p>
            <p value="3">
                <p>Input can be 0-2359 or 0000-2359 or 00:00-23:59</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the functions, which are used to access the records of the Application, entered in the corresponding Field 2.</p>
        <p> This field is used, together with the associated Fields 2.1 - 3.1 and 5.1 - 8.1 to specify precisely, which function, the user uses to access, which record and application. </p>
        <p>Valid Function codes are:            A 2 C D E H I L P Q R S V </p>
        <p>  (A=Authorise, 2=2nd Authoriser, C=copy, D=Delete, E=Exception, H=History restore, I=Input, L=List, P=Print, Q=Auditor review, R=Reverse, S=See, V=Verify)</p>
        <p>  If NOT is entered, plus one or more Function codes, the System converts the code to a list of all the Functions that are allowed. </p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b>During an input function, even if the function C (copy) is not allowed, the user           will still be able to transfer the ID (together with its           enrichment) of a selected record using the !           facility.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 0-29 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters</p>
            <p value="2">Function codes separated by spaces or    </p>
            <p value="3">   NOT + one or more Function codes or </p>
            <p value="4">      N (No Functions allowed) or    </p>
            <p value="5">   ALL (All Functions allowed). </p>
            <p value="6">Multi-valued field associated with Fields 2.1-3.1 and 5.1-8.1 </p>
            <p value="7">Mandatory input.</p>
            <p value="8">No Default Value. </p>
            <p value="9">If Function 2 (2nd Authorization) is allowed, but not A (1st Authorization), the User is allowed to enter Function Code A - a Security Violation is generated if the record requested is not ready for 2nd Authorization.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEMP.FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the additional functions allowed for a user, for a temporary period of time.</p>
        <p>Valid Function codes are: A 2 C D E H I L P Q R S V.</p>
        <p>  If NOT is entered, followed by one or more function codes, the system converts it to a list of all the functions that are allowed.</p>
        <p>  Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  0-29     type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.</p>
            <p value="2">  Function     codes separated by spaces or</p>
            <p value="3">  NOT + one or more     Function codes or </p>
            <p value="4">  N- Function is not     allowed here.</p>
            <p value="5">  ALL (All Functions     allowed). </p>
            <p value="6">  Multi-valued field associated with Fields APPLICATION</p>
            <p value="7">  Mandatory input if <b>START.DATE</b> and <b>END.DATE</b> is specified. </p>
            <p value="8">No Default Value. </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOWED.DAYS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of days a user can access the system. It is taken from the associated fields <b>DAY.ST.TIME</b> and <b>DAY.END.TIME</b>. The values allowed are 1 to 7 meaning 1  MONDAY, 2  TUESDAY and 7  SUNDAY.</p>
        <p>If the <b>ALLOWED.DAYS</b> field in USER record is empty, then the value in this field will be used. </p>
        <p> The period set in the fields <b>START.TIME</b> and <b>END.TIME</b> (fields 10 ; 11) are applicable for all days of the week.</p>
        <p> The access time for a particular day will be taken from the fields <b>DAY.ST.TIME</b> and <b>DAY.END.TIME</b> if defined, otherwise the common <b>START.TIME</b> and <b>END.TIME</b> will be used.</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> 1- Numeric character. </p>
            <p value="2">Multi-valued field associated with <b>DAY.ST.TIME</b> and <b>DAY.END.TIME</b> (Optional input)</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies which Application is used in the group. </p>
        <p>  This field is used, together with the associated Fields 3.1 to 8.1, to specify precisely, which record in which Application, can be accessed by the User, using which Version and Function.</p>
        <p>It must be the name of an existing Application, the name of an existing <b>USER.SMS.GROUP</b> preceded by the '@' sign, ALL.PG to allow access to all Applications or ALL.PG (program type) to allow access to all Applications of a certain type (see below). </p>
        <p>  The following program types can be used in conjunction with ALL.PG (e.g. ALL.PG.H) to give access to a particular type of program:- </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Program Type Meaning </p>
        </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> <![CDATA[  ]]><b>H Program</b> - 3 standard files exist - Live, Unauthorised and History, e.g. CUSTOMER.</p>
        </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> <![CDATA[  ]]><b>U Program</b> - Live and Unauthorised files exist, but no History, e.g. VERSION.</p>
        </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> <![CDATA[  ]]><b>L Program</b> - only a Live file exists (updated automatically by the system) e.g. STMT.ENTRY (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program).</p>
        </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> <![CDATA[  ]]><b>M Program</b> - designed to do other than processing the standard T24 functions using a specific file e.g. PASSWORD.ENABLE, End Of Day Batch programs.</p>
        </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> <![CDATA[  ]]><b>T Program</b> - handles automatically updated CONCAT files, e.g. CUSTOMER.ACCOUNT (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program). </p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[  ]]><b>Note:</b> The following 3 type M programs are available to all users and cannot be restricted:-   <b>SIGN.ON SIGN.OFF PASSWORD </b></p>
        <p>  E.g. 1:</p>
        <p> To create a group which allows the User, to access to all Applications, using all Functions (except auditor review) and Versions of all Applications:</p>
        <p>Enter the following:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 2.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 3.1(VERSION)</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 4.1(FUNCTION) ALL</p>
        </p>
        <p><![CDATA[  ]]><b>Note:</b> Fields 5.1-8.1 are used to specify particular records or types of records, which may be accessed within an Application. See FIELD NO (Field 5.1) for examples. </p>
        <p>  E.g. 2:</p>
        <p>  To create a group which allows the User, to List, Display, Input and Copy Customer records and to List and Display records for all other Applications: </p>
        <p>Enter the following:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 2.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 4.1(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 2.2(APPLICATION) CUSTOMER</p>
            <p value="4"> Field 4.2(FUNCTION) L S I C</p>
        </p>
        <p>  E.g. 3:</p>
        <p>  To create a group which prevents a USER, from using any type M Applications, but allows the user to List and Display records in any other Applications: </p>
        <p>Enter the following:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Field 2.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.H</p>
            <p value="2"> Field 4.1(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="3"> Field 2.2(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.U</p>
            <p value="4"> Field 4.2(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="5"> Field 2.3(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.L</p>
            <p value="6"> Field 4.3(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p value="7"> Field 2.4(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.T</p>
            <p value="8"> Field 4.4(FUNCTION) L S</p>
        </p>
        <p>  Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  1-25 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters,         Application name. </p>
            <p value="2">ALL.PG to allow all Applications. </p>
            <p value="3">ALL.PG (program type) see details. </p>
            <p value="4">  Multi-valued field associated with Fields 3.1 to 8.1.         (Mandatory input in each set of Fields 2.1 - 8.1).</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.COMPARISON</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the type of comparison, made between the contents of the field, indicated in FIELD NO (Field 5.1) and Fields 7.1 and 8.1. </p>
        <p>  The meanings of the Input are as follows: </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">           EQ   Equal to            GE   Greater than or </p>
            <p value="2">Equal to            GT   Greater Than            LE   Less than or </p>
            <p value="3">Equal to            LT   Less Than            NE   Not Equal to            LK   Like            UL   Unlike </p>
        </p>
        <p>  User can access the records, only if the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 5.1), satisfies the conditions indicated in Fields 6.1 to 8.1. </p>
        <p>  For examples see FIELD NO (Field 5.1). </p>
        <p>  Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  EQ, GE, GT, LE, LT, NE, LK, UL or no input. </p>
            <p value="2">Multi-valued field associated with Fields 2.1 to 5.1 and 7.1 to 8.1. </p>
            <p value="3">Mandatory input if FIELD NO (Field 5.1) is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.FROM</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies a value, or start of a range of values, with which the contents indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) are  compared.</p>
        <p>  1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
        <p>  Or         Up to 43 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following            way: </p>
        <p style="list-style-type: lower-roman;">
            <p value="1">       up to 24 characters (type ANY), must be a valid            entry on the <b>FILE.CONTROL</b> file, followed by, </p>
            <p value="2">       a gt (greater than) sign, followed by, </p>
            <p value="3">       up to 18 characters (type A) must be a valid entry            in the multi-valued field <b>SYS.FIELD.NAME</b> on the            <b>STANDARD.SELECTION</b> record for a file specified in            (i). </p>
        </p>
        <p> Specifies either a single value or a lower limit range value, with which the contents indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) are compared.</p>
        <p><![CDATA[ ]]><b>Note:</b> The values input in this field and the next field must be in agreement with the Format rules of the element specified in Field 21.1. </p>
        <p>E.g. the input in Field 21 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic - a minimum input of 3 characters is required in this field.</p>
        <p> When defining the enquires, a user can run, and also turn off all SMS checks for a particular enquiry. This is useful when the enquiry presents non sensitive information from sensitive files. </p>
        <p>i.e. you may wish to show customer and account static information (address, account titles etc ) but not the balances. </p>
        <p>As the enquiry by itself controls the presentation, there may be no need for any additional security. To suppress SMS you must append *NOSMS to the name of the enquiry. </p>
        <p> E.g. </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Field 2.1  (APPLICATION)      ENQUIRY.SELECT </p>
            <p value="2">Field 4.1  (FUNCTION)         I </p>
            <p value="3">Field 5.1  (FIELD.NO)         0 </p>
            <p value="4">Field 6.1  (DATA.COMPARISON)  EQ </p>
            <p value="5">Field 7.1  (DATA.FROM)        CUSTOMER.STATIC*NOSMS </p>
        </p>
        <p>  This mechanism works only with ENQUIRY.SELECT and must be entered in the format detailed above. </p>
        <p>  Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">  See details for format.</p>
            <p value="2">  Input must begin and/or end with 3 dots when DATA.COMPARISON = LK or UL</p>
            <p value="3">
                <p>Multi-valued field associated with Fields 2.1 to 6.1 and 8.1. </p>
            </p>
            <p value="4">
                <p>  Mandatory input if FIELD NO is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>