<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>EBS.AUTO.FUNCTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The T24 Auto Function allows records to be processed without user intervention at each record level. </p>
            <p>This facility can be used at takeover time to load data which has been written to the $NAU file in Hold Status and thus the T24 cross validation checks are performed on the data. </p>
            <p>This facility can also be used to Print a large number of records. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>KEYSTROKES</field>
<desc>
            <p>A sequence of automated actions to be applied to each of the selected records. </p>
            <p>Similar in function to INPUT.BUFFER field and allows the same type of input as described for that field. </p>
            <p>Any instructions entered in this field are executed after the sequence of instructions in INPUT.BUFFER. </p>
            <p>The "KEYSTROKE" instructions are executed in a slightly different way from those contained in "INPUT BUFFER".  They are for use in special cases only, where it is necessary to execute a sequence of commands which are not supported by the standard T24 Input Buffer (their behaviour can be likened to "forcing" the sequence of instructions). </p>
            <p>An example of this is the processing of Loans.and.Deposits records with schedules attached. </p>
            <p>The use of this field is only valid when processing in single-record groups. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 type A (alpha numeric) characters.  Multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Input only allowed if sample size is 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the field name from the associated standard selection record to be totalled across the records selected. </p>
            <p>Fields of type D or I may be used. If the field is not numeric a result of zero will be returned. If the field is a multivalued field then all the multivalues will be added into the total. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 50 type A (alpha numeric) characters.  Multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on the associated standard selection record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows selection criteria to be applied, i.e allows the user to select certain records from the file for processing. </p>
            <p>The UniVerse selection criteria apply. This field should contain whatever you wish to concatenate to the SELECT filename command, for your processing: </p>
            <p>           e.g. WITH @ID LIKE A... </p>
            <p>The multivalue field allows you to expand the selection request. </p>
            <p>If this field is left blank then the whole file is selected. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multivalue field. (Optional input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the version of the file input routine to be used if any. </p>
            <p>The file name is not entered only a comma followed by the version name. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 type A (alpha numeric) characters, starting with a comma.  (Optional input)</p>
            <p>The file name plus what is entered in this field must be on the VERSION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAMPLE.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of records to be processed before returning to the control screen. </p>
            <p>Records selected by EBS.AUTO.FUNCTION are processed in groups, the size of each group (or sample) being determined by this field. </p>
            <p>The program returns control to the EBS.AUTO.FUNCTION screen after each group of records is processed. </p>
            <p>The larger the sample size, the less frequently control returns to this screen and, consequently, the faster the entire process completes. </p>
            <p>A smaller sample size is useful in situations where the process may be interrupted, either by the user or by an error condition. </p>
            <p>If there is a problem with one of the records in the group for the sample size then the remaining records are not processed. </p>
            <p>The sample size controls where F4 pause option will come into effect (i.e. only after each full group). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters - Defaults to 1. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the text to be displayed with the associated total field. </p>
            <p>This field is to be used to display a narrative to the total produced due to the TOTAL FIELD. The &amp; character may be used to position the total within the narrative, otherwise the total will be appended. </p>
            <p>Example:   "TOTAL OF &amp; IS FOR DEBIT AMOUNT" </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Required if associated total field is present.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the file on which the auto function is to be processed. </p>
            <p>The file must have an associated H U L T or W type program of the same name as defined on the PGM.FILE. </p>
            <p>A sequence number is appended to the file name, thus allowing different auto-functions to be set up per file. </p>
            <p>On inputting the application name only, the users terminal number is concatenated on to the end of the id, as a default. </p>
            <p>Abbreviations may be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.SUFFIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the live or unauthorised file is to be processed. </p>
            <p>If this field is null then this routine uses the $NAU file for its processing. If the $NAU file is not available this field will be defaulted to NO which means the live file will be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the T24 function which is to be applied to each of the records selected. </p>
            <p>This field can contain any of the following: </p>
            <p>           A - Authorise            D - Delete            H - History            I - Input            P - Print            R - Reverse            S - See            V - Verify </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 character. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The function must be valid for file type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUT.BUFFER</field>
<desc>
            <p>A sequence of automated actions to be applied to each of the selected records. </p>
            <p>Each action is to be indicated in a separate value of this multivalued field. </p>
            <p>The following special inputs are recognised: </p>
            <p>a)   The keyword 'ID', which automatically brings up the next selected      record. </p>
            <p>b)   Function keys which are indicated by F1 F2 F3 etc. </p>
            <p>c)   Subroutines which are indicated by preceding the subroutine name with      the @ character. </p>
            <p>All other 'Input' is treated as a literal command as though is were typed at the keyboard. </p>
            <p>A typical sequence of actions would start with the keyword 'ID' and finish with the function key 'F5'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 type A (alpha numeric) characters.  Multivalue field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

