<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ENQUIRY.REPORT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>ENQUIRY.REPORT is an application which generates a report based on the parameters defined in the file ENQUIRY. It can be run either as an on-line request, using the Verify function, or requested during the end of day via the job EB.PRINT. </p>
            <p>Reports can be requested in FILE format if information is required for processing outside T24. </p>
            <p>To request during eod the following should be entered in the data field of the batch record: </p>
            <p>          6.1     JOB.NAME...... EB.PRINT           11.1.1  DATA.......... ENQ XXXXX </p>
            <p>Where XXXXX is the ENQUIRY.REPORT id. </p>
            <p>This ENQUIRY.REPORT record should contain the ID of the ENQUIRY, any sort or selection criteria and the report control ID for spooling. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.13</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.14</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTPUT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the format of the report. </p>
            <p>The output can either be in report format, intended for printing, or can be in file format which can be used as an input file for spreadsheet or WP analysis. </p>
            <p>The report format is exactly as defined on the ENQUIRY, with headers, correct column positions, page breaks, etc. </p>
            <p>The file format is simply the data produced by the ENQUIRY output as rows and columns. Columns are separated by a TAB, ascii character 9, and rows are separated by a LF, ascii character 10. All data is enclosed in quotes (double quotations) and any multi/subvalue fields are delimited by LF and SPACE respectively. </p>
            <p>In addition the field names can be inserted as the first row as a header (used by spreadsheets and WPs as column headers) by specifiying the column headers in the HEADER field of the ENQUIRY record. </p>
            <p>Note : The data output in file format is in the order in which the ENQUIRY fields are processed and is not based on the column settings. </p>
            <p>Note : For file format the TOP.MARGIN and BOTTOM.MARGIN in the related DE.FORM.TYPE record must be set to zero. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be one of the following: REPORT Output will be in         report format (default) FILE Output will be in file         format with TAB separated columns null Same as REPORT         (default)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the selection values required for the associated SELECTION and OPERAND defined in order to produce the report. </p>
            <p>This field is sub valued. Each sub value represents an additional selection value for the assocaited SELECTION and OPERAND. Multiple values can also be separated by spaces. </p>
            <p>This field is optional unless otherwise specified by the value in REQUIRED.SEL in the underlying ENQUIRY record for the associated SELECTION. In this case a value must be entered. </p>
            <p>Where no value is entered, all items will be selected which satisfy the associated OPERAND. </p>
            <p>When EQ operand is used the value entered willbe validated at F5 using the SYS.VAL.PROG defined in STANDARD.SELECTION for the SELECTION field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Selection fields to be used when producing the report. Each multivalue is considered to be an additional selection field. </p>
            <p>The selection entered must be defined as a type D, I, J, C, R or S FIELD.TYPE in the STANDARD.SELECTION record of the FILE.NAME defined in the ENQUIRY record identified in the field ENQUIRY. </p>
            <p>When a new ENQUIRY is entered, or is modified, the SELECTION field is automatically populated with the SELECTION.FLDS defined in the underlying enquiry record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>18 Alphanumeric (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the REPORT.CONTROL record which controls the form and ultimate output destination of the report. </p>
            <p>Where FILE output is required the REPORT.CONTROL record should specify a "form" suitable for file output. The appropriate form, specified in the field FORM.NAME on the REPORT.CONTROL record and defined in DE.FORM.TYPE, should have TOP.MARGIN and BOTTOM margin set to zero (not null) to prevent spacing lines and form feeds in the output file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>30 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the fields which will be used as the sort sequence for the report. </p>
            <p>If you require the report contents to be sorted then enter the names of the sort sequence fields, e.g. </p>
            <p>6.1       CATEGORY 6.2       CURRENCY </p>
            <p>This will sort the report in ascending order of currency within category. If you require descending order then enter: </p>
            <p>6.1       CATEGORY 6.2       WORKING.BALANCE DSND </p>
            <p>This will sort the report in descending order of balance within ascending order of category. </p>
            <p>Note : No validation is peformed when entering SORT. The data is verified        when processing the report. Any errors are printed in the report        itself. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>40 alphanumeric characters. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the operand to be used when with the associated SELECTION field and LIST to produce the report. </p>
            <p>This field will default from the underlying enquiry when the ENQUIRY field is modified, if there is only one SEL.FLD.OPER defined for the SELECTION. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input -  only EQ, NE, UL, LK, NR, RG, LE, LT, GE, GT, CT, NC, BW, EW, DNBW, DNEW                  allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.15</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi language Heading for the Enquiry Report. </p>
            <p>If the Enquiry Report has to be printed with a Standard           Heading (defined in field 6 - STANDARD.HEADING), the           contents of this field will be part of the Standard Heading           of the Report. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 35 Alphanumeric characters. Optional field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.HDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi language Heading for the Enquiry Report. </p>
            <p>If the Enquiry Report has to be printed with a Standard Heading (defined in STANDARD.HEADING), the contents of this field will be part of the Standard Heading of the report. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 alphanumeric characters (optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STANDARD.HEADING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines if a T24 standard report header should be printed on the report. This is in addition to any headers defined in the ENQUIRY itself. </p>
            <p>Defines the type of standard header required, if any: </p>
            <p>     80        Print a standard 80 column header      132       Print a standard 132 column header      blank   Do not print a standard header </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>80, 132 or blank (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDITIONAL.DATA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to store any additional information about the report. </p>
            <p>This field can also be used to pass data to the ENQUIRY accessable via a 'link' - see ENQUIRY field CONVERSION. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>40 alphanumeric characters. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-language description of enquiry report. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>35 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of ENQUIRY record which contains the parameters for building the report. </p>
            <p>Key to the report parameters. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>32 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry on the file ENQUIRY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of ENQUIRY.REPORT record. Has no special significance in the system but it is recommended that this is the same name as the ENQUIRY record itself. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>25 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

