<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ENQUIRY.MENU</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds the details of the enquiry menus defined on the system. </p>
            <p>Each menu can define a list of enquiries to be invoked and/or linked to other enquiry menus. </p>
            <p>The menus defined here are invoked via application "MENU". </p>
            <p>A default menu called "MAIN.MENU" can be defined to contain a list of all the lower level enquiry menus that can be invoked. </p>
            <p>This "MAIN.MENU" is invoked by default when the "MENU" application is entered at the T24 "AWAITING APPLICATION" action prompt without a menu name. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TITLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the title to be displayed at the top of the menu. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROMPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the option name that is to appear on the menu. </p>
            <p>The name specified here will appear as a selection item on the menu page and hence should describe the enquiry/menu (to be invoked) specified in LINK.NAME. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-30 (type A) alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.PROMPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields LL.PROMPT to LINK.NAME form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.MENU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name by which the enquiry menu will be referenced. </p>
            <p>The enquiry menu name specified here is used to identify the menu when it is referenced from within other menus and also when it is displayed via the MENU application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-15 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.PROMPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the option name that is to appear on the menu. </p>
            <p>The name specified here will appear as a selection item on the menu page and hence should describe the enquiry/menu (to be invoked) specified in LINK.NAME. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-30 (type A) alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name of the enquiry/menu to be invoked for the selection prompt. </p>
            <p>An enquiry or menu name to be invoked for the selection prompt should be specified here.  The enquiry name will be passed to application ENQUIRY.SELECT to invoke the enquiry and hence must exist as a record on the ENQUIRY file. </p>
            <p>The name of the menu to be displayed must exist as a record in this file (ENQUIRY.MENU). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-32 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the type of routine i.e. enquiry or menu to be invoked for the selection prompt. </p>
            <p>The type specified here relates to the entry specified in LINK.NAME. </p>
            <p>          M - Indicates that the link is to another menu. </p>
            <p>          S - Indicates that it is an enquiry to be invoked via the               ENQUIRY.SELECT application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric character, 'M' or 'S'. M - The item to be invoked is another menu. S - The item to be invoked is an enquiry.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

