<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>ENQUIRY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds the parameter definitions of the enquiries used by the enquiry system. </p>
            <p>It allows the user/programmer to define an on-line enquiry without any coding requirements. Essentially the parameters specify the file to be listed, the fields to be displayed and where, the formats and conversions to be applied prior to display and the break points (if any) to be used. </p>
            <p>In addition to this, the parameters can also define internally calculated data, totals/sub-totals, decision processing, user routines and finally a link to a lower level enquiry. </p>
            <p>Enquiries may be used to produce reports online, or from the end of day, by using the ENQUIRY.REPORT application to execute the report. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SINGLE.MULTI</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies that the instruction should be processed for every multi/ sub-value occurrence. </p>
            <p>If 'M' is specified the instruction will be processed for every multi-value and sub-value occurrence within the data record. All multi-value/sub-value fields are taken to be associated and aligned accordingly on the screen. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Either S or M (single or multi). If null is specified then S is used as the default.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LENGTH.MASK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines output length or mask for display. </p>
            <p>Any valid FMT operation is accepted (see INFO-BASIC manual for more detail on the FMT instruction). </p>
            <p>Standard formats are 30L, 19R etc. (30 bytes left justified with space padding and 19 bytes right justified). </p>
            <p>Additional display options may be appended to the length or mask to utilise the screen display attributes in classic T24. Options are: </p>
            <p>   ^RV       Use the REVERSE video attribute    ^UL       Use the UNDERLINE attribute    ^HI       Use the HALF.INTENSITY attribute    ^BL       Use the BLINK attribute    ^DING     Sound warning beep </p>
            <p>If no length/mask is specified then the data is output as it stands. Always specify a length/mask when displaying data outside the enquiry page as this area is not cleared when moving between pages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIXED.SORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the fixed sort field names. </p>
            <p>This specifies the dictionary field names for the primary sort which will be performed with the users selection criteria. A descending sort can be specified by entering 'DSND' after the sort fieldname. </p>
            <p>Examples: CUSTOMER     - Ascending sort by customer. </p>
            <p>          ACCOUNT DSND - Descending sort by Account number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-23 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAGE.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>These co-ordinates define the screen page which will be used by the enquiry. </p>
            <p>These co-ordinates represent the variable portion of the screen used to display the enquiry pages. Hence it is cleared prior to output of a page. </p>
            <p>It does not restrict the enquiry from addressing other areas of the screen, but it should be noted that these areas are not refreshed automatically by moving from one page to the next. </p>
            <p>Typically the page is used for line details leaving the remainder of the screen available for headings etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>XX,YY where XX defines the first line of the page and YY the last. Must be numeric, in the range 0 - 99, and be separated by a ','.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines a name for the enquiry 'field' and is used as a reference for the current value by other enquiry instructions. </p>
            <p>The field name allows you identify a enquiry instruction so that its current value can be referenced by another instruction, e.g. a break or total field. Other than this, it is provided only for the sake of clarity. </p>
            <p>If the name is equal to one of the field names on the FILE.NAME's Standard Selection record then the OPERATION field is defaulted to the name of that field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>18 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTI.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOOL.BRK.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies fields which on change of value between pages, will cause a new spool record to be generated for reports. </p>
            <p>When enquiries are used to produce reports (via ENQUIRY REPORT application), the enquiry will be produced as a single report. </p>
            <p>Certain reports may be required to produce output for particular Customers and Accounts, where it would be advantageous to create a separate report for each Customer or Account.  By specifying the relevant field name here, if the value changes between pages, a new spool record will be created. </p>
            <p>This will primarily be used to allow Enquiries to be produced for a Customer so that the output can be Held if required, in the same way as output from the delivery system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 18 'A' alphanumeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be defined previously on the Enquiry as a FIELD NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.LEVEL.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POPUP.DROPDOWN.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify which fields should popup a new window for dropdowns,to allow the display of all records instead of the default of 200 records. Used for Enquiry Selection Screen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMP.FOR.ENQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUILD.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Routine to be invoked prior to the selection phase when running the enquiry. This routine must have one passed argument which will contain the following: </p>
            <p>ENQ&lt;1&gt; = NAME OF ENQUIRY</p>
            <p>ENQ&lt;2,1&gt; = SELECTION FIELD NAMES (USER INPUT)</p>
            <p>ENQ&lt;3,1&gt;= ASSOCIATED OPERANDS</p>
            <p>(EQ,LK etc.. ENQ&lt;4,1&gt; = DATA LIST e.g: SUBROUTINE ONLINE.REVAL(ENQ) </p>
            <p>These routines should can be used to manipulate the data prior to selection. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-32 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NXT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>This is a language field. It accepts only text.The text specified here is displayed as the next level description. This field is associated with the fields from ENQUIRY.NAME to NXT.DESC.</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the enquiry instruction or 'field'. </p>
            <p>The field is defaulted if the FIELD.NAME field is populated with a field name that is found on the FILE.NAME's Standard Selection record. </p>
            <p>The following instructions are supported: </p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>FIELD.NAME</td>
                    <td>Dynamically locates the field reference by using FILE.NAME's STANDARD.SELECTION record. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>FIELD.NO</td>
                    <td>Field reference in Numeric format. (0 - ID) (Not recommended only use in cases where the (1-999) record is built by a routine and does not follow the layout of the file used - see USE.FIELD.NUMBERS) </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>IDESC XXX </td>
                    <td>Execute the I-descriptor defined in the STANDARD.SELECTION record of the FILE, as a Type I or J item, with the FIELD.NAME XXX. The result is returned in the same way as if the field was extracted from the record. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SELECTION XXX</td>
                    <td>Return the value of the SELECTION.FIELD XXX entered in the selection criteria. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>FIELD XXX</td>
                    <td>Extract current value of enquiry field XXX.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>TOTAL XXX</td>
                    <td>Total enquiry field XXX. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>BREAK CHANGE XXX</td>
                    <td>Break on change of enquiry field XXX. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>BREAK LINE NN</td>
                    <td>Break when line NN has been exceeded. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CALC XXX + YYY</td>
                    <td>Add enquiry field XXX and YYY. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CALC XXX / YYY </td>
                    <td>Divide enquiry field XXX by enquiry field YYY. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CALC XXX * YYY</td>
                    <td>Multiply two enquiry fields.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CALC XXX - YYY</td>
                    <td>Subtract two enquiry fields. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CALC XXX : YYY</td>
                    <td>Concatenate two enquiry fields. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>IF AA GT BB XXX YYY</td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Decision process. If enquiry field AA is greater than enquiry field BB then process enquiry field XXX or process enquiry field YYY and return the value to this enquiry field. The valid operands are EQ, NE, GT, LT, GE, LE, RG, NR, LK, UL. </p>
                        <p>Field is Subvalued to allow the decision criteria to span more than a single line for clarity.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>"zzzzz"</td>
                    <td>Use the constant contained in quotes. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>!USER</td>
                    <td>Extract current user id.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>!TODAY</td>
                    <td>Extract todays date.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>!COMPANY</td>
                    <td>Extract current company id.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>!LANGUAGE</td>
                    <td>Extract user's language code. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>!LOCAL.CCY</td>
                    <td>Extract local currency code.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>!LAST.WORKING.DAY</td>
                    <td>Extract last working day. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>!NEXT.WORKING.DAY</td>
                    <td>Extract next working day. </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>The result of the instruction is always stored in the enquiry field. The use of spaces in the syntax of the instruction must be strictly adhered to, although the instructions themselves can be abbreviated to a single character. eg 'BREAK CHANGE XXX' can be specified as 'B C XXX' </p>
            <p>Important note: Never reference a record field (XXX or 0-999) during the processing of a break. Always reference enquiry fields (FIELD XXX). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input. 32 characters (full character set).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REAL.TIME.FILES</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>This will hold the name of the files that will trigger Real Time Enquiry processing via JOURNAL.UPDATE</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Multi-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where enquiry data is exported via OFS, this field is used to determine in which area of the enquiry the data belongs.</p>
            <p>This information is not currently used elsewhere.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field that specifies whether the ENQUIRY should be exposed or not </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1. Length of 3 characters</p>
            <p>2. Options are 'YES', 'NO', ''</p>
            <p>3. No-input if 'PW' is not installed in the COMPANY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COL.WIDTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field only applies to T24 Browser. </p>
            <p>Users can specify a number of pixels wide that an ENQUIRY column should be. </p>
            <p>Note this 'width' is not an absolute fixed width, it is more like a minimum width with restrictions. These restrictions are as follows:</p>
            <p> a) Column widths will grow to accomodate the widest 'word' or image in the column. A 'word' is any sequence of characters that doesn't contain a space, for example 'SELF-EMPLOYED', 'NEW.CUSTOMER' are all considered as single words by the browser.</p>
            <p> b) Columns with 'left over' space created by larger than required COL.WIDTH values will shrink if there is not enough space in the window, frame or fragment to display all columns. However columns will never shrink so much that the first restriction is violated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 Integer characters. Note it is possible that some enquiries can define several fields as belonging to the same COLUMN, for example a field could be in '1' and another in COLUMN '1,+1'. These fields should be given the same COL.WIDTH values. If they are different, only the last specified value will count.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLUMN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the screen co-ordinates to display the enquiry field. </p>
            <p>Defines the exact or relative screen position to display the field value. The following formats are accepted: </p>
            <p>Column          Action </p>
            <p>''              Null - field will not be displayed. </p>
            <p>CC              Field will be displayed at column CC on the current line. </p>
            <p>CC,LL           Field will be displayed in column CC on line LL.                 (exact positioning, normally used for variable heading                 data). </p>
            <p>cc,+nn          Field will be displayed in column cc on the current line +                 nn lines (also supports -nn).                 Note that when a multi/sub value field is displayed.                 Each item will be displayed +nn lines from the last. </p>
            <p>cc,+nnM         Field will be displayed in column cc on the current line +                 nn lines (also supports -nn).                 When a multi/sub value field is displayed ONLY the first                 item will be displayed +nn lines, each subsequent item                 will be displayed on the next line. </p>
            <p>P               Used only in conjunction with break instructions -                 performs page 'throw' when break condition met. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATIC.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LABEL.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the enquiry field name to be numbered when a next level enquiry can be invoked. </p>
            <p>In order to invoke the next level enquiry the user must be able to select an item from the enquiry screen. This entry simply specifies the enquiry field which, every time it is displayed, will cause an incrementing number to be output. The number is restarted for every page. </p>
            <p>The number is displayed in column 0 on the same line as the specified enquiry field. It occupies two characters so the first available position for data is column 3. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>11 type A. Must be a valid enquiry field name.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NXT.LVL.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is a multi language field. Fields ENQUIRY.NAME to NXT.LVL.DESC form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. This field accepts only text .The text specified here is displayed as the next level description.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.CRIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Selection criteria for the next (drill down) enquiry to be invoked. This fields defines additional selections to be applied to the ENQUIRY for the drop-down list.</p>
            <p> Fields ENQUIRY.NAME to NXT.LVL.DESC form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p>Valid only when invoking another enquiry on the next level (not used when calling an application). </p>
            <p>If any of the 'words' correspond to an enquiry field name then the contents of the field are used instead of the literal. Normally the 'value' corresponds to an enquiry field but the same applies to the selection name and operand.</p>
            <p>The value of the field can contain the use of a system variable (e.g. TODAY, COMPANY, etc.).  For example, "DATE EQ !TODAY"</p>
            <p>The value of the field can contain the use of a user-defined variable (e.g. CURRENT.CUSTOMER, CURRENT.ACCOUNT, etc.).  For example, "DATE EQ !CURRENT.DATE"</p>
            <p>The value of the field can be used to set a user-defined variable (e.g. CURRENT.CUSTOMER, CURRENT.ACCOUNT, etc.).  For example, "CURRENT.DATE&gt;DATE" where DATE is a field on the enquiry, or using a literal as the value as in  "CURRENT.DATE&gt;20070101"</p>
            <p>In order to use the value of a variable an "!" character must be used preceding the variable name.  For example, a field can be defaulted to today's date by using "!TODAY" or the value of a user-defined variable containing a customer number by using "!CURRENT.CUSTOMER".</p>
            <p>In order to set the value of a user-defined variable a "&gt;" character must be used between the variable name and the variable value.  For example, "CURRENT.DATE&gt;DATE", or "CURRENT.DATE&gt;20070101".</p>
            <p>To set a list of values for a user-defined variable each value must be surrounded by "[]" characters.  For example, "CURRENT.ACCOUNTS&gt;[10010][100011][100012]"</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must contain a SELECTION.FLD as defined on the related ENQUIRY record.</p>
            <p>A valid SELECTION FLD followed by - a valid OPERATOR followed by - data in quotes.  The valid operands are EQ, NE, GT, LT, GE, LE, RG, NR, LK, UL.</p>
            <p>Example setting : CUSTOMER EQ CUST.ID VALUE.DATE EQ V.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BREAK.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOL.ITEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The item (command) to be run when the Browser tool on the toolbar is selected.</p>
            <p>If this is not specified then the ITEM defined in the BROWSER.TOOL record which will be used.</p>
            <p>If a JavaScript function is not supplied then the 'docommand' JavaScript function will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 'A' alphanumeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.FLD.OPER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines for the associated SELECTION.FLDS, which operands are allowed for the enquiry. </p>
            <p>This field allows the selection operands to be limited for a particular enquiry.  This may be required where the enquiry is based on one particular selection value, for example an enquiry based on Account movements may wish to restrict the BOOKING.DATE selection to RG or EQ. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null, EQ, NE, GT, GE, LT, LE, RG, NR, CT, NC, BW, EW, LK, DNBW or DNEW or any combination separated by a space. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.LVL.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 20 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.BREAK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines enquiry field to be processed only when a break condition is met. </p>
            <p>This field will only be processed when the break condition has been met. In the case of total fields, the total will be displayed (providing Column has been specified) and the current total cleared. </p>
            <p>Never specify a record field extract (0-999) to be processed on a break. This will extract the field from the data record which caused the break and not the previous record. Always use the FIELD XXX instruction instead. </p>
            <p>Standard break names are provided for certain conditions. They are: </p>
            <p>ONCE     Only processed once at the beginning of the enquiry END      Only processed at the end of the enquiry NEWPAGE  Processed at the start of every new page NONE     Only processed if no records matched the selection criteria. </p>
            <p>be used to process </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>15 type A (alphanumeric) characters. The name of the enquiry field which defines the break or one of the standard names.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows data to be converted prior to display. </p>
            <p>The conversion operation allows the manipulation of the result of an enquiry operation. The result of the conversion is then stored in the enquiry field. The following conversions are supported: </p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Conversion</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Action</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>FIELD X,N1,N2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Extract from the data, delimited by X, the N1th field to the N2th</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>DECRYPT Field.Name</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>DECRYPT is a standard text to inform T24 that this field is sensitive and the routine attached to the field ENQ.DECRYPT.RTN in EB.ENC.PARAMETER parameter table is to be called either for decrypting or masking the data</p>
                        <p>Field.Name must be a valid field name in the enquiry</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>EXTRACT N1,N2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Extract from the data starting at position N1 for N2 bytes</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>SUBSTITUTE X,Y</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>If the data equals X then replace it with Y.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>CONVERT X,Y</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Replace every occurrence of the character X with Y.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>VALUE X,Y</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Extract value X, sub-value Y from the data.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>JULIAN</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Convert the data from YYYYMMDD format to system internal format.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>OCONV XXX</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Convert data using Basic OCONV instruction XXX. See Basic manual</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>ICONV XXX</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Convert data using Basic ICONV instruction XXX. See Basic manual.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>LINK XXX,YYY</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Read file XXX using the current data as the key and return field name YYY as defined in the STANDARD.SELECTION record for XXX. Do not specify F. or company mnemonic in file name. Field Name YYY may be a data field or an I or J descriptor defined in the Standard Selection record of file XXX Note that if a multi or sub valued item is returned from a LINK conversion, the multi and sub values are converted to spaces, so the result cannot be displayed in separate lines. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>UTIL FIXEQU,ccy field</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Returns the equivalent value of an amount in a currency contained in the field ccy field. The rate used is the FIXED.RATE defined in the CURRENCY record. If no FIXED.RATE is specified a null value is returned. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>UTIL FIXRTE,ccy field</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Returns the rate used to convert an amount to the Fixed currency specified in the CURRENCY held in the field ccy field. If no FIXED.CCY is defined, a null value is returned. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>UTIL FIXCCY,ccy field</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Returns the equivalent currency linked to the currency defined in the field ccy field. If there is no FIXED.CCY defined, no value is returned. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>UTIL ABS </p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Return the Absolute value of an amount.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>UTIL MATCHFIELD XXX YYY</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Perform Basic MATCHFIELD function on XXX and YYY. See Basic manual</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>@ XXX </p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Call user subroutine XXX. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>$ XXX</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Call user subroutine XXX at selection stage only. Allows manipulation of user selection criteria. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>REPEAT</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Repeat previous data if current data is null - but only for the second and subsequent multi and subvalues - note: If the field you are displaying is subvalued then you will get repitition of mvalue=2 and svalue=1 (providing the data is null) because the mvalue is greater than one. If you do not want this then use REPEAT SUB</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>REPEAT SUB</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Repeat previous data if current data is null - only if the subvalue number is greater than one</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>REPEAT EVERY</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Repeat previous data if current data is null - regardless of multi/subvalue number</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>32 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid conversion as defined above.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of a BROWSER.TOOL record which will be displayed on the enquiry window in the toolbar.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a record in BROWSER.TOOLS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.BREAKS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.FIELD.NUMBERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether field numbers entered in the OPERATION field should not be converted to the relevant field name. </p>
            <p>Some enquiries may use a specified FILE.NAME for selection purposes, however a work record is constructed using a conversion routine in the body of the enquiry. Enquiry will usually attampt to convert a field number entered in the OPERATION field to the correct field name for the FILE.NAME, so that the enquiry is compatible with future file layout changes. However where the conversion routine builds a work record, this layout is fixed and should not be converted to the field name, as the layout may be entirely different. </p>
            <p>In order to suppress the conversion of the number entered in OPERATION to a name, a value of Y should be entered in this field. This will leave the field OPERATION as entered. Null and NO are treated in the same way. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Field. May be Y or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOL.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The text to be displayed on the Browser tool on the toolbar.</p>
            <p>If this is not specified then the TEXT defined in the BROWSER.TOOL record which will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 'A' alphanumeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINES.OSIDE.PAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.DISP.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The format of the field can be passed to external systems, for example via the Open Financial Service (OFS). Valid options are:</p>
            <p>DATE, NUMERIC, ALPHANUMERIC, AMOUNT and HIDDEN</p>
            <p>Using these values may assist in the formatting or totalling of data in external systems. The exact interpretation depends on the external system being used and is outside the control of T24.</p>
            <p>NO-EDIT: Applies to APPLICATION.ENQUIRY enquiries with the TARGET.FIELD set. By default such fields will be editable. Use the NO-EDIT property to override the default behaviour and make the field not-editable.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SMS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The enquiry field which holds the id of the record to be read from SMS.APPLICATION. </p>
            <p>Each time this enquiry field is processed then the record from SMS.APPLICATION will be read and subsequently verified for SMS. If it does not pass the SMS check then the current record will not be displayed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 18 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.GRAPH.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the main file to be accessed/displayed by the enquiry system. </p>
            <p>This specifies the main file to be processed. </p>
            <p>The file must be a valid entry on F.FILE.CONTROL and should not contain the 'F.' or 'FXXX.' prefix. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows further formatting of the data based on the type of field. </p>
            <p>This formatting is performed immediately prior to display (i.e. after conversion) </p>
            <p>CCY XXX Y Amount format using currency held in enquiry field XXX and the negative amount format specified in Y. Current valid formats are: </p>
            <p>E formats a -ve number as &lt;123,456.12&gt; M formats a -ve number as 123,456.12- B formats a -ve number as 123,456.12db N formats a -ve number as 123,456.12 null formats a -ve number as -123456.12 e.g. CCY CURRENCY E </p>
            <p>TRANSLATE Translate data using 'dynamic text' mechanism. </p>
            <p>LANGUAGE Extracts correct language value (based on users language code) from the multi-valued field. </p>
            <p>DATE Formats T24 internal date format (YYYYMMDD) to DD Mmm YYYY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The valid types are: CCY XXX TRANSLATE LANGUAGE DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOLBAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows a custom toolbar to be displayed when enquiry results are displayed.</p>
            <p>This toolbar takes precedence over defined tool items.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid BROWSER.TOOLBAR record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUIRED.SEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies for the associated SELECTION.FLDS whether selection criteria are mandatory for the enquiry. </p>
            <p>Certain Enquiries may require a specific selection field to be specified. This may be in cases where the selection field calls a routine or uses concat file processing to improve the performance of the enquiry, or simply to limit the scope of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Defines the Application / Product to which this Enquiry belongs eg: FX, MM etc.</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the EB.PRODUCT file.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the name by which the enquiry can be identified. </p>
            <p>This identifier is used when invoking the on-line enquiry, hence it should be made as meaningful as possible. </p>
            <p>If the ID is in the format %application, %application.P or %application$HIS then this enquiry will be used to list the application file, print it or list the application history file respectively. Note: The ID can also refer to the VERSION name hence %CUSTOMER,OPEN would be invoked when the user lists the cutomer file while running under the version ,OPEN.</p>
            <p>If the ID begins CURRENT.XXX then the first selection criteria entered is stored by the enquiry system and can be used in subsequent enquiries (by entering !CURRENT.XXX) see the user guide for more details.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>32 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SMS.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name of the application to be used for SMS verification. </p>
            <p>If an enquiry is based on a "NOFILE" application the only SMS verification which can take place is based on 'linked' data defined in the conversion field. In order to supplement these checks you can define, here, the name of the application whose SMS rules should be also be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 24 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional Input).</p>
            <p>The name entered must be the key to a record on FILE.CONTROL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SMS.ABORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate if the enquiry is to be aborted when the first SMS violation is recorded. </p>
            <p>The enquiry system will read and SMS verify all records it selects. This can be very time consuming if all the records fail the SMS checks. Consequently this flag enables the enquiry to abort at the first SMS violation encountered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Can be either Y or No. (Optional Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of purpose and function of enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>A   maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p> Should be completed where possible.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.SELECT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is used in a multi branch system to control enquiry access to financial level data.</p>
            <p>Multi branch indicates that the MB product is installed, the term Multi Book can also be used.</p>
            <p>This product basically allows financial level data to be stored in the same database table for all companies, as opposed to Multi Company where the data is stored in a separate table for each company.</p>
            <p>If this field is set to ALL then records will be selected for all companies, with the current SMS restrictions being applied to what the user can actually access.</p>
            <p>If this field is left blank then the data selected will be restricted to the current company. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Optional input of ALL      in a system with the MB product installed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINES.O.SIDE.PAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEADER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Static header details to be displayed at the start of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>The static text is displayed at the start of the enquiry (not every page) and is used for column headings, titles, etc. </p>
            <p>Text can be specified in the format: </p>
            <p>          @(C,L)AAAA @(C,L)XXXX etc... </p>
            <p>Multiple headings should be specified as sub-values of HEADER not multi-values. Multi-values are used for headings in a foreign language. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>42 Type A (alphanumeric) characters. The format is @(C,L)AAAA..... where @(C,L) is the screen column and line position and AAAA is the text to be displayed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSE.BRACKET</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The selection conditions can be grouped using the fields OPEN.BRACKET and CLOSE.BRACKET. Conditions enclosed in brackets are evaluated before those outside of the brackets.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Options YES or NO, Multi value, associated field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input not allowed if the corresponding SELECTION.FIELD is not entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p> Field to specify option of which file of the application, the enquiry can run </p>
            <p> Can enquire on unauthorised, live, history or simulation file</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be NAU,HIS,LIV,SIM</p>
            <p>Must be present in suffixes of FILE.CONTROL of the application specified in FILE.NAME</p>
            <p>Allows LIV though not present in suffix of FILE.CONTROL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.LABEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The text that will appear in the column heading for the data field defined in FIELD.NAME.</p>
            <p>This is use for grid style enquiries (refer to the ENQUIRY chapter of the System Administration Guide for further details) and also the export of enquiry data via the Open Financial Service (OFS).</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>A short description for an Enquiry to make more meaningful. This description appears in the title bar of an enquiry screen.</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the enquiry instruction or 'field'. </p>
            <p>The following instructions are supported: </p>
            <p>          Instruction         Action </p>
            <p>          0                   Extract ID of record. </p>
            <p>          1 - 999             Extract field nnn from record. </p>
            <p>          FIELD XXX           Extract current value of                               enquiry field XXX. </p>
            <p>          TOTAL XXX           Total enquiry field XXX. </p>
            <p>          BREAK CHANGE XXX    Break on change of enquiry                               field XXX. </p>
            <p>          BREAK LINE NN       Break when line NN has been                               exceeded. </p>
            <p>          CALC XXX + YYY      Add enquiry field XXX and                               YYY.           CALC XXX / YYY      Divide enquiry field XXX by                               enquiry field YYY. </p>
            <p>          CALC XXX * YYY      Multiply two enquiry fields. </p>
            <p>          CALC XXX - YYY      Subtract two enquiry fields. </p>
            <p>          CALC XXX : YYY      Concatenate two enquiry fields. </p>
            <p>          Instruction         Action </p>
            <p>          IF AA GT BB XXX YYY Decision process. If enquiry                               field AA is greater than enquiry                               field BB then process enquiry                               field XXX or process enquiry                               field YYY and return the value                               to this enquiry field. The valid                               operands are EQ, NE, GT, LT,                               GE, LE, RG, NR, LK, UL. </p>
            <p>          "zzzzz"             Use the constant contained in                               quotes. </p>
            <p>          !USER               Extract current user id.           !TODAY              Extract todays date.           !COMPANY            Extract current company id.           !LANGUAGE           Extract user's language code.           !LOCAL.CCY          Extract local currency code. </p>
            <p>          !LAST.WORKING.DAY   Extract last working day.           !NEXT.WORKING.DAY   Extract next working day. </p>
            <p>The result of the instruction is always stored in the enquiry field. The use of spaces in the syntax of the instruction must be strictly adhered to, although the instructions themselves can be abbreviated to a single character. eg 'BREAK CHANGE XXX' can be specified as 'B C XXX' </p>
            <p>Important note: Never reference a record field (0-999) during the processing of a break. Always reference enquiry fields (FIELD XXX). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>32 characters (full character set). Mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIXED.SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the fixed selection criteria for the enquiry. </p>
            <p>This specifies the primary selection to be performed when the enquiry is invoked. The general format of this field is: Field.name&lt;space&gt;operand&lt;space&gt;value. </p>
            <p>The value of the field can contain the use of a system variable (e.g. TODAY, COMPANY, etc.). </p>
            <p>The value of the field can contain the use of a user-defined variable (e.g. CURRENT.CUSTOMER, CURRENT.ACCOUNT, etc.).</p>
            <p>In order to use the value of a variable an "!" character must be used preceding the variable name.  For example, a field can be defaulted to today's date by using "!TODAY" or the value of a user-defined variable containing a customer number by using "!CURRENT.CUSTOMER".</p>
            <p>For example :</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>3.1 FIXED.SELECTION</td>
                    <td>APPLICATION.ID EQ LD</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>3.2 FIXED.SELECTION</td>
                    <td>TRANSACTION.TYPE UL O... </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>3.3 FIXED.SELECTION</td>
                    <td>DATE EQ !TODAY</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>3.4 FIXED.SELECTION</td>
                    <td>DATE EQ !CURRENT.DATE</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>Multiple fixed selections can be specified. The fixed selections are always executed first, before the selection criteria entered by the user.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>0 to 50 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the next enquiry or application to be invoked when descending enquiry levels. </p>
            <p>To envoke another enquiry the name of the enquiry should be entered. </p>
            <p>The next enquiry invoked will be XXXX.FUNCTION where FUNCTION has been entered by the user, eq S, P V etc. If this does not exist then XXXX will be invoked. </p>
            <p>To invoke an application (in See mode) you must specify the name of the application (or version), 'S' and the id of the application file, e.g. </p>
            <p>          MM.MONEY.MARKET SEE ID </p>
            <p>If any of the 'words' match the name of an enquiry field, then the field content is substituted in place of the 'word'. This mechanism allows variable data to determine the next level down. If the second 'word' is not 'S' or 'SEE' then the next level is determined to be an enquiry and not an application. </p>
            <p>To view a text record, such as a report the option VIEW should be specified. This needs to specify the file from which the text record is to be read, and the id of the record, separated by a "&gt;" character. </p>
            <p>For example, to view a report from HOLD.CONTROL the option </p>
            <p>        VIEW &amp;HOLD&amp;&gt;987654321 </p>
            <p>Should be specified, where 987654321 is the id of the report in the file &amp;HOLD&amp;. The file and id need not be specified explicitly but can be assigned in the same way as any field in enquiry. </p>
            <p>               CONTEXT BASED WORKFLOW                ---------------------- </p>
            <p>When defining next level enquiries for usage within the GUI driven Context Based Workflow, you should ensure that these are inserted after the default next level enquiry. This will ensure that the "Classic" version T24 enquiries continue to function as before. Only when enquiries are run under the GUI version of T24 can multiple enquiries be offered as the next level down. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Either an Enquiry Name, Application Name, or the option to display text, such as a report. See Enquiry field:  NEXT.ENQUIRY                         or APPLICATION SEE XXX                  or VIEW file&gt;ID (E.g &amp;HOLD&amp;&gt;9911223322)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows further formatting of the data based on the type of field. </p>
            <p>This formatting is performed immediately prior to display (i.e. after conversion) </p>
            <p>CCY XXX Y Amount format using currency held in enquiry field XXX and the negative amount format specified in Y. Current valid formats are: </p>
            <p>E formats a -ve number as &lt;123,456.12&gt; M formats a -ve number as 123,456.12- B formats a -ve number as 123,456.12db N formats a -ve number as 123,456.12 null formats a -ve number as -123456.12 e.g. CCY CURRENCY E </p>
            <p>TRANSLATE Translate data using 'dynamic text' mechanism. </p>
            <p>LANGUAGE Extracts correct language value (based on users language code) from the multi-valued field. </p>
            <p>DATE Formats T24 internal date format (YYYYMMDD) to DD Mmm YYYY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The valid types are: CCY XXX TRANSLATE LANGUAGE DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the defined field which contains the value of the customer number, to be used for purposes of spooling. </p>
            <p>When the Enquiry is used to produce a report from the ENQUIRY.REPORT module, the value in the nominated field will be passed to the Report Control system for each spooled record.  The report Control System will then be able to determine whether the report generated is to be spooled or held for the customer. </p>
            <p>Note that the field nominated should not be extracted on a page break as the previous value may be extracted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 18 'A' alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>The field must be defines as a FIELD NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.LBL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a language field. It accepts only text.The text specified here is displayed as the field label. This field is associated with the fields from FIELD.NAME to SINGLE.MULTI. </p>
            <p>Where a field label is not required "" can be entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 20 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p>Blank field labels should be entered as "".</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAGE.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REL.NEXT.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be set to AND or OR and the selection conditions are grouped using these relational operators. If the field is left blank then AND will be used as operator. It can be used in conjunction with the OPEN.BRACKET and CLOSE.BRACKET.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p>Options AND or OR, if left blank defaults to AND, Multi       value, associated</p>
            <p />field<p /><p /><p>Input not allowed if the next multi value set is not present</p><p /><p>Input not allowed if the corresponding SELECTION.FIELD is not entered.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIAB.LC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a new ENQUIRY and is basically the same as the standard enquiry LIAB except for the fact that this enquiry allows the user to include by means of a separate Selection Parameter LC.BENEFICIARY, all the Letter of Credit transactions (both Export and Import) where the  Liability Customer is the Beneficiary Customer of the LC (BENEFICIARY.CUSTNO). </p>
            <p>As a general rule, the amount that will be displayed from this Enquiry will be calculated as: LC Original Amount + (Positive) Tolerance - Drawings Amount </p>
            <p> converted into the Local Currency. </p>
            <p>However, if the Drawings under any LC are of the AC or the DP type and they have not been discounted, they will still be taken into account and included in the total balance that is displayed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.LABEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a language field and accepts a description. The text in this field is displayed in the selection window. This field forms a related multi value set with the fields from SELECTION.FLDS to REQUIRED.SEL.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 20 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.BRACKET</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The selection conditions can be grouped using the fields OPEN.BRACKET and CLOSE.BRACKET. Conditions enclosed in brackets are evaluated before those outside of the brackets.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Options YES or NO, Multi value, associated field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input not allowed if the corresponding SELECTION.FIELD is not       entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Applies to application enquiries (see ATTRIBUTES/APPLICATION.ENQUIRY). Specifies the field name on the TARGET.APPLICATION that the field should map to.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field that contains the ID of an EB.SERVICE record. It may be an existing record. If the record is not present, then upon authorising the ENQUIRY, a new record is created.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1. Length of 35 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p>2. If EXPOSE is set to 'YES', then this field is mandatory</p>
            <p>3. No-input if EXPOSE is not set to 'YES'</p>
            <p />
            <p>The following validations/processing is done based on the fields SERVICE and ACTIVITY.</p>
            <p>If both SERVICE and ACTIVITY do not exist, then a new activity is created in PW.ACTIVITY, with the TARGET field mapped to the Enquiry and a new record is created in EB.SERVICE with the activity added to it.</p>
            <p>If the SERVICE is existing EB.SERVICE and ACTIVITY does not exist in PW.ACTIVITY,a new activity is created in PW.ACTIVITY and the same is appended to the EB.SERVICE record.</p>
            <p>If SERVICE does not exist and ACTIVITY exists, a check is done to ensure that the activity relates to this Enquiry, i.e. the TARGET field in PW.ACTIVITY is mapped correctly, otherwise an error message is thrown. Then, a new EB.SERVICE record is created with the activity added to it.</p>
            <p>If both SERVICE and ACTIVITY exists and the activity relates to the Enquiry, a check is done to ensure that the EB.SERVICE does not contain the ACTIVITY.ID already.Otherwise an error message is thrown. Finally,EB.SERVICE is updated with the activity appended to it.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OF.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal field used for processing of the enquiry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the selection fields to be displayed in the ENQUIRY.SELECT application. </p>
            <p>Specify here the selection field names to be displayed in the ENQUIRY.SELECT application. If this field is left blank then all the selection field names (from STANDARD.SELECTION) will be displayed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-18 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the associated field and processing. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 50 alphanumeric characters (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSE.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the exposed ENQUIRY.This would be updated in the DESCRIPTION fields of both PW.ACTIVITY and EB.SERVICE,when they are newly created from the ENQUIRY </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1. Length of 35 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p>2. If EXPOSE is set to 'YES', then this field is mandatory</p>
            <p>3. No-input if EXPOSE is not set to 'YES'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Applies to application enquiries (see ATTRIBUTES/APPLICATION.ENQUIRY). Specifies the application to be operated on by the enquiry.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CONVERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag to indicate if the enquiry is to be automatically converted if fields are added to or deleted from a file used by this ENQUIRY. </p>
            <p>This field will be used to determine if field numbers in this enquiry will be automatically incremented or decremented if fields are added to or deleted from the file in the FILE.NAME field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Can be either Y or NO (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.MANDATORY.SELECTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>             An optional field. </p>
        <p>Allows to input values in either REQUIRED.SEL or NO.MANDATORY.SELECTION</p>
        <p>While designing an enquiry, if the field NO.MANDATORY.SELECTION is input with a value, then the field REQUIRED.SEL values should be removed.</p>
        <p>If the value is not input in the field SELECTION.FLDS then the system disallows to input in the field NO.MANDATORY.SELECTION</p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Optional field</p>
            <p value="2">Numeric field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the defined field which contains the value of the account number, to be used for purposes of spooling. </p>
            <p>When enquiry is used to produce a report from the ENQUIRY.REPORT module, the value in the nominated field will be passed to the Report Control system for each spooled record.  The report control system will then be able to determine whether output for the report and the specified account is to be spooled or held. </p>
            <p>In order for the full definition of DE.PRODUCT records for Held Customer output to be utilised, a CUSTOMER.FLD.NO should be defined with this field. </p>
            <p>Note that the field nominated should not be extracted on a page break, as the previous value may be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 18 'A' alphanumeric characters.  (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be defined as a FIELD NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field that contains the ID of a PW.ACTIVITY record. It may be an existing record. If the record is not present, then upon authorising the ENQUIRY, a new record is created.</p>
            <p>The ID of the new PW.ACTIVITY record created through the ENQUIRY will have prefix 'WS.'</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1. Length of 35 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p>2. If EXPOSE is set to 'YES', then this field is mandatory</p>
            <p>3. No-input if EXPOSE is not set to 'YES'</p>
            <p />
            <p>The following validations/processing is done based on the fields SERVICE and ACTIVITY.</p>
            <p>If both SERVICE and ACTIVITY do not exist, then a new activity is created in PW.ACTIVITY, with the TARGET field mapped to the Enquiry and a new record is created in EB.SERVICE with the activity added to it.</p>
            <p>If the SERVICE is existing EB.SERVICE and ACTIVITY does not exist in PW.ACTIVITY,a new activity is created in PW.ACTIVITY and the same is appended to the EB.SERVICE record.</p>
            <p>If SERVICE does not exist and ACTIVITY exists, a check is done to ensure that the activity relates to this Enquiry, i.e. the TARGET field in PW.ACTIVITY is mapped correctly, otherwise an error message is thrown. Then, a new EB.SERVICE record is created with the activity added to it.</p>
            <p>If both SERVICE and ACTIVITY exists and the activity relates to the Enquiry, a check is done to ensure that the EB.SERVICE does not contain the ACTIVITY.ID already.Otherwise an error message is thrown. Finally,EB.SERVICE is updated with the activity appended to it.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify attributes of the column, the following are defined:</p>
            <p>HIDDEN: The column will be collapsible, have an icon to show / hide the column.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Attributes that determine the behavior of the entire enquiry are held in this field. </p>
            <p>These attributes are only processed within the Graphical User Interface. </p>
            <p>The following attributes are currently used: </p>
            <p>REMOVE - Where a pick operation is performed on an enquiry grid, this flag will remove the item from the display. </p>
            <p>ALLDATA - Forces the retrieval of all data before the enquiry is displayed. </p>
            <p>APPLICATION.ENQUIRY - Browser only. Allows an enquiry to edit a record. Similar to fastpath enquiries but operates on a single record only rather than a list of records. Uses fields TARGET.APPLICATION and TARGET.FIELD.</p>
            <p>INCREMENTAL - For Browser only. Indicates that the enquiry should show all pages from page 1 up to the current page, as opposed to the the current page + the previous page.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input may only be REMOVE or ALL DATA. No duplicates are permitted. Nulls only permitted if no multi values have been expanded. </p>
            <p>REALTIME enables the enquiry to be user by a Real-time enquiry user, must be followed by a multi valued ATTRIBUTE field with  ZERORECORDSDISPLAYED flagged.</p>
            <p>Input can also be ZERORECORDSDISPLAY.</p>
            <p>NO.BREADCRUMBS - this will remove the list of previously viewed enquiry navigation links from the top of the screen.  This option is only used for enquiries that have been drilled down to.</p>
            <p>NO.SELECTION - the selection/criteria below the enquiry data will not be available to the user.</p>
            <p>NO.TOOLBAR - this will remove the toolbar from the top. Paging toolbar will be retained.</p>
            <p>STATIC.PAGING.TOOL - place the paging toolbar inside the enquiry header and top left of the enquiry page.</p>
            <p>DRILLDOWNS.AS.HYPERLINKS - Drilldowns appear as hyperlinks in the enquiry data column.</p> 
            <p>SELECTION.HORIZONTAL    - Selection criteria is displayed horizontally along the screen</p>
            <p>NO.COLUMN.HEADER -  Displays enquiry without headers for the selected columns.</p>
            <p>NO.MORE.OPTIONS  - To remove the 'More Options' function from enquiry selection screen.</p>
            <p>NO.CLEAR.SELECTION - To remove the 'Clear selection' function from enquiry selection screen.</p>
            <p>SINGLE.BACKGROUND.COLOUR  -  Header section and all fetched rows will be of same background colour.</p>
            <p>DISABLE.NO.SORT.OPTIONS   - The NO.SORT.OPTION field when enabled performs normal SELECT rather than sorted select(SSELECT).To disable this field from enquiry selection screen, this attribute can be used.</p>
            <p>NO.ENQUIRY.FAVOURITES   - This option disables the favourites function for the enquiry</p>
            <p>SHOW.ALL.SELECTION - Displays all selection fields along with the enquiry data displayed.</p>
            <p>UNDERLINE.HEADER.ROW   - Thick line will be displayed below the header</p>
            <p>UNDERLINE.ALL.ROWS - All the rows which are fetched will be underlined</p>
            <p>SELECTION.ABOVE.DATA   - Selection criteria is displayed above data.</p>
            <p>FASTPATH -  This attribute is used to authorize, delete, reverse, edit and see bulk of records for the underlying application.</p>
            <p>NO.HEADER.STYLE  -  Headers appear in the exact column position as defined in enquiry instead of using any auto adjustment </p>
            <p>NO.FOOTER.STYLE  -  Footers appear in the exact column position as defined in enquiry instead of using any auto adjustment</p>
            <p>VIEWLIST    -  DESKTOP only, Converts grid enquiries to display records in list format as per windows standard.</p>
            <p>VIEWLARGEICONS -DESKTOP only, Converts grid enquiries to display records as large Icons as per windows standard.</p>
            <p>VIEWSMALLICONS  -   DESKTOP only, Converts grid enquiries to display records as small Icons as per windows standard.</p>
            <p>PAGE - Desktop only. Displays enquiry output in page format.</p>
            <p>MULTI.DOWNLOAD -  To indicate that the enquiry is to be used for a multi-select secure document download function.</p>
            <p>HORIZONTAL.DRILLDOWNS -  Displays the drilldowns in a horizontal line rather than using a combo box.</p>
            <p>UNDERLINE.DRILL.ROWS    -  Horizontal line appears in enquiries under drill rows.</p>
            <p>ENQ.HEADERS.ON.EACH.PAGE  - Enquiry headers and footers are displayed on each page</p>
            <p>CV.TRANSLATE     - The session specific !CURRENT variables are changed to enquiry specific variables.
				When this attribute is set,the enquiry output details are stored in the T24 server with the current variable values and also based on the window name. 
				And on clicking the back to window or refresh , system retrieves the same data stored in the T24 server.</p>
			 <p>ADD.ACTION.TOOLS  - To add the ENQUIRY.ACTION toolbar along with the custom toolbar</p>	
		     <p>ZERORECORDDISPLAY - If an Enquiry selection criteria does not return any records a message will be shown to report this.With this attribute set,the message is suppressed and a blank page is displayed.</p>
			 <p>SHOWTREE - Shows an explorer tree for multi values and sub values.</p>
		     <p>UNDERLINE.TREE.ROWS    - To add a horizontal rule row in the enquiry response if the attribute is set.</p>
		     <p>NORMALISE    -  Allows normalisation of data(Value and subvalue markers will not be converted)</p>
			 <p>SELECTION.SORTONLY     - Selection sort only criteria is displayed.</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

