<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>FICHE.DE.HEADER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies 'PRINT', 'TELEX', 'TELEXP' 'TELEXF', 'EUCLID', 'TANDEM', or 'SWIFT' as the Carrier to be used for a message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 alphanumeric field with maximum of 8 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TESTKEY.INP.VER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the name of the person who input the testkey in outgoing messages. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is only used on telex messages which required a test key to be input on outgoing messages or a test key verified on incoming messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard       T24 alphanumeric field with maximum of 16 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This       is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields       CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX.BATCH.NO form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.LANGUAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the Language to be used for formatting this message. </p>
            <p />
            <p>If the customer requires either multiple copies of all messages or certain specific messages sent to special addresses, then special DE.PRODUCT records will be required. </p>
            <p />
            <p>These records will explicitly state the Language required for each copy of the Messages involved.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2   type AAA (Alpha) characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No   Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION.QUEUE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies to which Banking Application's Inward Message Queue a message will be sent. Only for inward Messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A   2-character Application mnemonic.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPOSITION.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>If this copy of the Message has been changed due to the presence of a Disposition Control record, then the ID of that record is recorded in this field to ensure that it is not subsequently changed by a Disposition Control record with a higher ID. This is because the Disposition Control record with the lowest ID applying to this copy of the Message must be allowed to take precedence.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 5 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX BATCH NO form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.PAY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the INWARD PAY TYPE from the FUNDS TRANSFER transaction record. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Used for Disposition Control and statistical reporting.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 30 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FRAME.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the sequence number of a segment from a SWIFT Message that has been divided up because it contains more than 2000 characters. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The maximum number of characters allowed in a SWIFT message is 2000. </p>
            <p />
            <p>If a Message exceeds 2000 characters but needs to be sent via SWIFT (this only occurs with statements, Message Type 950), then the SWIFT Formatting module automatically divides it up into 'Frames' of less than 2000 characters. To each 'Frame' it allocates a sequential Frame Number and writes a set of fields at the end of the Header record for each one, all with the same Copy Number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Numeric,   valued 1-99 (Not input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Defines the name of the Customer or Company abbreviated to 35 characters. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is taken from the DE.ADDRESS file. </p>
            <p />
            <p>It has no specific use within the Delivery System, but is useful for enquiries.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX BATCH NO form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>3-35   type S (SWIFT) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWITCH.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is only used when a switch other than the default is used. </p>
            <p />
            <p>At present the only such case is the use of DMNL in place of the default SWIFT switch ST200.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Identifies   the message switch through which this message passed to or from its carrier. </p>
            <p />
            <p>8   type A(alpha.) </p>
            <p />
            <p>(Not   Input - updated in appropriate carrier control module.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARRIER.ADDR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CARRIER ADDR NO to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEST.KEY.REQ.</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Defines whether a testkey is required for this message. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Testkeys will be required (if set to 'Y') for all copies of the message sent by telex. </p>
            <p />
            <p>If a copy is suitable for batching however, a single testkey will be required for a completed batch which contains the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>'Y'   or 'NO'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>No   Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.DISPOSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Describes the type of processing to be done on this copy of the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX BATCH NO. form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>A   maximum of 18 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The   following values are permitted: DELETE, REROUTE, RESUBMIT, REPAIR, ACK.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FICHE.CYCLE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Stores the name of the fiche cycle that is defined in the CREATE.FICHE.TAPE file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>0-20   type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p />
            <p>System   maintained. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORM.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>When a message has been Formatted the Form Type specified for this copy of the Message is recorded in this field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Formatted Messages which are for Carrier 'Print' are put onto separate Queues for each Form Type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 8 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX BATCH NO. form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 9 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CARRIER ADDR NO to  form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CARRIER ADDR NO to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Holds either a multivalue set containing the address to send a message to, or the number of a customer who is to receive the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 16 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a multi valued field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.ERROR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CARRIER ADDR NO to  form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CARRIER ADDR NO to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CARRIER ADDR NO to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 19 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       N      U      P</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME.STAMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 25 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TELEX.BATCH.NO.</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the number of the batch an outward telex message is contained in if it has been batched. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Outward telex messages can be batched into batched telexes containing up to ten messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 5 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX.BATCH.NO form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESTINATION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies where the message will be printed should the selected carrier be 'PRINT'. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field may be passed by the application or may be entered by the user. </p>
            <p />
            <p>If present, and the message is to be printed, it will be directed to the printer ID specified on the department printer file (DE.DEPT.PRINT). This will override the printer ID from the department printer file accessed using department code and form type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 4 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPARTMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the transaction identifier, which is the key to the transaction details in the Banking Application where the message originated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 alphanumeric field with maximum of 16 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SENT.STAMP</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The time that the Msg Disposition was changed to 'WACK'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>For an outward SWIFT or Telex message this field will contain the time that the message was sent.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Numeric.   Hours, minutes and seconds (HH:MM:SS).</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX BATCH NO. form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.DEL.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of  35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARRIER.SEQ.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT and Telex use a sequence number to identify each message. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The last sequence number used is held on the System Status record as SWIFT MF SEQUENCE and TELEX MF SEQUENCE for outgoing messages and SWIFT SF SEQUENCE and TELEX MF SEQUENCE for incoming messages. </p>
            <p />
            <p>When a SWIFT or Telex message is sent, 1 is added to SWIFT MF SEQUENCE or TELEX MF SEQUENCE respectively and its value is stored in the Carrier Seq No for the appropriate copy of the message. Similarly the appropriate fields are updated when an inward message is received. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Sites using ST400 - SWIFT 2 link have a session number added to the sequence number in the format 'XXXXXYYYYY' where 'XXXXX' is the Sequence Number and 'YYYYY' is the Session Number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX BATCH NO form a related multi value set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>1-10   numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEST.KEY.AUTH.</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains the name of the person who authorised the test key on outgoing messages. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is only used on outgoing telex messages which require a test key to be authorised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 alphanumeric field with maximum of 16 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX.BATCH.NO form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CARRIER ADDR NO to  form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.PDE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the Banking Application that originated the message. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field may contain an application code or may be in the format xxyy, where xx is the application code and yy is the Funds Transfer product code. </p>
            <p />
            <p>If this field contains a product code, it will not have been used as part of the application code when reading the Mapping file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 2 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>It   is picked up from the Mapping key when an outward message is created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies an account number which may be used for controlling the Status and Priority of the message and Statistical reporting.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 16 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Contains a number that subdivides the Message Type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example: A SWIFT message type 320 is used to confirm new loans, changed loans, new deposits and changed deposits; these all use the same SWIFT format. However, when they are printed they need different layouts, so different Application Formats are used to enable different Format Print records to be employed within the same basic Message Type. (Application Format is part of the ID of the Format Print records.)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This   field is not input - it is picked up from the Banking Application by using APP   FORMAT in Mapping.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 6 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields CARRIER ADDR NO to  form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       N      U      P</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COPY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the ID of a message referred to by this set of data. </p>
            <p />
            <p>It is usually the occurrence number within a multivalue set, but this is not the case if the copy has been subdivided (see FRAME NO). </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example: A statement of more than 2000 characters is to be sent via SWIFT, but has gone into the repair queue because the customer's SWIFT address is not on file. Once the address has been added (to the DE.ADDRESS file), the message can be resubmitted. The new message will be split into two messages, each less than 2000 characters. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The Msg Disposition of the first will start as 'Repair' and then change to 'Resubmitted' and the Copy Number will be 1. The Msg Disposition of the second and third sets will change from 'Formatted' to 'WACK' (awaiting acknowledgement) and after that to 'ACK'. Both will have Copy Numbers of 2 and Frame Numbers of 1 and 2. </p>
            <p />
            <p>After the 1st attempt at Formatting: 26.1 COPY NUMBER 1 32.1 MSG DISPOSITION REPAIR 33.1 MSG ERROR CODE Customer 1234 address missing. After being successfully formatted and sent: 26.1 COPY NUMBER 1 32.1 MSG DISPOSITION RESUBMITTED 26.2 COPY NUMBER 2 27.2 FRAME NUMBER 1 32.2 MSG DISPOSITION ACK 26.3 COPY NUMBER 2 27.3 FRAME NUMBER 2 32.3 MSG DISPOSITION ACK For print carrier sets the field might optionally contain the customer id to whom the advice has been sent - if a MDR.CUSTOMER has been specified in the DE.PRODUCT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 3 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX BATCH NO. form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVED.STAMP</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The time that the Msg Disposition was changed to 'ACK'. </p>
            <p />
            <p>For a SWIFT or Telex message this field will contain the time an acknowledgement was received, but for a printed message it will be the time that it was handed out of the Delivery system to be printed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Numeric.   Hours, minutes and seconds (HH:MM:SS).</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 13 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields   CARRIER.ADDR.NO to TELEX BATCH NO. form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 8 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPOSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       DELETE      RESUBMIT      REPAIR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.DUP.ENTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUS..COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the Code of a Company where the Customer file is held. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The Customer's Company Code is used when accessing the DE.PRODUCT file at the Customer level and for reading Customer names and addresses from the DE.ADDRESS file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 numeric field with maximum of 9 characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This   is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

