<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>HELPTEXT.MAINMENU</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>T24 for the convenience of the user, allows to define various main menus which can be attached to a user profile or requested at any time by entering, when the prompt 'AWAITING APPLICATION' is displayed, the question mark followed by the main menu ID. </p>
            <p>These main menus can, in turn, be linked to sub-menus to allow a further breakdown of the main menu items. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LL.DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields ID.OF.HELP.MENU to LL.DESCRIPT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of  45 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TITLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the main menu title or header which the user wants to display on the screen (line 0) when requesting the display of this main menu. </p>
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the main menu in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (ref: General Tables) and will indicate to the user the language in which the description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field.  (Optional input; no default value.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any main menu can be inserted in a user profile and will then be displayed after successful sign on.  Alternatively, when the prompt 'AWAITING APPLICATION' is displayed, it can be requested on line by entering the question mark followed immediately by the main menu reference number e.g. '?1' will display the main menu 1. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the text which the user wants to display on the screen for the ID specified in the previous field.  This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the main menu in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (ref: General Tables) and will indicate to the user the language in which the description must be entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>A maximum of 45 characters may be entered. </p>
            <p>Subvalue field. </p>
            <p>(Optional input.  No default value.) </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.ID.OF.MENU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to request the inclusion of the ID of the menu(s) when displaying the main menu. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The following values will be accepted in this field:  Y:    to request the display of the ID specified in field       ID.OF.HELP.MENU.  blank when the ID entered in field ID.OF.HELP.MENU must not be       displayed in the main menu.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.OF.HELP.MENU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ID of a record in the HELPTEXT.MENU table.  This allows the user to include sub-menus within a main menu. </p>
            <p>The system will accept any ID in this field.  Obviously to be of any use, this ID must also be defined on the HELPTEXT.MENU table. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-25 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha)      characters  or  '*' when the user wants to enter a 'blank' or 'comment' line in the next field.  Multivalue field.  (Mandatory input; no default value.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

