<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>HELPTEXT.MENU</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>T24, for the convenience of the user, allows to define various main menus which can be attached to a user profile or requested at any time by entering, when the prompt 'AWAITING APPLICATION' is displayed, the question mark followed by the main menu ID. </p>
            <p>These main menus can, in turn, be linked to lower level menus (i.e. sub-menus) to allow a further breakdown of the main menu items.  This table will be used to define the contents of these sub-menus. </p>
            <p>If desired, these menus can be attached to a user profile or requested at any time by entering, when the prompt 'AWAITING APPLICATION' is displayed, the question mark followed by the menu ID. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MENU.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>T24 allows you to create as many menus as desired. This field, therefore, represents the ID by which each menu will be uniquely identified. </p>
            <p>A menu can be inserted in a user profile and will then be displayed after successful sign on.  Alternatively, when the prompt 'AWAITING APPLICATION' is displayed, it can be requested on line by entering the question mark followed immediately by the menu reference ID e.g. '?FX.MENU' could display the menu of the Foreign Exchange application. </p>
            <p>It is not permissible though to use an application name (or an Abbreviation that runs an application) as the id of a menu. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-50 type AA (alphanumeric, first character must be alpha)      characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Id must not be a valid application or an Abbreviation that runs an application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Application name(s) which the user wants to include in this specific menu.  Alternatively, the user can also enter an '*' when he wants to define a 'blank' or 'comment' line in the next field. </p>
            <p>This field is multivalue to allow the user to include as many applications as he wants in the menu.  Furthermore, if desired, he can enter after the Application name a valid Function code which in turn could be followed by a valid reference number within the respective Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Application can contain following values</p>
            <p>1)Valid Application Name or an Abbreviation code, or '*' to define a 'blank' or 'comment' line in the next field.</p>
            <p>2)Valid Help Text Menu Id</p>
            <p>3)Valid Version </p>
            <p>4)Following Launches can also be included in application</p>
            <p>ENQ &lt;enquiry name&gt;: This allows to launch an enquiry </p>
            <p>(Note:Selection criteria can be included in enquiry.</p>
            <p>But validness of selection criteria or fieldname will not be checked)</p>
            <p>TAB &lt;Tabbed screen name&gt; :This allows you to attach Tabbed screen.</p>
            <p>COS &lt;composite screen&gt; : This allows you to attach composite screen</p>
            <p>UTIL &lt;Utility name&gt;: This allows you to call a browser routine. </p>
            <p>PW &lt;workflow&gt; :This allows you to trigger PW workflow</p>
            <p>(Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the text which the user wants to display on the screen for the Application</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the main menu in various languages.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. </p>
            <p>Multilanguage field. (Optional input; no default value.) </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPL.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to request the inclusion of the Application name when displaying the menu. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The following values will be accepted in this field:  Y:     to request the display of the Application name. blank  when the Application entered in field GB TITLE must not be        displayed in the menu.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields APPLICATION to LL.DESCRIPT form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of  45 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

