<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>JOB.TIMES.HISTORY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is a replica of JOB.TIMES file, to hold the historical information recorded in JOB.TIMES. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Current service name can be fetched from here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROGRAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the actual process name / routine name that executed this job.  Usually it will be BATCH.JOB.CONTROL.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.VERIFY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the processing (value -1) or elimination (value -2)  of the incoming keys.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ELAPSED.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time taken for the job to get completed (I.e., END.TIME - START.TIME)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time job was started.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>READ.WRITE.CACHE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether CACHE.OFF is set as null.  Accepts 'Y' or 'N'.  Y indicates that CACHE.OFF is set as null.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE.OF.SEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of selection requested within BBL. What the select routine had passed as to whether it is a full select or filtered select or command being passed. Valid values are ALL,CRITERIA,FILTER and PREDEFINED</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESSED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the total number of records/contracts that was processed.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCK.COLLISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of lock collisions during the whole job. This information is already available and has to be just updated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.WRITE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should be the total number of writes happening in the job. Currently this field is not being updated </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THROUGHPUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the number of records processed per minute. (calculated as: keys processed / elapsed time * 60)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.MANAGEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Would be updated as ‘N’ in case the job is set as .NTX in PGM.FILE. Otherwise this field will be updated as ‘Y’</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the time taken to do the SELECT </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FASTEST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the fastest single throughput.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JOB</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the job that was processed.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the time the SELECT part of the job started.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.STATEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Actual select statement used in the .SELECT routine</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGENTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the number of agents that were processing the particular batch job</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BATCH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The bank date on which the batch was run</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the setup has been done to process the records on bulk, this field will hold the number of records that were processed in bulk</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPLETED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of IDs that were completely processed by this batch job</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The clock time when the job was complete</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.JOB</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key used to identify the different records maintained on this file.  The format of the ID is PROCESS.NAME-JOB.NAME.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.RESPONSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the average response time per transaction rounded to three decimal places.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTROL.LIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provides the first 35 characters of the CONTROL.LIST value.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

