<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>LANGUAGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table identifies the Languages that may be used on the System when defining multilanguage fields. </p>
            <p>The Abbreviation code assigned to each Language is used as a screen prompt when displaying multilanguage fields.  To enable these prompts to be meaningful to the operator, it is recommended that a code is used which is the same as, or similar to the Country code associated with that Language. </p>
            <p>This table must be set up first when installing the General Tables. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MIN.MAND.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the specification of the minimum length to be used in validation for manadatory language fields of the specified language code.</p>
            <p>In English many mandatory language fields such as descriptions are defined to accept a <em>minimum</em> of 3 characters. However in certain languages such as Korean or Chinese only a single character is required to give a meaningful description. </p>
            <p>By specifying a value in this field the minimum value can be made as short (minimum 1 character) or as long as is appropriate. This validation will only be applied when the field is mandatory.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 or 2 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Abbreviation to be used for the Language. </p>
            <p>The Abbreviation to be used throughout T24 for each language is indicated by this field.  It is also the screen prompt that will be displayed for the Language. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type MNE characters (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.').  (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The first character must be A-Z.</p>
            <p>Each Language Mnemonic must be different.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISO.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Description</p>
        <p>Specifies the universally standard two letter language code, as defined by ISO 639-1, to identify the locale. </p>
        <p>(ISO 639 is a standardized nomenclature, that is used to classify all known languages) </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">LANGUAGE NAME               - ISO 639-1  </p>
            <p value="2">English                         - en </p>
            <p value="3">French                          - fr </p>
            <p value="4">German                          - de </p>
            <p value="5">Spanish -                        es </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the code by which the Language can be identified. </p>
            <p>New languages must be added sequentially, in the table e.g. Language 6 may not be specified unless Language 5 has previously been defined and authorised. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note : The user should use the language code '1' for English since all        error messages and text are written in English and no translation        is performed on this code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters.  (Mandatory input)  The code must be in the range 1-12.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the separators to be used when formatting amounts for Enquiry, Repgen &amp; screen input. </p>
            <p>This field specifies the separators to be used when formatting amounts. Input of '</p>
            <p><strong>,.</strong>
            </p>' will use commas to separate the thousands and a full stop for the decimal place. Whilst input of '<p><strong>.,</strong></p>' will use a comma decimal place separator and full stop for thousands. These two methods are the most common '<p><strong>,.</strong></p>' is used in the United Kingdom whilst on the Continent the '<p><strong>.,</strong></p>' is preferred.  <p>For certain uses the separators can be set to use an apostrophe with either the comma or full stop.</p><p>Here are some examples:</p><table border="0"><tr><td><strong>Setting</strong></td><td><strong>Unformatted Amount</strong></td><td><strong>Formatted Amount</strong></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>,.</strong></p></td><td>12345</td><td>12,345.00</td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>,.</strong></p></td><td>1234567.89</td><td>1,234,567.89</td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>.,</strong></p></td><td>12345</td><td>12.345,00</td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>.,</strong></p></td><td>1234567.89</td><td>1.234.567,89</td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>'.</strong></p></td><td>12345</td><td>12'345.00</td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>'.</strong></p></td><td>1234567.89</td><td>1'234'567.89</td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>',</strong></p></td><td>12345</td><td>12'345,00</td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>',</strong></p></td><td>1234567.89</td><td>1'234'567,89</td></tr></table><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>2 alpha, comma, full stop or apostrophe. Any combination         of 2 can be used. (Optional input)</p><p>Must be either comma, full stop or apostophe.</p><p>The same character cannot be used twice.</p><p>The default is '</p><p><strong>,.</strong></p>'  </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Idenitifes the specification of the direction of language, like whether it is left-to-right or right-to-left.</p>
            <p>  Null values indicates the direction is left-to-right..</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the format in which the DATE should be displayed. </p>
            <p>DATE.FORMAT          DATE.DISPLAY  </p>
            <p>    1                           DD MONTH YEAR </p>
            <p>    2                           DD/MM/YYYY     </p>
            <p>    3                           YYYY/MM/DD      </p>
            <p>    4                            YYYYMMDD        </p>
            <p>    5                            MM/DD/YYYY       </p>
            <p>	   6							DD.MM.YYYY		</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Language. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

