<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>LIST.PROFILE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>When the List function is selected for any Application, the Data Section of the T24 screen provides an unformatted display of field values for each record.  (Each record will be shown on 1 line with its fields displayed in sequence).  The List Profile facility has been developed to enable the User to redesign the Data Section and the Header Section of the T24 List screen to suit his own preferences.  One List Profile can be created for each Application. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SCREEN.HDR.40..78</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the headings for columns 40-78 of the Screen to be specified. </p>
            <p>his field can be used to specify the column headings for use with the LIST Function.  Spaces will not be cancelled.  One space must be left between fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 39 type A (alphanumeric) characters including required spaces. (Optional input.  No default value.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Application code by which the List Profile details can be identified. </p>
            <p>he name, or an abbreviation, of the Application for which a List Profile is required must be entered.  Only one List Profile can be defined for each Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-25 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) character Application name (or Abbreviation). (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Only a valid Application name or abbreviation will be accepted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies which field numbers are to be displayed for the List function. </p>
            <p>his field can be used to specify the fields required for the LIST function. </p>
            <p>There is no need to define the 'ID (Field 0) as it will be automatically displayed by the System in column 2 (after the line number identification).  Definition of value and sub-value fields is allowed.  If a multivalue fields is input without indication of the Value Number, the System will choose the value or sub-value '1'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric characters (including up to 3 decimals). Multivalue field. (Mandatory input.  At least one field must be defined).</p>
            <p>Field number must exist for the Application entered in Field 0.</p>
            <p>Duplicate field numbers are not allowed.</p>
            <p>The System will also verify that the total length of the fields defined by the User does not exceed 78 columns.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCREEN.HDR.01..39</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the headings for columns 1-39 of the Screen to be specified. </p>
            <p>his field can be used to specify the column headings for use with the LIST Function.  Spaces will not be cancelled. </p>
            <p>It is important to note that the System will always reserve the three first columns of the Data Section to display the line number of each record.  This line number will be followed by a space and the ID of the record.  The number of columns reserved for the ID will be in accordance with the ID of each Application (e.g. 6 for CUSTOMER file, 4 for SECTOR code etc...). The User should thus start in this field with a Text like 'SEQ REF ....' and then add his own header text. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-39 type A (alphanumeric) characters including required spaces. (Mandatory input.  No default value.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

