<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>LN.ASSET.CLASS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used to capture the Various Asset classifications which the user may use for provision calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The table also has facility to capture the applicable provision for each risk category, write-off indicators, Income recognition indicators among others.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The table can store up to 999 asset classes.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is used to store the short-description of loan classification, which may be used for enrichments.</p>
            <p>Multi-value field in order to provide local language support.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters alphanumeric field</p>
            <p>Mandatory input </p>
            <p>Language field     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.RESV.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the internal account category to which the provision amount should be parked. An internal account has to be opened in local currency for this category. System shall automatically create account for other currencies whenever needed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid category range 10000-19999.</p>
            <p>Invalid input if WRITE.OFF is set to "YES".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.EXP.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the PL category to which provision expense should be booked.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid category range 50000-59999.</p>
            <p>Invalid input if WRITE.OFF is set to "YES".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WRITE.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether WRITE.OFF is applicable for this class of asset.  When the underlying contract (Like LD, MG) is fully liquidated, then the PD contract would be automatically written off (FWOF). STATUS would be updated as FWOF in PD and in the underlying contract as well.  When the underlying contract is not fully liquidated, system writes an exception log in PD.PROV.EXCEPTION.LOG file and the user may manually WRITE-OFF the contract later on. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid values are YES/NULL     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Up to 35 characters alphanumeric description field.   Detailed description of the Asset class may be stored in this field.  Multi-value field in order to provide local language support.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters alphanumeric field </p>
            <p>Mandatory input </p>
            <p>Multi-value field </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCOME.RECOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether income should be accrued for this class of asset. If this field is set to "NO" system would switch from accrual basis to cash basis i.e. Income would be suspended and memo accruals would be posted.  STATUS would be updated as "NAB" in PD and underlying contracts and POST.END.DATE would be updated as null.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid values are NO/YES</p>
            <p>NULL/YES would mean that Income would continue to accrue</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LN.ASSET.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Assets are classified with a Numeric code.</p>
            <p>Assets are rated by their IDs. In other words, a class with ID '10' is considered a better performing asset than a class with ID '40'. Customer records are updated with the worst asset class using this principle.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 3 Numeric characters </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Percentage of provision applicable for this asset class. Provision would be calculated by applying this provision percentage on outstanding balance in LD/MG and overdue principal in PD.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rate field and accepts Zero value.</p>
            <p>Up to 11 characters Numeric field </p>
            <p>Invalid input if WRITE.OFF is set to "YES"</p>
            <p>Accepts decimal value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

