<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>LN.PROV.BALANCES.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>Internal balances file to hold contract wise provision balances.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Each provision movement are recorded in this file.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TOT.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the total provision amount for PROV.DATE. It is the sum of all  PROV.MVMT field within the date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 15 Numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Can hold Positive or Negative balance.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Provision percentage that was applied during the current movement. Sub-value field to store Multiple movements on a single day.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 11 Numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Date on which provision movement occurred. Dates would be stored in Chronological order with the most recent event at the bottom.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format of 11 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Indicates the provision movement amount during the provision date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>In case of Incremental provision this field will hold Positive amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Incase of Write-back (when the previously provisioned amount is higher than the current provision amount, the excess provision amount is credited back to PL), this field would hold Negative value</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 15 Numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Can hold positive or Negative value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the asset classification for this contract on the above mentioned date. Sub-value field to store multiple asset movements occurring on a single day.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid records in LN.ASSET.CLASS</p>
            <p>Maximum of 3 Numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid contract IDs of LD, MG and PD application.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the currency in which the Deal is denominated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard currency field.</p>
            <p>Maximum of 3 characters.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.PROV.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the net amount provisioned for this contract. It is the sum of all TOT.MVMT fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 11 Numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Can hold Zero value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

