<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>LOCAL.REF.TABLE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this table is to specify the names of any Applications that are to include any previously defined Local Table elements as Input fields and the order in which they are to appear on the screen. </p>
            <p>Up to 999 elements may be specified for each Application which allows Local Reference fields. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Application code by which the Local Reference Table details can be identified. </p>
            <p>his field identifies the Application for which the Local Table elements are being referenced. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-25 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) character Application name (or Abbreviation). (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TABLE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>LOCAL.REF.TABLE</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4      Alphanumeric character, Local Table code. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)      It must contain an existing id on the LOCAL.TABLE .</p>
            <p>Alternatively, 1 &amp;#8211; 40 alphabetic string representing SHORT.NAME on</p>
            <p />
            <p />LOCAL.TABLE. This short name must exist on the LTA.SHORT.NAME file, <p />which is automatically updated when the LOCAL.TABLE record is authorised.  <p /><p /><p /><p>LOCAL.TABLE      items with CHAR.TYPE = AMTLCCY cannot be used in applications with a file      classification other than FIN or CCY. </p><p /><p /><p /><p>LOCAL.TABLE</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p />1 - 999 numeric field, maximum 7 characters optionally separated by '/'. Optional Input - mandatory if input in APPLICATION -field 8)   <p /><p /><p />1-40 alphabetic string consisting of field name.  <p /><p /><p />LOCAL.REF fields can be entered as follows:  <p>LOCAL.REF-n &amp;#8211; where &amp;#8216;n&amp;#8217; represents the position of the LOCAL.REF field as set up on LOCAL.REF.TABLE.</p><p>Or</p><p>LOCAL.REF-name &amp;#8211; where name is the SHORT.NAME of the LOCAL.REF field.</p><p>Or</p><p>N.n &amp;#8211; where &amp;#8216;N&amp;#8217; represents the LOCAL.REF field number on the application and &amp;#8216;n&amp;#8217; is the position of the LOCAL.REF field as set up on LOCAL.REF.TABLE.</p><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ASSOC.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether a local reference field for an application is single value, multivalue, or subvalue, and the other local reference fields that are associated. </p>
            <p>For each application that uses this local reference the user may specify if the field is single value, multivalue, or subvalue. In addition they may also specify that other local references for the same application are associated. </p>
            <p>Example: a) Single value </p>
            <p>1.1 1 LOCAL REF 1 2.1 left blank </p>
            <p>1.2 2 LOCAL REF 2 2.2 left blank </p>
            <p>1.3 3 LOCAL REF 3 2.3 left blank </p>
            <p>result on application: </p>
            <p>157.1 LOCAL REF 1 ....... 157.2 LOCAL REF 2 ....... 157.3 LOCAL REF 3 ....... </p>
            <p>Fields cannot be expanded, only single value allowed for each local reference. </p>
            <p>b) Multivalue </p>
            <p>1.1 1 LOCAL REF 1 2.1 XX. </p>
            <p>1.2 2 LOCAL REF 2 2.2 XX. </p>
            <p>1.3 3 LOCAL REF 3 2.3 XX. </p>
            <p>result on application: </p>
            <p>157.1.1 LOCAL REF 1 ....... 157.1.2 LOCAL REF 1 ....... 157.2.1 LOCAL REF 2 ....... 157.3.1 LOCAL REF 3 ....... </p>
            <p>Fields can be expanded separately to allow multiple input in each local reference. In this example only 157.1.1 LOCAL REF 1 has been expanded. </p>
            <p>c) Associated subvalue </p>
            <p>1.1 1 LOCAL REF 1 2.1 XX&lt; (XX&lt; denotes start of association) </p>
            <p>1.2 2 LOCAL REF 2 2.2 XX- (XX- denotes part of association) </p>
            <p>1.3 3 LOCAL REF 3 2.3 XX&gt; (XX&gt; denotes end of association) </p>
            <p>result on application: </p>
            <p>157.1.1 LOCAL REF 1 ....... 157.1.2 LOCAL REF 1 ....... </p>
            <p>157.2.1 LOCAL REF 2 ....... 157.2.2 LOCAL REF 2 ....... </p>
            <p>157.3.1 LOCAL REF 3 ....... 157.3.2 LOCAL REF 3 ....... </p>
            <p>Fields are expanded together to allow multiple input for all local references. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 3 alpha characters. Multivalue field (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

