<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>MB.TXN.ENTRY.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>MB.TXN.ENTRY.PARAM is the parameter table for the enquiry TXN.ENTRY.MB.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXC.ASSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multivalue field  used to define the asset types that should be excluded from being displayed in the enquiry TXN.ENTRY.MB.</p>
            <p>For example : For a contract AA1, there is a SPEC entry with asset type S1. If S1 asset type is entered in the field EXC.ASSET, then when the enquiry TXN.ENTRY.MB is run for the contract AA1, this  SPEC entry with asset type S1 is not displayed in the ouput of the enquiry.”</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXC.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multivalue field specifies the CATEGORY  that should  be excluded from being displayed in the enquiry TXN.ENTRY.MB.</p>
            <p>For example : If a CATEG or STMT entry (say C1 or S1) raised on a contract say, AA1, contains the CATEGORY that is specified in the field. Then, when the enquiry TXN.ENTRY.MB is run for the contract AA1, the transaction entry, C1 or S1 is not displayed in the output</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation – should be a valid record in category.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXC.RE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a mutlivalue field specifies the RE.TXN.CODE that should be excluded from being displayed in the enquiry TXN.ENTRY.MB.</p>
            <p>For example : If a SPEC entry say S1, raised on a contract say AA1, contains the RE.TXN.CODE specified in this field. Then when the enquiry TXN.ENTRY.MB is run for the contract AA1.Then the entry S1 will not be displayed in the output.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation – should be a valid record in RE.TXN.CODE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MB.TXN.ENTRY.PARAM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allowed ID format is SYSTEM</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

