<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>OVERRIDE.CLASS.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Override messages generated by a T24 application can be classified into different groups. Different levels of authority to approve these override conditions can be given to different users of the system. </p>
            <p>This facility is more fully described in the T24 Help Text for the application OVERRIDE CLASS. </p>
            <p>The OVERRIDE CLASS DETAILS table can be used in more complex cases where a detailed sub-classification of an individual override condition is required. </p>
            <p>A typical example might be the override condition which arises when an unauthorised overdraft is generated by a transaction.  The OVERRIDE CLASS table will allow this condition to be classified so that only certain users can approve the transaction.  The OVERRIDE CLASS DETAILS table will, on the other hand, allow this condition to be given one of several sub-classifications according to, for example, the extent of the overdraft. </p>
            <p>An override classification, once assigned to a transaction record, has exactly the same functionality whether it has been established by OVERRIDE CLASS or by the OVERRIDE CLASS DETAILS decision table. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DATA.ELEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A variable element of the override message which may be used as the basis for sub-classification. </p>
            <p>Identifies either a variable element of the message to which the table relates, or a subroutine by which elements of the message may be manipulated.  In association with the decision fields 3 to 6, this can be used to further qualify the message and sub-divide into one or more override classes. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example:   The subroutine '@LIMIT.CCY.CONV' can be used to            convert the amount of an overdraft or limit excess            message into a common currency, to which separate            classes can then be allocated based upon the extent of the            overdraft or excess. </p>
            <p>Note:      The following T24 subroutines of type 'V' are            currently supplied: </p>
            <p>(a)        LIMIT.CCY.CONV (currency code) </p>
            <p>           which returns the amount of an account overdraft or limit            excess message in terms of the currency requested, </p>
            <p>(b)        LI.OVE.SECTORT (no argument) </p>
            <p>           which returns the sector code from the customer record            belonging to (the account or limit of) an account            overdraft or limit excess message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>&amp;n, where n is a numeric digit indicating a variable element of the message, or up to 35 alphanumeric character subroutine name in the format @program.name(argument). Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>If the format '@program.name(argument)' is used, the program name must reference a record on the PGM FILE which has a type of 'V'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end value of a range against which the DATA DEF in field 1 is compared. </p>
            <p>The value indicated in field 1, DATA DEF (according to the DATA DEF NO in field 3), is compared against the value in this field according to the operator in field 4 (COMPARISON).  If the outcome of the comparison is true, the corresponding override CLASSIFICATION, from field 2, will be allocated. </p>
            <p>This field is only used in the case of a range comparison (field 4, COMPARISON = 'RG' or 'NR'), where it represents the end of an inclusive range. </p>
            <p>The multi-value associated fields 3 to 6, which form the decision set, are evaluated in sequence and the value of override CLASSIFICATION (field 2) taken on a first-match basis.  They are connected by a logical 'OR' condition.  Within each multi-value, the sub-valued sets represent a series of conditions which must all be met (ie. a logical 'AND' connects them). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field in association with fields 2 to 5, subvalued in association with fields 3 to 5. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>No input is allowed without a corresponding COMPARISON of either 'RG' or 'NR' in field 3.</p>
            <p>The value in this field must be greater than that in the corresponding DATA FROM (field 5).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value against which the DATA DEF in field 1 is compared. </p>
            <p>The value indicated in field 1, DATA DEF (according to the DATA DEF NO in field 3), is compared against the value in this field according to the operator in field 4 (COMPARISON).  If the outcome of the comparison is true, the corresponding override CLASSIFICATION, from field 2, will be allocated. </p>
            <p>In the case of a range comparison (field 4, COMPARISON = 'RG' or 'NR'), the value in this field represents the start of an inclusive range. </p>
            <p>The multi-value associated fields 3 to 6, which form the decision set, are evaluated in sequence and the value of override CLASSIFICATION (field 2) taken on a first-match basis.  They are connected by a logical 'OR' condition.  Within each multi-value, the sub-valued sets represent a series of conditions which must all be met (ie. a logical 'AND' connects them). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field in association with fields 2 to 6, subvalued in association with fields 3 to 6. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 12 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASSIFICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the classification type for the override message. </p>
            <p>The various classifications which can be entered in this field allow the user to define within each application different levels of approval according to the nature of the override itself. </p>
            <p>For further details refer to the T24 Help Text for application OVERRIDE CLASS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 type S (SWIFT character set). Multivalue field in association with fields 3 to 6. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPARISON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Operator linking the DATA DEF in field 1 to the values for comparison in fields 5 &amp; 6 (DATA FROM &amp; DATA TO). </p>
            <p>The value indicated in field 1, DATA DEF (according to the DATA DEF NO in field 3), is compared against the values in fields 5 &amp; 6 (DATA FROM &amp; DATA TO) according to this operator.  If the outcome of the comparison is true, the corresponding override CLASSIFICATION, from field 2, will be allocated. </p>
            <p>The permitted operators are EQ (equal), NE (not equal), LT (less than), GT (greater than), LE (less or equal), GE (greater or equal), RG (within range), NR (outside range), LK (like) and UL (unlike). </p>
            <p>The multi-value associated fields 3 to 6, which form the decision set, are evaluated in sequence and the value of override CLASSIFICATION (field 2) taken on a first-match basis.  They are connected by a logical 'OR' condition.  Within each multi-value, the sub-valued sets represent a series of conditions which must all be met (ie. a logical 'AND' connects them). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 alphabetic characters; for allowed values see details. Multivalue field in association with fields 2 to 6, subvalued in association with fields 3 to 6. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.DEF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.DEF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates which data item, as defined in field 1 (DATA DEF), the decision fields 4 to 6 refer to. </p>
            <p>The number in this field identifies which multi-value from field 1, DATA DEF, the decision fields 4 to 6 refer to.  For example, the number '1' indicates that it is the data item defined by field 1.1, the number '2' indicates that it is the content of field 1.2 and so on. </p>
            <p>Each individual element of the override message which is to be used as a decision criterion need only be defined once in field 1 (DATA DEF). The same element can then be referenced as many times as required within the body of the decision table by a simple number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 or 2-digit numeric. Multivalue field in association with fields 2 to 6, subvalued in association with fields 4 to 6. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The number must correspond to an existing value in DATA DEF (field 1).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

