<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>OVERRIDE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RAISE.EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field to specify whether the event of accepting an Override within the specific channel should be notified to TEC. </p>
            <P />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> 1. Yes/No field. </p>
            <p> 2. Non-mandatory. </p>
            <p> 3. To be set 'YES', when event to be notified. </p>
            <p> 4. Will not raise event for APPROVE.METHOD 'Error' </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the new override message has changed in any way from the original text in the old overrides (before the override file) then insert that text here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMERIC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the key identification number for error message.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System generated field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the "Override Variable (&amp;)" position to be validated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Must be already defined in the DATA.TYPE field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALIDATION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>   A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>   Must exist in CONDITION field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXACT.MATCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>When checking if an OVERRIDE message has already been accepted, the system needs to know how to match the OVERRIDE message.</p>
            <p>   YES - The OVERRIDE suppression programs will check the message exactly, including all values in the message. If any of the values do not match then the OVERRIDE will be shown. If the OVERRIDE message is exactly the same as the one stored in the EB.OVERRIDE.APPROVED file then the OVERRIDE message will be suppressed. </p>
            <p>    NO - The OVERRIDE suppression programs will only check the Internal ID of the OVERRIDE, therefore if any of the text changes in the OVERRIDE the message will still be suppressed.</p>
            <p>   E.g. If the OVERRIDE CASH.FLOW.OVERDRAFT creates the message "15/01/02 18599 CASH FLOW OVERDRAFT GBP -2234.99" has already been created in a previous application but the application we are in creates the same OVERRIDE with the message "15/01/02 18599 CASH FLOW OVERDRAFT GBP </p>
            <p>    With EXACT.MATCH set to "NO" the system will compare the two OVERRIDE message ID's which are both CASH.FLOW.OVERDRAFT &amp; therefore suppress the message. </p>
            <p>    With EXACT.MATCH set to "YES" not only are the message ID's checked but also the text. In this example the ID's match but the text is different because the overdraft amount has changed. Therefore this message will not be suppressed &amp; will be displayed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   YES or NO</p>
            <p>   Cannot be input unless the SC product is installed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUBROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Applies only when OFS/GTS is being used.</p>
            <p>   Should validation be required then the highest priority will be given to a user defined subroutine. Should a subroutine be called no further validation will be performed.</p>
            <p>   The subroutine should test the incoming data &amp; return either a "Y" or "NO" to indicate whether the Override is automatically approved or not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Valid subroutine in the PGM.FILE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Signifies whether this message is to be included in the Dispo processing.</p>
            <p>   Dispo processing may basic or full.</p>
            <p>   Basic dispo processing is available on all overrides. </p>
            <p>   Full Dispo processing, available on the overrides listed below, includes </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Currently, </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Other OVERRIDES may be enhanced to allow full dispo processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Must be either Y or N</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This determines if the Override message is part of the T24 core software &amp; not user defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field cannot be input on site.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the value that is to be compared with the data passed in from the Override record.</p>
            <p>   If the OPERATOR field is "RG" then a SEPARATOR must be used to separate the range of values, e.g. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory if DATA.POSN field is populated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The override class related to this message for the specified application</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Up to 4 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRECEDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This signifies the order in which applications need to be viewed and the field used to determine which officer the override must be routed to.</p>
            <p>   In this field the user can specify the application and field name the system must use. The application that the user can specify will be limited to the application specified in the APPLICATION field on the Override table, ACCOUNT, CUSTOMER, LIMIT and POSTING.RESTRICT applications.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   An entry in the format: APPLICATION&gt;FIELDNAME</p>
            <p>   APPLICATION         can be:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.ACCT.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Added in G14.2.00)</p>
            <p>   The input at this field instructs the system how to continue processing during the 'off-line' when an entry for the application mentioned in the field SUSP.APPLN above, would require an override.</p>
            <p>   During the end of day processing the system call to accounting is replaced by a call to EOD ACCOUNTING.  The important parameter in this call, as far as the user is concerned, is the field EOD ACCT MODE which can have one of the following values:-</p>
            <p>    SSS - (System Suspense) - any override condition will automatically have the answer 'YES' assigned to it if the entry is to an internal account. An entry to a customer account will be replaced by an entry to a suspense account in the event of an override condition being encountered.</p>
            <p>   NULL: -Any override condition will automatically have the answer 'YES' assigned to it if the entry is to an internal account. An entry to a customer account will not be replaced by an entry to a suspense account. Instead, the override messages will be incorporated in the STMT.ENTRY</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   1 - 3 alphabetic characters -  'SSS'(meaning System Suspense). </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory input, if SUSP.APPLN field is filled in.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEPARATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to separator multiple entries of data in the VALUE field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Only allowed for "RG", "EQ" &amp;         "NE" OPERATOR's</p>
            <p>   Mandatory for OPERATOR "RG"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the operator that will be used in the validation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   EQ, NE, RG, LT, LE, GT or GE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of override:</p>
            <p>          Auto       - Are auto overrides which are accepted automatically without the user's consent.</p>
            <p>          Error       - Are overrides which turn into errors when raised.</p>
            <p>          Message - Are overrides which turn into notifications when raised.</p>
            <p>          Warning  - Are overrides which turn into warnings when raised. </p>
            <p>                         Warnings accept input from the user but don't stop the transaction, only record the input.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELPTEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The help message that will appear when the message help is invoked</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELP.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the format of the help message associated with this override.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Must be either TEXT , HTML or RICHTEXT</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVE.SUPPRESSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine if an application should display OVERRIDE messages that have already been accepted by previous applications.</p>
            <p>   If an application is used that is in the OVE.SUPPRESSION field encounters an OVERRIDE it will read the EB.OVERRIDE.APPROVED record to see if the OVERRIDE has already been accepted &amp; if so will not show the OVERRIDE again.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Either SC.EXE.SEC.ORDERS or SEC.TRADE applications.</p>
            <p>   Cannot be input unless the SC product is installed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define channel specific messages. Every OFS.SOURCE record can be set to a specific channel. If there is a channel specified, the channel specific message will be displayed as an override.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   The key to the OVERRIDE.CLASS.DETAILS file that that this override is associated with</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional field where information relevant to this Override can be stored.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>   A maximum of 65 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field's funcitonality has not been implemented yet.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.IND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction Code Indicator (TRANSACTION.IND)</p>
            <p>   Certain types of accounting transactions are exempt from Dispo processing depending on the application used to generate the transaction/contract. For example, fees generated by a Funds Transfer transaction can cause the account to go into overdraft, this overdraft override is exempt from Dispo processing. This field indicates whether the exempt indicator on the transaction code should be used in determining if the override is exempt. If the field is set to YES, then the system must look at the exempt indicator on the transaction code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Valid entries for this field are: YES, NO,                 or empty field.</p>
            <p>   YES in this field indicates                 that the transaction file is checked for the                 exempt indicator</p>
            <p>   NO, or null in this field indicates that the                 transaction file will not be checked, and the                 Dispo instructions specified on the OVERRIDE file                 should be followed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Rule 1</p>
            <p>   Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format text to appear on override message. Position an '&amp;' to indicate where values will be inserted.</p>
            <p>   Multi value fields allow multi language function for overrides.</p>
            <p>   On selecting and validating a second multi language field, a mirror record for the multi language text will be created in DYNAMIC.TEXT with this field as the key.</p>
            <p>   Note: When Multi valuing language fields the fields appear in a pre set order, so in order to use a set language you will need to have the languages preceding it multi valued as well.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   65 Character Field length</p>
            <p>   Alpha, numeric and symbol input accepted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSP.APPLN</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Field added in G14.2.00)</p>
            <p>   The application ID where the entries are to be routed to an Internal Suspense Account during END.OF.DAY, when there are overrides.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Valid T24 Application.</p>
            <p>   Associated Multi-value field with fields with the fields SUSP.CONDN.RTN      and FWD.ACCT.MODE.</p>
            <p>   Optional Field.</p>
            <p>   A record must be available for this  application in the application: AC.APPLICATION.LINK</p>
            <p>   If a record is not available in AC.APPLICATION.LINK, then online error     message will be given by the system.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONDITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the SUBROUTINE field is left blank the system will use the validation parameters stored on the OVERRIDE record. This field is multi-valued &amp; determines Validations will be used.</p>
            <p>   As soon as a TRUE condition is met with a Valid ACTION then no further validation will be performed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   A valid ID from the VALIDATION field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATE.OVE.LIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine which applications will create records on the EB.OVERRIDE.APPROVED file for OVERRIDE suppression. </p>
            <p>   If an application is entered here &amp; an OVERRIDE situation is encountered during that application then the OVERRIDE will be stored in the EB.OVERRIDE.APPROVED file.  If an application is used that is in the OVE.SUPPRESSION field encounters an OVERRIDE it will read the EB.OVERRIDE.APPROVED record to see if the OVERRIDE has already been accepted &amp; if so will not show the OVERRIDE again.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Either SEC.OPEN.ORDER or SC.EXE.SEC.ORDERS applications.</p>
            <p>   Cannot be input unless the SC product is installed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The entry here will decide to whom the dispo items are to be routed for further processing.</p>
            <p>   The entry is mandatory to allow input for </p>
            <p>   DISPO</p>
            <p>   DISPO.ALLOWED</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   It should be a valid record in </p>
            <p>   DISPO.OFFICER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSP.COND.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Field added in G14.2.00)</p>
            <p>   This field can be used for attaching a User defined routine.  The routine can be to  check different conditions. Based on the outcome transactions with override conditions will be routed to an internal suspense account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.ALLOWED</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES -   Specify whether DISPO is allowed for this override message.</p>
            <p>        This entry, which </p>
            <p>        cannot be input on site,</p>
            <p>        DISPO, DISPO.OFFICER  </p>
            <p>FORCE - Enforce DISPO items for this override message</p>
            <p>        specially for external DDA systems </p>
            <p>        Cannot be input on site</p>
            <p>        APPLICATION, DISPO and DISPO.OFFICER need not be set up for this FORCE type</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      "YES" or FORCE or blank</p>
            <p>      Cannot be input on site.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFS.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This determines which OFS processes will be considered for automatic Override validation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Any valid record ID from the OFS.SOURCE application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the order that the Dispo Transactions will be displayed in on the application DISPO.ITEMS.</p>
            <p>   1 representing the highest level 99 the lowest, thus in DISPO.ITEMS the transactions with a LEVEL of 1 will be displayed ahead of transactions with a level of 2 and so on up to a level of 999.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Numeric input, three characters. Giving a range of 1-999.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the action that will be performed assuming that the data validation performed is TRUE.</p>
            <p>   AND - This will connect one validation with the next one assuming that the result of this validation was TRUE. ACCEPT - Assuming that the data validation is TRUE the Override will be automatically accepted. DECLINE - Assuming that the data validation is TRUE the Override will be automatically declined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory id DATA.POSN field populated.</p>
            <p>   AND, ACCEPT or DECLINE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This determines which Versions or Applications will perform automatic Override validation during an OFS process.</p>
            <p>   The program follows a structure which is a follows:</p>
            <p>   Version - The Version that is being processed via OFS is         the scanned for. If the Version cannot be found then,</p>
            <p>   Application - The Application that is being processed via         OFS is scanned for. If the Application cannot be found         then,</p>
            <p>   * - If an "*" is located then this denotes all         Applications/Versions. If the "*" cannot be         found then no validation will be performed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Valid Version, Application or "*".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The application/routine that will produce this message.</p>
            <p>   The wilcard character "*" may be used to apply settings to all applications.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Must be a valid T24 application or "*"</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPROVE.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field's funcitonality has not been implemented yet.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Conditional Override (CON.OVERRIDE)</p>
            <p>   Dispo overrides can be conditional on whether the customer has sufficient funds on their accounts. If the customer has sufficient funds then other Dispo overrides such as &amp;#145;Limit has expired&amp;#146; can be prevented from going to DISPO. You can define whether certain overrides are dependent on other overrides.</p>
            <p>   In this field the user can specify the other override that this particular override is dependent on. The user is able to enter more than one override per application.</p>
            <p>   If an override has conditional overrides, and one of these conditional overrides is present on the contract, then the override will go to the dispo queue. However if none of the conditional overrides are on the contract then the override will not invoke dispo processing, that is, it will not go to the dispo queue.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Field is optional</p>
            <p>   Must be a valid Dispo                 Override. Ie. DISPO.ALLOWED field is set                 to YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

