<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>PASSWORD.RESET</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This S.M.S. application provides the security administrator with the following three facilities: </p>
            <p> 1.     It allows a Password to be 'reset' so that a       user who has forgotten it may enter a new one. </p>
            <p> 2.     It also allows the administrator to 'enable' a       profile which has exceeded the number of       attempts permitted. </p>
            <p> 3.     It finally allows the administrator to       'reactivate' a profile during a period for       which it has been deactivated. </p>
            <p> These functions should be restricted to the security administrator of the bank. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>USER.PWD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the encrypted form of one shot password specified in the associated USER.PASSWORD.</p>
            <p> Validation rules:</p>
            <p> No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.RESET</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> This is the ID of a user (Bank user) whose password is to be reset. A new password must be set in the associated USER.PASSWORD field. This password will be set up as expired and thus the user will be forced to change it on the next sign-on. External user reset cannot be done using this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.DEACT.PERD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ID of the user for whom the security administrator wants to reactivate the profile before the end of the deactivation period. This field is applicable only for Bank users and not for External users. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Up to 16 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters. Optional input; Default = Nil</p>
            <p> The user ID must be existing on the USER file.</p>
            <p> Duplicates are not allowed.</p>
            <p> The USER ID may be the same as any possible USER ID entered in Fields USER ATTEMPT or USER PW ATTEMPTS.</p>
            <p> The user ID must be different from the inputter or the authorisor.</p>
            <p> The user must have an actual deactivation period.</p>
            <p> At least one input is mandatory between fields 1, 2 and 4.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the type of user for whom the Security administrator wants to reset the Password. The possible types are Bank user (INT) or External user (EXT). </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> A one-shot password for the user specified in the associated USER.RESET.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ATTEMPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ID of the user (Bank user or External user) for whom the security administrator wants to enable the profile because of an excess of allowable attempts.  This field applies to External users or Bank users when the USER.TYPE field is selected as "EXT" or "INT" respectively. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Up to 16 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters. Optional input; Default = Nil</p>
            <p> The user ID must exist on the USER/EB.EXTERNAL.USER file.</p>
            <p> Duplicates are not allowed.</p>
            <p> The USER ID must be different from any possible user ID entered in the previous field.</p>
            <p> The USER ID must be different from the inputter or authorisor.</p>
            <p> The user must have a number of attempts to be reset.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.PW.ATTEMPT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> Specifies the ID of the user (Bank user or External user) for whom the Security administrator wants to reset the Password and enable the profile at the same time. The External user id can be entered only when the USER.TYPE field is selected as "EXT", in case of Bank user the USER.TYPE field should be selected as "INT". </p>
            <p> The password is cleared and the user is asked to set a password the next time he tries to log in.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEACTIV.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the current deactivation period of the user specified in the previous field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Internal field. Content is system generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the code by which a record in this application can be identified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 - 14 SWIFT characters type SSS. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.ATTEMPTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the current number of attempt of the user specified in the previous field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Internal Field. Content is system generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

