<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>PRINT.HELPTEXT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>T24 allows the creation and maintenance of a complete user guide on-line.  This user guide can then be retrieved on-line at any time by the user whenever he wants to get some help or detailed information on T24 facilities. This helptext is maintained and can be retrieved at three levels, i.e. at the Application level (by means of HELPTEXT.APPLICATION), at the function level, (by means of HELPTEXT.FUNCTION) and at the field level by means of the HELPTEXT. FIELD).  The purpose of the PRINT.HELPTEXT facility is to allow the user to print the content of the three above mentioned files.  When the PRINT.HELPTEXT is invoked, T24 will display a menu to the user allowing him to select 1 out of 4 options: </p>
            <p>1)         Application + all fields </p>
            <p>           The first selection code allows the user to print the            Helptext relating to a specific Application (module            overview i.e. HELPTEXT.APPLICATION) as well as the            helptext referring to all fields of this Application            (HELPTEXT.FIELD).  When this option is selected: </p>
            <p>           o    The user will be requested to specify the                 Application name for which a print is desired. </p>
            <p>           o    When this has been done, the Application selected                 will be displayed in the line 2 of the Header and                 the user will now be invited to indicate in which                 language he wants to receive the print-out. If no                 language code is entered, the system will assume                 as a default the language defined on the profile of                 the user. </p>
            <p>           o    If the Helptext does not exist for the selected                 Application and language, the message 'Helptext                 record not available' will be displayed.                 Otherwise, printing will start immediately                 including the Application and fields on line                 Helptext. </p>
            <p>2)         Application </p>
            <p>           The second selection code allows the user to print the            Helptext relating to a specific Application i.e. the module            overview contained in the file HELPTEXT.APPLICATION. </p>
            <p>3)         Field </p>
            <p>           The third selection code allows the user to print the            Helptext relating to a specific field within an Application            i.e. the field description contained in the file            HELPTEXT.FIELD. </p>
            <p>           When this option is selected, T24 will ask the user to            specify first the Application and then the field number            which he wants to print.  Both the Application name and            field number will then be displayed on line 3 next to the            prompt 'RECORD ID'. </p>
            <p>4)         Function </p>
            <p>           The fourth and last selection code allows the user to print            the Helptext relating to a specific function i.e. the            function description contained in the file            HELPTEXT.FUNCTION. </p>
            <p>It must be noted that for anyone of the 4 options, T24 allows the user to specify the language in which he wants to print the Helptext. If he does not specify any language the one defined in his user profile will be selected as far as it exists on the appropriate application (HELPTEXT.APPLICATION, HELPTEXT.FUNCTION, HELPTEXT.FIELD). </p>
            <p>Finally, for the ease of the user, T24 also allows the printing of Helptext while it is being displayed to the user after a request via the '?' facility.  Entering the command 'PRT' in the action line will automatically print the content of the record being displayed. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

