<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>PRINTER.ATTRIBUTES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to define the special printer attribute initialisation and reset sequences that are required to be printed with the report in order for it to be printed in Landscape, Portrait mode etc. </p>
            <p>The initialisation/reset sequence for each attribute must relate to a printer type that can support it. Hence the key to the file is: </p>
            <p>           "Printer type"."Attribute name"        or   "Printer type" </p>
            <p>The "Printer type" is the "make" or "model" of the printer, eg. QMS, EPSON etc.  This is defined in field 3 of the PRINTER.ID file. </p>
            <p>The "Attribute name" is the name referenced in field 7 of the DE.FORM.TYPE file, eg. LANDSCAPE, PORTRAIT etc. </p>
            <p>When the report is spooled, the report control system reads the DE.FORM.TYPE record for the report to determine whether any special attribute names have been specified and it also reads the PRINTER.ID record for the destination printer to determine the printer type.  The two items are combined to form the key for the PRINTER.ATTRIBUTES file to get the special attribute initialisation/reset sequences for the report. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESET.SEQUENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Control sequence to be sent to the printer immediately after outputting the report. </p>
            <p>Optional characters to send to the printer after output of the report. </p>
            <p>Should be used to return the printer to a default state if an initialisation sequence was sent i.e. returning a laser printer to portrait mode. </p>
            <p>Characters which cannot be entered directly from the keyboard can be defined by entering the ASCII decimal code in angle brackets e.g. &lt;13&gt; - a carriage return. To enter a &gt; or &lt; the equivalent ASCII code should be used. </p>
            <p>The field is multivalued to allow lengthy sequences to be entered. The multivalue markers are removed prior to translating &lt;nnn&gt; to the correct code and sending to the printer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>60 Any Character. The ASCII code of control characters         should be entered in angle brackets e.g. &lt;12&gt; would         be a form feed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the printer attributes and what function the attributes perform, eg. Landscape mode etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-50 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INIT.SEQUENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Initial control sequence to be sent to the printer prior to outputting the report. </p>
            <p>Optional characters to send to the printer prior to output of report. </p>
            <p>Can be used to set up special printer characteristics e.g. change the font on a laser printer or turn it into Landscape mode etc.. </p>
            <p>Characters which cannot be entered directly from the keyboard can be defined by entering the ASCII decimal code in angle brackets e.g. &lt;13&gt; - a carriage return. To enter a &gt; or &lt; the equivalent ASCII code should be used. </p>
            <p>The field is multivalued to allow lengthy sequences to be entered. The multivalue markers are removed prior to translating &lt;nnn&gt; to the correct code and sending to the printer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>50 Any character. The ASCII code of control characters         should be entered in angle brackets e.g. &lt;12&gt; would         be a form feed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINTER.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Printer type and special attribute name. eg. QMS, LANDSCAPE </p>
            <p>The record key must be constructed as follows:     (i) "Printer type"."Attribute name"         or  (ii) "Printer type" </p>
            <p>The "Printer type" is the "model" or "make" of printer as defined in field 3 of the PRINTER.ID file. For example, ten QMS laser printers would have ten entries on PRINTER.ID but could be collectively referred to as the type "QMS". </p>
            <p>The "Attribute name" is the name referenced in field 7 (RPT.ATTRIBUTE) of the DE.FORM.TYPE file. </p>
            <p>When a report is spooled, the DE.FORM.TYPE record for the report is read to get the special printer attribute names (if any) and the PRINTER.ID record read to determine the printer type.  The initialisation sequence in the PRINTER.ATTRIBUTE file for record "Printer type"."Attribute name" is then sent to the printer before the report is printed. </p>
            <p>Examples:   QMS.LANDSCAPE            This record would define the            initialisation/reset sequences to turn the            QMS laser printer into Lanscape mode            before the report is printed. </p>
            <p>           QMS            This record would define the default            initialisation/reset sequences i.e. line            spacing etc. for any report sent to this            printer which does not have special            attributes specified in the DE.FORM.TYPE            file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-20 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

