<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>PROTOCOL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is the table in which details of all security violations are stored, plus optional details of permitted user activity as specified in USER Records. </p>
            <p> In addition to this, it can be used to capture the details such as 1. the successful transaction commit 2. Enquiry executed with selection criteria details.</p>
            <p> This table is only available to certain Users such as Security Administrators. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record which was being accessed, or which someone was attempting to access, at the time the activity was recorded. </p>
            <p> his field is not used when logging permitted activities except for Users with FUNCTION ID LOG (Field 28 in USER) equal to Y. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROTOCOL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the code by which a record in this table can be identified. </p>
            <p> YYYYMMDD is the date on which the recorded event (security violation or other activity) occurred. </p>
            <p> NNNNN is the sequence number allocated to the event when it was recorded.  The first event recorded each day is 00001 and the sequence numbers are increased by 1 each time an event is recorded. </p>
            <p> When this ID is displayed, it is reformatted as follows:           DD MMM YYYY . 00105           e.g. 19 FEB 1985 </p>
            <p> To reference the current day's records it is only necessary to enter the sequence numbers, the System date is then automatically added. </p>
            <p> The protocol record keyed by USER id contains the last security violation or activity made by that user. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 13 numeric characters with '.' after the 8th, i.e. YYYYMMDD.NNNNN. or   11 numeric characters with '.' after the 6th, i.e. DDMMYY.NNNNN or USER.id appended with Session Number and Time delimited by hyphen. i.e. 'USER id-Session Number-Time'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the time at which the recorded event took place. </p>
            <p> hen this field is displayed, it is reformatted HH:MM:SS. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 6 numeric characters HHMMSS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Refer HelpText from USER field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TERMINAL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the terminal at which the recorded activity took place. </p>
            <p> The terminal id is in two parts separated by a space eg. NN XX.  Where NN is the Universe user number and XX is the last two characters of the UNIX terminal id. </p>
            <p> This provides the ability to trace the user both at Universe and UNIX levels. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 0-15 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEVEL.FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies whether the Application had been accessed directly or via '!' and the Function which was being used, or which someone was attempting to use, at the time the activity was recorded. </p>
            <p> his field is not used when logging permitted activities except for Users with FUNCTION ID LOG (Field 28 in USER) equal to Y. </p>
            <p> Level 1 indicates that the Application was accessed directly.  Level 2 indicates that the Application was accessed from another Application via '!' mark. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1 numeric character (Level) and 1 type AAA (alpha) character (Function)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REMARK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used when security violations are recorded, to explain why the System would not allow the attempted activity. </p>
            <p> Also, below values gets updated, </p>
            <p> 1. TRANSACTION.SUCCESSFUL.COMMIT - When successful transaction committed to disk. </p>
            <p> 2. ENQUIRY.SELECTION.DETAILS - Enquiry executed with selection criteria, this is when APPLICATION.LOG = Y in user profile as followed for normal enquiry request </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PHANTOM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> Identifies the terminal at which the recorded activity took place. I.e., the Universe user number, same as the first part in TERMINAL.ID</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 0-15   type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the User who had signed on at the terminal where the recorded activity was performed. </p>
            <p> his is the USER ID (Field 0) of the USER record. </p>
            <p> If the User was not Signed On at the time of the recorded activity, this field will not be used (e.g. if recorded activity was an attempt to Sign On using an unknown Sign On Name). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 0-16 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.MSECS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the time of recorded event in milli seconds.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1)1-15 numeric characters HHMMSSMSS</p>
            <p> 2)Time is reformatted HH:MM:SS:MSS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Refer Helptext from TIME field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the date of business which was being processed on the System at the time the activity was recorded. </p>
            <p> his is normally, but not necessarily, the same date as the System date in the Record ID (Field 0).  Sometimes the System may be being used to process work for another date, e.g. finishing Friday's work on Saturday. </p>
            <p> When this date is displayed it is reformatted - DD MMM YYYY           e.g. 19 FEB 1985 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> YYYYMMDD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Application which was being used, or which someone was attempting to use, at the time the activity was recorded. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 0-25 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLIENT.IP.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the IP address of client's machine in which recorded activity</p>
            <p> took place.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Company whose records were being accessed by the User who performed the recorded activity. </p>
            <p> his is the Company name held in Field 1 of the COMPANY record (Ref: General Tables). </p>
            <p> The Company accessed is determined by the Company Code(s) held in the COMPANY field (Field 5) of the USER record. If no User is Signed On, this field is not used (e.g. if the recorded activity was an attempt to SIGN.ON using an unknown SIGN.ON.NAME). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 0-25 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>LOCAL.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
			<p> Specifies the time of recorded event in milli seconds specific to the current company zone</p>			
			<p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional field.</p>
			<p> 0-30 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>      
            <p>Time will be displayed in the format HH:MM:SS:MSS </p>
      		<p> Zone time updated only when USE.LOCAL.TIME field is set in SPF. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the field name which acts as a selection criteria for the enquiry request.</p>
            <p>The SELECTION.FIELD,SELECTION.OPERAND and SELECTION.VALUE fields are associated multi value set</p>
       		<p> This field gets updated when USER>APPLICATION.LOG = 'Y' as same as normal enquiry request. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid Operand used to filter data from T24 file based on the given selection criteria, to display results in enquiry output.</p>
            <p>The SELECTION.FIELD,SELECTION.OPERAND and SELECTION.VALUE fields are associated multi value set</p>
        	<p> This field gets updated when USER>APPLICATION.LOG = 'Y' as same as normal enquiry request. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field value checked against the operand to extract data from t24 file.</p>
            <p>The SELECTION.FIELD,SELECTION.OPERAND and SELECTION.VALUE fields are associated multi value set.</p>
            <p> This field gets updated only if ENABLE.AUDIT.LOG in SPF set to YES. </p>
            <p> This field gets updated when USER>APPLICATION.LOG = 'Y' as same as normal enquiry request. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PW.ACTIVITY.TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Process workflow transaction id for PW activity requests.</p>
            <p> This field gets updated only for successful commit transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Holds the value only for PW requests.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the channel through which the recorded activity was processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid record id of EB.CHANNEL application should be given in the CHANNEL field of OFS.SOURCE record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASSIFICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of message stored.</p>
            <p> This field gets updated for all messages logged into PROTOCOL. The Classifications are, </p>
            <p> TECHNICAL - For technical errors or logs .</p>
			<p> SECURITY - For sign on, sign off, login error , Security violations or anything related to security.</p>
			<p> AUDIT - The user activity messages (except above two category) are can be logged under this for e.g, commit request, enquiry request, etc. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

