<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>REGION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this table is to segregate a Region within a Country where the public holidays differ from other parts of the Country. </p>
            <p>This enables a separate HOLIDAY table to be defined for the Region, to allow delivery to be controlled correctly within the T24 system. </p>
            <p>Up to 99 regions may be specified for each Country. </p>
            <p>The COUNTRY table must be set up before this table can be created. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REGION.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Region Name </p>
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the Region in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters. Multilanguage field (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REGION.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the code by which the Region can be identified. </p>
            <p>This code can specify up to 99 separate Regions within a Country, enabling separate Holiday tables to be recorded for each Region.</p>
            <p>Additionally records may be entered that include the year suffix, for example US01.1999. These records are used only for captial gains processing where different index values are issued by the tax authorities for each calendar year. In this case the transactions will apply the index values for the trade date year record, for example a transaction with trade date 01 Jan 1999 will use US01.1999, and a transaction with trade date 27 Dec 1998 will use US01.1998.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character Country code.</p>
            <p>1 or 2 numeric character Region code. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Region code must be within the range 1 - 99</p>
            <p>Additional year suffix, optional input.</p>
            <p>If the year suffix is specified the region record must be         present without a year suffix.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INDEX.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This multi-value field is used to define an apply to date for the index level in the INDEX field.</p>
            <p>The dates should be in descending order and the last (multi-value-1) date field should be blank to indicate that it's the current period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid date format</p>
            <p>Cannot be in the future</p>
            <p>The first multi-value field must be blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INDEX</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the inflation index associated with the region and the date recorded, unless the date field is blank to indicate that the index is current.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard numeric with 2 decimals.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REGION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the 4 Character Financial centre. To be used in Swift message TAG 22B</p>
            <p>For example:</p>
            <p />
            <p>REGION.KEY</p>: US01  <p>GB.REGION.NAME</p>: New York   <p>DELIVERY.REGION</p>: USNY  <p /><p>REGION.KEY</p>: US02   <p>GB.REGION.NAME</p>: Chicago   <p>DELIVERY.REGION</p>: USCH  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>4 characters</p><p>Mandatory Input</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

