<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>REPGEN.SORT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW FOR REPGEN SORT </p>
            <p>This module creates a sort file using the program created in REPGEN.SOURCE for a report defined in the file REPGEN.CREATE. </p>
            <p>This step in the report generation can be run on-line or be part of a end-of-day job stream. </p>
            <p>This routine maintains records on the REPGEN.SORT file which are called up when a report is to be produced. </p>
            <p>The records are loaded using the (I)nput or (C)opy functions. </p>
            <p>The (V)erify function is used to produce the report on line.  If Verify mode is run and the REPGEN.CREATE record has been updated but REPGEN.SOURCE not run an override message appears. </p>
            <p>The functions (L)ist, (P)rint, (R)eversal and (S)ee are also available. </p>
            <p>The end of day production of these types of reports is explained in the REPGEN.OUTPUT overview. </p>
            <p>The sort file created, with the information as of the last creation, is available for print or display until the next creation or until physically removed through use of the module REPGEN.FROP.LIST. unless the print run was asked to delete the sort file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REPORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Is the key of REPGEN.CREATE record for which the sort is to be run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-15 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Must be the key of a record on the REPORT.CREATE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID to identify this REPGEN.SORT record. </p>
            <p>The ID of this record can be any characters but is is recommended that it be the REPGEN.CREATE record key where possible. </p>
            <p>For reports to be run as part of the end of day the records key names must be the same on the REPGEN.SORT and REPGEN.OUTPUT files. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 swift characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>User defined extra fields for defining variables to be used in the REPGEN Processing at run time. </p>
            <p>Where a REPGEN.CREATE record has indicated that it needs variables at run time, then these variables can be entered here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSTANTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the variables that are to be passed into the REPGEN processing at a run time. </p>
            <p>Where a REPGEN.CREATE record has indicated that it needs variables at run time, then these variables are to be entered here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. Subvalue field Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME.COMPILER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the date and time that REPGEN.SOURCE was last run for the REPGEN.CREATE record in field 2. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Displayed as Date followed by Time. Held as 6 characters Date and 4 characters time in the format YYMMDDHHMM. External Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME.SORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the date and time that this sort was last run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Displayed as Date followed by Time. Held as 6 characters Date and 4 characters time in the format YYMMDDHHMM. External maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format narrative for notes explaining use of record. </p>
            <p>This field is not used other than as a notes field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

