<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>RESTRICTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SEL.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input only allowed when the key to the record starts with "</p>
            <p>The "ALL" type RESTRICTION is applicable to all transactions. This field allows the user to restrict even further which transactions the "ALL" records applies to.</p>
            <p>Enter the value into this field which will be compared with the SEL.FIELD field in the SEL.APPLI application using the SEL.OP operand.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Any text up to 18 characters in length.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALID.FROM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is date that makes a restriction applicable. It can be in 3 formats which are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>&gt;nnnX, &lt;nnnX or up to 9 type D date characters, (Standard         Date Format in range 1950-2049).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALID.TO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date entered here will be compared with the system date. If the system date is the less than the date entered here, then this restriction is valid. Data can only be entered into this field if VALID.FROM.DATE is entered in the standard T24 date format.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>"NOINPUT" field if the VALID.FROM.DATE field is         populated with either &gt;nnnX or &lt;nnnX.</p>
            <p>Up to 9 type D date characters, (Standard Date Format in         range 1950-2049) if VALID.FROM.DATE is a standard T24         date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input only allowed when the key to the record starts with "</p>
            <p>The "ALL" type RESTRICTION is applicable to all transactions. This field allows the user to restrict even further which transactions the "ALL" records applies to.</p>
            <p>Enter an valid field name from the SEL.APPLI application into this field to limit the restriction to transactions taking place in this application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid field in the SEL.APPLI application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEPARATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the type of separator that will be used to determine multiple values in one field.</p>
            <p>When using the NE or EQ operands it is possible to enter more than one value by using a separator. The separator that is being used must be specified in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>* (Asterisk)</p>
            <p>, (Comma)</p>
            <p>. (Full Stop)</p>
            <p>/ (Forward Slash)</p>
            <p>NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALIDATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This determines when a restriction will be valid.</p>
            <p>Input can either be ONLINE (T24 Online) or BATCH (T24 EOD)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>ONLINE or BATCH</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.OP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input only allowed when the key to the record starts with "</p>
            <p>The "ALL" type RESTRICTION is applicable to all transactions. This field allows the user to restrict even further which transactions the "ALL" records applies to.</p>
            <p>Enter an operand into this field to limit the restriction to transactions taking place in this application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Either</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a sub-value field which allows a list of applications to be entered. The restriction will only apply to the applications entered, however, if the field is left blank then the restriction will apply to all applications.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid application in the PGM.FILE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This application is used to set up relationships between certain customers, transactions etc.</p>
            <p>This allows applications to search through this file &amp; obtain lists of restrictions which apply to certain transactions.</p>
            <p>The key to the application is constructed in the following way:</p>
            <p>* ALL - All transcations are applicable to this group of restrictions e.g. ALL.SC</p>
            <p>* CUSTOMER - Only the customer number is applicable to this group of restrictions e.g. 50030.SC</p>
            <p>* PORTFOLIO - Only the potfolio number is applicable to this group of restrictions e.g. 50030-1.SC</p>
            <p>* ACCOUNT - Only the account number is applicable to this group of restrictions e.g. 18345.SC</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>An ID which adheres to the rules above.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTRICTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a sub-value field &amp; contains a list of the restriction ID's to be processed. It is a user defined field but the field must start with "R-".</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>Must start with "R-".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.APPLI</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input only allowed when the key to the record starts with "</p>
            <p>The "ALL" type RESTRICTION is applicable to all transactions. This field allows the user to restrict even further which transactions the "ALL" records applies to.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowable applications for EB.PRODUCT: SC</p>
            <p>SECURITY.MASTER, SEC.ACC.MASTER, ACCOUNT, CUSTOMER</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A valid application from the table above.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

