<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>SEAT.APPLICATION.MANAGER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>SEAT.APPLICATION.MANAGER is used to set up default routines that need to be executed for scripts in addition to the routines that are attached to the SEAT record specified in the SEAT.ID field of SEAT.SCRIPTS. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RELATED.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used for records Created in other Applications during COB. E.g. for a LD contract a PD may get Created during COB.                                     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESULT.FILES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field and its associated fields are used for RECORDING option. This is used for specifying the application name for which the result files needs to be created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid operand like GT, LT, EQ, NE, GE, LE, RG, NR and IN or any S type PGM.FILE routine. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECIS.VAL.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>To be used when the RG or NR operand are used</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.SCOPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>During which stage the Field values needs to be recorded.      </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Accepts one of these values </p>
            <p>  'INPUT’</p>
            <p>  ’AUTHORISATION’</p>
            <p>  ’DELETE’</p>
            <p>  ’REVERSAL’</p>
            <p>  ’ALL’</p>
            <p>  ’COB'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts one of these values 'ABSOLUTE’,’INCREMENT’,’LOCATE’ </p>
            <p />
            <p>  ABSOLUTE – Gets the Value in the Field as it is </p>
            <p />
            <p>  INCREMENT – Compares the BEFORE and AFTER image and updates the difference.                                                                                                 </p>
            <p>  LOCATE – This option is used for MULTIVALUE fields in the application</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies how the field value is updated.             </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Accepts one of these values </p>
            <p>  'UPDATE’</p>
            <p>  ’CALCULATED'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDEX.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts values Y or N</p>
            <p>Maximum of 3 characters allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MASTER.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the application name from SEAT.APPLICATION manager, for which the RESULT.FILES and FIELD.VALUES need to be generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.ID.MAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the ID of the RESULT.FILE is generated from a routine, then that Routine name is given in this field. This value is updated in SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES – REC.ID.MAP field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECIS.VAL.FRM</field>
<desc>
            <p>A value that should be returned by the routine or checked against the operand</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.FROM.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the FIELD.TYPE is UPDATE then in this field the file from which the field is updated is given</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>A Valid Field name in the application given in the RESULT.FILES field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATED.APPLN.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Routine for getting the TRANSACTION.ID of the application given in RELATED .APPLICATION field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.RELEASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This BASE.RELEASE field gets defaulted when SEAT.TEST record is verified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COB.RESULTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether Results need to be recorded during COB                     </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Accepts one of these values </p>
            <p>  ‘NO’ - no need of recording results during COB    </p>
            <p>  ’END.OF.DAY’ - results need to be recorded during END.OF.DAY              </p>
            <p>  ’START.OF.DAY’ - results need to be recorded during START.OF.DAY      </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONCAT.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the result file is a table file or not.</p>
            <p>Option Y allowed only if it is a table file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Accepts value Y or N</p>
            <p>Maximum characters allowed 3.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECIS.EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The event manager id that needs to be picked up if the above condition is satisfied by the transaction. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECIS.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>For the SYSTEM record, can be STANDARD.SELECTION. </p>
            <p>  For an application record – can be any field from the application or any field from the link application for e.g. to extract the RESIDENCE of a CUSTOMER from ACCOUNT application, the format to be specified is RESIDENCE, CUSTOMER, CUSTOMER.NO (field in ACCOUNT application). Similarly to specify a multi value or sub value field then specify it in the format CALC.CHRGS: 2:1 </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.EVENT.MGR</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid SEAT.EVENT.MANAGER id, this is the default event manager id which gets triggered for the application specified irrespective of any conditions or a Seat record can be inputted with convention ‘SEAT*Seat record ID’. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to SEAT.APPLICATION.MANAGER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum of 35 characters.</p>
            <p>Free flow text.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

