<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>SIGN.ON.RESET</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW FOR SIGN ON RESET </p>
            <p>This application is to be used, when a user has been forced out of the system and has then left details in the F.LOCKING and F.ACTIVITY files. </p>
            <p>To clear a user from above files a record has to be entered using the (I)nput function.  The key to this record is the ID of user to be cleared/reset.  The the (A)uthorisation function must be run to actually perform the clear/reset and on successfully running the record is deleted from SIGN.ON.RESET file. </p>
            <p>A different user is required to run the (A)uthorisation function from the one that ran the I(nput) function and neither user can be the user whose Id is being reset. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the user whose details are to be removed from the F.LOCKING and F.ACTIVITY file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-16 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>The USER ID must be a valid key on the USER file.</p>
            <p>The USER ID cannot be that of the Inputter or Authorisor.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the name of the person that ran the Input function. </p>
            <p>At the Input Stage the Inputters Id is stored on this field.  Then at the Authorisation Stage a check is made that a different user to the one stored here is running the Authorisation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 16 alphanumeric characters. No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for free form notes. </p>
            <p>This field is provided for entering of notes, and is not used anywhere else. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. Multivalued. (Optional Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

