<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>SIGNATURE.PARM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds the instructions for formatting the signature display screen. In addition it holds the list of valid card mandate conditions along with the terminals supported for capture and display of signatures. </p>
            <p>There is only one record called "SYSTEM" and this will be entered automatically when any function is entered within the application. </p>
            <p>Also defined are the signature boxes available on each signature card. Any number may be defined dependant simply on how many may visibly be displayed on the screen. Each signature box may be labelled uniquely and positioned anywhere on the screen. Each box may also have it's area defined with a drawn around rectangle. </p>
            <p>Lines of text may be entered for display on each signature card. Any number may be entered and displayed anywhere on the available area of the screen. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FILLER.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILLER.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGNATURE.BOX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the label for a signature box </p>
            <p>This field begins a multivalue set describing each signature box on the card. It is not mandatory but if entered the signature box label will be displayed on the screen at the co-ordinates defined in LABEL.POSN. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 20 alphanumeric Signifies the beginning of the multivalue set of fields 7 to 12.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILLER.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONDITION.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the screen co-ordinates for display of the card mandate condition. </p>
            <p>The card mandate is preceded by a multilanguage translation of the text "Card condition:" and is displayed at the co-ordinates specified on the signature card display. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric  ','  1 -3 numeric</p>
            <p>Enter as XXX,YYY where XXX = X axis co-ordinate in the range 1-1000 YYY = Y axis co-ordinate in the range 026-750 Co-ordinates are converted at display time into a fraction of the available screen area of the terminal being used for display. The 026 minimum on the Y axis allows for the status line on the signature card.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEXT.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the screen co-ordinates for display of a line of text. </p>
            <p>This field is multivalue associated with TEXT and defines the screen co-ordinates for display of a line of text. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric  ','  1 -3 numeric Ends the multivalue set of fields 13 and 14.</p>
            <p>Enter as XXX,YYY where XXX = X axis co-ordinate in the range 1-1000 YYY = Y axis co-ordinate in the range 026-750 Co-ordinates are converted at display time into a fraction of the available screen area of the terminal being used for display. The 026 minimum on the Y axis allows for the status line on the signature card.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores overrides on changes made. </p>
            <p>No input allowed to this field. It is updated automatically when a change is made to the SIGNATURE.PARM record SYSTEM which requires the recording of an override condition. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 50 alphanumeric. No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the file </p>
            <p>Only one record exists on the file and the ID of "SYSTEM" is 2selected by default on entry of a function. Any other ID entered is ignored. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Defaults to "SYSTEM"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILLER.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the names of those applications which may request the display of a signature. </p>
            <p>Any T24 application containing an account number may request display of a signature providing the application is defined in this field and the location of the account number field given in the next field DISPLAY.FIELD. </p>
            <p>Once this is entered the signature for an account may be requested with the signature hotkey when operating within the application concerned. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 35 alphanumeric. Begins the multivalue set of fields 15 and 16.</p>
            <p>Application must exist on the PGM.FILE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ENABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the signature display system is enabled to the tellers. </p>
            <p>Input must be either "Y" or "N". When changing from "Y" to "N" an override is required since this will close down signature display to any calling application. This override is written to the exception log file for reporting at end of day. The user is warned about this on-line when a shutdown is requested. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether any name saved with a signature is to displayed on the label line of the signature box. </p>
            <p>When signatures are captured or at a later stage if required a name may be added for each signature box. If this field is set to 'Y' for any signature box then the name if it exists will be appended to the actual signature box label and displayed at the screen position defined in LABEL.POSN. This field is multivalue associated with SIGNATURE.BOX. The default setting is 'N'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric Multivalue associated with fields 7 to 12</p>
            <p>Input must be 'Y' or 'N' only.</p>
            <p>Defaults to 'N'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.APPL</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the application, which invokes the signature card.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Fields   DISPLAY.APPL to DISPLAY.FIELD form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard   T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>A   maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must   be the key to a valid entry on the PGM.FILE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.LEFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the screen co-ordinates for the top left corner of a signature box. </p>
            <p>Each signature box is positioned on the screen by specifying the TOP.LEFT and BOTTOM.RIGHT screen co-ordinates. This field is multivalue associated with SIGNATURE.BOX. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric  ','  1 -3 numeric Multivalue associated with fields 7 to 12</p>
            <p>Enter as XXX,YYY where XXX = X axis co-ordinate in the range 1-1000 YYY = Y axis co-ordinate in the range 026-750 Co-ordinates are converted at display time into a fraction of the available screen area of the terminal being used for display. The 026 minimum on the Y axis allows for the status line on the signature card.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILLER.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the location of the account number field in an application requesting a signature display. </p>
            <p>Any T24 application may request the display of a signature providing the application is defined in the previous field DISPLAY.APPL and the location of the account number field within the application is entered in this field. </p>
            <p>The other input option is 'C' which means that the location of the account number field may vary within records of the application and must therefore be calculated by the application itself. An example of this is TELLER where the debit account number must be determined from the two possible sides of the transaction before the signature can be requested. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 alphanumeric. Ends the multivalue set of fields 15 and 16.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid field within the application entered in the DISPLAY.APPL field or a 'C'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.TERMS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminals supporting display of signatures. </p>
            <p>Only certain terminals will support signature display due to the complex routines required to display the signature. Do not change this field without prior consultation with T24 technical support. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 20 alphanumeric Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Entry must exist on TERMINAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields DISPLAY.APPL to DISPLAY.FIELD form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the list of card mandates </p>
            <p>Each signature card may have a mandate condition assigned to it. This field defines a list of the most commonly used mandates with their multilanguage translations. In the signature application a mandate may be chosen from this list by typing a single number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 50 alphanumeric Mulivalue field Multilanguage</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.CONDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines a line of free text to be displayed on the screen on every signature card. </p>
            <p>This is a multivalued field associated with TEXT.POSN. Any number of lines of text may be entered for display on the signature card screen at the co-ordinates entered for each in the TEXT.POSN screen. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 35 alphanumeric Signifies the beginning of the multivalue set of fields 13 and 14.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LABEL.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the screen position for display of the signature box label. </p>
            <p>The signature box label is built from the SIGNATURE.BOX field and appended with the name saved for the signature if DISPLAY.NAME is set to 'Y'. This field positions the label on the screen at the co-ordinates specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric  ','  1 -3 numeric Ends the multivalue set of fields 7 to 12.</p>
            <p>Enter as XXX,YYY where XXX = X axis co-ordinate in the range 1-1000 YYY = Y axis co-ordinate in the range 026-750 Co-ordinates are converted at display time into a fraction of the available screen area of the terminal being used for display. The 026 minimum on the Y axis allows for the status line on the signature card.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOTTOM.RIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the screen co-ordinates for the bottom right corner of a signature box. </p>
            <p>Each signature box is positioned on the screen by specifying the TOP.LEFT and BOTTOM.RIGHT screen co-ordinates. This field is multivalue associated with SIGNATURE.BOX. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric  ','  1 -3 numeric Multivalue associated with fields 7 to 12</p>
            <p>Enter as XXX,YYY where XXX = X axis co-ordinate in the range 1-1000 YYY = Y axis co-ordinate in the range 026-750 Co-ordinates are converted at display time into a fraction of the available screen area of the terminal being used for display. The 026 minimum on the Y axis allows for the status line on the signature card.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOX.AROUND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether a box is to be drawn around the available signature box area. </p>
            <p>Signature boxes may be delineated with a box drawn on the screen. If signatures exceed the dimensions of the box they will still appear completely but will overwrite the box area where necessary. This is merely a display option and defaults to 'N'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 alphanumeric Multivalue associated with fields 7 to 12</p>
            <p>Input must be 'Y' or 'N' only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPTURE.TERMS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminals capable of running signature capture </p>
            <p>Only certain terminals will support signature capture due to the complex capture routines required to digitise the signature. Do not change this field without prior consultation with T24 technical support. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 20 alphanumeric Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Entry must exist on TERMINAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARD.ID.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the screen co-ordinates for display of the card id. </p>
            <p>The card id is preceded by a multilanguage translation of the text "Card id:" and is displayed at the co-ordinates specified on the signature card display. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric  ','  1 -3 numeric</p>
            <p>Enter as XXX,YYY where XXX = X axis co-ordinate in the range 1-1000 YYY = Y axis co-ordinate in the range 026-750 Co-ordinates are converted at display time into a fraction of the available screen area of the terminal being used for display. The 026 minimum on the Y axis allows for the status line on the signature card.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

