<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>SPF</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds the details of the system wide parameters that are required to run the T24 system.</p>
            <p>It contains one record identified as SYSTEM.</p>
            <p>This allows the user to define various parameters, such as, the main data accounts and their associated disk backup areas (for the start / end of day processes), the backup mode, the shared memory files to be used, the maximum number of pages allowed to be displayed in the enquiry system.</p>
            <p>In addition to these there are other fields in the SYSTEM record not input by the user but updated by other processes, these include the system operation mode and the recovery date and time.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRODUCTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies all the T24 products which have been installed.</p>
            <p>This field contains all the products installed on your system.  If you wish to use a new product, contact Temenos who will supply you with a product code for the new product.  Enter the new product in this field and the product code in field 40 (PRODUCT CODES).  A new product cannot be added unless a product code is entered.</p>
            <p>See the Installation Guide for further information on installing a new product.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 alphanumeric (type A) characters (Optional input, multivalue field, fields 39 - 40 form a multivalue set)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTRICT.RPT.VIEW</field>
<desc>
            <p>Restricts the reprint and view of reports to those received at end of day.</p>
            <p>If this is set a user will only be allowed to reprint or view reports which he specifically receives from the end of day run.</p>
            <p>This is in addition to any SMS controls applied to the HOLD.CONTROL application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y/N (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MASTER.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used when programs are shared between accounts and is used to specify in which account the programs reside.  However, normally programs should reside in each account and this field should be left blank. Sharing programs between accounts can cause problems when upgrading and should be avoided.</p>
            <p>If you wish to share programs between accounts, please contact Tememos Support before doing so.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Blank or account name where programs reside.  Should be blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.STAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to store current stage of an update or packager installation and is used to identify and restrict t24 system features during updates or packager installation.</p>
            <p>The system will restrict t24 user from accessing t24 applications if the stage 'INPROGRESS' is stored in this field, this indicates that the system is in middle of an update installation process</p>
            <p>Until completion of T24.UPDATES or T24.MODEL.PACKAGE service, the t24 user will not have full fledged access to t24 system.</p>
            <p>Allowed applications when the stage is 'INPROGRESS' :  </p>
             <p> TSA.SERVICE :records T24.UPDATES,TSM and T24.MODEL.PACKAGE </p>
             <p> BATCH : records T24.UPDATES , T24.MODEL.PACKAGE </p>
             <p> SPF,T24.MODEL.PACKAGES, T24.UPDATE.RELEASE table - all records can be accessed </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field (System maintained field)</p>
            <p>System generated values are : </p>
            <p> 1. INPROGRESS :- set at the stage of updating data records (T24.UPDATE.RELEASE also can be considered as default data record in an update) during updater utility process </p>
            <p> 2. COMPLETED :- set when final SPF update happens at the end of T24.UPDATES service </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PATCHES.INSTLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>With the advent of T24 updates, this field will not be updated anymore</p>
            <p>No input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVE.USER.BATCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates if the end of day is allowed to start when there are users currently logged into the system, but are not actually performing operations that can update the database. Any function other then, See, List, Print and Exception or null will result in the prevention of the batch starting.</p>
            <p>The default will be to retain the existing functionality i.e. the EOD will not start until all users are logged out. If the field is set, then EOD will only start if the users logged in are not performing functions that can update the data base.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid options are</p>
            <p>YES</p>
            <p>NO or null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALL.PG.INC</field>
<desc>
            <p>If ALL.PG.INC is set to 'YES' then all functions specified on the user profile under application ALL.PG</p>
            <p>will be added to the function lists for all applications specified on the user profile.</p>
            <p>'NO' or null is current standard functionality.</p>
            <p>Allowed value YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARC.USER.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDIT.APPEND.IP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The IP address and machine name from which the T24 request orginated is updated in the audit fields INPUTTER and AUTHORISER if this field is set to YES. If set to NO these extra details are not included in the audit fields</p>
            <p>Default value is Null which is same as NO</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Can be set to YES / NO / Null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.MANUAL.BATCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows EOD, backups, and start of day to be performed automatically once the initial backup has commenced.  Alternatively these processes can be performed manually.</p>
            <p>Input of 'Automatic' in this field will cause automatic processing to take place when the 'Initiate EOD' option is chosen from the BATCH.CONTROL monitor application (option 8).</p>
            <p>In automatic mode at initiate EOD, once correct replies to the continue and spool prompts have been input, backup will be done followed by AUTO.BATCH and start on-line, including its backup.</p>
            <p>Use of automatic backup implies that no journal phantoms will be restarted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Automatic or Manual (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If an input is made to this field no input other that AUTOMATIC or MANUAL is accepted.  No input in this field is equivalent to having input MANUAL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTOLOG.TIME.MINS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the time a user may be inactive during the authorisation/validation phase of a transaction before the user is timed out.</p>
            <p>The authorisation commit phase inactivity is only considered when ACTIVE TIMEOUT.MODE is selected.</p>
            <p>Typically this value will be a relatively short amount of time compared to the TIME.OUT.MINUTES defined in the user profile, as incativity by the user at this point of the transaction can cause congestion in the system, with users waiting for locks held by the user to be released.</p>
            <p>Where REPORT.LOCKS is set to YES, this field will be used additionally to provide the user with the opportunity to continue waiting for a lock  to be released, or to exit T24.</p>
            <p>A null value in this field with ACTIVE TIMEOUT.MODE will cause the TIME.OUT.MINUTES setting in the USER profile to be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Number of minutes in the range 1 to 999 Only allowed if TIMEOUT.MODE is set to ACTIVE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACKUP.CYCLE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the backup areas and backup devices for the start of day backup.</p>
            <p>This field should contain the names of the start of day backup areas on disk corresponding to the list of accounts specified in MAIN ACCOUNT (field 5).</p>
            <p>In addition it is also possible to define backup devices such as tape within this field to aid the automatic running of the backup cycle using the UNIX.BACKUP (field 24) where examples will be found.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Upto 50 alphanumeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACKUP.CYCLE.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the backup areas and backup devices for the start of batch backup.</p>
            <p>This field should contain the names of the start of batch backup areas on disk corresponding to the list of accounts specified in MAIN ACCOUNT (field 5).</p>
            <p>In addition it is also possible to define backup devices such as tape within this field to aid the automatic running of the backup cycle using the UNIX.BACKUP (field 24) where examples will be found.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 50 alphanumeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BATCH.SESSIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in conjunction with the T24 GUI End of Day process, this field specifies the number of sessions which will run the end of day process. Where possible, these sessions will run the end of day processing concurrently.</p>
            <p>If the GUI is not used to control the End of Day process, this field will have no effect upon the running of the batch process.</p>
            <p>Where the GUI is used to control the End of Day process, but this field has been left blank, then the default of one session will be used to control the batch.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be numeric. Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRANCH.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must contain the Branch key if the SPF record belongs to the branch. This must remain blank if the SPF record belongs to the Central Server.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only used if BR product is installed.</p>
            <p>Blank for the Head Office but must contain a valid Branch ID at each branch</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BREAK.KEY.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ascii number of the break key. Eg CNTRL P would be ascii character 16.</p>
            <p>An optional break key can be defined for all users. Normally it is disabled by the parameters in the TERMINAL record but it can be enabled, under operator control and for a specific user, by using the MASTER BREAK utility in the UV account (See Universe HELP).</p>
            <p>Once enabled the user can break out of the current task and login again.  This must not be used when there is a danger of corrupting the database.  Ie. IT MUST NEVER BE USED DURING THE 'UPDATING FILES' PART OF A TRANSACTION.  If in doubt contact T24 support.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 Numeric characters.(Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROWSER.REC.LOCK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether or not extra record locking is to take place over and above the system locking. This functionality is only necessary when the database is using the Browser interface. If the browser is not being used this should be set to 'NO'</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>YES or NO</p>
            <p>Null is treated as NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CACHE.EXPIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the time interval (in number of seconds) between the cache file refreshes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CACHE.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the cache size to be used within the T24 system for record writes.</p>
            <p>Internally within the T24 system this field defines the size of the cache held before records are written to file. Previously defined within T24 as a size of 500, it is now amendable.</p>
            <p>Users of the LD module who wish to enter long term deals of 10 years or more with monthly settlements of interest &amp;/or commission will need to set this value above the default. A 25 year monthly settled deal would require a value of about 1800, more if Position Management is used (see also PM.LD.PARAM field</p>
            <p>PM.MAX.PERIOD</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 Numeric characters (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If this field is left blank it will default to 500,         otherwise a value between 250 and 9999 is allowed.</p>
            <p>No amendment may be made to this field if other users are         accessing the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATALOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provides the option to locally catalog the T24 programs.</p>
            <p>If 'LOCAL' or blank is specified the object code is stored in BP1.0 or BP2.0.  If  'GLOBAL' is specified this object code is moved to the system catalog space or/catdir.</p>
            <p>This option is only operational when running GLOBUS.RELEASE or REPGEN.SOURCE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 A "LOCAL", "GLOBAL" or blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMIT.TIME.OUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the Number of seconds, any of the Override Message that is generated when Committing the Transaction, would wait for the User response.</p>
            <p>If  no response either  OK / Cancel   is received for Override message, within the given number of seconds, then  Automatically the  Override message is  cancelled and  returns to the Transaction.</p>
            <p>A running  Timer is displayed in the Override Message, if  input is provided in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input must be a number between 1 and 999.</p>
            <p>Indicates the Number of seconds.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMP.MNE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 9 Alphanumeric (type A) characters (No input, multivalue field, fields 33 and 34 field a multivalue set)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.RELEASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the release of T24 currently installed at your site.</p>
            <p>The format of the release number is as follows:</p>
            <p>XX.YY.ZZ</p>
            <p>XX   Major release (New modules / functionality)  YY   Minor release (Enhancements) ZZ   Dot release number (Fixes)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 Numeric characters XX.YY.ZZ. (No input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.ACC.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the data account.</p>
            <p>Contains the name of the Information UFD where the files for the T24 system physically reside.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 alphanumeric (type A) characters (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATABASE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines if this database is a Branch or a Central Server when the T24 Branch System is installed.</p>
            <p>For the Central Server, this field will be set to Null</p>
            <p>For the Branch the value in this field will define the name of the branch.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input. If this field is Null then the Database is the Central Server.</p>
            <p>Can be input only if BA is installed as a Product on the COMPANY record.</p>
            <p>The value present in this field must be available in the file BA.STATUS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME.MV</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the system field DATE.TIME is to be updated multi valued, together with enhanced INPUTTER information.</p>
            <p>When set to "YES" the INPUTTER and DATE.TIME fields will be updated as follows:</p>
            <p>TNO_OPERATOR_FUNCTION_STATUS_GTS/OFS_OFS.SOURCE.ID</p>
            <p>Where all data items are separated by '_'(underscore).</p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Data Item</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Usage</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>TNO</td>
                    <td>is the terminal or phantom number of the user</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>OPERATOR</td>
                    <td>is the USER name</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>FUNCTION</td>
                    <td>e.g. I for Input</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>STATUS</td>
                    <td>e.g. INAU for unauthorised input</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>GTS</td>
                    <td>indicates that the record was input via the GTS module</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>OFS</td>
                    <td>indicates that the record was input via the OFS module</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>OFS.SOURCE.ID</td>
                    <td>indicates the OFS.SOURCE record used by OFS.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>DATE.TIME</td>
                    <td>will be multi valued with the first value indicating the latest action.</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>Example</p>
            <p>4. 1 INPUTTER....... 31_J.BROWN_I_INAU 4. 2 INPUTTER....... 31_S.SMITH_I_INAU 5. 1 DATE.TIME...... 15 NOV 99 09:15 5. 2 DATE.TIME...... 15 NOV 99 09:10 5. 3 DATE.TIME...... 15 NOV 99 09:05 6 AUTHORISER........ 31_P.HARRIS</p>
            <p>This record has 2 inputters and an authoriser. It was input by S.SMITH at 9:05, then amended by J.BROWN at 9:10 and finally authorised by P.HARRIS at 9:15.</p>
            <p>The first DATE.TIME value corresponds to when the record was authorised. The second DATE.TIME value will indicate when the second inputter modified the unauthorised record, first value in INPUTTER field. The third DATE.TIME value will indicate when the record was first input, last inputter field.</p>
            <p>When set to "NO" or left blank the INPUTTER and DATE.TIME fields will be updated as follows:</p>
            <p>Updating will be in the format:</p>
            <p>TNO_OPERATOR_'' _''_GTS/OFS_OFS.SOURCE.ID where '' is null.</p>
            <p>Irrespective of the setting of this field when an authorised record is modified then the INPUTTER and DATE.TIME fields are cleared.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>If input then must be set to "YES" or "NO"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DICT.ACC.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the account containing dictionaries.</p>
            <p>A seperate account can be set up containing all dictionaries, rather than the dictionaries residing in the data account. This is useful due to the Primos limitation in the number of items in an account.  DICT ACC NAME can be the same as DATA ACC NAME.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 alphanumeric (type A) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENCRYPTION.ALGORITHM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field for specifying any user defined encryption algorithm</p>
            <p>A BASIC/JAVA routine needs to be written and defined in EB.API. The same name has to be provided in this field if the system has to skip the normal T24 password encryption mechanism and follow the user-defined encryption method written in the routine.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1. Optional field</p>
            <p>2. Length: Maximum of 35.</p>
            <p>3. This field is of type HOOK </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.PAGE.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the maximum number of pages allowed to be displayed in the ENQUIRY system.</p>
            <p>This field allows the user to setup a limit on the maximum number of pages the ENQUIRY system can build/display. A page limit of 50 should be adequate in most cases.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters in the range 1 to 200. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.SERV.LVL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used with the event service. It allows to limit the event processed to a certain severity level. The levels below the severity level</p>
            <p>selected are not processed.</p>
            <p>This field can be used in conjunction with the</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A valid event severity ( alphabetic format )</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.SERV.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used with the event service. It allows to limit the events processed to a specific type.</p>
            <p>It can be used in conjunction with the</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Empty ( all event type are processed )</p>
            <p>Event type existing in EB.EVENT.TYPE table. The events processed are     limited to this type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.AI.USERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.AP.USERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTENDED.PREC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether extended precision (string maths) is being used.  This increases the length of amount fields to allow up to 14 integers with 0 dps; 13 integers with 2 dps; 12 integers with 3 dps.  Without extended precision, amount fields are limited to 12 integers minus the number of decimal places (12 integers with 0 dps; 10 integers with 2 dps; 9 integers with 3 dps).</p>
            <p>Extended precision is supported by default in jBASE and the field is no longer used. Whatever the setting all T24 programs will use extended precision. Therefore the field setting is assumed to be Y.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Will be assumed to be Y in all cases.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GAC.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the GAC account. This must be completed manually for a T24 administration account.It will be completed by the GAC.ACCOUNTS LINK action for a linked entity.</p>
            <p>Must be the name of a UniVerse account in UV.ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GLOBAL.PROCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:YES NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELD.RPT.RETENTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of days after which a report that has been spooled and held will be removed from the hold file, the customer held file, and the &amp;HOLD&amp; file.</p>
            <p>If this field is set to null the number of days will default to the standard report retention (field 17).</p>
            <p>This value will be overridden by the value set up in the REPORT.CONTROL record for the report if a value has been entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 Numeric characters (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIST.LIFE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of days for which the exception log history is retained.</p>
            <p>This field should contain the number of days to which the in the exception log history (EXCEPTION.LOG.HIST) file should be retained.</p>
            <p>Examples:  4    -   The details in the exception log history file                     will be retained for the last 4 days.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric characters. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HOLD.BATCH.OUTPUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Suppresses printing of all output from a Batch run.  The reports etc. are stored in the HOLD file and can be printed using the SPOOL.BATCH.OUTPUT application.</p>
            <p>If this flag is set to 'Y' then all output from the batch is stored in the HOLD file.  This can then be printed (in sorted order) by using the SPOOL.BATCH.OUTPUT application.</p>
            <p>If the job/process is re-run in the batch the COMO is printed immediately.  This is to ensure the operator receives the error details contained in the COMO file.  It will be re-printed when SPOOL.BATCH.OUTPUT is run.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y/N (Mandatory)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INFO.JOURNAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>INFO.JOURNAL field which if set to Y will keep journal  entries for users.This is not intended to provide full journal</p>
            <p>information (which should be available in the jBase or Oracle journals). It is meant to be for investigation purposes.</p>
            <p>INFO.JOURNAL if set to Y will allow the system to write  out a limited number of journal records per user. A hard  coded limit of 20 is there. </p>
            <p>This is purley for debug and investigation and not a way to continue updating the JOURNAL file.</p>
            <p>Allowed value Y or null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.LOG.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field decides whether to use log files internally within T24 or to use TAF level logging</p>
            <p> This switch has been enabled for below T24 log files : </p>
            <p>    1. Log file directory specified in field LOG.FILE.DIR of OFS.SOURCE </p>
            <p>    2. EXCEPTION.LOG.FILE </p>
            <p>    3. EB.LOGGING </p>
            <p>    4. EB.CONVERSION.EXCEPTION </p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allowed values are : YES/null </p>
            <p> If set to YES - T24 level logging enabled and messages will be logged into T24 level log files </p>
            <p> If not set (null) - TAFC level logging enabled by default and messages will be logged to TAFC log files.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LICENSE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies your license code code for T24.  This code may not necessarily be the same as the code which appears on your contract.</p>
            <p>Although this field is optional, it should entered as soon as it is known. Please contact Temenos if you do not know your license code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>12 characters (9 alphanumeric characters,3 numeric characters)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LICENSE.ENC.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies your contract code for T24.</p>
            <p>lthough this field is optional, it should entered as soon as it is known.  Please contact Temenos if you do not know your contract code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>12 characters, 6 alpha, 6 numeric. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAIN.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the main system file accounts to be backed up.</p>
            <p>This field should contain the names of the main system file accounts which are required to be backed up during the start/end of day cycles.</p>
            <p>The first entry in this field should name the main data account for the bank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-50 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINT.TEC.OUTPUT</field>
<desc>
            <p> The field to specify if notification to TEC should be recorded in TEC.OUTPUT </p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1. Y/N field. </p>
            <p> 2. Non-mandatory. </p>
            <p> 3. To be set as 'N' to stop recordding to TEC.OUTPUT. By default, TEC.OUTPUT will be record if set as NULL. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINTENANCE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code required to enable maintenance date to be amended.</p>
            <p>If the date is incorrect or your maintenance contract has been renewed, please contact Temenos who will supply you with a new maintenance code. Alternatively, if you do not have a maintenance contract with Temenos, please contact Temenos who will give you a code to cycle this date. When contacting Temenos, please give them your current maintenance date and license code.</p>
            <p>Enter your new maintenance date in this field and the maintenance code in field 38 - MAINTENANCE CODE.  Maintenance date cannot be amended unless a maintenance code is entered.  Alternatively, just a MAINTENANCE CODE can be entered which will cause the maintenance date to cycle by a given number of months specified by the maintenance code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 numeric characters (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINTENANCE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on which your maintenance contract is due for renewal.</p>
            <p>If the date is incorrect or your maintenance contract has been renewed, please contact Temenos who will supply you with a new maintenance code. Alternatively, if you do not have a maintenance contract with Temenos, please contact Temenos who will give you a code to cycle this date. When contacting Temenos, please give them your current maintenance date and license code.</p>
            <p>This date is used by the system to ensure that Temenos are aware of all copies of T24.  The date can be cycled by Temenos, regardless of whether maintenance has been paid or not.  Linking the date to the maintenance date is purely a means of enabling regular checking of all copies of T24 to take place.</p>
            <p>If this date is overdue by more than one week, a warning message will appear every time a user signs onto T24.  If this date is more than one month overdue, access will not be granted to T24 until the date is cycled.  Therefore, the date should be checked and a code obtained to cycle it before warning messages are produced.</p>
            <p>Enter your new maintenance date in this field and the maintenance code in field 38 - MAINTENANCE CODE.  Maintenance date cannot be amended unless a maintenance code is entered.  Alternatively, just a MAINTENANCE CODE can be entered which will cause the maintenance date to cycle by a given number of months specified by the maintenance code.</p>
            <p>This date is set when the system is delivered initially.  For existing clients, it is updated when upgrading through G5.</p>
            <p>NOTE : Do not amend the maintenance date by using the uniVerse editor - this will cause a corruption of the SPF which will result in access to T24 being denied after a warning period of one month.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8 characters, type D (date format) (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MICROFICHE.OUTPUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the microfiche system.</p>
            <p>If this flag is set to Y or R then whenever a report is produced, which has been selected for microfiching (REPORT.CONTROL field MICROFICHE OUTPUT), it is copied to the microfiche area.  When the MF system is run then this area will be copied to tape.</p>
            <p>All delivery output (SWIFT, TELEX and PRINT) will be copied to this area if this flag is set to Y.</p>
            <p>N    =   disable microfiching            Y    =   microfiche all delivery and selected reports            R    =   microfiche selected reports only</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y, N or R (Mandatory)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.PASSWORD.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.ROUNDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 6 amount (type AMT) characters (No input, multivalue field, fields 33 and 34 field a multivalue set)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.INDEXES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will disable the use of index based selects in programs and instead use a programatical based select. This field should only be set on advice from Temenos.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.RETRIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximum number of rekey attempts to be allowed can be specified here. The number of rekey attempts specified here applies to all applications.</p>
            <p>This field is not mandatory. If left empty the user is allowed to rekey indefinite number of times.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 Numeric characters. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.USERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of users for which T24 is licensed.  If this field is amended, a maintenance code must be entered, which should be obtained from Temenos Help Desk.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric input</p>
            <p>If entered, a valid maintenance code must be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.2DEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Currency field (No input, multivalue field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OP.CONSOLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the terminal numbers which will serve as operator consoles to receive any  messages from the system.</p>
            <p>The terminal numbers entered here will receive any critical error messages sent out by the T24 system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OP.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the current system operation mode.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>O - On-line B - Batch mode R - Database restored (recovery) (System maintained. No manual input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATING.SYSTEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to tell T24 which operating system type is in use. Due to the different command structures between Unix and Windows NT is most important that this flag is set correctly. Accordingly, when input is made in this field the value entered will be checked against the system and only the correct value will be allowed.</p>
            <p>When transferring from one type to another the SPF record will need amending and this field will need changing.</p>
            <p>T24 supports two categories of Operating System:</p>
            <p>Unix</p>
            <p>Most types of Unix, as supported by UniVerse, can be used to run T24. Transfers of databases/files between different types of Unix can be done (as long as the appropriate byte-swapping [format.conv] has been performed). Use HELP FORMAT.CONV at the UniVerse command prompt for full details.</p>
            <p>Windows NT</p>
            <p>Windows NT commands are structured differently from Unix. Byte-swapping permits databases from Unix to be ported to systems running Windows NT, T24 then makes allowances for the different command structures.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be either UNIX or NT dependent on system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASS.LOWER.ALPHA</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of lowercase alphabetic characters that must exist in the T24 user password</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input. Up to 3 numeric characters between 0 and 999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASS.MIN.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum length required for a T24 user password.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.The length cannot be less than 6 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASS.NUMERIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of numeric characters that must exist in the T24 user password.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional. Up to 3 numeric characters between 0 and 999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASS.OTHER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Can be a character of any nature for example "#". That particular character must exist in the T24 user password.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.MVMT.HIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies how many days history of position movement entries are to be maintained. POS.MVMT.TODAY entries are moved to POS.MVMT.LWORK.DAY each night, and are also copied to the POS.MVMT.HIST file. POS.MVMT.LWORK.DAY contains only the position movement details from the last working day, POS.MVMT.HIST stores the details of position movements for a number of working days defined in this field. If no details are specified the default value is 5 days.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input Must be a number between 1 and 999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.BATCH.ROUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines an API call.</p>
            <p>It enables users to add their own routines or automatically run enquiries or reports at the pre batch stage.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input is optional.</p>
            <p>Input can be the name of a Subroutine or Script or Enquiry or Crystal report.</p>
            <p>Unless it is a Subroutine, the field should contain both the type and the name of the api.call. i.e. Scripts should be prefixed with SPT, Crystal reports with RPT,Enquiries with ENQ. Type and name should be separated by a space. Eg: ENQ ENQ.SEL.FIELDS</p>
            <p>If the input is a Subroutine , it must have an entry in PGM.FILE as an S type program.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREVIOUS.RELEASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the last release installed in this account.  This field is updated when GLOBUS.RELEASE is run.  The previous value of release number is moved to this field.  It is used by RUN.CONVERSION.PGMS (the automated running of conversion programs) to determine which conversion programs should be run.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input</p>
            <p>System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the data account for specific products. Defaults to the data account name (field 19).</p>
            <p>If any products are held on separate data accounts they may be specified here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 40 Alphanumeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.CODES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code required to enable a new product to be added.</p>
            <p>If you wish to use a new product, please contact Temenos who will supply you with a new product code.  Enter your new product in the PRODUCTS field and the product code in this field.  New products cannot be added unless a product code is entered.</p>
            <p>The value entered in this field is erased when the record is authorised.</p>
            <p>See the Installation Guide for further information on installing a new product.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 6 numeric characters (Optional input, multivalue field, fields 39 - 40 form a multivalue set)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PWD.REPETITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of different passwords a user must input before being able to repeat the first one. The default (or minimum number) is 3.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 Numeric characters From 3 to 99</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECV.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the date and time (seconds since midnight) on which the last system recovery was done.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric. 'YYYYMMDDseconds since midnight'. (System maintained. No manual input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.CORE.DUMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field to be set to record logs in EB.SYSTEM.STATUS</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p>"Y" or NULL</p>
            <p>If the field specified "Y" then the records updated in EB.SYSTEM.STATUS file</p>
            <p>If the field contains the value NULL then the records not updated in EB.SYSTEM.STATUS file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.RETENTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of days after which a report will be removed from the hold file &amp;HOLD&amp;.</p>
            <p>If this field is set to null the number of days will default to 5.  This value will be overridden by the value set up in the REPORT.CONTROL record for the report if a value has been entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 numeric characters. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.ACC.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the run account.</p>
            <p>For security reasons a seperate account, a run account, can be created which is used as the initial attach point on login for users.  This account does not contain any files, only pointers for files to the data account and for programs to the account where programs have been catalogued.  Various verbs have been removed from the account and on exiting the T24 system the user is automatically logged out.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 alphanumeric (type A) characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the machine date as at start of day.</p>
            <p>This field contains the machine date the last time the start of day was run.</p>
            <p>This date is also held on the journal header record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-11 type D (date format in range 1950-2049). (System Generated)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.PCK.INSTLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>With the advent of T24 updates, this field will not be updated anymore</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SITE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the installation.</p>
            <p>This field contains the name of the installation at which T24 is installed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.RELEASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether source releases are required or not.</p>
            <p>Prior to G8, T24 upgrades were performed by releasing source code, then compiling and cataloging it on the client site.  Although this procedure worked, for large releases, the upgrade process was quite slow.</p>
            <p>Since G8, object code has been released, removing the need to compile programs onsite.</p>
            <p>If you require programs to be compiled during the upgrade process for any reason, set this field to "Y".  However, please let Temenos Help Desk know you have done this, giving your reasons why, as you will require a special upgrade tape.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or N</p>
            <p>Defaults to "N"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.BACKUP.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the backup media for the start/end of day backup cycles.</p>
            <p>When the start/end of day cycles are performed a backup of the main system files/accounts specified in field MAIN ACCOUNT (5) is done. The backup mode allows the user to specify the storage device to be used for the backup. The following options are available:</p>
            <p>DISK - The files will be backed up to the backup areas on disk specified in fields BACKUP CYCLE 1 (6) or BACKUP CYCLE 2 (7) depending on whether it is the start/end of day cycle.</p>
            <p>TAPE - The files will be backed up to magnetic tape.</p>
            <p>Note:If a restore of the files is to be done then the backup mode must be set to the same mode used to perform the initial backup.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>DISK or TAPE. (Optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.SPEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name of the main record on the file.</p>
            <p>The single record on this file must always be named 'SYSTEM'.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>SYSTEM (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>T24.UPDATES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the  T24 Updates that has been installed in T24 system..</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Allows upto 50 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIMEOUT.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether users are automatically signed off the system after the specified time out period is exceeded, or whether sign off occurs at the next input.</p>
            <p>Entry of ACTIVE will cause the automatic sign off of a user after the TIME.OUT.MINUTES specified in the USER profile during normal processing, or after the AUTOLOG.TIME.MINS if defined in the SPF record. The AUTOLOG.TIME.MINS only becomes effective during the authorisation/validation phase of the transaction.</p>
            <p>Entry of PASSIVE, or null will sign the user off if the TIME.OUT.MINUTES specifed in the user profile is exceeded, at the NEXT input made by the user. There is no distinction made between the authorisation/validation phase  and normal processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>ACTIVE or PASSIVE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.MANAGEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls whether Transaction Management is active or not.</p>
            <p>Transaction Management allows a T24 transaction which consists of updates to one or more database files to roll back the database updates if a physical error is detected on any of the updates, i.e. the database automatically reverts to the state prior to the series of transactional updates.</p>
            <p>Only when all updates have completed successfully does the condition of the database change to reflect the new transaction.</p>
            <p>This means that if a failure occurs then only that transaction will be lost and the integrity of the database remains intact.</p>
            <p>This removes the necessity to restore and recover the database.</p>
            <p>The default status of transaction management is enabled i.e. this field is left blank.</p>
            <p>There is only one situation when transaction management should be disabled and that is when files are updated via uv/net.</p>
            <p>If an attempt is made to update a file via uv/net within a transaction then a fatal error will occur and the database will need to be restored and recovered.</p>
            <p>If this is the case then transaction needs to be turned off; entering OFF in this field does this.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input, 3-character field, can be either set to OFF or left blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNIX.BACKUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unix system backup commands to be used for BACKUP.CYCLE.1 and BACKUP.CYCLE.2 should be entered in this field.</p>
            <p>Unix system backup commands may be entered in this field to be used with MAIN.ACCOUNT, BACKUP.CYCLE.1 and BACKUP.CYCLE.2</p>
            <p>The pipe command may contain a backup device such as '&gt; /dev/rmt1'.</p>
            <p>The two literals '&amp;M&amp;' or '&amp;B&amp;' if used in this field will be replaced as follows; when the Unix backup is executed:</p>
            <p>&amp;M&amp; will be replaced by the contents of MAIN.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>&amp;B&amp; will be replaced by the contents of BACKUP.CYCLE.1 or BACKUP.CYCLE.2 depending on whether start of day or start of batch is being run.</p>
            <p>This field is sub-valued and can be expanded to allow long commands to be entered over 1 or more lines. Use of a sub-values will result in the command being added to that of the previous sub-value. Use of one or more multi-values will result in separate commands.</p>
            <p>Note.Continuation lines may need a leading space to prevent the resulting command being incorrect</p>
            <p>Examples</p>
            <p>To split the unix command over 2 lines</p>
            <p>24.1.1 UNIX.BACKUP find &amp;M&amp; -print | cpio -ovcBdum</p>
            <p>24.1.2 UNIX.BACKUP &gt; /dev/rmt1</p>
            <p>Results in the command</p>
            <p>To process 2 commands</p>
            <p>24.1.1 UNIX.BACKUP find &amp;M&amp;-print | cpio -ovcBdum &gt; /dev/rmt1</p>
            <p>24.2.1 UNIX.BACKUP mt -f /dev/rmt1 rewoffl</p>
            <p>Results in 2 separate commands</p>
            <p>The shell script 'backup.sh' is built and run at backup time in order to ensure the latest command is used from the authorised SPF record. If you experience trouble with the execution of the backup it can be checked to ensure the commands are correct. It is stored in the 'run' directory. Refer to your Systems Administrator if you wish to check where this is.</p>
            <p>Note</p>
            <p>Using a shell script in the command line effectively builds the 'backup.sh' to run that command. However, this can be an advantage if complex or lengthy commands are required locally, also centralised shell scripts can be used. This technique can be used to make disk-to-disk backups (an example 'backup.hd' can normally be found with the demo system we supply).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 50 characters(Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNIX.RESTORE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unix system restore commands to be used for BACKUP.CYCLE.1 and BACKUP.CYCLE.2 should be entered in this field.</p>
            <p>Inclusion of the literals '&amp;M&amp;' or '&amp;B&amp;' in this field will cause them to be replaced by details from MAIN.ACCOUNT, BACKUP.CYCLE.1 or BACKUP.CYCLE.2 as for UNIX.BACKUP (field 24).</p>
            <p>This field is sub-valued and can be expanded to allow long commands to be entered over 1 or more lines. Use of a sub-values will result in the command being added to that of the previous sub-value. Use of one or more multi-values will result in separate commands.</p>
            <p>Note. Continuation lines may need a leading space to prevent the resulting command being incorrect.</p>
            <p>Example</p>
            <p>To process 2 commands:</p>
            <p>25.1.1 UNIX.RESTORE rm -r &amp;M&amp;</p>
            <p>25.2.1 UNIX.RESTORE cpio -iBvudc&lt;/dev/rmt1</p>
            <p>Results in 2 separate commands.</p>
            <p>See HELPTEXT for the field UNIX.BACKUP for an example of one command string split over several sub-values.</p>
            <p>When the SYSTEM.RESTORE command is run from outside of T24 the commands are written from the authorised SPF record to the 'restore.sh' script which is then executed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 50 Alphanumeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.LOCAL.TIME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field displays if the local time zone is enabled or disabled.</p>
        <p>Determines whether the audit fields are updated in  local zone date and time or application server date and time.</p>
        <p>When <b>USE.LOCAL.TIME</b> field is set to <b>YES</b> , local zone date and time is used in audit field.</p>
        <p>When <b>USE.LOCAL.TIME</b> field is set to <b>NULL</b> , application server date and time is used in audit field.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>Optional field.</p>
        <p>  YES_NULL type field.</p>
        <p>If USE.LOCAL.TIME field is set to <b>YES</b> and the record is committed, then the value cannot be changed.</p>
        <p>&#160;</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.DICTIONARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code required to enable a new product to be added.</p>
            <p>If you wish to use a new product, please contact Temenos who will supply you with a new product code.  Enter your new product in the PRODUCTS field and the product code in this field.  New products cannot be added unless a product code is entered.</p>
            <p>The value entered in this field is erased when the record is authorised.</p>
            <p>See the Installation Guide for further information on installing a new product.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 6 numeric characters (Optional input, multivalue field, fields 39 - 40 form a multivalue set)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION.AUTH.CTRL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether to use the mechanism to control the authorisation of composite tab versions.</p>
            <p>If the field value is "YES", it enables following mechanism in a multi-tab version composite screen</p>
            <p>Each version tab of a composite screen will be treated as a separate view that must be seen by the authoriser. A version tab that is defined as zero authorisers will not be required to be seen by authoriser to allow T24 to complete the authorisation process.</p>
            <p>For each version tab that must be seen, the authoriser must view all fields on the version tab, and a visible indication, a red exclamation mark, is given to show the user that this is the case.</p>
            <p>Following are some scenarios of this mechanism</p>
            <p>If the parent version and any of the child versions are set to require one or more authorisers (by specifying the field No of Authorisers in VERSION,DESIGNER), all the fields of the parent and that child version need to be seen before authorisation.</p>
            <p>If the parent version is set to require one or more authorisers and a child version does not need to have any authoriser, the child version does not need to be seen.</p>
            <p>If the parent version is set to require zero authorisers, both the parent version and the child versions don not need to be seen for authorisation.</p>
            <p>A red exclamation mark will appear on the version tab indicating the tab needs to be seen. If the user has seen all fields of the tab, the exclamation mark will disappear, otherwise the authorisation will not proceed.</p>
            <p>If user has seen all fields in the full view, all the exclamation marks on tabs will disappear.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid options are</p>
            <p>YES</p>
            <p>NO or null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASS.UPPER.ALPHA</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of uppercase alphabetic characters that must exist in the T24 user password.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input. Up to 3 numeric characters between 0 and 999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWD.ROLLOVER.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is a frequency field containing the password rollover frequency.</p>
            <p>Used when ENCRYPTION.ALGORITHM specified to re-encrpt the Users password  with new security settings for the specified frequency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1. Optional field</p>
            <p>2. Length: Maximum of 17.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT.TENANT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Only used in a Multi-Tenant System. This field will contain tenant id if the SPF belongs to a tenant. This must remain blank if the SPF record belongs to the Master system and additional app server(s) in multi tenant architecture or when the client is not part of a Multi-Tenant system. </p>
            <p>Value in this field is to provide information about a tenant system and also this will be checked when installating updates in the tenants system, to restrict updater utility parameter options which are not suitable for tenant architecture</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Blank for the standard installations, master system or additional app server(s) but must contain a valid tenant id for a tenant setup.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT.TENANT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Only used in a Multi-Tenant System. This field must contain tenant type if the SPF belongs to tenant. This must remain blank if the SPF record belongs to the Master system and additional app server(s) in multi tenant architecture or when the client is not part of a Multi-Tenant system. </p>
            <p>Value in this field is just to provide information about the current tenant system </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Blank for the standard installations, master system or additional app server(s) but must contain a valid tenant type for a tenant setup</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.UPGRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field used to enable the automation options for T24 upgrade , updates and model package. </p>
            <p> If set to YES, then automation options are enabled and the steps below are followed during upgrade procedures: </p>
            <p> 1. T24.PRE.RELEASE sets User to that of the TSM Service user automatically, to allow unattended processing in tenant systems (in MT architecture). </p>
            <p> 2. The CONVERSION.PGMS records get released to LIVE during upgrade, so that processing can continue with PRE.RUN.CONVERSION without manual intervention of authorising such records.  </p>
            <p>    Any corresponding unauth records get deleted if they conflict with the upgrade replacements. </p>
            <p> 3. New TSA.SERVICE records released to INAU with TSM user in USER field.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid options are</p>
            <p>YES - Automation facility enabled for upgrade,updates and model package.  </p>
            <p>Null - Normal upgrade, updates and model package procedures are followed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>MODULE.UPGRADE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
