<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>SYSGEN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>When a client purchases T24, he initially receives a copy of the T24 demonstration account. This account is a fully populated account, containing sample customers, accounts, transactions, etc. and includes all the products available in T24. The client can use the demo account to familiarise himself with the system, begin training his staff and decide how he would like his system configured. Data can be amended as required and End of Days run in it. </p>
            <p>Once the client has decided on the configuration of his system, the Client Details form and the Client Implementation form at the back of this manual are completed and sent to the Distribution department at Temenos. Normally, the project manager from Temenos or one of Temenos' Business Partners would complete the form on the client's behalf.  It is very important that the client fully understands each of the questions asked on the form, as many of these settings cannot be changed after the tape has been generated. </p>
            <p>Distribution will create an implementation tape according to the parameters and requirements entered on the Client Details and Implementation forms. This is then used as the starting point for the client's implementation. </p>
            <p>Some clients who have purchased T24 for a number of different sites have adopted the practise of creating a "model bank".  This is normally created from the initial implementation tape.  The client then updates it with the customisation required for their bank.  For example, they will create SMS groups, versions, perhaps with additional validation in the form of user written subroutines, local reference fields, menus, enquiries including context sensitive enquiries and auto launch enquiries, additional helptext, etc.  Although all of this information can be transported by using the Data Library (see the Data Library chapter in the System Administration Guide), some clients prefer to be able to create their own implementation tapes from their "model bank". </p>
            <p>Therefore, T24 has made the system generation tool available to selected clients: it is not generally available.  However, the client must always advice the Distribution department at Temenos when new tapes are being created.  The detail and implementation forms must be sent to Temenos.  Upon checking this information, a license and maintenance code will be generated to enable the system generation program to be run. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TELEX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to add the telex delivery address record for the company to the delivery address file (DE.ADDRESS). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Up to 40 type A characters</p>
            <p>Should be in the format:   9999999 aaaaaaaaa  where 9999999 is the telex number       aaaaaaaaa is the answerback  e.g. 2356495 TEMENOS GB</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LICENSE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>License code assigned to the client for whom the sysgen is being run. You should send a copy of the client's details and implementation forms to Distribution, Temenos London, who will then assign a license code. </p>
            <p>This will be used to set the license code field on the SPF. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>12 type A characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is used for assigning the local country code on the company record and thus ensuring that the correct holiday tables are used for cycling dates.  Enter the SWIFT country code (e.g.  CH). </p>
            <p>If LOCAL.COUNTRY does not reference a record on the COUNTRY file, a record is created and written to IHLD by the PRE.SYSGEN. </p>
            <p>Holiday records for the next ten years will be written to the HOLIDAY table as IHLD by the PRE.SYSGEN if they do not already exist. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>2 type "SSS" (SWIFT) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHECKDIGIT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to identify the account checkdigit calculation method (account checkdigit type on COMPANY). </p>
            <p>1     When the local currency code is BEF (Belgium Francs, 12-digit       account numbers, modulus 97, 2 checkdigits) </p>
            <p>2     When the local currency code is LUF (Luxembourg Francs, 14-digit       account numbers, modulus 97, 2 checkdigits) </p>
            <p>3     For 10 digit account numbers with a modulus 11 check, 1 checkdigit </p>
            <p>5     For a standard checkdigit calculation (1 checkdigit, modulus 11)       with the account numbers zero filled to the account mask </p>
            <p>99    No checkdigit calculation with the account number zero filled to       the account mask </p>
            <p>blank Standard checkdigit (1 checkdigit, modulus 11), not zero filled,       or a user-written routine is to be used to calculate the       checkdigit </p>
            <p>This field is used to update the ACCT.CHECKDIG.TYPE on the COMPANY record. </p>
            <p>NOTE:   The checkdigit can be changed on the COMPANY record after the SYSGEN has been run, providing no customer accounts have been entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to set the order of languages for all translatable fields.  English must be the first language. </p>
            <p>If any of the languages do not already exist on the LANGUAGE file, they will be created by the PRE.SYSGEN as IHLD. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Up to 2 type A characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINTENANCE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date up to which maintenance has been paid.  If you are unsure of the date, contact Distribution, Temenos London. </p>
            <p>This will be used to set the maintenance date on the SPF. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Up to 8 type D (date) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.RUN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the SYSGEN was run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to add the SWIFT delivery address record for the company to the delivery address file (DE.ADDRESS).  The first four characters followed by characters 7-8  are also used to set the SWIFT common reference on the COMPANY record. If this field is left blank, the SWIFT common reference is set to XXXXXX. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>The format for a SWIFT address is as follows:             bbbbcclltrrr where:             bbbb is the bank code (must be alpha).            cc   is the country code.  The country code must                 exist on the country file.            ll   is the location code and must be in the range A-Z                 or 2-9.            t    is the terminal code.  Must be in the range A-Z                 or 2-9.            rrr  is the branch code and is optional.  If entered it                 must be alphanumeric.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the SYSGEN record is verified, all files in the database will be checked to see if they contain any records.  Only files which SYSGEN expects to be populated should contain data.  An override message will be issued for any file which contains unexpected data.  You should take great care if overriding the warning, as, although the SYSGEN may complete, the integrity of the database could be questionable. </p>
            <p>A list of all files which can be populated can be found in the User Guide. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINANCIAL.YEAR.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for setting the financial year end and last year end on the company record on COMPANY. This field is also used for setting the date on year end jobs on BATCH records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Up to 13 type FQU (frequency) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.FILES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for setting the local currency. Enter the SWIFT currency code (e.g. CHF). </p>
            <p>The LOCAL.CURRENCY field on the COMPANY record is set to the contents of this field.  Rank is set to 0 on this CURRENCY record. </p>
            <p>If the LOCAL.CURRENCY does not reference a record on CURRENCY.PARAM, a record will be written to IHLD by the PRE.SYSGEN.  Similarly, a record will be written to CURRENCY as IHLD if it does not already exist. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>3 type "SSS" (SWIFT) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINTENANCE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>After the client's details and implementation forms are sent to Distribution, Temenos London, a maintenance code will be issued.  This validates that the license details have been entered in SYSGEN correctly. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Up to 10 type "A" characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the list of products purchased.  This field is updated automatically from the list of products on the SPF file when the SYSGEN record is first being updated for a new implementation.  Products can be removed if not required.  However, if new products are required, they must be entered on the SPF initially, obtaining the necessary product code from Temenos. </p>
            <p>This will be used to set the products field on the SPF and the applications field on the COMPANY file.  Also PGM.AUTOM.ID on COMPANY will be set according to the products purchased. </p>
            <p>Any programs, files and data for products not installed will be removed by the SYSGEN. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Up to 2 type A characters</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid product on the SPF</p>
            <p>If MM or LD are present, LM must be present</p>
            <p>LM cannot be present if LD and MM are not.</p>
            <p>XT cannot be present if SC is not.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The company code will default to cc0010001, where cc is the local country code.  However, some clients may prefer to specify a paticular company code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Up to 11 type "COM" (company) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.USERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of users for which T24 has been licensed. </p>
            <p>This will be used to set the number of users on the SPF. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSGEN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>There is only one record on the SYSGEN file, the id of which is "SYSTEM" </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>SYSTEM</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>SYSGEN can only be run in "V"erify mode if the BANK.NAME on the SPF is "BASE BANK". This is to ensure that the SYSGEN is not run inadvertently on the incorrect database.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.MASK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to set the account mask on the COMPANY file (e.g.  ######-##-###); must include the checkdigit. The mask for internal accounts is hardcoded (###-#####-####). </p>
            <p>NOTE:   The checkdigit can be changed on the COMPANY record after the SYSGEN has been run, providing no customer accounts have been entered. </p>
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>1. No = 1234;      Mask = ##### - ##### Display =          1234 </p>
            <p>2. No = 1234567;   Mask = ##### - ##### Display =          12 - 34567 </p>
            <p>3. No = 1234;      Mask = R##### - ##### Display =          00000 - 01234 </p>
            <p>4. No = 1234567;   Mask = R##### - ##### Display =          00012 - 34567 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 to 20 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Input in this field must contain 4 '#' characters as a minimum. The number of '#' characters defines the maximum length of the account number.</p>
            <p>When ACCT.CHECKDIG.TYPE = 1, input in this field must contain 12 '#' characters.</p>
            <p>When ACCT.CHECKDIG.TYPE = 2, input in this field must contain 10 '#' characters.</p>
            <p>Characters '0...9', 'A...Z', 'a...z' are not allowed.  The only exception being that the 1st character can be 'R' which means that the account number will be right adjusted and that it may contain leading zeros.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name and address will be used to update: </p>
            <p>. the NAME.ADDRESS field on the COMPANY record . the name and address fields for the company record on the delivery address file (fields name 1, name 2, street address, town county, post code and country). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>1-35 type "S" (SWIFT) characters</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The DATES record will be updated with all dates based on the BANK.DATE entered.  All the dates on the batch records set accordingly.  Similary dates will be set on the following application parameter files: </p>
            <p> LMM.INSTALL.CONDS  REVALUATION.PARAMETER  LIMIT.PARAMETER </p>
            <p>The BANK.DATE should be set to a date close to the "go live" date, to avoid running numerous end of days to cycle the date forwards. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Up to 11 characters, date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will be used for:  The site name on the SPF  Trimmed to 22 characters for the company name on the COMPANY file  The branchname/title on the delivery address file (DE.ADDRESS) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>3-35 type "S" (SWIFT) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

