<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>SYSTEM.RECORD</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction codes that are important(required) for the installation of the given application in the ID. Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a value from the TRANSACTION application.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The RECORDS (with the given name), that need to be present in the file mentioned in FILE.NAME field. </p>
            <p>Field # 6 and 7 form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 25 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Files that need to exist for effective </p>
            <p />installation of the application in the ID. Field # 6 and 7 form a related multi-value set.  <p>There is a mainline program called INSTALL.SYS.RECS that generates a report using this application. This program checks if the given transaction codes, account.classes exist in the system and produces a report in HOLD.CONTROL - CHECKLIST.OF.COMPULSORY.RECS, which lists whether the transaction codes, account.classes have been created or not. A similar check is done for files defined in the field FILE.NAME. If they don't exist, then the record fatals out of T24. If the files exist, then the system checks if the necessary records have been created.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>A valid T24 Application      name.</p><p>A maximum of 25 characters      may be entered.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>SYSTEM.RECORD is an application that is used at installation to check if all necessary check has been completed for a product. </p>
            <p>The ID of this application is any meaningful application or submodule name (e.g. SCTR - SC.TRADING)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.CLASS.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The Account classes that are important(required) for the installation of the application in the ID. Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a value from the      ACCOUNT.CLASS application.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters      may be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.CLASS.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Classes that are important(required) for the installation of the application in the ID. Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a value from the     ACCOUNT.CLASS application.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may     be entered.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The categories that are important for the installation of the application in the ID.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid value from the CATEGORY application.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 6 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. This is a sub valued language field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

