<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>T24.MODEL.PACKAGES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>   New mechanism for installing local changes packed via Design studio called as packager. This will help in any kind of local changes deployment from one environment to another</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This is similar to the core updates procedure where the entire bins and libs are replaced and data records also will get released</p>
	    <p> This table is to store the details of data records in respective packager, these data records will be released during T24.MODEL.PACKAGE service</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains valid file names like F.EB.ERROR,F.FILE.CONTROL etc.</p>
            <p>FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME form a associated multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to store record id</p>
            <p>FILE.NAME and RECORD.NAME form a associated multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATED.UPDATES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specfies the dependent package of this package.</p>
            <p>Multi value field.</p>
            <p>Allowed upto 50 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAVED.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the current system time.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAVED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the current system date of when the package was released.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CD.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the change document number if any.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of change document pertaining to the change document number.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are BG,CI,EF,EN</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<field>DATA.RELEASED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the information whether the data record of this package has been released or not. Noinputtable  field </p>
            <p> Possible values are Y or N or C</p>
            <p>N = No, Data Records not yet Released only the libraries and Binaries are copied</p>
            <p>Y = Yes, Data Released Successfully but Not yet updated in SPF</p>
            <p>C = Completed, Updates Successfully completed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description about the package that is to be released.</p>
            <p>Langauge multi value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains released file name details for e.g like F.EB.ERROR,F.FILE.CONTROL etc</p>
            <p>SV.FILE.NAME and SV.RECORD.NAME form a associated multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RECORD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Released data items id of this package</p>
            <p>SV.FILE.NAME and SV.RECORD.NAME form a associated multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTORED.USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the operator whose is doing the package released.</p>
            <p>Format is TERMINAL.NO_OPERATOR.</p>
            <p>Fields RESTORED.USER to RESTD.TIME form a multi-value associated set.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTD.RELEASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the T24 release in which the package was released.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-9 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Internal field</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Fields RESTORED.USER to RESTD.TIME form a multi-value associated set.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTD.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the time in which the package was released.</p>
            <p>Fields RESTORED.USER to RESTD.TIME form a multi-value associated set.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the DATE in which the update was released.</p>
            <p>"D"ate field.</p>
            <p>Internal field.</p>
            <p>System Date.</p>
            <p>Fields RESTORED.USER to RESTD.TIME form a multi-value associated set.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPD.PARAM.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field is to store the parameter option used with T24PackageInstaller parent JBC routine when installing respective pacakges</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Valid values : </p>
            <p> DataOnly - package installer triggered with parameter option 'DataOnly' to deploy data records from package  </p>
            <p> LocalPack - package installer triggered with parameter option 'LocalPack' to deploy both object codes and data records from package , object code gets deployed into local object directory defined in DS.PARAMETER SYSTEM record if DS installed.</p>
            <P> Blank if package installer triggered without any parameter options to deploy both object code and data records from package, the object code gets deployed into t24lib & t24bin</P>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>T24.MDL.PAKG.NO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
