<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>TAKEOVER.MAPPING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The TAKEOVER.MAPPING program is designed to load data from a sequential (flat) file into the T24 format. Records are loaded as IHLD. The intention being that the EBS.AUTO.FUNCTION be used to INPUT and AUTHORISE the records. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The data to be mapped to T24 must reside in a type 1 Universe file (a directory). Eg. Directory TK.DATA may contain the item DC.DATA. Other items to be loaded may be loaded to the same or another directory. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The key used in TAKEOVER.MAPPING must be the T24 application name and may have a numeric number appended. Eg. DATA.CAPTURE.1 </p>
            <p />
            <p>TAKEOVER.MAPPING is not a conventional file conversion program. Data supplied in the flat file must be in the same general format as in terminal input. For example, numeric fields do not have leading zeroes. All fields if less than the field length have leading or trailing spaces. </p>
            <p>           ----------------------------------- </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MULTI.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field which contains the T24 multi-value number. </p>
            <p>Example: 23 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Integer number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCREMENTAL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This (optional) field specifies a key to be used as the basis for an automatically calculated key. In verification, before each record is written, this key if supplied will be incremented by 1 and used as the key for the new record. </p>
            <p>Example: SECTSC9229000100 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Alpha numeric.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUT.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the number of bytes reserved in the input record for the field. Any fields requiring less characters in the input record should contain either leading or trailing spaces. </p>
            <p>Example: 12 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Integer number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT.ERROR.REPORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether or not to print the error report. When data is loaded from two or more input files, it may be desirable to set this field to "N" initially to prevent the printing of a massive error report which would be of no use. </p>
            <p>Example: Y </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or N</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFSET.BASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>File layouts may be relative to zero or one, therefore the purpose of this field is to accommodate the file layout being used. </p>
            <p>Example: 1 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0 or 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAKEOVER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the T24 Application which is being mapped with an optional numeric suffix. </p>
            <p>Example:   DATA.CAPTURE.1 </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.SUBROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This (optional) field specifies the name of a subroutine to be called to perform the file update process in the verification process (ie. by TAKEOVER.MAPPING$RUN). This is necessary when the update is more complex than simply writing the unauthorised record. Eg. DATA.CAPTURE </p>
            <p>Example: TK.DATA.CAPTURE.1 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Alpha</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.FILES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether or not to update the T24 file. When data is initially loaded, a test on portion of the file may be preferred with this field set to "N", in order to view the error report. If "Y" then the record will be loaded as unauthorised. . </p>
            <p>Example: Y </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or N</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field which contains the T24 sub-value number. </p>
            <p>Example: 2 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Integer number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.DIRECTORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the type 1 file (Directory) which contains the sequential file (flat file) with the data to be converted to T24. </p>
            <p>Example: TAKEOVER.DATA </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUT.POSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the starting character in the input file for the field to be loaded. Depending on the entry in the field above named OFFSET.BASE, this field will be relative to either zero or one. </p>
            <p>Example: 1 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Integer number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the sequential (flat) file which resides in the specified directory and is to be loaded into T24. </p>
            <p>Example: DC.DATA </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.TO.PROCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of records from the sequential (flat) file which are to be processed. This can be useful as a preliminary test on data which has just been loaded. </p>
            <p>Example: 10 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Integer number or "ALL"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORDS.PRE.EXIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines whether or not the records being loaded should already exist in T24. The possible values being: Y  -  record must already exist. N  -  record must not already exists. M  -  record may or may not already exist. </p>
            <p>Example: N </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y, N, or M</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOW.NOINPUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whether or not data is permitted in NOINPUT fields. If "Y" then data in a NOINPUT field will not be treated as an error. . </p>
            <p>Example: Y </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or N</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the logical record size in physical bytes of the sequential (flat) file or is used to specify that the sequential file processed is record delimited by a field separator. </p>
            <p>If a value of SEQ is specified the file is processed in Databasic terms using a READSEQ command, data is extracted up to the next field separator.</p>
            <p>If a numeric value is specified the file is processed using sequential READBLK commands reading n bytes of data from the sequential file. Note that in UTF8 operation one character may be represented by multiple bytes of data and therefore this mode of operation cannot be used and files must be processed using the SEQ mode. </p>
            <p>Example: 100 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Integer number or a value of SEQ</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.SUBROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This (optional) field specifies the name of a subroutine to be called in verification (ie. by TAKEOVER.MAPPING$RUN) to load additional data. This is necessary when additional processing is to be performed on the data prior to loading it. ie. the data cannot simply be loaded, but must first be modified. </p>
            <p>Example: TK.TELEKURS.3 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>alpha</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the field number in the T24 file being loaded. Either the field number or field name may be used. </p>
            <p>Example: 0 OR @ID </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Alpha numeric.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

