<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>TEC.PROFILE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Specifies the list of TEC items to be monitored. Multiple TEC.ITEMS are combined into a TEC.PROFILE to determine which metrics to monitor. To activate a TEC.PROFILE, the record should be verified.  TEC.ACTIVE.ITEMS is the file where all the active profiles are stored.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>USERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the T24 users for which the active TEC items can be monitored.</p>
            <p>The active TEC items will be monitored only if the current signed on USER matches with any of the users specified in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi value field.</p>
            <p>Valid entry in USER file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFRESH.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the time for rebuilding TEC enquiry output.  TEC.DISPLAY details will be rebuilt every N seconds when the Enquiry is executed.  This is the control factor for TEC enquiries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The default value is 15 seconds</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SESSION.MAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field not in use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEC.PROFILE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference to identify the TEC.PROFILE</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Allows maximum of 35 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A description of the TEC profile</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLUSH.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of seconds after which the TEC events should be flushed from cache memory to TEC.OUTPUT file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Default value is 30 seconds.</p>
            <p>Note: TEC events will not be recorded when MAINT.TEC.OUTPUT field in SPF is set to 'N'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEMS</field>
<desc>
            <p>List of TEC items to be monitored</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multi value field.</p>
            <p>A valid entry in TEC.ITEMS file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOG.SETS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of Log sets to be created when flushing the records in TEC.OUTPUT file.  When the number exceeds, the first log set record will be overwritten with the new flushed details.</p>
            <p>This in turn provides self-cleaning mechanism for TEC.OUTPUT file storage space</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example:- Let FLUSH.TIME = 30 seconds and LOG.SETS = 5 </p>
            <p>When flushing TEC events for the 1st time (after 30 seconds), Log set number 1 will be used.  TEC.OUTPUT record will be created with the ID as (session number).(log set number).(TEC.ITEM) [as 6330.1.READ.SIZE, 6330.1.WRITE.SIZE etc].</p>
            <p>When flushing for the 2nd time, details will be available in the TEC.OUTPUT record 6330.2.READ.SIZE, 6330.2.WRITE.SIZE etc.</p>
            <p>When Log set number is reached and details are flushed for the next time, TEC.OUTPUT record 6330.1.READ.SIZE will be overwritten.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Default value is 10</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUEUE.MAX.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A threshold for storing TEC event messages in TEC.OUTGOING.MESSAGES file that can be consumed and dispatched to T24monitor by T24MONITOR.DISPATCHER service.</p>
            <p>The count of TEC event messages stored in TEC.OUTGOING.MESSAGES queue will be measured by each session for every 1000th message and will continue to push messages.</p>
            <p>When the threshold is reached or recognized in one session, TEC events will not be flushed further from that session.  However, the other sessions may continue to flush messages by the time it measures the count and recognizes the threshold.</p>
            <p>This size does not reflect the total number of messages in TEC.OUTGOING.MESSAGES but acts as a threshold for every session in flushing the messages.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Default value is 20000</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

