<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>TEC.DISPLAY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>TEC.DISPLAY is a table contains the list of TEC events which are triggered from various Applications. Entries are not created in TEC.DISPLAY as and when the events are triggered. All TEC events are updated in a flat file F.TEC.OUTPUT as and when the events are triggered. We need to run an Enquiry TEC.ITEM.DETAIL to populate this TEC.DISPLAY with list of TEC events triggered in T24. Purpose of this enquiry TEC.ITEM.DETAIL is to copy the records from TEC.OUTPUT to the application file TEC.DISPLAY.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TXN.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>if the TEC event is triggered during the transaction then the corresponding transaction reference would be logged here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVER.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the TEC activity got generated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Start time of the event trace.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVER.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Time on which the TEC activity got generated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVER.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Server name on which the TEC activity got generated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THRESH.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THRESHOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This filed holds the THRESHHOLD.TYPE of the event mentioned in the TEC.ITEMS. We can identify under which THRESHHOLD.TYPE(INFO,WARNING or CRITICAL) event is logged.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>METRIC.HIGH</field>
<desc>
            <p>THRESHOLD value of the TEC metric. E.g) Value updated here is 500 and If “READ.SIZE” got updated in ITEM.TYPE field then we could say my record size exceeds 500 when I try to read the record (DS.TOP.KEY) on the file (ITEM.DETAIL) during the transaction of the APPLICATION(ID is DS.TXN.REF).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of the file mentioned in ITEM.DETAIL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>If TEC event is triggered during the transaction then the corresponding application name of the transaction would be logged here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>To identify the OFS.SOURCE Channel used for the communication with T24.If there is no channel specified in OFS.SOURCE record then this field holds the value of OFS.SOURCE id.During the service if any event is triggred then this field holds the value "SERVICE"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>End time of the Event trace </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEM.DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the file name on which the event is triggered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>METRIC.AVG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEM.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key of the TEC.ITEMS record which is used to identify the TEC event initialization.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THRESH.COUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>METRIC.COUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of times this event got triggered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field also holds the ID of the TEC.ITEMS records to identify the THRESHOLD and THRESHOLD.TYPE defined in TEC.ITEMS records</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEC.DISPLAY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Numeric id which will be assiged in a sequence while launching the ENQUIRY TEC.ITEM.DETAIL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>METRIC.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the same event has triggered more than one time then it just add the metric value with previous one(updated in METRIC.HIGH) and also the old values of time and date would be replaced with latest values in respective fields like SERVER.DATE,SERVER.TIME,START.TIME and END.TIME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

