<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>TERMINAL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds the control codes and escape sequences for various terminal models. </p>
            <p>It allows the user to define:- </p>
            <p>     (1)   The terminal dependant escape sequences for the visual            attributes used by T24,            eg. Underline on/off, Reverse video on/off etc. </p>
            <p>     (2)   The values returned by the function keys F1,F2,F3 etc. </p>
            <p>     (3)   Special terminal initialisation sequences and commands to            be performed just before signing onto T24.            For example, set cursor type to solid block, display            terminal status line, disable/enable break key etc. </p>
            <p>Control characters are inserted in the format 'nnn', where nnn is the decimal ASCII value of the character, eg. 27 = 'escape' character. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRT.HOTKEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used in conjunction with Deal Slip printing where the user requires a custome advices associated with the application and function. They can be produced automatically based on the function, or manually by this hot key and the function.</p>
            <p>The input here defines the value returned by the print hot key </p>
            <p>This sequence is normally downloaded into a function key for convenience. You will need to refer to your Terminal User Guide or the Emulation software help on how to map the function keys. When this key is depressed, during contract input, the Deal Slip processing is invoked. You can use either a Control Character or a keyword but bear in mind the trigger may have an impact on data being entered at the time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the word DEALSLIP is entered as the trigger you would map a function key with;</p>
            <p>DEALSLIP&lt;cr&gt;</p>
            <p>where &lt;cr&gt; implies a carriage return.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>0-40 any characters.</p>
            <p>Control characters need to be entered in the form &lt;001&gt;         for CTRL A or &lt;018&gt; for CTRL R.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INIT.EXECUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the INFORMATION commands/routines to be executed just before signing onto T24. Eg. BREAK OFF - disable break key PTERM-KILL - define line kill character </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IDS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 40 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURSOR.CTRLS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the acsii values returned by the terminal's cursor control keys (left, right, up and down). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Details;   The values should be in the order: Field 28.1.1 - left Field 28.1.2 - right Field 28.1.3 - up Field 28.1.4 - down Note:These are currently only used by the IDS application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOECHO.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the "noecho on" (invisible) attribute on. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELETE.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to delete the current line. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCREEN.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the screen off (blank screen). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COL132.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to set the columns per line to 132. Details;   0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to print the current screen page.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCREEN.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the screen on (whole screen on). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSE.VIDEO.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the "reverse video" attribute off. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HALF.INTENSITY.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn "half intensity" mode on. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COL132.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to set the columns per line back to 80. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.PRINT.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Control sequence to redirect the output to a printer attached to the auxillary part of the terminal. This is normally used to connect Passbook printers for Savings Accounts or for Print Advices. The data is dependent on the physical Terminal or the Emulation software so you will need the handbook that came with the Terminal or reference to the Emulator help files.</p>
            <p />
            <p>At the time of writing this helptext the codes for Reflection Version 7 for Windows were:</p>
            <p>Printer On </p>
            <p>&lt;27&gt;[5i </p>
            <p>Printer Off </p>
            <p>&lt;27&gt;[4i</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>0-40 any characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.SCREEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to clear the whole screen. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.PRINT.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Control sequence to redirect the output back to the screen rather than to a printer attached to the auxillary part of the terminal. This is normally used to connect Passbook printers for Savings Accounts or for Print Advices. The data is dependent on the physical Terminal or the Emulation software so you will need the handbook that came with the Terminal or reference to the Emulator help files.</p>
            <p />
            <p>At the time of writing this helptext the codes for Reflection Version 7 for Windows were:</p>
            <p>Printer On </p>
            <p>&lt;27&gt;[5i </p>
            <p>Printer Off </p>
            <p>&lt;27&gt;[4i</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>0-40 any characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TERMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal model/name. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 type A (alphanumeric) characters (Mandatory input) Details;   The name entered here will be used to identify the terminal to the T24 system via application TERMINAL.USER.  The name should be made as meaningful as possible and should relate to the specific terminal model.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IDS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 40 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURSOR.BACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>For T24 use only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-2 numeric digits. Details;   This field is used to correctly position the cursor for certain terminal models (eg. for TV950 should be set to 1).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIG.HOTKEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the control sequence returned by the signature key </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 any characters. Details;   Valid only for terminals capable of supporting TEK 4041 graphics to display customer signatures. This sequence is normally downloaded into function key 9 and tested during contract input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the "PRIME" terminal type. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric digits. (Mandatory input) Details;   The number entered here should be one of those listed by the "SET.TERM.TYPE" command of PRIME INFORMATION which relates to the specific terminal model being defined. For example, a TELEVIDEO 955 terminal is identified by the PRIME INFORMATION terminal type 2 (TV925).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INIT.SEQUENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the initial terminal command sequences to be executed just before signing onto T24.  These sequences can be used to set the cursor mode, screen blank period etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNC.KEY.VALUES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the ascii values returned by the function keys F1,F2,F3 etc. </p>
            <p>Note:      For terminals whose function keys have been pre-set by            the manufacturer and do not allow for them to be            re-programmed, the ascii values returned by each F1,F2            etc should be entered here (FUNC KEY VALUES) and            field 18.1 (FUNCTION KEYS) left blank. </p>
            <p>           It is important that the function keys only return single            values. Keys which return more than one value will cause            problems in certain T24 functions. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Details;   The acsii values returned by the function keys F1,F2,F3 etc should be specified here. If this field is left blank then the system assumes that the default values defined by the escape sequence in field 18.1 (FUNCTION KEYS) are going to be: FUNCTION KEY            ASCII VALUE F1                      21 F2                       2 F3                       6 F4                       5 F5                      22 F6                      23 F7                      20</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNDERLINE.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the "underline" attribute off. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNDERLINE.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the "underline" attribute on. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION.KEYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequences to program the function keys (F1,F2 etc) to return specified values. </p>
            <p>Note:      It is important that the function keys only return single            values. Keys which return more than one value will cause            problems in certain T24 functions.            If the terminal function keys cannot be programmed, i.e.            function key values are pre-defined by the manufacturer,            then this field (function keys) should be left blank and            the pre-defined values returned by each function key            specified in field 25.1 (FUNC KEY VALUES). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Details;   The terminal command sequence to set up the function keys F1,F2 etc should be specified here.  The value that each function key has been programmed to return should also be specified in field 25.1 (FUNC KEY VALUES).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSE.VIDEO.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the "reverse video" attribute on. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HALF.INTENSITY.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn "half intensity" mode off (full intensity). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the general terminal command sequence to reset the attributes back to normal, i.e. underline off, reverse video off etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOECHO.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the "noecho" (invisible) attribute off. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT.ECHO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of characters the terminal sends to the computer after each page print to signal the end of the transmission.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BELL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to sound the terminal's bell. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLINK.OFF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the "blink" attribute off. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLINK.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to turn the "blink" attribute on. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.EOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the terminal command sequence to erase from the cursor position to the end of the line. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-40 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

