<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>TSA.SERVICE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The TSA.SERVICE records contain the details of the routines to be run either in the close of business or online mode.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STOP.COUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of crashes allowed for a service in a time period as specified in the field STOPPAGE.TIME. When not specified, the value is taken from TSA.PARAMETER</p>
            <p />
            <p>1.Non-mandatory field, accepts numeric value </p>
            <p>2.Value can be given in this field only when STOPPAGE.TIME is specified.</p>
            <p />
            <p>e.g. STOPPAGE.TIME = 80</p>
            <p> STOP.COUNT = 2</p>
            <p />
            <p>Here the Service can have 2 crashes in a time period of 80 seconds. At the third crash within 80 seconds, Service will be stopped.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVER.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not used currently and is reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of transaction processed by the service.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields from DATE to TRANSACTION form a related multivalue set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ELAPSED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the elapsed time of the service in seconds.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Fields from DATE to TRANSACTION form a related multivalue set.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STARTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the time on which the service was started.</p>
            <p>Holds the machine date and time in the format DD/MM/YYYY HH:MM:SS</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Fields from DATE to TRANSACTION form a related multivalue set.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the reference to the USER application. The appropriate Service will be run on the system  by loading the profile of the specified USER. The updates made during the Service will be made with reference to the USER specified here.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be a valid USER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WORK.PROFILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains reference to the record in TSA.WORKLOAD.PROFILE  Every Service can be attached to multiple workload profiles where the number of agents to use will be defined. The profile specified here will be used to run the service on the server name specified in the associated multi value set. If this field is left blank then the TSA.WORKLOAD.PROFILE record with DEFAULT as the ID will be picked up. If this record is not available, then the value in the field BATCH.SESSIONS from SPF will be assumed as number of agents</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be a valid entry in TSA.WORKLOAD.PROFILE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVIEW.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is not used currently and is reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the control the user wishes to exercise upon the current service. Currently it can hold the following values.</p>
            <p />
            <p>START - The Service is ready to start and can be kicked off.</p>
            <p />
            <p>STOP   -  The Service has to be stopped. The service if it had been running will be terminated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>AUTO  -  If   AUTO is specified, then the service is ready for kicking off and does not require manual input of START . The service will be available for starting and can be stopped at the end of the process.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 Characters.</p>
            <p>Valid values are START, STOP and AUTO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the unique reference to the TSA.SERVICE application. Currently the following two IDs  have to be used.</p>
            <p />
            <p>TSM - This refers to the  Service Manager which controls the various services and the agents running on the system.</p>
            <p>COB - This refers to the  Close of Business (Batch Processing)</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 character Alpha Numeric.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field associated with ATTRIBUTE.VALUE.</p>
            <p>This field along with ATTRIBUTE.VALUE acts as a place holder for storing any parameters which are unique to that TSA.SERVICE. </p>
            <p>The field ATTRIBUTE.TYPE stores the parameter name and the field ATTRIBUTE.VALUE stores the corresponding parameter's value.</p>
            <p>  Services could be written to read the parameter type &amp; its value from these fields and process accordingly.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example: Service OFS.MESSAGE.SERVICE.</p>
            <p>  The field ATTRIBUTE.TYPE contains the value as purge and ATTRIBUTE.VALUE contains the purge duration.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 30 characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTE.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalue field associated with ATTRIBUTE.TYPE.</p>
            <p>This field along with ATTRIBUTE.TYPE acts as a place holder for storing any parameters which are unique to that TSA.SERVICE. </p>
            <p>The field ATTRIBUTE.TYPE stores the parameter name and the field ATTRIBUTE.VALUE stores the corresponding parameter's value.</p>
            <p>Services could be written to read the parameter type &amp; its value from these fields and process accordingly.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example: Service OFS.MESSAGE.SERVICE.</p>
            <p>The field ATTRIBUTE.TYPE contains the value as purge and ATTRIBUTE.VALUE contains the purge duration.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 30 characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on which the service was started.Date will be the bank's date not the machine date.</p>
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Fields from DATE to TRANSACTION form a related multivalue set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the description of the Service. A brief description of the service can be stored here.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 Characters (Alpha Numeric)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOPPED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the time on which the service was stopped.</p>
            <p>Holds the machine date and time in the format DD/MM/YYYY HH:MM:SS</p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p>Fields from DATE to TRANSACTION form a related multivalue set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts a value in the format     </p>
            <p />
            <p>Date Time  Frequency </p>
            <p>The date can be entered in the T24 date format(system date). The time in the format HH:MM(24 hour format). The frequency can be entered in the format 1D,2D,etc</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example</p>
            <p>20151231 15:00 1D</p>
            <p />
            <p>TSM would build the service profile only for the services which are START or AUTO. But when the frequency is specified in the service and SERVICE.CONTROL  set as ‘STOP’ , the TSM would check whether the specified frequency has been reached taking into account the time as well and would start the service. When the service is stopped, the frequency would  be cycled to the next  date. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The frequency field is not allowed for an AUTO service. </p>
            <p>The service control cannot be changed if the frequency is present.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVER.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the hostname of the Server on which the service will run. A Service can run in multiple servers and the server names should be provided in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 Characters - Alpha Numeric</p>
            <p>Should be a Valid host name.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.OUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time out in seconds after which an agent should be declared as DEAD should be specified here. This field will accept only numeric values. The value in this field should be greater than 60 and cannot be less than the value in REVIEW.TIME in TSA.PARAMETER. The value specified is in terms of seconds.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOPPAGE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Time interval specified for a service to be monitored for the number of crashes allowed as specified in the field STOP.COUNT. When not specified, the value is taken from TSA.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1. Non-mandatory field, accepts numeric value </p>
            <p>2. STOPPAGE.TIME should be greater than the time specified in TIME.OUT</p>
            <p>3. The Value given should be greater than the time specified in DEATH.WATCH time in TSA.PARAMETER when no TIME.OUT is specified.</p>
            <p>4. When no TIME.OUT and DEATH.WATCH time in TSA.PARAMETER is given, then STOPPAGE.TIME should be greater than default death watch time 300s.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

