<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>TSA.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STOP.COUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of crashed that is allowed for a service in a time period as specified in the field STOPPAGE.TIME. </p>
            <p />
            <p>1.Non-mandatory field, accepts numeric value </p>
            <p />
            <p>2.If this field is allowed to input only when STOPPAGE.TIME field is specified.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>e.g. STOPPAGE.TIME = 80</p>
            <p />
            <p>STOP.COUNT = 2</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Here the Service can have 2 crashes in a time period of 80 seconds. At the third crash within 80 seconds, Service will be stopped.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOPPAGE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Time interval specified for a service to be monitored for the number of crashes as specified in the field STOP.COUNT. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1. Non-mandatory field, accepts numeric value </p>
            <p />
            <p>2. STOPPAGE.TIME should be greater than the time specified in TIME.OUT</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If DEATH.WATCH time is left blank then STOPPAGE.TIME should be greater than the default time 300.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEATH.WATCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the seconds for the death watch. The system if it does not find a contact with a particular agent for a time greater than the death watch will mark the particular agent as DEAD. The Service Manager will review the response from every agent and will act upon agents that don't respond for a given period of time.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 3 digits numeric value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.AGENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the highest agent that is running as a part of TSA.SERVICE. The system while starting every agent for different service updates the highest number of agent in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains unique reference to the TSA.PARAMETER record. This field should contain one single record called SYSTEM.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVIEW.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the review time by the Service Manager of all the agents that are running currently. The system does a periodical review of all the agents running in the system. The delay time during every  review can be specified in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric Value - (3 digits)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>SELECT.DEATH.WATCH</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
