<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>UNAU.INSTL.PROGRAMS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file holds the name of those installation level applications, where the records on the unauthorised file are to be reported on the exception log and there is an additional option to change the status to hold. </p>
            <p>The applications that can be held on this file are those applications where the file level is 'INT'  i.e. at installation level. </p>
            <p>The End of Day Batch Process.  EB.UNAU.INSTL scans the unauthorised files for the applications entered on the file UNAU.INSTL.PROGRAMS.  If the status is to remain as unauthorised then an exception log record with code 130 - Record Left as unauthorised - is output.  If the status is to be changed to Hold then an exception log record with code 120 - Record put on Hold - is output and the status field in the unauthorised record is updated. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates to which main application (sub system) the program belongs. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 characters type A. Data transferred from the FILE.CONTROL file record. No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether record status is to be changed or left as is. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 characters type A.  The following values only allowed: .  UNAU - Leave in current status. .  HOLD - Change status to Hold. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROGRAM.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the application for which details are being entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 type A (alphanumeric characters) and the program type must be 'H' or 'U'. Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>The program name must be the key of a record on the PGM.FILE file.</p>
            <p>The program name must be the key of a record on the FILE.CONTROL file.</p>
            <p>The file classification must be INT (Installation).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

