<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>USER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used by the Security Management System to control who has access to T24., when and to what information and facilities.</p>
            <p>  For every person who is allowed to use T24., a User record must be created.  This contains identification details and specifies precisely what information and facilities are available, the dates and times at which the System may be accessed and other information required for Security Management.  The information held is detailed below:</p>
            <p>  1.        Identification</p>
            <p>  Identifying details for each User include a unique Sign           On Name, Secret Password, Name, Classification           ('External' customer or 'Internal' employee of the           bank), Company or branch and Department.</p>
            <p>  In addition, User preferences such as the Language in           which messages etc. should be displayed, can be           specified.</p>
            <p>  2.        Permitted Times of Use</p>
            <p>  Details specifying when each User can access the           System include Start Date, End Date, Start Time, End           Time, the maximum time during which the User may be           inactive without being Signed Off automatically, the           number of unsuccessful attempts to Sign On allowed           before the Password is disabled, the frequency with           which the Password must be changed and dates           between which the Password should be deactivated.</p>
            <p>  3.        Permitted Activity</p>
            <p>  For 'External' Users, the customer(s) whose records           may be accessed must be specified and account           numbers may be specified.           For all Users the information and facilities which may           be accessed are specified at 4 levels: COMPANY           APPLICATION (and VERSION), FUNCTION, FIELD so           that it is possible to specify precisely which records,           belonging to which company, may be accessed and what           may be done with them.</p>
            <p>  Up to 999 combinations of Company, Application,           Function and Field are allowed.</p>
            <p>  4.        Activity Logging</p>
            <p>  Security Violations are always recorded in the           PROTOCOL file, in addition it is possible to specify in           the User record that some or all permitted activities by           selected Users should be recorded.</p>
            <p>  5.        Local Elements</p>
            <p>  Additional data elements can be defined to suit local           requirements.  This is done by using LOCAL.TABLE           and LOCAL.REF.TABLE as explained in the Utilities           Help Text.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEPARTMENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the bank department in which the User works.</p>
            <p>  This is used as a default in DATA.CAPTURE batch numbers and may be used for reporting purposes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-4 numeric characters. (Mandatory input) It must be the ID of an existing Department/Account Officer (DEPT.ACCT. OFFICER) record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.RESTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Company to which the User must be Signed On in order to use the Applications, Versions and Functions specified in the related Fields 18 to 24.</p>
            <p>  This field is used, together with the associated Fields 18-24, to specify for each Company to whose records this User has access, precisely which records in which Applications can be accessed using which Versions and Functions.</p>
            <p>  The group of Fields, 17-24 can be repeated up to 999 times.  Refer to APPLICATION (Field 18) for examples.</p>
            <p>  Any files for which standard or special file mnemonics have been specified in the Company record can only be accessed by Users who have Signed On to that Company (or have used the PASSWORD Application to access that Company).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Permits "ALL" to allow the functions for all companies listed in the COMPANY.CODE field. In a Multi Book company set up, if this field is defined as "ALL" then it allow the functions for Lead company and all book companies under that Lead company.</p>
            <p>  9 alphanumeric characters 'CCGGGLLLL' where: CC   is 2 alpha characters Country code GGG  is 3 numeric characters Company Group LLLL is 4 numeric local code. or    2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or '.') Company Mnemonic characters. Multi-value field associated with Fields 18-24. Mandatory input.  No Default Value. It must be a Company Code from the COMPANY.CODE field of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the end period or the log out time till which the user is allowed access to the system on a specific day defined in the ALLOWED.DAYS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Input can be 0-2359 or 0000-2359 or 00:00-23:59</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Note: (1) This field is always displayed formatted with ':' (2) For whole day/night login, start should be 00:00, end should be 24:00 (ie. 24 hours). (3) There may be two or more separate periods each day when the User is allowed to access the System, e.g. morning and afternoon, but not during lunchtime. (4) If only 1 or 2 digits are entered, they correspond to minutes between midnight and 1 o'clock in the morning.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1-4       numeric characters with optional ':' i.e. HHMM or HH:MM Sub-value field       associated with ALLOWED.DAYS and DAY.ST.TIME (Optional input)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINTER.FOR.RPTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Printer to be used when reports are spooled.  Must be a valid entry on the PRINTER.ID file.  If blank the system printer is used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  30 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of any BASIC subroutine or a java class is entered here. This field speficies the routines that needs to be triggered when the user successfully logs in.This is a multi value field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The routines entered should have a record on the EB.API application</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOGIN.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the login status of the User.</p>
            <p>When user login into T24 the field will be defaulted to “ACTIVE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> : </p>
            <p>Alphanumeric field, NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.LAST.SIGN.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the date this User last Signed On successfully.  It is displayed on the SIGN.ON Screen.</p>
            <p>  This date is the actual date (system date) on which the User Signed On.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Displayed in the format DD MMM YYYY e.g 18 JAN 1985 (Internal field.  No Manual input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.ST.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the start of period or the log in time at which the user is allowed access to the system on a specific day defined in ALLOWED.DAYS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Input can be 0-2359 or 0000-2359 or 00:00-23:59</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Note: (1) This field is always displayed formatted with ':' (2) There may be two or more separate periods each day when the User is allowed to access the System, e.g. morning and afternoon, but not during lunch time. (3) If only 1 or 2 digits are entered, they correspond to minutes between midnight and 1 o'clock in the morning.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1-4       numeric characters with optional ':' i.e. HHMM or HH:MM Sub-value field       associated with ALLOWED.DAYS and DAY.END.TIME (Optional input)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.RIGHTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows a user to access and update DISPO items with the rights of other dispo officers. This facilitates a higher-ranking officer to take over the duty of a lower level one as and when</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  required.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Multi-value field (Optional      input)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid dispo officer      as defined in the DISPO.OFFICER file.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The DISPO.RIGHTS must not be      the same as the DISPO.OFFICER.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Duplicates not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  DISPO.RIGHTS cannot be      entered when DISPO.OFFICER is empty.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE.PROFILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the earliest date on which the User represented by this record may have access to the System.</p>
            <p>  Input may be all numeric DDMMYY or MMDDYY depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH format in Field 29 of the User record, or alphanumeric, DDMMMYYYY where the day and year are numeric and the month is the first 3 letters of the month, in capitals.</p>
            <p>  If you omit the year and/or the month, the System assumes they are the same as today.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. (Mandatory input) It must not be less than today's date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.OFF.LOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not a record should be written to the PROTOCOL file recording every time this User SIGNS.ON or SIGNS.OFF.</p>
            <p>  Note:     Unsuccessful attempts to SIGN.ON are always logged,           regardless of the value in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Y (Yes) or    N or NO (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies which override class the user is allowed to approve.</p>
            <p>  Format; 4 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>  Multi-value field. (Optional input; default value = none.)</p>
            <p>  T24. override messages can be classified by means of the OVERRIDE.CLASS table. The</p>
            <p>  OVERRIDE.CLASS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the start of period each day at which the User is allowed access to the System.</p>
            <p>  Input can be 0-2359                  or 0000-2359                  or 00:00-23:59</p>
            <p>  Note: (1)   This field is always displayed formatted with ':'</p>
            <p>  (2)   There may be two or more separate periods                 each day when the User is allowed to access                 the System, e.g. morning and afternoon, but                 not during lunch time.</p>
            <p>  Note:     If only 1 or 2 digits are entered, they correspond to           minutes between midnight and 1 o'clock in the morning.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-4 numeric characters with optional ':' i.e.  HHMM or HH:MM Multi-value field associated with END TIME (Field 11) (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEACTIVATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that defines the start of the deactivation period. This can only be entered or changed by the User via the PASSWORD Application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard Date format</p>
            <p>  Input only via PASSWORD Application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the name entered by the User to SIGN.ON to the System.  It is used by the System as an alternative key to access User details.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  6-16 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>  It must be different from the USER ID (Field 0) of this record.</p>
            <p>  It must be different from the SIGN ON NAME (Field 2) of any other User record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the reference ID of an entry in the LDAP.PARAMETER which point on external identity store</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies for all External Users the Customer(s) whose records they may access.</p>
            <p>  If CLASSIFICATION (Field 3) is EXT there must be at least one entry in this field.</p>
            <p>  The External User cannot access financial information for any Customers except those specified in this field. Input must be the Customer Code or Mnemonic of an existing Customer record. If Mnemonic is entered, the System will convert it to the corresponding Customer Code.</p>
            <p>  You should also set up the table USER.EXTERNAL.FIELD to indicate which fields in the applications specified constitute a CUSTOMER and/or an ACCOUNT field.</p>
            <p>  Note: For external customers, there is no need to duplicate this restriction for each Application in field 17 to 24.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Either: 1-10 numeric characters Customer Code or 3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') Customer Mnemonic characters. Multi-value field (Mandatory input for External Users; otherwise not allowed. No default value)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.DEPT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Field is marked as NOINPUT Field.No longer used. Made Obsolete.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINTER.FOR.P.FUNC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Printer to be used when the 'P' function is used.  Must be a valid entry on the PRINTER.ID file.  If blank then the system printer is used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  30 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional. The DISPO.OFFICER  Id to be assigned to this user if  they are to have authorisation to approve dispo items.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid dispo officer as defined in the DISPO.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field to determine the attributes that are associated with a particular user.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid settings in this field are;</p>
            <p />
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>COMMAND.LINE</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>The user is allowed the use of the command line in T24 Desktop.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>EXPLORER</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Allows the user to use the Application explorers</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>ENQUIRY.INDEX</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Allows access to the enquiry index</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>REALTIMEENQUIRY</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Allows the use of real time enquiries for this user. When signing onto T24, Desktop will create another session for use by the real time enquiries. This does use an additional database license, but not an additional T24 license.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>LOCK.PREFERENCES</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>If the user is given this option then the 'User Preferences' option under the 'Tools' menu on the Desktop toolbar will be disabled.<p />This will prevent the user from gaining access to various Desktop settings including file locations and some system administrative functions.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>SUPER.USER</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>The user has access to all of the features detailed above, and for all future functionality with the exception of REALTIMEENQUIRY.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>LOCK.DEACTIVATION</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>To Disable "Deactivation profile" menu item on desktop menu Bar.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>LOCK.DESIGNERS</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>To disable all Designer's menu items on Desktop menu bar.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>LOCK.MISC.ITEMS</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>If the user is given this option then this will prevent the user from gaining access to user toolbar, list of enquiries and list of reports in desktop.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>COMMIT.DETAILS</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>This attribute is set as a diagnostic and displays the filenames updated when a transaction is updated.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LEAD.PREF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field has been made obsolte and is not in use anymore.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTEMPTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of unsuccessful Attempts to SIGN.ON allowed using the SIGN ON NAME (Field 2) of this record, before the Password is Disabled.</p>
            <p>  The System stores the number of unsuccessful Attempts to SIGN.ON since the last successful SIGN.ON.  Once the number of unsuccessful Attempts is greater than or equal to the number specified in this field, the Password is DISABLED and all further Attempts result in a SECURITY VIOLATION. User records DISABLED in this way are shown in the PASSWORD.EXCEPTION list.</p>
            <p>     (i)  The PASSWORD.RESET Application can be used to allow a user who has forgotten his Password to enter a new one.</p>
            <p>  (ii) Attempts to SIGN.ON may be unsuccessful for the following reasons:</p>
            <p>  1.    Incorrect Password</p>
            <p>  2.    Today's date less than START DATE PROFILE (Field 8)</p>
            <p>  3.    Today's date later than END DATE PROFILE (Field 9)</p>
            <p>  4.    Time is earlier than START TIME (Field 10)</p>
            <p>  5.    Time is later than END TIME (Field 11)</p>
            <p>  6.    The Password has been Deactivated (for further details see PASSWORD Application)</p>
            <p>  7.    The Password has been Disabled after too many unsuccessful attempts.</p>
            <p>  8.    The User record is not in Live status i.e new input or change has not yet been Authorised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1 numeric character. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTEMPTS.SINCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the number of unsuccessful attempts to SIGN.ON since the last successful SIGN.ON.  It is displayed on the SIGN.ON screen.  If the number in this field is not less than the number permitted by ATTEMPTS (Field 13), the Password is Disabled and cannot be used until it is reset using the PASSWORD.RESET Application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Numeric. (Internal field.  No manual input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the dealer desk code applicable to the user being entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  2 alphanumeric characters in the range A-Z, a-z, plus 0-9 Optional Input</p>
            <p>  Must be an existing code on the DEALER.DESK table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION.LOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not records should be written to the PROTOCOL file recording every Application accessed by this User.</p>
            <p>  If Y is entered, a record is written to the PROTOCOL file every time this User accesses a different Application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Y (Yes) or    N or NO (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>  Security Violations are always logged, regardless of this field.</p>
            <p>  It must be NO if SECURITY MGMT LOG (Field 26) is NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies, for External Users, the Accounts which they may access. Not used at the present time.</p>
            <p>  If there is an entry in this field, the External User cannot access financial information for any accounts except those specified in this field.</p>
            <p>  You should also setup the table USER.EXTERNAL.FILED to indicate which fields in the applications you specify constitute a CUSTOMER and/or an ACCOUNT field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Either: 2-14 numeric Account Number characters or 3-10         type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') Account         Mnemonic characters. Multi-value field Only allowed for         External Users</p>
            <p>  It cannot be entered unless CUSTOMER (Field 15) also         entered.</p>
            <p>  Up to 999 accounts may be entered in each group of fields         corresponding to an entry in Field 15.</p>
            <p>  Each input must be an Account Number or Mnemonic of an         existing Account record.</p>
            <p>  Each Account entered must have a Customer code (Field 1)         equal to the Customer code in the corresponding Field 15         of this record.</p>
            <p>  No duplicates are allowed.</p>
            <p>  If Mnemonic is entered, the System will convert it to the         corresponding Account Number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOWED.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the day for which the period for users access to the system is taken from the associated fields DAY.ST.TIME and DAY.END.TIME. The values allowed are 1 to 7 meaning 1  MONDAY, 2  TUESDAY and 7  SUNDAY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The period set in the fields START.TIME and END.TIME (fields 10 &amp; 11) is applicable for all days of the week.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The access time for a particular day will be taken from the fields DAY.ST.TIME and DAY.END.TIME if defined, otherwise the common START.TIME and END.TIME will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1-       Numeric character. Multi-value field associated with DAY.ST.TIME and       DAY.END.TIME (Optional input)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the separators to be used when formatting amounts for Enquiries, Repgens &amp; screen input/display.</p>
            <p>  This field specifies the separators to be used when formatting amounts.</p>
            <p>  The millions &amp; thousands separator can be a comma, full stop or apostrophe.</p>
            <p>  The decimal separator can only be either a comma or full stop.</p>
            <p>  The format is entered as a 2 character pair. For example ,.</p>
            <p>  The first value is the separator used for millions and thousands. The second value is the one used as a decimal separator.</p>
            <p>  Examples</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td width="16%">Setting</td>
                    <td width="84%">Enter and displayed as</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td width="16%">,.</td>
                    <td width="84%">1,234,567.89</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td width="16%">.,</td>
                    <td width="84%">1.234.567,89</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td width="16%">',</td>
                    <td width="84%">1'234'567,89</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td width="16%">'.</td>
                    <td width="84%">1'234'567.89</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional field  - system will use ,. if field left blank</p>
            <p>  Any valid combination of 2 can be used.</p>
            <p>  Decimal separator must be either comma or full stop.</p>
            <p>  Thousands separator must be either a comma, full stop or apostrophe.</p>
            <p>  The same character cannot be used twice.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies which Application may be used to access records belonging to the Company specified in the related COMPANY RESTR (Field 17).</p>
            <p>  This field is used, together with the associated Fields 17 and 19-24 to specify precisely which records in which Applications can be accessed by the User using which Versions and Functions. It must be the name of an existing Application, the name of an existing USER.SMS.GROUP preceded by the '@' sign (in which case further input in fields 19.1 to 24.1 will not be allowed), ALL.PG to allow access to all Applications or ALL.PG (program type) to allow access to all Applications of a certain type (see below).</p>
            <p>  The following program types may be used in conjunction with ALL.PG (e.g. ALL.PG.H) to give access to a particular type of program:-</p>
            <p>  Program Type Meaning</p>
            <p>  H Programs for which the standard 3 files exist - Live, Unauthorised and History, e.g. CUSTOMER.</p>
            <p>  U Programs for which Live and Unauthorised files exist, but no History, e.g. VERSION.</p>
            <p>  L Programs for which only a Live file exists (updated automatically by the system) e.g. STMT.ENTRY (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program).</p>
            <p>  M Programs which are designed to do something other than processing the standard T24 functions using a specific file e.g. PASSWORD.ENABLE, End Of Day Batch programs.</p>
            <p>  T Programs which handle automatically updated CONCAT files, e.g. CUSTOMER.ACCOUNT (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program). Note: The following 3 type M programs are available to all users and cannot be restricted:- SIGN.ON SIGN.OFF PASSWORD</p>
            <p>  Example 1:</p>
            <p>  To give a User access to the records of only one Company (GB-001-0000) but allow access to all records for this Company using all Functions (except auditor review) and all Versions of all Applications, enter the following:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Field 5.1 (COMPANY) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p>  Field 17.1(COMPANY CODE)</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG</p>
            <p>  Field 19.1(VERSION)</p>
            <p>  Field 20.1(FUNCTION) ALL</p>
            <p>  Note: Fields 21-24 are used to specify particular records or types of records which may be accessed within an Application. See FIELD NO (Field 21) for examples.</p>
            <p>  Example 2:</p>
            <p>  To give a User full access (except auditor review) to the records of Company GB-001-0000 and to give limited access to the records of Company GB-001-0001, only allowing the List and Display functions for Customer Application.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Field 5.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p>  Field 5.2(COMPANY) GB-001-0001</p>
            <p>  Field 17.1(COMPANY.CODE) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG</p>
            <p>  Field 19.1(VERSION)</p>
            <p>  Field 20.1(FUNCTION) ALL</p>
            <p>  Field 17.2(COMPANY.CODE) GB-001-0001</p>
            <p>  Field 18.2(APPLICATION) CUSTOMER</p>
            <p>  Field 19.2(VERSION)</p>
            <p>  Field 20.2(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example 3:</p>
            <p>  To give a User access to the records of only one Company (GB-001-0000), allowing him to List Display, Input and Copy Customer records and to List and Display records for all other Applications:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Field 5.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG</p>
            <p>  Field 20.1(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p>  Field 18.2(APPLICATION) CUSTOMER</p>
            <p>  Field 20.2(FUNCTION) L S I C</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example 4:</p>
            <p>  To prevent a USER from using any type M Applications, but allow him to List and Display records in any other Applications:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Field 5.1(COMPANY) GB-001-0000</p>
            <p>  Field 17.1(COMPANY CODE)</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.H</p>
            <p>  Field 20.1(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p>  Field 18.2(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.U</p>
            <p>  Field 20.2(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p>  Field 18.3(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.L</p>
            <p>  Field 20.3(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p>  Field 18.4(APPLICATION) ALL.PG.T</p>
            <p>  Field 20.4(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1. 1-30 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters, Application name.</p>
            <p>  or 2. ALL.PG to allow all Applications.</p>
            <p>  or 3. ALL.PG (program type) see details. or</p>
            <p>  4. '@' sign followed by a valid USER.SMS.GROUP</p>
            <p>  Multi-value field associated with Fields 17 and 19-24. (Mandatory input in each set of Fields 17-24.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the channel through which the user logs in. This field is updated during sign and then cleared while signing off</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Alphanumeric Field</p>
            <p> No-input Field</p>
            <p> For a user logging through a OFS.SOURCE enabled Interface, the CHANNEL is updated in this field. When there is no channel specified in the OFS.SOURCE, the OFS.SOURCE ID is updated in this field.</p>
            <p> For a user logging though service, this field will be updated with the name of the service</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASSIFICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the User is 'Internal', i.e. an employee of the bank using T24., or 'External', i.e. a customer.</p>
            <p>  If the user is defined as EXT (external) then you should enter the valid customer and account numbers ino the fields CUSTOMER and ACCOUNT. You should also setup the table USER.EXTERNAL.FILED to indicate which fields in the applications you specify constitute a CUSTOMER and/or an ACCOUNT field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-3 uppercase alpha characters: I, IN or INT for an employee of the bank E, EX or EXT for a customer. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.SCREEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not the Screen is to be cleared whenever this User finishes processing a record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Y (Yes) or    N or NO (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the company or companies whose records this User can access.</p>
            <p>  Whenever the User Signs On he will be able to access the records of the Company specified in this field.  If more than one Company is specified, the User can access the records of another Company by using the PASSWORD Application or via "Tools/Change Company" in an environment using T24 Administration Company.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Note:     (i)   It is always displayed reformatted, with the dashes.</p>
            <p>  (ii)  Any files, for which standard or special file mnemonics are specified in the COMPANY record, can only be accessed by Users Signed On to that Company.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Either: 1)    Company ID: CCGGGLLLL where CC is alphabetic Country code GGG  is numeric Company.Group LLLL is local Code or    2)    Company Mnemonic: 2-3 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') characters Multi-value field (Mandatory input) It must be the ID or Mnemonic of an existing COMPANY record. The company may be in linked business entity where T24 Administration Company is active.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.COMPARISON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of comparison to be made between the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) and the values specified in Fields 23 and 24.</p>
            <p>  The meanings of the Inputs are as follows:           EQ   Equal to           GE   Greater than or Equal to           GT   Greater Than           LE   Less than or Equal to           LT   Less Than           NE   Not Equal to           LK   Like           UL   Unlike</p>
            <p>  The User may only access records in which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) satisfy the conditions specified in Fields 22-24. For examples see FIELD NO (Field 21).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  EQ, GE, GT, LE, LT, NE, LK, UL or no input. Multi-value field associated with Fields 17-21, 23 and 24. (Mandatory input if FIELD NO (Field 21) is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value, or start of a range of values, with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) are to be compared.</p>
            <p>  1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>  OR Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following way:</p>
            <p>  (i) Up to 30 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by,</p>
            <p>  (ii) A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by,</p>
            <p>  (iii) Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid entry on the multi-value field SYS.FIELD.NAME on the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in (i).</p>
            <p>  Multi-value field associated with Fields 17-22 and 24.</p>
            <p>  (Mandatory input if FIELD NO is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.)</p>
            <p>  This field specifies either a single value or the lower limit of a range with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) are compared.</p>
            <p>  Note: The values input in this field and the next one must be in agreement with the Format rules of the element specified in Field 21.1. If, for example, the input in Field 21 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic, a minimum input of 3 characters will be required in this field.</p>
            <p>  When defining the enquires a user can run, you can also 'turn off' all SMS checks for a particular enquiry. This is useful when the enquiry presents non sensitive information from sensitive files. I.e you may wish to show customer and account static information (address, account titles etc ) but not show the balances. As the enquiry itself controls the presentation there may be no need for any additional security. To suppress SMS you must append *NOSMS to the name of the enquiry. E.G.</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1 (APPLICATION) ENQUIRY.SELECT</p>
            <p>  Field 20.1(FUNCTION) I</p>
            <p>  Field 21.1(FIELD.NO) 0</p>
            <p>  Field 22.1(DATA.COMPARISON) EQ</p>
            <p>  Field 23.1(DATA.FROM) CUSTOMER.STATIC*NOSMS</p>
            <p>  This mechanism works only with ENQUIRY.SELECT and must be entered in the format detailed above.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  See Details for format.</p>
            <p>  Input must begin and/or end with 3 dots when         DATA.COMPARISON = 'LK' or 'UL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the end of a range of values with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 21) are to be compared.</p>
            <p>  0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>  OR        Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the           following way:</p>
            <p>  (i)       Up to 30 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid           entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by,</p>
            <p>  (ii)      A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by,</p>
            <p>  (iii)     Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid           entry on the multi-value field SYS.FIELD.NAME on the           STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in           (i).</p>
            <p>  Multi-value field associated with Fields 17-23.</p>
            <p>  (Optional input if Field 22 contains EQ or NE, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Note:     The values input in this field and the previous one           must be in agreement with the Format rules of the           element specified in Field 21.1.  If, for example, the           input in Field 21 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic,           a minimum input of 10 characters will be required in           this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  See Details for format.</p>
            <p>  It may only be input if corresponding DATA COMPARISON (Field 22) contains EQ (Equal To) or NE (Not Equal To).</p>
            <p>  Must not be less than DATA FROM (Field 23)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>DATE.FORMAT field is used for deciding in which format the dates are to be displayed for a user / for a       </p>
            <p>language. It takes inputs 1, 2, 3, 4 ,5 and 6.</p>
            <p>1) (dd) (month) (year) </p>
            <p>2) (DD)/(MM)/(YYYY) </p>
            <p>3) (YYYY)/(MM)/(DD)</p>
            <p>4) YYYYMMDD.</p>
            <p>5) (MM)/(DD)/(YYYY)</p>
            <p>6) DD.MM.YYYY </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE.PROFILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the latest date on which the User represented by this record may have access to the System.</p>
            <p>  The Input may be all numeric DDMMYY or MMDDYY depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH format in Field 29 of the User record, or alphanumeric, DDMMMYYYY where the day and year are numeric and the month is the first 3 letters of the month, in capitals.</p>
            <p>  If you omit the year and/or the month, the System assumes they are the same as today.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. (Mandatory input) It must not be less than today's date or less than START DATE PROFILE (Field 8).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the end of a period each day at which the User is allowed access to the System.</p>
            <p>  Input can be 0-2359                  or 0000-2359                  or 00:00-23:59</p>
            <p>  Note:  1. This field is always displayed formatted with ':'        2. For whole day/night login, start should be 00:00, end           should be 24:00 (ie. 24 hours).        3. There may be two or more separate periods each day           when the User is allowed to access the System, e.g.           morning and afternoon, but not during lunchtime.        4. If only 1 or 2 digits are entered, they correspond to           minutes between midnight and 1 o'clock in the morning.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-4 numeric characters with optional ':' i.e.  HHMM or HH:MM Multi-value field associated with START TIME (Field 10) (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies, when used together with Fields 22-24, precisely which records may be accessed in the Application specified in the corresponding APPLICATION (Field 18.) A record may only be accessed if the field indicated here has a value allowed in the corresponding Fields 22-24.</p>
            <p>  0-3 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>  OR Up to 55 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following way:</p>
            <p>  (i) Up to 30 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by,</p>
            <p>  (ii) A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by,</p>
            <p>  (iii) Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid entry on the multi-value field SYS.FIELD.NAME or USR.FIELD.NAME on the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in (i).</p>
            <p>  Eg: FOREX&gt;COUNTERPARTY</p>
            <p>  It is recommended that field names and not field numbers are specified. If field numbers are specified then when a file layout changes you will be forced to manually change all user profiles affected.</p>
            <p>  Multi-value field associated with Fields 17-20 and 22-24.</p>
            <p>  (Optional input. No input means all records may be accessed, regardless of contents.)</p>
            <p>  For multi-value fields, only the field number may be specified, not the entry number, e.g. 21, not 21.1, all entries in the multi-value field will be checked. The System displays the name of the field indicated.</p>
            <p>  Example 1: To allow a User to See and List all Accounts records, but only Input (or change), Copy or Delete Accounts in pounds sterling.</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>  20.1(FUNCTION) L S</p>
            <p>  18.2(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>  20.2(FUNCTION) I C D</p>
            <p>  21.2(FIELD NO.) ACCOUNT&gt;CURRENCY (currency)</p>
            <p>  22.2(DATA COMPARISON) EQ (equal)</p>
            <p>  23.2(DATA FROM) GBP</p>
            <p>  Example 2:</p>
            <p>  To allow a User access to Account records only if they have Currency equal GBP and Category not in the range 01-001 to 01-099.</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>  20.1(FUNCTION) ALL</p>
            <p>  21.1(FIELD.NO) ACCOUNT&gt;CURRENCY (Currency)</p>
            <p>  22.1(DATA.COMPARISON) EQ (equal)</p>
            <p>  23.1(DATA.FROM) GBP</p>
            <p>  18.2(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>  20.2(FUNCTION) ALL</p>
            <p>  21.2(FIELD.NO) ACCOUNT&gt;CATEGORY (Category)</p>
            <p>  22.2(DATA.COMPARISON) NE (not equal)</p>
            <p>  23.2(DATA.FROM) 01-001</p>
            <p>  24.2(DATA.TO) 01-099</p>
            <p>  Example 3:</p>
            <p>  To allow a User to Authorise Data Capture records, but only if they do not contain an override.</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) DATA.CAPTURE</p>
            <p>  20.1(FUNCTION) A</p>
            <p>  21.1(FIELD.NO) DATA.CAPTURE&gt;OVERRIDE (Override)</p>
            <p>  22.1(DATA COMPARISON) LT (Less Than)</p>
            <p>  23.1(DATA.FROM) " (lowest possible value)</p>
            <p>  Note: It is not possible to prevent a User from entering on override during input, but Authorization can be restricted, as above, to ensure that any overrides are checked by a more senior person. " is the lowest value a field can have, so specifying LT (Less Than) " ensures that no override may be present.</p>
            <p>  Example 4:</p>
            <p>  Restricting FOREX transactions to a counterparties that belong to a specific account officer.</p>
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) FOREX</p>
            <p>  20.1(FUNCTION) I</p>
            <p>  21.1(FIELD.NO) CUSTOMER&gt;ACCOUNT.OFFICER</p>
            <p>  22.1(DATA COMPARISON) EQ</p>
            <p>  23.1(DATA.FROM) 100</p>
            <p>  Note: As you can see the field specified does not have to belong to the application. If the system can link the APPLICATION to the field then the SMS restriction will be applied. In this example the COUNTERPARTY field on the FOREX file provides the link to the CUSTOMER file. Hence when the transaction is input T24 reads the CUSTOMER file using the COUNTERPARTY as the key and checks that the ACCOUNT.OFFICER is 100. You do not have to define that the COUNTERPARTY as the key to CUSTOMER file this is done automatically based on the RELATED.FILE stored in the STANDARD.SELECTION record for FOREX.</p>
            <p>  Note: If you wish to test a value in a related file a consderable process load can be incurred when the user lists the file. This can be relieved by defining the related field as a J-descriptor user field on the STANDARD.SELECTION record and using that. Thus in the example above define CUST.OFFICER as type J, CUSTOMER&gt;ACCOUNT.OFFICER and then specify the FIELD.NO as FOREX&gt;CUST.OFFICER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  See Details for format.</p>
            <p>  It must not be higher than the number of fields in         records of the Application specified in APPLICATION         (Field 18.)</p>
            <p>  Input in this field will not be allowed when 'N' has been         input in 'FUNCTION' (Field 20.1).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Functions which may be used to access records of the Application entered in the corresponding Field 18.</p>
            <p>  his field is used, together with the associated Fields 17-19 and 21-24 to specify precisely which Functions the User may be used to access which records in which Applications. Valid Function codes are:           A 2 C D E H I L P Q R S V If NOT is entered, plus one or more Function codes, the System converts it to a list of all the Functions which are allowed.  (See Fields 18, 19 and 21 for examples.)</p>
            <p>  Note:     Even if the function 'C' (copy) is not allowed, the user           will still be able to transfer the ID (together with its           enrichment) of a selected record when using the '!'           facility during an input function.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  0-29 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters: 1.    Function codes separated by spaces or    2.    NOT + one or more Function codes or    3.    N (No Functions allowed) or    4.    ALL (All Functions allowed). Multi-value field associated with Fields 17-19, 21-24. Mandatory input except if a USER.SMS.GROUP was defined in field 18.1 in which case input is not allowed. No Default Value. If Function 2 (2nd Authorization) is allowed, but not A (1st Authorization) the User is allowed to enter Function Code A, a Security Violation is generated if the record requested is not ready for 2nd Authorization.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION.ID.LOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not full details of every Application, Function and record ID accessed by this User should be recorded in the PROTOCOL file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Y (Yes) or    N or NO (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>  It must be NO if APPLICATION LOG (Field 27) is NO.</p>
            <p>  Security Violations are always logged, regardless of this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INIT.APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies that, whenever the User Signs On from the Classic interface he will always go straight into the same Application immediately, without having to enter the Application name.</p>
            <p>  Note that this should not be viewed as a security measure as the user can still switch to another permitted application.</p>
            <p>  If this field is not used, the System will request the User to enter an Application name as soon as SIGN.ON is complete.</p>
            <p>  Input to this field is free format. It may be used in the same way as the ACTION line to enter an Application (or Abbreviation or Version) name and, optionally, a Function Code and a Record ID.</p>
            <p>  If a Menu is required as the initial Application, '?n' should be entered for a Main Menu, where 'n' is the Id of the Main Menu required, or '?xx' for a System Menu where 'xx' is the Id of the Menu. Whenever a menu has been specified in a User Profile, the system will always return to this menu at the Top level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  0-42 type A (alphanumeric) characters (Optional input. No         default value.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUT.DAY.MONTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether this User enters Days or Months first when entering dates.</p>
            <p>  If DDMM is entered, the System will interpret 0102 as 1st February and 0419 as an invalid date.  If MMDD is entered, the System will interpret 0102 as January 2nd and 0419 as April 19th.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  DDMM or MMDD (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Language in which the System should communicate with this User.  All messages, instructions, Help Text etc. will be displayed when possible in the Language indicated by this code.</p>
            <p>  ll information displayed by the System will be in the Language specified, provided the translation has been entered into the System.  Any information for which the translation has not been entered into the System will be displayed in whichever Language has been defined as Language 1 in the LANGUAGE table (ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-2 numeric characters. (Mandatory input) The number entered must be the ID of an existing record in the LANGUAGE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.SPOOL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with RPT TO RECEIVE (Field 45.1).  The date when the report was last spooled.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  YYYYMMDD (No input field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.SPOOL.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with RPT TO RECEIVE (Field 45.1).  The time the report was last spooled.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  HHMM (No input field)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAP.DN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the external distinguish name (DN) of the external identity which map the T24User.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.SESSIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>With T24 Desktop version 1.1.00 it is possilble for each user to run multiple applications concurrently, or multiple instances of each application.</p>
            <p>  Each session is a distinct UniVerse sessions and as such requires a separate UniVerse licence. This field is used to control the maximum number of sessions that a user can "own".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFLINE.SMS.PROFILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid USER.SMS.PROFILE record.</p>
            <p>  The properties of this profile are applied when the Branch is offline overwriting the main USER properties. This gives one set of properties for normal use and another smaller set for use when the branch is offline</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Input into this field is only allowed if the BR product is installed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFLINE.SMS.ROLE</field>
<desc>
        <p>A valid <b>EB.USER.ROLE</b> record.</p>
        <p> The properties of this ROLE is applied, when the Branch is offline and overwriting the main USER's ROLE. </p>
        <p>Gives one set of properties for normal use and another smaller set for use, when the branch is offline.</p>
        <p> Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Input  is only allowed if the BR product is installed.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.COMMIT.LOG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether or not records should be written to the PROTOCOL file recording every commit activity performed by the user</p>
        <p>If Y is entered, a record is written to the PROTOCOL file every time this User commits a transaction.</p>
        <p>
        	<p>Validations Rules:</p>
        </p>
         <p>Accepts the value ‘Y’ or left blank (Optional input) </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.BOOK.ACCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define in a multi branch system the companies that this user CAN access for inter company accounting.</p>
            <p>  Multi branch indicates that the MB product is installed, the term Multi Book can also be used.</p>
            <p>  This product basically allows financial level data to be stored in the same database table for all companies, as opposed to Multi Company where the data is stored in a separate table for each company.</p>
            <p>  Input to this field is mutually exclusive with input to the OTH.BOOK.BLOCK field.</p>
            <p>  It is possible in a multi branch system for a user to be able transact business with other branches without being able to sign in to those branches, unlike multi company</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  The first multi value can      contain a valid company code or a valid COMPANY.SMS.GROUP key</p>
            <p>  If</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.BOOK.BLOCK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define in a multi branch system the companies that this user CANNOT access for inter company accounting.</p>
            <p>  Multi branch indicates that the MB product is installed, the term Multi Book can also be used.</p>
            <p>  This product basically allows financial level data to be stored in the same database table for all companies, as opposed to Multi Company where the data is stored in a separate table for each company.</p>
            <p>  Input to this field is mutually exclusive with input to the OTH.BOOK.ACCESS field.</p>
            <p>  It is possible in a multi branch system for a user to be able transact business with other branches without being able to sign in to those branches, unlike multi company</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  The first multi value can      contain a valid company code or a valid COMPANY.SMS.GROUP key</p>
            <p>  If the first field contains      a COMPANY.SMS.GROUP key then no further input can take place</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSW.CHANGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used at present.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  (Internal field.  No manual input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSW.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used at present.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  (Internal field.  No manual input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the User's secret Password.  It can only be changed by the User, either when prompted by the System because it has expired, or whenever the User wishes to, using the PASSWORD Application.</p>
            <p>  Note:     If a User has forgotten his secret Password, it can be           reset using the PASSWORD.RESET Application to enable           him to start again with a new one.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  (6-16 characters.  Encrypted.  Never displayed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSWORD.VALIDITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies how often and on what date the User must change his Password.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1. Next Change Date If this is entered, it must be greater than today's date. It should be entered in the format DDMMYY or MMDDYY depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH (Field 29) format of the User record.  Spaces between days, months and years are optional.  Alternatively, the date may be entered in any of the standard formats permitted by the system. If you do not enter the year and/or the month, the System will assume that they are the same as today's date.  Every time the Password is changed, the System recalculates this date depending on the change frequency.</p>
            <p>  2. Change Frequency This can be daily, every 1-9 weeks, twice a month (on 15th and last day of each month) or every 1-6 Months. a) Daily Enter D or DAILY</p>
            <p>  If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the System assumes the Next Change Date will be tomorrow.</p>
            <p>  (b) Every 1-9 weeks Enter Wn where n is 1-9</p>
            <p>  If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the System assumes the Next Change Date will be n x 7 days from today.</p>
            <p>  c) Every 1-6 months Enter Mnndd</p>
            <p>  Where nn is the number of months 01-06 and dd is the day in the month on which the password must be changed, (01-31).  If this date does not exist (e.g. 30th February) the next day will be assumed (1st March)</p>
            <p>  If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the System assumes day 'dd' in 'nn' months from the current month.</p>
            <p>  Example:</p>
            <p>  If today's date is 26 FEB 1985 and you enter M0215 the System will assume the Next Change Date should be 15 APRIL 1985.</p>
            <p>  d) Twice a month Enter T</p>
            <p>  If you do not enter the Next Change Date, the System assumes the 15th of the current month if today is not after the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month is assumed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  This field is in two parts. 1)    Next Change Date: 1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters.  Default value calculated by the System depending on change frequency. (Optional input) 2)    Change Frequency: 1-5 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REACTIVATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that defines the end of the deactivation period. This can only be entered or changed by the User via the PASSWORD Application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard Date format</p>
            <p>  Input only via PASSWORD Application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROLE.COMPANY.RESTR</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the Company, to which the user signs on, in order to use specific roles.</p>
        <p> Used, together with the associated field 74, to specify for each Company, which Role, the user is allowed to login. </p>
        <p>Defines within each Role precisely, which record and application, the user can access, using which version and function.</p>
        <p>User who have signed on to a Company, can only access files for which standard or special file mnemonics are specified in the Company record (or have used the PASSWORD Application to access that Company).</p>
        <p> Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Permits ALL - to allow the functions of all companies listed in the <b>COMPANY.CODE</b> field. </p>
            <p value="2">In a Multi Book company set up, if this field is defined as ALL, - it allows the functions for Lead company and all book companies under that Lead company.</p>
            <p value="3"> 9 alphanumeric characters CCGGGLLLL where: CC   is 2 alpha characters Country code, GGG  is 3 numeric characters Company Group and LLLL is 4 numeric local code. or </p>
            <p value="4">   2-3 type MNE (uppercase alphanumeric or ) Company Mnemonic characters. </p>
            <p value="5">Multi-valued field associated with Field 75. </p>
            <p value="6">Mandatory input if legacy SMS restriction is not given.  </p>
            <p value="7">No Default Value. It must be a Company Code from the <b>COMPANY.CODE</b> field of this record.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RPT.COPIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Associated with RPT TO RECEIVE (Field 45.1).  The number of copies this user should receive.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RPT.TO.RECEIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name(s) of the reports this user is to receive from the over-night batch run.  Must be a valid entry on the REPORT.CONTROL file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-30 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SALT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.MGMT.L</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether or not a record should be written to the PROTOCOL file everytime this User accesses any of the Security Management Applications.</p>
            <p>  If Y is entered, a record is written to the PROTOCOL file everytime this User accesses any of the following Applications:</p>
            <p>  PASSWORD           PASSWORD.ENABLE           PASSWORD.RESET           USER           PASSWORD.RESET</p>
            <p>  Note:     Security Violations are always logged, regardless of the           values in Fields 25-28.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Y (Yes) or    N or NO (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.OFF.ITEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of any BASIC subroutine can be entered into this field.</p>
            <p>  During the SIGN OFF process, any subroutines defined in this field will be CALLed with one parameter. If this parameter returns with the values N, or NO the SIGN OFF processes will be halted</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Any BASIC subroutine that must contain one parameter.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN.ON.ITEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This multi-valued field is checked during SIGN ON, and consists of any commands that can be entered at the Desktop COMMAND line.</p>
            <p>  Any command(s) that are found in this field during SIGN.ON are invoked one at a time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.LAST.SIGN.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the time of day at which this User last Signed On successfully.  It is displayed on the SIGN.ON Screen.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Displayed in format HH:MM, 00:00 - 23:59. (Internal field.  No Manual input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.OUT.MINUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum time in minutes during which the User may be inactive without being Signed Off automatically.</p>
            <p>  If TIMEOUT.MODE in SPF is not defined as ACTIVE, and the User has Signed On to the System but has not been active for longer than the time specified in this field, the next time he attempts to do anything, the System will automatically SIGN.OFF and he will need to SIGN.ON again before continuing. The time count will be effective at all levels within T24. {In Classic - WAITING APPLICATION, AWAITING FUNCTION, AWAITING ID and AWAITING PAGE INSTRUCTIONS, whenever the cursor is located in the ACTION line}. During an input session, when the cursor is within the Data Section of the screen, the time count will not be initiated.</p>
            <p>  If TIMEOUT.MODE is set to ACTIVE and the transaction is not in the authorisation/validation phase, an inactive user will be automatically signed off after this time. In the authorisation/validation phase the AUTOLOG.TIME.MINS period defined in SPF will be used as the inactivity period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-3 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Address that will be printed on the report banner page.  Each multi-value represents one line on the banner a maximum of three lines can be used.  If blank then the delivery point from the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file is used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-22 Any character.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies details of the user.</p>
            <p>  This code is written for audit trail purposes in all records which are Input, Changed or Authorised by the User.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  3-16 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name by which the User is known and can be used for reporting purposes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ROLES</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines atleast one role for the user, if legacy SMS restrictions are not given. </p>
        <p>It is possible to mention multiple roles for a user in a specific Company.</p>
        <p>Validations</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">
                <p>Must be a valid <b>EB.USER.ROLES</b> record. </p>
            </p>
            <p value="2">Mandatory if <b>ROLE.COMPANY.RESTR</b> is specified.</p>
            <p value="3">Sub-value field, validated against <b>EB.USER.ROLES</b> application.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a particular Version which may be used to access records for the Application entered in the corresponding APPLICATION (Field 18.)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field is used, together with the associated Fields, 17, 18 and 20-24, to specify precisely which records in which Applications may be accessed by the User, using which Versions and Functions.</p>
            <p>  *  and  ?  can be used in this field , to specify more than one Version. They act as wild card characters ,where  *  replaces any number of characters including null, numbers, alphabets etc. and  ?  replaces one character including null, numbers, alphabets etc.</p>
            <p>  The version field in can have the value for eg : ,SAVE* , which allows the user to access Versions of ACCOUNT applications for eg : ACCOUNT,SAVESTUDENT</p>
            <p>  ACCOUNT,SAVERESIDENT , ACCOUNT,SAVESALARIED, etc The version field can have the value for eg : ,SAVE1000?00,which allows the user to access versions of ACCOUNT application for eg: SAVE1000100, SAVE1000200, SAVE1000300 , etc</p>
            <p>  Note: Versions of Applications may be used to change the screen layout or the rules for Input, Validation and Authorization.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example 1:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  To allow a User to List and See all Accounts except for those with Account Officer = 1234 using the standard version of Account, and to List and See all Accounts for Account Officer = 1234 only, using a special Version Account,99:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 19.1(VERSION) ,0 20.1(FUNCTION) L S 21.1(FIELD NO) 9 22.1(DATA COMPARISON) NE 23.1(DATA FROM) 1234 18.2(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 19.2(VERSION) ,99 20.2(FUNCTION) L S 21.2(FIELD NO) 9 22.2(DATA COMPARISON) EQ 23.2(DATA FROM) 1234</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example 2 :</p>
            <p />
            <p>  To allow a User to Input and See all Account version with name starting with SAVINGS followed by any character:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Field 18.1(APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 19.1(VERSION) ,SAVINGS* 20.1(FUNCTION) I S</p>
            <p />
            <p>  For more examples of Fields 17-24 see Fields 18 and 21.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1. 0-50 type A (alphanumeric) characters beginning with ','. or 2. ',0' to allow only the standard version. or 3. No input to allow all Versions. Multi-value field associated with Fields 17, 18 and 20-24. (Optional input except if a USER.SMS.GROUP was defined in field 18.1 in which case input is not allowed. If not entered, access to all Versions is allowed.</p>
            <p>  Special character  *  will replace any number of characters and  ?  replaces one character. Also  ?  after  *  and two occurances of  *  are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

