<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>USER.EXTERNAL.FIELD</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>USER EXTERNAL FIELD - Description </p>
            <p>This table will allow the user to specify for each T24 Application, which field number(s) identify a 'Customer' or 'Account' field. </p>
            <p>This information will then be used by the Security Management System to control EXTERNAL type users for whom specific Customer and account number(s) have been specified on the profile.  (Field 15.1 and 16.1.1 of the USER profile). </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the Override messages which the user agreed to during Input. </p>
            <p>During the validation stage of this table the system may provide the user with override messages. </p>
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the Override, the full text of the actual Override Message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field. </p>
            <p>If subsequently, the contract record is either fully displayed or printed, then all override messages will be present. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field. Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.FD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Account field number(s) within the Application defined in APPLICATION (field 1.1). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 numeric characters. Subvalue field associated with fields 1.1 and 2.1.1. Optional Input; Default = Nill.</p>
            <p>The field number must be within the range of field numbers of the Application defined in APPLICATION (field 1.1).</p>
            <p>'Zero' (i.e. ID) as a single input will be accepted.</p>
            <p>Duplicates within the same Application will not be allowed.</p>
            <p>At least one input will be mandatory if no CUSTOMER Field (field 2.1.1) has been defined.</p>
            <p>Input is not allowed if APPLICATION. (field 1.1) has not been entered.</p>
            <p>An override will be required when the field number input is not of a 'ACC', 'ALL' or 'ANT' type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Application for which the user wants to specify the Customer and Account fields. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-25 characters identifying a valid program name. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1.1 and 3.1.1. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Duplicates will not be allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the company for which the user wants to specify the various customer and account fields within the Applications available in this company. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>9 alphanumeric character COMPANY CODE or    1-5 mnemonic character identifying the company. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>The input must be the ID of a COMPANY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.FD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the customer field number(s) within the Application defined in the previous field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 numeric characters. Subvalue field associated with fields 1.1 and 3.1.1. Optional Input;  Default = Nill.</p>
            <p>The field number must be within the range of field numbers of the Application defined in the previous field.</p>
            <p>Zero ('0' = ID) as a single input will be accepted.</p>
            <p>Duplicates within the same application will not be allowed.</p>
            <p>An override will be required when the field number input is not of a 'CUS' type.</p>
            <p>Input is not allowed if Application has not been entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

