<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>USER.SMS.GROUP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file allows the user to group together various T24 Applications.  This enables the creation of logical groups which can then be specified directly in a user profile.  This will avoid repetition of related applications in different user profiles. </p>
            <p>   When a modification is entered into the group, it will automatically impact all the profiles which contain this group. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date from which the user may have access to the additional functions in TEMP.FUNCTION can be specified here.</p>
            <p>   Input may be all numeric DDMMYY or MMDDYY depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH format in Field 29 of the User record, or alphanumeric, DDMMMYYYY where the day and year are numeric and the month is the first 3 letters of the month, in capitals.</p>
            <p>   If you omit the year and/or the month, the System assumes they are the same as today.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   1-9 type D (date     format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces.     </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Cannot be greater than     END.DATE     </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory if     TEMP.FUNCTION or END.DATE is present.     </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEMP.FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The additional functions to be allowed to a user for a temporary period of time can be specified here. The period for which these additional functions may be</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Valid Function codes are: A 2 C D E H I L P Q R S V.</p>
            <p>   If NOT is entered, followed by one or more Function codes, the System converts it to a list of all the Functions that are allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   0-29     type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters:</p>
            <p>   Function     codes separated by spaces or</p>
            <p />
            <p>   NOT + one or more     Function codes or </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   N- Function is not     allowed here.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   ALL (All Functions     allowed). </p>
            <p>   Multi-value field associated with Fields APPLICATION</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory input if START.DATE and END.DATE is specified. No Default Value. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>   Specifies a particular Version which may be used to access records for the Application entered in the corresponding APPLICATION (Field 2.1). </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     This field is used, together with the associated Fields, 2.1 and 4.1 - 8.1, to specify precisely which records in which Applications may be accessed by the User, using which Versions and Functions.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Note: Versions of Applications may be used to change the screen layout or the rules for Input, Validation and Authorization. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Example: 1</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   To create a group which allows a User to List and See all Accounts except for those with Account Officer = 1234 using the standard version of Account, and to List and See all Accounts for Account Officer = 1234 only, using a special Version Account,99: </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Field 2.1 (APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 3.1 (VERSION) ,0 4.1 (FUNCTION) L S 5.1 (FIELD NO) 9 6.1 (DATA COMPARISON) NE 7.1 (DATA FROM) 1234 2.2 (APPLICATION) ACCOUNT 3.2 (VERSION) ,99 4.2 (FUNCTION) L S 5.2 (FIELD NO) 9 6.2 (DATA COMPARISON) EQ 7.2 (DATA FROM) 1234 </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    1. 0-23 type A (alphanumeric)     characters beginning with ','. or 2. ',0' to allow only the standard     version. or 3. No input to allow all Versions. Multivalue field associated     with Fields 2.1 and 4.1 to 8.1. (Optional input. If not entered, access to     all Versions is allowed.)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date till which the user may have access to the additional functions in TEMP.FUNCTION is specified here.</p>
            <p>   The Input may be all numeric DDMMYY or MMDDYY depending on the INPUT DAY MONTH format in Field 29 of the User record, or alphanumeric, DDMMMYYYY where the day and year are numeric and the month is the first 3 letters of the month, in capitals.</p>
            <p>   If you omit the year and/or the month, the System assumes they are the same as today.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   1-9     type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters with optional spaces. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Must     not be less than today's date or START.DATE. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory if TEMP.FUNCTION or START.DATE is present.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the end of a range of values with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 5.1) are to be compared. </p>
            <p>   0-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p>   OR         Up to 43 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following            way: </p>
            <p>   (i)        Up to 24 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid            entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by, </p>
            <p>   (ii)       A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by, </p>
            <p>   (iii)      Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid entry            on the multivalue field SYS.FIELD.NAME on the            STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in            (i). </p>
            <p>   Multivalue field associated with Fields 2.1 to 7.1 </p>
            <p>   (Optional input if Field 6.1 contains EQ or NE, otherwise not allowed.) </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Note:      The values input in this field and the previous one must            be in agreement with the Format rules of the element            specified in Field 5.1.  If, for example, the input in Field            5.1 corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic, a minimum            input of 10 characters will be required in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   See details for format.</p>
            <p>   It may only be input if corresponding DATA COMPARISON (Field 6.1) contains EQ (Equal To) or NE (Not Equal To).</p>
            <p>   Must not be less than DATA FROM (Field 7.1)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for free form narrative.  It is recommended to enter a meaningful description such as the name of the Module/Group to facilitate the recognition of the facilities contained in the group. </p>
            <p>   This field is provided for entering a comprehensive description of the SMS group being defined by the user. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 alphanumeric characters characters. Multivalue Field. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SMS1</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the same field in USER record is empty, then the value in this field will be used. Defines the end period or the log out time till which the user is allowed access to the system on a specific day defined in the ALLOWED.DAYS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Input can be 0-2359 or 0000-2359 or 00:00-23:59</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Note: (1) This field is always displayed formatted with ':' (2) For whole day/night login, start should be 00:00, end should be 24:00 (ie. 24 hours). (3) There may be two or more separate periods each day when the User is allowed to access the System, e.g. morning and afternoon, but not during lunchtime. (4) If only 1 or 2 digits are entered, they correspond to minutes between midnight and 1 o'clock in the morning.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-4 numeric characters with optional ':' i.e. HHMM or HH:MM Sub-value field associated with ALLOWED.DAYS and DAY.ST.TIME (Optional input)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Functions which may be used to access records of the Application entered in the corresponding Field 2. </p>
            <p>   This field is used, together with the associated Fields 2.1 - 3.1 and 5.1 - 8.1 to specify precisely which Functions the User may be used to access which records in which Applications. Valid Function codes are: </p>
            <p>              A 2 C D E H I L P Q R S V </p>
            <p>   (A=Authorise, 2=2nd Authoriser, C=copy, D=Delete, E=Exception, H=History restore, I=Input, L=List, P=Print, Q=Auditor review, R=Reverse, S=See, V=Verify)</p>
            <p>   If NOT is entered, plus one or more Function codes, the System converts it to a list of all the Functions which are allowed. </p>
            <p>   Note:      Even if the function 'C' (copy) is not allowed, the user            will still be able to transfer the ID (together with its            enrichment) of a selected record when using the '!'            facility during an input function. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   0-29 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters: 1.   Function codes separated by spaces or     2.   NOT + one or more Function codes or     3.   N (No Functions allowed) or     4.   ALL (All Functions allowed). Multivalue field associated with Fields 2.1 - 3.1 and 5.1 - 8.1. Mandatory input.  No Default Value.</p>
            <p>   If Function 2 (2nd Authorisation) is allowed, but not A (1st Authorisation) the User is allowed to enter Function Code A, a Security Violation is generated if the record requested is not ready for 2nd Authorisation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.ST.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the same field in USER record is empty, then the value in this field will be used. Defines the start of period or the log in time at which the user is allowed access to the system on a specific day defined in ALLOWED.DAYS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Input can be 0-2359 or 0000-2359 or 00:00-23:59</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Note: (1) This field is always displayed formatted with ':' (2) There may be two or more separate periods each day when the User is allowed to access the System, e.g. morning and afternoon, but not during lunch time. (3) If only 1 or 2 digits are entered, they correspond to minutes between midnight and 1 o'clock in the morning.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-4 numeric characters with optional ':' i.e. HHMM or HH:MM Sub-value field associated with ALLOWED.DAYS and DAY.END.TIME (Optional input)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SMS.GROUP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Uniquely identifies the SMS group being created. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1 to 14 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies, when used together with Fields 6.1 - 8.1, precisely which records may be accessed in the Application specified in the corresponding APPLICATION (Field 2.)  A record may only be accessed if the field indicated here has a value allowed in the corresponding Fields 6.1 - 8.1. </p>
            <p>   0-3 numeric characters. </p>
            <p>   OR         Up to 43 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following            way: </p>
            <p>   (i)        Up to 24 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid            entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by, </p>
            <p>   (ii)       A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by, </p>
            <p>   (iii)      Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid entry            on the multivalue field SYS.FIELD.NAME on the            STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in            (i). </p>
            <p>   Multivalue field associated with Fields 2.1 to 4.1 and 6.1 to 8.1. </p>
            <p>   (Optional input.  No input means all records may be accessed, regardless of contents.)For multivalue fields, only the field number may be specified, not the entry number, e.g. 21, not 21.1, all entries in the multivalue field will be checked.  The System displays the name of the field indicated. </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Example 1: </p>
            <p>   To create a group which allows a User to See and List all Accounts records, but only Input (or change), Copy or Delete Accounts in pounds sterling. </p>
            <p>   Field  2.1 (APPLICATION)      ACCOUNT        4.1 (FUNCTION)         L S        2.2 (APPLICATION)      ACCOUNT        4.2 (FUNCTION)         I C D        5.2 (FIELD NO.)        8       (currency)        6.2 (DATA COMPARISON)  EQ      (equal)        7.2 (DATA FROM)        GBP </p>
            <p>   Example 2: </p>
            <p>   To create a group which allows a User access to Account records only if they have Currency equal GBP and Category not in the range 01-001 to 01-099. </p>
            <p>   Field 2.1  (APPLICATION)      ACCOUNT       4.1  (FUNCTION)         ALL       5.1  (FIELD.NO)         8       (Currency)       6.1  (DATA.COMPARISON)  EQ      (equal)       7.1  (DATA.FROM)        GBP       2.2  (APPLICATION)      ACCOUNT       4.2  (FUNCTION)         ALL       5.2  (FIELD.NO)         2       (Category)       6.2  (DATA.COMPARISON)  NE      (not equal)       7.2  (DATA.FROM)        01-001       8.2  (DATA.TO)          01-099 </p>
            <p>   Example 3: </p>
            <p>   To allow a User to Authorise Data Capture records, but only if they do not contain an override. </p>
            <p>   Field 2.1  (APPLICATION)      DATA.CAPTURE       4.1  (FUNCTION)         A       5.1  (FIELD.NO)         24 (Override)       6.1  (DATA COMPARISON)  LT (Less Than)       7.1  (DATA.FROM)        "  (lowest possible value) </p>
            <p>   Note:      It is not possible to prevent a User from entering on            override during input, but Authorisation can be            restricted, as above, to ensure that any overrides are            checked by a more senior person.  " is the lowest value            a field can have, so specifying LT (Less Than) " ensures            that no override may be present. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   See details for format.</p>
            <p>   It must not be higher than the number of fields in records of the Application specified in APPLICATION (Field 2.)</p>
            <p>   Input in this field will not be allowed when 'N' has been input in 'FUNCTION' (Field 4.1).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOWED.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the same field in USER record is empty, then the value in this field will be used. Specifies the day for which the period for users access to the system is taken from the associated fields DAY.ST.TIME and DAY.END.TIME. The values allowed are 1 to 7 meaning 1 MONDAY, 2 TUESDAY and 7 SUNDAY.</p>
            <p>  The period set in the fields START.TIME and END.TIME (fields 10 &amp; 11) is applicable for all days of the week.</p>
            <p>  The access time for a particular day will be taken from the fields DAY.ST.TIME and DAY.END.TIME if defined, otherwise the common START.TIME and END.TIME will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1- Numeric character. Multi-value field associated with DAY.ST.TIME and DAY.END.TIME (Optional input)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies which Applications are to be included in the group. </p>
            <p>   This field is used, together with the associated Fields 3.1 to 8.1 to specify precisely which records in which Applications can be accessed by the User using which Versions and Functions. It must be the name of an existing Application, ALL.PG to allow access to all Applications or ALL.PG (program type) to allow access to all Applications of a certain type (see below). </p>
            <p>   The following program types may be used in conjunction with ALL.PG (e.g. ALL.PG.H) to give access to a particular type of program:- </p>
            <p>   Program Type Meaning </p>
            <p>   H Programs for which the standard 3 files exist - Live, Unauthorised and History, e.g. CUSTOMER. </p>
            <p>   U Programs for which Live and Unauthorised files exist, but no History, e.g. VERSION. </p>
            <p>   L Programs for which only a Live file exists (updated automatically by the system) e.g. STMT.ENTRY (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program). </p>
            <p>   M Programs which are designed to do something other than processing the standard T24 functions using a specific file e.g. PASSWORD.ENABLE, End Of Day Batch programs. </p>
            <p>   T Programs which handle automatically updated CONCAT files, e.g. CUSTOMER.ACCOUNT (only L, S and P functions can be used with this type of program). </p>
            <p>   Note: The following 3 type M programs are available to all users and cannot be restricted:- </p>
            <p>   SIGN.ON SIGN.OFF PASSWORD </p>
            <p>   Example 1: </p>
            <p>   To create a group which will give the User access to all Applications using all Functions (except auditor review) and all Versions of all Applications, enter the following:- </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Note: Fields 5.1-8.1 are used to specify particular records or types of records which may be accessed within an Application. See FIELD NO (Field 5.1) for examples. </p>
            <p>   Example 2: </p>
            <p>   To create a group which will allow the User to List Display, Input and Copy Customer records and to List and Display records for all other Applications: </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Example 3: </p>
            <p>   To create a group which will prevent a USER from using any type M Applications, but allow him to List and Display records in any other Applications: </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   1. 1-25 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters,         Application name. </p>
            <p>   or 2. ALL.PG to allow all Applications. </p>
            <p>   or 3. ALL.PG (program type) see details. </p>
            <p>   Multivalue field associated with Fields 3.1 to 8.1.         (Mandatory input in each set of Fields 2.1 - 8.1).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.COMPARISON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of comparison to be made between the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 5.1) and the values specified in Fields 7.1 and 8.1. </p>
            <p>   The meanings of the Inputs are as follows:            EQ   Equal to            GE   Greater than or Equal to            GT   Greater Than            LE   Less than or Equal to            LT   Less Than            NE   Not Equal to            LK   Like            UL   Unlike </p>
            <p>   The User may only access records in which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 5.1) satisfy the conditions specified in Fields 6.1 to 8.1. </p>
            <p>   For examples see FIELD NO (Field 5.1). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   EQ, GE, GT, LE, LT, NE, LK, UL or no input. Multivalue field associated with Fields 2.1 to 5.1 and 7.1 to 8.1. (Mandatory input if FIELD NO (Field 5.1) is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value, or start of a range of values, with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 5.1) are to be compared. </p>
            <p>   1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p>   OR         Up to 43 characters (type ANY) formatted in the following            way: </p>
            <p>   (i)        Up to 24 characters (type ANY) which must be a valid            entry on the FILE.CONTROL file, followed by, </p>
            <p>   (ii)       A '&gt;' (greater than) sign, followed by, </p>
            <p>   (iii)      Up to 18 characters (type A) which must be a valid entry            on the multivalue field SYS.FIELD.NAME on the            STANDARD.SELECTION record for the file specified in            (i). </p>
            <p>   Multivalue field associated with Fields 2.1 to 6.1 and 8.1. </p>
            <p>   (Mandatory input if FIELD NO is entered, otherwise input is not allowed.) </p>
            <p>   This field specifies either a single value or the lower limit of a range with which the contents of the field indicated in FIELD NO (Field 5.1) are compared. </p>
            <p>   Note:      The values input in this field and the next one must be in            agreement with the Format rules of the element specified            in Field 5.1.  If, for example, the input in Field 5.1            corresponds to a Customer Mnemonic, a minimum input of            3 characters will be required in this field. </p>
            <p>   When defining the enquires a user can run, you can also 'turn off' all SMS checks for a particular enquiry. This is useful when the enquiry presents non sensitive information from sensitive files. I.e you may wish to show customer and account static information (address, account titles etc ) but not show the balances. As the enquiry itself controls the presentation there may be no need for any additional security. To suppress SMS you must append *NOSMS to the name of the enquiry. E.G. Field 2.1  (APPLICATION)      ENQUIRY.SELECT Field 4.1  (FUNCTION)         I Field 5.1  (FIELD.NO)         0 Field 6.1  (DATA.COMPARISON)  EQ Field 7.1  (DATA.FROM)        CUSTOMER.STATIC*NOSMS </p>
            <p>   This mechanism works only with ENQUIRY.SELECT and must be entered in the format detailed above. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   See details for format.</p>
            <p>   Input must begin and/or end with 3 dots when DATA.COMPARISON = 'LK' or 'UL'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

