<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>USER.ABBREVIATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>User Abbreviations may be defined when an individual User requires a particular Abbreviation which is not included in the ABBREVIATION table, and for which a general Abbreviation is unnecessary. </p>
            <p>Any Abbreviation specified in this table can only be accessed by the User whose name is defined in Field 0. </p>
            <p>When setting up a User Abbreviation, care should be exercised to ensure that it is not a duplicate of an existing Abbreviation record. If duplication exist between these two files, the Abbreviation defined in the User Abbreviation file will take precedence, for this specific User, over the Abbreviation defined in the general Abbreviation file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ABBREVIATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Abbreviation to be used for the corresponding original text. </p>
            <p>his field is used to specify the Abbreviation which will generate the corresponding ORIGINAL TEXT (Field 2.1) </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>ABBREVIATION ORIGINAL TEXT CU CUSTOMER In this example, the User need only input the Abbreviation CU to run the Customer Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-35 characters, type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character uppercase alpha.) Multivalue field. (Mandatory input) Duplicate Abbreviations are not allowed. No comma will be allowed in the abbreviation Text. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGINAL.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the original Application or function command from which the corresponding Abbreviation was created. </p>
            <p>his field contains the Application and function commands to be performed and the record to be accessed in response to the Abbreviation being entered.  It is then used by the system to translate the Abbreviation into a meaningful command. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-54 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input) This field is not allowed if the corresponding Abbreviation is not entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the User name by which the User Abbreviation details can be identified. </p>
            <p>his field is used to identify the User for whom the Abbreviations in this record have been defined. </p>
            <p>The Abbreviations defined in this record can only be accessed by the user specified in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-16 character type AA, (alphanumeric, first character alpha), User name. (Mandatory input) Cannot be changed. Must be an existing User name</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

