<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EB</product>
<table>WS.CREATE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Creates either Web Services or T24 Software Development Kit (TSDK) classes.</p>
            <p>The generated class files will then be packaged in to a Java Archive (JAR) file if the Jar Name and Location fields are populated.</p>
            <p>For Web Services, the generated class files can be packaged in to a web service offering using third party products.</p>
            <p>For TSDK classes, the generated class and JAR files can be supplied to T24 developers for use in writing their own Java routines.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PACKAGE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The package name for the Web Service or TSDK Java classes (e.g. "com.companyx.tsdk.local").</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WEB.SERVICE.URI</field>
<desc>
            <p>The URL for the Web Service as used for the Web Service Definition Language  (WSDL).</p>
            <p>Currently not used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCOPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines the scope of the web service as used in the web service descriptor file.</p>
            <p>Only used if the Deployment Type record is WEB.SERVICE.</p>
            <p>Currently not used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Application - An application scope causes the same instance of the implementation to be used for all requests on the application.</p>
            <p>Session - A session scope causes the same instance to be used for all requests on each session.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WS.CREATE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Id of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPLOY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the WS.DEPLOY file containing details of the deployment descriptor for the generated classes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains a description for this creation record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JAR.LOCATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The directory location of the Java Archive (JAR) file to create if required.</p>
            <p>This is only used if a JAR is required, as determined by the JAR Name field.</p>
            <p>This can be a relative path to the account .run directory or a full pathname.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JAR.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the Java Archive (JAR) file to create if required.</p>
            <p>If this is not specified then the application will only create the Java and class files.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>METHOD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of a method to expose as a Web Service.</p>
            <p>Only used if the Deployment Type record is WEB.SERVICE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A multi-value field containing a list of applications (and enquiries or versions for Web Services) to be created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

