<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>IS</product>
        <table>IS.CONTRACT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>IS.CONTRACT is the application to create Islamic Contracts. The entire workflow of the product with different statuses is captured in this application.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>The contract evolves into different statuses like REQUEST, APPROVAL, PURCHASE based on the workflow defined in the product parameter file IS.PARAMETER.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>COST.DR.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Debit Account for the Cost Payment </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory if Cost Type is given </p>
                <p>2. Defaulted from the FT Commission type or FT Charge type record of the Cost type specified </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COST.PAY.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Payment Type by which the Cost has to be paid.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Valid values are Purchase, Vendor and Finance </p>
                <p>2. Field Mandatory if Cost Type is given </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COST.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the costs incurred during purchase of the Contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the table IS.COST.TYPE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The currency in which the contract is booked.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field Mandatory</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record in the table CURRENCY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Customer who requests the asset and the contract is booked for.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field Mandatory.</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record in the table CUSTOMER.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Customer account recorded in the Purchase contract. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the table ACCOUNT.</p>
                <p>2. Account must belong to the Contract Customer.</p>
                <p>3. NOSTRO or VOSTRO account not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEAL.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Deal date of the contract specifies the actual date the Customer requests for the asset and the details being captured in the screen. The current date of the system(TODAY) is defaulted in this field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>2. Standard T24 Date Field.</p>
                <p>3. Current date (TODAY) is defaulted.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DELIVERY.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Delivery Date of the asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Standard T24 Date Field.</p>
                <p>2. Functionality yet to be developed for delivery of Assets.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Description of the Contract or the Asset being requested.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Standard T24 Alphanumeric field.</p>
                <p>2. Mandatory Input.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Down Payment amount corresponding to the Down Payment transaction</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input. </p>
                <p>2. Defaulted with the Debit amount corresponding to the FT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNTING.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>List of Accounting events like APPROVAL, PURCHASE , etc. that take place during status transition of the workflow.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>System updates this field while updating the PREV.STATUS multi-value set.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.ASSET.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Asset against which the Down Payment is paid.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the Asset table of IS.COMMODITY.</p>
                <p>2. The commodity must be one of the defined assets in the Purchase contract.</p>
                <p>3. Input allowed only if DP.BY.ASSET flag is set to 'YES'.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.BANK.CONTRIB</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Total Bank Contribution for the Asset or Commodity. This field is updated with the difference of Customer contribution from the Purchase Price of the Asset or Commodity.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>2. System updates the difference of Customer contribution from the Purchase Price of the Asset or Commodity in this field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.BY.ASSET</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes whether the down payment is paid against Asset or Commodity.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Flag field to accept Down payment by Asset or Commodity.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.COMMODITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Commodity against which the Down Payment is paid.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the table IS.COMMODITY.</p>
                <p>2. The commodity must be one of the defined commodities in the Purchase contract.</p>
                <p>3. Input not allowed if DP.BY.ASSET flag is set to 'YES'.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.CONTRIB.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to specify the Contribution Amounts for Corresponding Contribution types </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Sum of the Contribution Amounts must match the DP.CUST.CONTRIB value </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.CONTRIB.PAYTO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether the Customer Contribution to be paid to Bank or Supplier.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Valid values are Bank and Supplier. </p>
                <p>2. Input Mandatory if DP.TYPE is given.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.CONTRIB.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Type of Customer Contribution Payment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Valid values are Cash and Asset.</p>
                <p>2. Field Mandatory if DP.TYPE is given.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.CUST.CONTRIB</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Total contribution of the Customer for the Asset or Commodity.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>2. System updates the customer contribution as DP.VALUE of the down payment. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.PERCENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Down Payment Percentage for the individual asset or a commodity.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Input Mandatory if DP.TYPE is Percentage.</p>
                <p>2. System defaults amount in case DP.TYPE is Amount and a valid percentage is given in the field DP.PERCENT</p>
                <p>3. Valid percentage (less than 100). </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Down Payment transaction reference(FT) updated on payment of Down Payment using the FT application</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-Input.</p>
                <p>2. System updates the FT reference through which the Down Payment is performed.</p>
                <p>2. Defaulted with the FT reference generated as and when Down Payment is done </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The action codes act as checklist to be performed as part of the Purchase Contract. The actions are defined in the table IS.CONTRACT.TASK.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Valid record from the table IS.CONTRACT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if the Down Payment Amount can be defined in Amount or Percentage.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Valid values are Percentage and Amount</p>
                <p>2. Input Mandatory if DP.VALUE or DP.PERCENT is given </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DP.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Down Payment Amount for the individual asset or a commodity.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Input Mandatory if DP.TYPE is Amount.</p>
                <p>2. System defaults percentage in case DP.TYPE is Percentage and a valid amount is given in the field DP.AMOUNT</p>
                <p>3. Valid percentage (less than 100).</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GUARANTOR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Customer who will act as Guarantor for the contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record from the table CUSTOMER.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IS.CONTRACT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The ID of the application IS.CONTRACT is an auto-generated ID. The same contract is used to capture Request, Purchase  and other related operations.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MMIA.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The MMIA Agreement reference of the Purchase contract.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEXT.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the expected Next Status of the Contract which is defined in the IS.PARAMETER workflow.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. The values to the field are defined in the EB.LOOKUP table with prefix "IS.WF.STATUS*".</p>
                <p>2. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>3. Defaulted by the system based on the value in the field STATUS.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NOTES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Captures additional information about the contract </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Standard T24 Alphanumeric field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user has confirmed during input.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>During Commit, the system may generate a series of screen override messages waiting for User Approval. If the record is subsequently displayed or printed, all override messages are shown in this field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>System generated. Multi-value field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PREV.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The status in which the contract was present before transition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>2. Copied from the field STATUS during status transition.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PREV.STATUS.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The value date of the previous status in which the contract was present before transition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>2. Copied from the field STATUS.VALUE.DATE during status transition.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION.COMPLETED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The status of the action code linked in ACT.CODE field is marked completed by setting this field Y or N.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PREV.STATUS.NOTES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the details of the last action happened on the contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is to specify the type of product the asset will be processed </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field Mandatory</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record from the table IS.PARAMETER.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PURCHASE.PRICE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the total price of the commodity or asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>QUANTITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the quantity of the commodity or asset being requested </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. This is a Mandatory field </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RECOVERABLE.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Amount which is recoverable for the Repossessed Asset.</p>
                <p>This is the difference between market value inputted during the Finance re-posses and the resale price inputted during Purchase.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RECOVERED.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Amount which is recovered for the Repossessed Asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RECOVERY.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the account in which the recovered amount is maintained.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record from the table ACCOUNT</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RECOVERY.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the amount yet to be recovered for the repossessed asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REPOS.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Amount received during Repossession of an asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REPOS.PUR.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The reference captured during repurchase of the repossessed asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION.SUCCESS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The status of the action code linked in ACT.CODE field is marked Success by setting this field Y or N</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REPURCHASE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if the contract is repurchased after repossession.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESALE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if the contract is resold after repossession</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESALE.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the total Resale value of the repossessed asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESALE.CUST.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The account of the Resale Customer.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the table ACCOUNT.</p>
                <p>2. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESALE.CUSTOMER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Customer to whom the repossessed asset is sold. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESALE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The date on which the Resale of the repossessed asset is performed.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESALE.FT.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The reference captured during the resale of the repossessed asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESALE.PRICE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The price at which the repossessed asset is sold again.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESALE.QTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The quantity of the asset resold during Resale of the repossessed asset.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. No-input field currently. Will be opened for user-input in future.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SALE.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The AA arrangement reference is captured in this field when the contract is financed. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ASSET.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The asset being purchased is captured in this field. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory Input for Named Assets.</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record in the Asset table defined in the Commodity. record </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SIMULATION.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The AA simulation reference which can be linked to the Purchase contract. User can simulate the finance and the repayment schedules using the AA simulation and the same can be linked here during purchase.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record from the table "AA.SIMULATION.CAPTURE".</p>
                <p>2. The Total Purchase amount should not exceed the Simulation Amount.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The status of the Contract like REQUEST, APPROVAL, PURCHASE. The status transition happens according to the workflow defined in the IS.PARAMETER.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. The values to the field are defined in the EB.LOOKUP table with prefix "IS.WF.STATUS*". </p>
                <p>2. Currently, APPROVAL and PURCHASE is designed to raise accounting entries. The Accounting entries for Cost is raised during the PURCHASE status</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>List of Statement Entries generated as the result of Accounting.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.PURCHASE.PRICE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Total Price of the contract (Sum of the purchase amounts of all commodities/assets) </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>2. System updates the field value as sum of all the purchase price.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOTAL.DP.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Total Down Payment amount of the Contract </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>2. System updates the field value as sum of all the down payment specified.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOTAL.DP.CASH</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Total Down Payment amount contributed in terms of DP.CONTRIB.PAYTO as 'Bank' and DP.CONTRIB.TYPE as 'Cash'.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UNIT.PRICE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The unit price of the commodity or asset being requested</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field Mandatory.</p>
                <p>2. Defaulted from the Asset Table in case of Named Assets.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UNITS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The units in which the commodity or asset can be expressed. For example, Tin could be expressed in Tons, Real Estate building could be expressed in acres or square feet. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. The values to the field are defined in the EB.LOOKUP table with prefix "IS.UNIT*"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VALUE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Value date of the Purchase Contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Defaulted to TODAY.</p>
                <p>2. Cannot be future dated.</p>
                <p>3. Standard T24 Date field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VENDOR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Vendor of the Purchase contract who supplies the asset. The Vendor could be an individual or a company.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field Mandatory </p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record in the table IS.VENDOR.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMMODITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The commodity being purchased is captured in this field. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. This is a Mandatory field </p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid entry in the IS.COMMODITY table </p>
                <p>3. Duplicate Commodity codes are not allowed </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VENDOR.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The name of the Vendor who supplies the asset. The value for the field is defaulted from the Vendor table. User-defined Names can be overwritten.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Standard T24 Alphanumeric field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VENDOR.WASH.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The account used to act as Wash account for Vendor Payment. This Account is credited during Purchase and the Vendor Payments are disbursed from this account.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Field No-input.</p>
                <p>2. Defaulted with the Multi Supplier Category of the Parameter record  </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WAKALA.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The AA Arrangement Contract reference which has to be considered as a Wakala contract.</p>
                <p>This is keyed in for structured products like WAKALA-MUSAWAMA.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Valid record in the table AA.ARRANGEMENT</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COST.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The cost amount for the chosen Cost type in the Purchase Contract Currency</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory if Cost Type is given </p>
                <p>2. Defaulted from the FT Commission type or FT Charge type record of the Cost </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COST.CR.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Credit Account for the Cost Payment </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1.  This field is defaulted with supplier account defined in the Parameter table</p>
                <p>2. This field is user inputtable if the Cost Pay Type is Purchase </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COST.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The description of the costs incurred during purchase of the Contract. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Standard T24 Alphanumeric field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
