<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>IS</product>
        <table>IS.MOVEQUIPMENT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>IS.MOVEQUIPMENT is the application to capture asset details related to Movable Equipment as per customer requirement.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
           <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to input the ID of the Customer.  Valid input from the CUSTOMER application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to input the CURRENCY in which Customer wants the Asset request Transaction to happen.  Valid entry from the CURRENCY application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>VENDOR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to input the Vendor who delivers or produces the asset. Valid input from the related IS.VENDOR application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>UNIT.PRICE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to input the Unit Price of the Asset in Decimals.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>ASSET.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Description of the Asset procured. Input should be in Alphanumeric.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>ASSET.SHORT.TITLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Short Title of the Asset procured. Input should be in Alphanumeric.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>EQUIPMENT.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the name of the Equipment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>MAKE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field defines the make of the equipment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>MODEL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the model of the equipment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>YR.MANUFACTURE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the year of manufacture of the Equipment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>EQUIPMENT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the type of Property (Ex. OLD or NEW).</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>CTRY.ORIG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Country of Origin for the Equipment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>REGN.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Registration Number of the Equipment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>EMIRATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the place /country where this equipment is to be installed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>INVOICE.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the number of the invoice that has been created for the particular equipment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>REGN.EXP.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the Registration Expiry Date of the Equipment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		   <t>
            <field>PURCHASE.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Purchase Reference of the Asset. This field is automatically updated during authorisation of Purchase transaction. This is a Noinput field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
