<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>IS</product>
        <table>IS.REVIEWER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>IS.REVIEWER is the table to capture the appraisers who valuate the asset. Different kind of Reviewers like Surveyor, Valuator, Appraiser, Adviser, etc. who service in asset appraisal are captured in this table.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the type of review the reviewer will perform. </p>
                <p>The values to the field are defined in the EB.LOOKUP table with prefix "REVIEW".</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Valid values like Appraiser, Surveyor, Adviser should be defined in EB.LOOKUP table as "REVIEW*"</p>
                <p>2. Mandatory field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the Accounts that are used during Payment to the Reviewer. These accounts are defined Company-wise and Currency-wise. When a Payment is initiated, the field credit account gets defaulted from here for the given Reviewer Currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. This is a Mandatory field.</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record in the table ACCOUNT.</p>
                <p>3. The field can accept a valid Account Mnemonic which will be converted to Account Number.</p>
                <p>4. The Account must belong to the Vendor Customer exception being the NOSTRO accounts.</p>
                <p>5. Part of Associated multi-value set COMPANY-BENEFICIARY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BENEFICIARY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the Beneficiary for the Reviewer in case of NOSTRO Payments.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the table BENEFICIARY.</p>
                <p>2. Part of Associated multi-value set COMPANY-BENEFICIARY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMMENTS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Captures comments about the reviewer(if any).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Standard T24 TEXT field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPANY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the list of Company to capture Reviewer accounts in different companies.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the table COMPANY.</p>
                <p>2. Part of Associated multi-value set COMPANY-BENEFICIARY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the currency to identify vendor accounts/beneficiary related to a particular currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. This is a Mandatory field</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record in the table CURRENCY.</p>
                <p>3. Part of Associated multi-value set COMPANY-BENEFICIARY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IS.REVIEWER.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The @ID of the application Identifies a Customer as a Reviewer.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record from the table CUSTOMER.</p>
                <p>2. Customer Mnemonic can be provided which will be converted to Customer Reference.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the Name of the Reviewer. Defaulted as Name of the Customer (@ID being Customer Reference). It can be over-written to specify User-Defined names.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Defaulted as NAME.1 from the Customer table.</p>
                <p>2. Standard T24 Alphanumeric field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user has confirmed during input.</p>
                <p>During Commit, the system may generate a series of screen override messages waiting for User Approval. If the record is subsequently displayed or printed, all override messages are shown in this field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>System generated. Multi-value field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the status of the Reviewer. </p>
                <p>The values to the field are defined in the EB.LOOKUP table with prefix "IS.REVIEWER.STATUS*".</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Valid values are Active, Inactive should be defined in EB.LOOKUP table as "IS.REVIEWER.STATUS*"</p>
                <p>2. Mandatory field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
