<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>IS</product>
        <table>IS.VEHICLE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>IS.VEHICLE is the application to capture asset details of type Vehicle as per customer requirement.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to input the ID of the Customer.  Valid input from the CUSTOMER application</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to input the CURRENCY in which Customer wants the Asset request Transaction to happen.  Valid entry from the CURRENCY application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VENDOR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to input the Vendor who delivers or produces the asset. Valid input from the related IS.VENDOR application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UNIT.PRICE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to input the Unit Price of the Asset in Decimals.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ASSET.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Description of the Asset procured. Input should be in Alphanumeric.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ASSET.SHORT.TITLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Short Title of the Asset procured. Input should be in Alphanumeric.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VEHICLE.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Status of the Vehicle procured (Ex. Old or New).</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>YR.MANUFACTURE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Year of Manufacture of the Asset.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>ENGINE.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Engine Number of the Vehicle.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>CHASSIS.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Chassis Number of the Vehicle.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>CAPACITY.CC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Power of the Vehicle in Cubic Capacity.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	     <t>
            <field>NO.OF.SEATS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the seating capacity of the Vehicle in Numbers.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>MAKE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the manufacturing company (Ex. FIAT,HONDA etc) of the Vehicle.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>MODEL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the model of the vehicle which holds specific features into it.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>COLOR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Colour of the Vehicle.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>USABILITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the usage of the Vehicle (Ex. Personal or Commercial).</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>DEALER.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Dealer Name of the Asset.  Free text input.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>DEALER.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Dealer Code of the Asset.  Free text input.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>REGN.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the number under which the vehicle is Registered.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		 <t>
            <field>REGD.LOC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the place where the vehicle is registered.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INVOICE.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Invoice Number of Bill produced by the Vendor.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>REGN.VALID.TILL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the date upto which the Registration is Valid.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>PURCHASE.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field refers to the Purchase Reference of the Asset. This field is automatically updated during authorisation of Purchase transaction. This is a Noinput field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
