<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>IS</product>
        <table>IS.VENDOR</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>IS.VENDOR is a table to define the registered vendors to perform Islamic Asset Purchase.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the Accounts that are used during Vendor Payment for the Vendor. These accounts are defined Company-wise and Currency-wise. When a Payment to Vendor is initiated through the application IS.PAYMENT, the field VENDOR.ACCT gets defaulted from here for the given Vendor Currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. This is a Mandatory field.</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record in the table ACCOUNT.</p>
                <p>3. The field can accept a valid Account Mnemonic which will be converted to Account Number.</p>
                <p>4. The Account must belong to the Vendor Customer exception being the NOSTRO accounts.</p>
                <p>5. Part of Associated multi-value set COMPANY-BENEFICIARY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BENEFICIARY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the Beneficiary for the Vendor in case of NOSTRO Payments.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the table BENEFICIARY.</p>
                <p>2. Part of Associated multi-value set COMPANY-BENEFICIARY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPANY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the list of Company to capture Vendor accounts in different companies.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record in the table COMPANY.</p>
                <p>2. Part of Associated multi-value set COMPANY-BENEFICIARY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the currency to identify vendor accounts/beneficiary related to a particular currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. This is a Mandatory field</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid record in the table CURRENCY.</p>
                <p>3. Part of Associated multi-value set COMPANY-BENEFICIARY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IS.VENDOR.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The @ID of  the application Identifies a Customer as a Vendor. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Must be a valid record from the table CUSTOMER.</p>
                <p>2. Customer Mnemonic can be provided which will be converted to Customer Reference.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the Name of the Vendor. Defaulted as Name of the Customer (@ID being Customer Reference). It can be over-written to specify User-Defined names.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Defaulted as NAME.1 from the Customer table.</p>
                <p>2. Standard T24 Alphanumeric field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user has confirmed during input.</p>
                <p>During Commit, the system may generate a series of screen override messages waiting for User Approval. If the record is subsequently displayed or printed, all override messages are shown in this field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>System generated. Multi-value field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Status of the Vendor. No transactions are permitted for a Vendor with status as "Inactive".</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory Input.</p>
                <p>2. The values to the field are defined in the EB.LOOKUP table with prefix "IS.VENDOR.STATUS*".</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
