<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>USREGS</product>
<table>CEDD.CUSTOMER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This Application contains Enhanced due diligence and Political information about any "Customer" which the bank has dealings with.</p>
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.EXPOSED</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is used to indicate whether the customer is a politically Exposed person or not.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: It is a Standard T24 Dropdown Button field, Optional Field and Text Field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.POSITION</field>
<desc><p>This field shows political position of politically exposed person.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field, This field is mandatory if the field POLITIC.EXPOSED Person is Yes. Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.TITLE</field>
<desc><p>Shows the political position of the customer. This is mandatory if the field POLITICAL = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character </p></desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>POLITIC.CNTY</field>
<desc><p>Shows the political country of the customer. This field is mandatory field if the field is POLITICAL = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field. Dropdown will show values COUNTRY table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SR.POLITICAL</field>
<desc>
<p> This field is used to indicate whether the customer is a senior political official or not </p>
<p>Validation Rule: It is a Standard T24 Dropdown Button field with values ‘Yes’ and ‘No’, Optional Field. </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.NAME</field>
<desc>
<p>Shows the Name of the political party which customer is a senior official at. This is mandatory if the field SR.POLITICAL = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTY.CNTY</field>
<desc>
<p>Shows the country name of the political party. This field is mandatory field if the field SR.POLITICAL = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field: Dropdown will show values COUNTRY table.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SR.EXECUTIVE</field>
<desc>
<p> This field is used to indicate whether the customer is a senior executive  of the government owned corporation or not </p>
<p>Validation Rule: It is a Standard T24 Dropdown Button field with values ‘Yes’ and ‘No’, Optional Field. </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORP.NAME</field>
<desc>
<p>It shows the name of the government owned corporation, where the customer is a senior executive. This field is mandatory if the field SR.EXECUTIVE = 'Yes' or else this is no input field</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORP.CNTY</field>
<desc>
<p>Shows the country name of the government owned corporation. This field is mandatory field if the field SR.EXECUTIVE = 'Yes' or else this is no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field. Dropdown will show values from COUNTRY table.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.RELATIVE</field>
<desc>
<p> This field is used to indicate whether the senior politically exposed person whom customer is related to or not </p>
<p>Validation Rule: It is a Standard T24 Dropdown Button field with values ‘Yes’ and ‘No’, Optional Field. </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.REL.NAME</field>
<desc>
<p>Shows name of the senior politically exposed person whom customer is related to. This is mandatory if the field POLITIC.RELATIVE = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.REL.CNTY</field>
<desc>
<p>Shows the country name of the senior political person to whom the customer is related. This is mandatory if the field POLITIC.RELATIVE = 'Yes' or else no input field</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field Dropdown will show values COUNTRY table.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field> POLITIC.ASSOCIATE </field>
<desc>
<p> This field is used to indicate whether the senior political person with whom customer has a close association or not </p>
<p>Validation Rule: It is a Standard T24 Dropdown Button field with values ‘Yes’ and ‘No’, Optional Field. </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.ASSOC.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Shows the name of the senior political Person  with whom the customer has a close association. This is mandatory if the field POLITIC.ASSOCIATE = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.ASSOC.CNTY</field>
<desc>
<p>Shows the country to which the senior political person is associated with. This is mandatory if the field POLITIC.ASSOCIATE = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field. Dropdown will show values COUNTRY table.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.ASSOC.REL</field>
<desc>
<p>Describes the relationship of the customer with the senior political person. This is mandatory if the field POLITIC.ASSOCIATE = Yes or else no input.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 15 Alphanumeric Character.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field> POLITIC.CORP </field>
<desc>
<p> This field is used to indicate whether the politically exposed person who is associated with business/ corporation or not </p>
<p>Validation Rule: It is a Standard T24 Dropdown Button field with values ‘Yes’ and ‘No’, Optional Field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.PERSN.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Name of politically exposed person  who is associated with business/ corporation, This is mandatory if the field POLITIC.CORP = 'Yes' or else No input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field, Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POLITIC.PERSN.CNTY</field>
<desc><p>Country of politically exposed person  who is associated with business/corporation. This is mandatory if the field POLITIC.CORP = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field. Dropdown will show values COUNTRY table.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OWNERSHIP.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
<p>Shows the political person’s percentage of ownership in the associated corporation or business. This is mandatory if the field POLITIC.CORP = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:Text Field, Max 3 numeric characters, should be equal to or less than 100.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field> FCY.CORP </field>
<desc>
<p> This field is used to indicate whether the politically exposed person owns corporation (fully or partially) or not </p>
<p>Validation Rule: It is a Standard T24 Dropdown Button field with values ‘Yes’ and ‘No’, Optional Field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FCY.CNTY</field>
<desc>
<p>Shows the foreign country where the politically exposed person owns a corporation (fully or partially). This field is mandatory if field FCY.CORP= ‘Yes’, otherwise it is no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field. Dropdown will show values from COUNTRY table</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FCY.MINISTRY</field>
<desc><p>Shows the name of the particular ministry. This field is mandatory field if the field FCY.CORP = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field, Maximum 20 Alphanumeric Character</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FCY.DEPT</field>
<desc><p>Shows the name of department of the foreign ministry. This field is mandatory field if the field FCY.CORP = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.TYPES</field>
<desc><p>It shows the types of accounts of the customer. Mandatory Field</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field. Multivalued field. Dropdown will show below values from EB.LOOKUP.</p>
<p>				Checking</p>
<p>				Savings</p>
<p>				Time Deposits</p>
<p>				Credit Facilities</p>
<p> 			Investments</p>
<p>				Other</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field> ACCOUNT.OTHER </field>
<desc>
<p> This field shows name of other account type . Mandatory field if the field ACCOUNT.TYPE is Other, Or else No input field</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.SIZE</field>
<desc><p>It shows the anticipated customer account activity amount. Mandatory Field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field. Dropdown will show below values from EB.LOOKUP.</p>
<p>			    - Up to $100,000,</p>
<p>				- More than $100,000 and less than $500,000,</p>
<p>				- $500,000 or more.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.PER.MTH</field>
<desc><p>It shows anticipated number of transactions per month for a customer.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Mandatory Field. Text Field. Dropdown will show below values from EB.LOOKUP.</p>
<p>				- Up to 5</p>
<p>				- More than 5 and less than 15</p>
<p>				- 15 or more</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENTS</field>
<desc><p>It shows any additional comments to be added. Optional Field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 35 Alphanumeric Character</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.CRS.BRD.WIRE</field>
<desc><p>Shows whether the customer expects to be involved in any cross border transfers.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Optional Field. Dropdown Field. Dropdown Button values are 'Yes' and 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.CRS.BRDR.NO</field>
<desc><p>Number of transactions per month for Incoming Cross Border Wires.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 3 numeric Characters. Mandatory if the field IN.CRS.BORDER.WIRE = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.CRS.BRDR.AMT</field>
<desc><p>Amount per incoming cross border transaction.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Standard T24 AMOUNT field Mandatory field if the field IN.CRS.BORDER.WIRES = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.CRS.BRDR.CNTY</field>
<desc><p>Country of Incoming Cross Border Wires transaction.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field.</p>
<p>	   			 Standard T24 COUNTRY field.</p>
<p>				 Mandatory if the field IN.CRS.BORDER.WIRE = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUT.CRS.BRD.WIRE</field>
<desc><p>It shows whether the customer expects to do Outgoing cross border activities.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Optional Field.</p>
<p>     			Dropdown Field.</p>
<p>				    Dropdown Button values are 'Yes' and 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUT.CRS.BRD.NO</field>
<desc><p>Number of transactions per month for Outgoing Cross Border Wires.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Maximum 3 numeric Characters </p>
<p>				 Mandatory if the field OUT.CRS.BORDER.WIRE = 'Yes' or no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUT.CRS.BRD.AMT</field>
<desc><p>Amount of outgoing cross border transaction.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field.</p>
<p>				 Standard T24 AMOUNT field.</p>
<p>				 Mandatory if the field OUT.CRS.BORDER.WIRE = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUT.CRS.BRD.CNTY</field>
<desc><p>Country of Outgoing Cross Border Wires transaction, Dropdown Field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Standard T24 COUNTRY field.</p>
<p>			        Mandatory if the field OUT.CRS.BORDER.WIRE = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.TRANS</field>
<desc><p>It shows whether the customer expects to perform cash transactions.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Optional Field.</p>
<p>				    Dropdown Field</p>
<p>				    Dropdown Button values are 'Yes' and 'No'</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.TRANS.PER.MTH</field>
<desc><p>Anticipated number of cash transactions per month</p>
<p>Validation Rule:  Text Field. Max 4 numeric characters</p>
<p>				  Mandatory field if the field CASH.TRANS = 'Yes'.</p>
<p>				  No input field if the field CASH.TRANS = 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.TRANS.AMT</field>
<desc><p>Anticipated amount per cash transaction</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field</p>
<p>				 Standard T24 AMOUNT field.</p>
<p>				 Mandatory field if the field CASH.TRANS = 'Yes'.</p>
<p>				 No input field if the field CASH.TRANS = 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ACH.TRANS</field>
<desc><p>It shows whether customer anticipates conducting international ACH transactions.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Optional Field.</p>
<p>				 Dropdown Field.</p>
<p>				 Dropdown Button values are 'Yes' and 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ACH.TRANS.NO</field>
<desc><p>Number of transactions per month for International ACH transactions.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Max 4 numeric characters</p>
<p>				 Mandatory if the field INT.ACH.TRANS = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ACH.TRANS.AMT</field>
<desc><p>Amount of transactions per month for International ACH transactions.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field.</p>
<p>				 Standard T24 AMOUNT field.</p>
<p>				 Mandatory if the field INT.ACH.TRANS = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTRUMENTS</field>
<desc><p>Shows whether the customer expects to conduct transactions in monetary instruments.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Optional Field.</p>
<p>				 Dropdown Field.</p>
<p>				 Dropdown Button values are 'Yes' and 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTRUMENTS.NO</field>
<desc><p>Number of transactions per month for Monetary Instruments.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Text Field. Max 4 numeric characters. </p>
<p>				 Mandatory if the field INSTRUMENTS = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTRUMENTS.AMT</field>
<desc><p>Transaction amount on monetary instrument</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>				 Standard T24 AMOUNT field.</p>
<p>				 Mandatory if the field INSTRUMENTS = 'Yes' or else no input field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.FINANCE</field>
<desc><p>It shows whether customer expects any trade finance activity.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Optional Field.</p>
<p>				 Dropdown Field.</p>
<p>				 Dropdown Button values are 'Yes' and 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.COLL.LOANS</field>
<desc><p>It shows whether the customer expects to do cash or marketable securities collateralized loans.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Optional Field.</p>
<p>				    Dropdown Field.</p>
<p>				    Dropdown Button values are 'Yes' and 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KYC.EXEMPT</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to indicate whether the customer is exempt from KYC process or not. Mandatory Field.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Dropdown Field. Dropdown values are 'Yes' and 'No'.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KYC.EXEMPT.REASON</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is used to indicate the reason for customer being exempt from KYC process.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:	Mandatory if the field KYC.EXEMPT = 'Yes'. Dropdown Field. The dropdown values are from EB.LOOKUP</p>
<p>			1 customer was acquired through a business combination (merger or acquisition).</p>
<p>			2 customer's only account with the institution was opened for the purpose of participating in an employee benefit plan established under ERISA.</p>
<p>			3 customer is a financial institution.</p>
<p>			4 customer is a government agency.</p>
<p>			5 customer is a publicly-held company.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXMPT.REV.DATE</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to indicate the date when customer exemption was reviewed last time.</p>
<p>Validation Rule: Mandatory field if the field KYC.EXEMPT = 'Yes'. Date Field. Standard T24 Date Field.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>
