<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>REG.PROGRAMS.SUMMARY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>REG.PROGRAMS.SUMMARY is an LIVE template, which gives the complete details about the 
all the programs/routines avaliable in the System. It gives the details like Product, 
Program type, Total calls, Application from where the program is called from, Number
of calls made in the program/routine and also gives the details about the program source
called from. With the help of this application we can get the complete details about the 
programs/routines regressed in each Regression cycle.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.CALLS.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field gives the details about the program from which the Source program is called from.
(Source here refers the program defined in the ID of the record).</p>
            <p>Any Alphanumeric characters are allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CALLS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the count of number of times the program/routine is being called from the specified
Product( i.e the Product defined in the ID of the record).This field value is the summation of multi 
value field NO.OF.CALLS</p>
            <p>This field allows Numeric Input or Specified Input by Table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>With the help of this field, we can identify the product to which the program/routine belong to.</p>
            <p>This field allows Numeric Input or Specified Input by Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROGRAM.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the program type. The program/routine may fall under any of the following types.
INBUILD ROUTINES, INSERT.FILES, ENQUIRY.ROUTINES, CONVERSION.ROUTINES, DAS.ROUTINES, TEST.ROUTINES,
SELECT.ROUTINES, LOAD.ROUTINES or FILTER.ROUTINES.</p>
            <p>This field allows Numeric Input or Specified Input by Table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALLED.FROM.APPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the Application name from which the routine is being called</p>
            <p>Any Alphanumeric characters are allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.CALLS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the count of number of times the program/routine is called from each application.</p>
            <p>It checks for the application (from where the program/routine is called from) in the record already stored in the 
REG.PROGRAMS.SUMMARY file, if applictaion found, then this field count will be incremented by one.</p>
            <p>This field allows Numeric Input or Specified Input by Table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.RTN.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the unique ID to identify the record created under this file.Any alphanumeric characters are allowed.</p>
            <p>The ID of the Regression Programs summary file is the combination of Product name and program/routine name</p>
            <p> PRODUCT*PROGRAM/ROUTINE NAME.</p>
            <p>E.g.,AA*AA.ACTIVITY.CHARGES.CALCULATE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

