<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SCRIPT.REPOSITORY.INTERFACE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The interface can be used to upload scripts from User Area to Script Repository or to download scripts from Script Repository to User Area. Repository is stored in a designated area in server 24 (grepos), which is hard coded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The upload/download involves two activities:</p>
            <p>   SELECTION ACTIVITIY</p>
            <p>   1. To be executed (by Verifying a user defined record) in the user Area for Upload</p>
            <p>   2. To be executed (by Verifying a user defined record) in the Repository for Download</p>
            <p />
            <p>   UPDATE ACTIVITY:</p>
            <p>   1. To be executed (by Verifying a user defined record) in the Repository for Upload</p>
            <p>   2. To be executed (by Verifying a user defined record) in the User Area for Download</p>
            <p />
            <p>   For Uploading Scripts:</p>
            <p>   1. Complete the Selection Activity for upload in User Area. This will select the records and transfer them to an outside folder in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   2. Log in to the Repository with the same user/password and complete the Update Activity for upload. This will transfer the contents of the folder to the intended files.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   For Downloading Scripts:</p>
            <p>   1. Complete the Selection Activity for download in Repository (grepos). This will select the records and transfer them to an outside folder in User Area</p>
            <p>   2. Log in to the User Area with the same user/password and complete the Update Activity for download. This will transfer the contents of the folder to the intended files.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   As users can upload stand alone records in SEAT.SCRIPTS, SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY, SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES, SEAT.SCRIPT.FIELD.VALUES and SEAT.SCRIPT.FORMAT.OUTPUT  alone, any linkages between them need to be ensured by them for correct uploading of scripts and for checking results.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the status on the files and the number of records transferred from the user and repository area during the upload and download action, Also holds the error status when the upload or download action is not successful.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWNLOAD.USERNAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates area name of the Destination User Area while downloading scripts from the Repository. The fields DOWNLOAD.USERNAME does not have any meaning while uploading scripts to Repository. The inputs are required to be furnished in the Repository area during Selection Activity while downloading scripts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWNLOAD.PASSWORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the password of the Destination User Area while downloading scripts from the Repository.The fields DOWNLOAD.PASSWORD does not have any meaning while uploading scripts to Repository. The inputs are required to be furnished in the Repository area during Selection Activity while downloading scripts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FTP.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the status of the file transfer while uploading and downloading scripts from the user and repository area.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The values to be matched for the given Operand. Works with OPERAND for selecting records from SEAT.SCRIPTS. Can be used without Operand if the selection is to be done on SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY, SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES, SEAT.SCRIPT.FIELD.VALUES and SEAT.SCRIPT.FORMAT.OUTPUT</p>
            <p />
            <p> The possible values in this field are ids of SEAT.SCRIPTS, SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY, SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES, SEAT.SCRIPT.FIELD.VALUES, SEAT.SCRIPT.FORMAT.OUTPUT or any valid entry in SEAT.TESTBASE.</p>
            <p />
            <p> The SEAT.TESTBASE id is used only when the ACTION is RELEASE.SPLITTER.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPOSITORY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>A free text field, any alphanumeric character allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Operand to be used for selection criteria. Meant to be used for selecting scripts from SEAT.SCRIPTS based on fields on SEAT.SCRIPTS.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid Inputs are:</p>
            <p> EQ, LIKE and UNLIKE</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to select records from SEAT.SCRIPTS (SST) and other associated applications viz, SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES (RF), SEAT.SCRIPT.FIELD.VALUES (FV), SEAT.SCRIPT.FORMAT.OUTPUT (SSFO), SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY (SSA)  based on Record ID’s or to select records based on contents on the fields in SEAT.SCRIPTS </p>
            <p />
            <p> Use SSA.ID for selection on SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY</p>
            <p> Use RESULT.FILE.ID for selection on SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES</p>
            <p> Use FIELD.VALUE.ID for selection on SEAT.SCRIPT.FIELD.VALUES</p>
            <p> Use SSFO.ID for selection on SEAT.SCRIPT.FORMAT.OUTPUT</p>
            <p />
            <p> Use other values for selecting records from SEAT.SCRIPTS based on contents on the respective fields.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid inputs are:</p>
            <p> SSA.ID, SSFO.ID, BASE.RELEASE, PRODUCT.GROUP, PRODUCT.CODE, SCRIPT.GROUP, APPLICATION, FUNCTION, COMPANY.CODE, SCRIPT.SOURCE, SCRIPT.ID, RESULT.FILE.ID, FIELD.VALUE.ID.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates what needs to be done with the selection.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Use UPLOAD.SSA, UPLOAD.SCRIPTS, UPLOAD.RF, UPLOAD.FV, UPLOAD.SSFO, UPLOAD.ALL, DOWNLOAD.SSA, DOWNLOAD.SCRIPTS, DOWNLOAD.RF, DOWNLOAD.FV, DOWNLOAD.SSFO and DOWNLOAD.ALL for Selection Activity.</p>
            <p>   Use  UPLOAD.TO.MASTER and DOWNLOAD.FROM.MASTER for Update Activity.</p>
            <p>   Use RELEASE.SPLITTER for downloading scenarios with results Test Base wise, generally intended for Regression Execution.</p>
            <p>   Valid Inputs are:</p>
            <p>   UPLOAD.SSA, UPLOAD.SCRIPTS, UPLOAD.RF, UPLOAD.FV, UPLOAD.SSFO, UPLOAD.ALL, DOWNLOAD.SSA, DOWNLOAD.SCRIPTS, DOWNLOAD.RF, DOWNLOAD.FV, DOWNLOAD.SSFO, DOWNLOAD.ALL, UPLOAD.TO.MASTER, DOWNLOAD.FROM.MASTER, RELEASE.SPLITTER</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   a. SSA.ID ALL UPLOAD.ALL Selects all SSA, linked SST, linked RF, linked FV and linked SSFO in User Area</p>
            <p>   b. SSA.ID ALL UPLOAD.SSA Selects all SSA in User Area</p>
            <p>   c. SSA.ID List of IDs as Sub Value UPLOAD.ALL Selects given SSA, linked SST, linked RF, linked FV and linked SSFO in User Area</p>
            <p>   d. SSA.ID List of IDs as Sub Value UPLOAD.SSA Selects given SSA in User Area</p>
            <p>   e. SCRIPT.ID ALL UPLOAD.ALL Selects all SST, SSA that has the SST in multi-value, RF linked to those SSA, FV/SSFO linked to those RF. Will fail if SSA multi-value count does not add up SST Count.</p>
            <p>   f. SCRIPT.ID ALL UPLOAD.SCRIPTS Selects all SST in User Area</p>
            <p>   g. SCRIPT.ID List of IDs as Sub Value UPLOAD.ALL Selects given SST, SSA that has the SST in multi-value, RF linked to those SSA, FV/SSFO linked to those RF. Will fail if SSA multi-value count does not add up SST Count.</p>
            <p>   h. SCRIPT.ID List of IDs as Sub Value UPLOAD.SCRIPTS Selects given SST in User Area</p>
            <p>   i. RESULT.FILE.ID ALL UPLOAD.ALL Selects all RF, linked FV and linked SSFO in User Area</p>
            <p>   j. RESULT.FILE.ID ALL UPLOAD.RF Selects all RF in User Area</p>
            <p>   k. RESULT.FILE.ID List of IDs as Sub Value UPLOAD.ALL Selects given RF, linked FV and linked SSFO in User Area</p>
            <p>   l. RESULT.FILE.ID List of IDs as Sub Value UPLOAD.RF Selects given RF in User Area</p>
            <p>   m. FIELD.VALUE.ID ALL UPLOAD.FV Selects all FV in User Area</p>
            <p>   n. FIELD.VALUE.ID List of IDs as Sub Value UPLOAD.FV Selects given FV in User Area</p>
            <p>   o. SSFO.ID ALL UPLOAD.SSFO Selects all SSFO in User Area</p>
            <p>   p. SSFO.ID List of IDs as Sub Value UPLOAD.SSFO Selects given SSFO in User Area</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   BLANK BLANK UPLOAD.TO.MASTER Transfers all the given records to the respective files in Repository</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   a. SSA.ID ALL DOWNLOAD.ALL Selects all SSA, linked SST, linked RF, linked FV and linked SSFO in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   b. SSA.ID ALL DOWNLOAD.SSA Selects all SSA in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   c. SSA.ID List of IDs as Sub Value DOWNLOAD.ALL Selects given SSA, linked SST, linked RF, linked FV and linked SSFO in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   d. SSA.ID List of IDs as Sub Value DOWNLOAD.SSA Selects given SSA in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   e. SCRIPT.ID ALL DOWNLOAD.ALL Selects all SST, SSA that has the SST in multi-value, RF linked to those SSA, FV/SSFO linked to those RF. Will fail if SSA multi-value count does not add up SST Count.</p>
            <p>   f. SCRIPT.ID ALL DOWNLOAD.SCRIPTS Selects all SST in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   h. SCRIPT.ID List of IDs as Sub Value DOWNLOAD.ALL Selects givenl SST, SSA that has the SST in multi-value, RF linked to those SSA, FV/SSFO linked to those RF. Will fail if SSA multi-value count does not add up SST Count</p>
            <p>   g. SCRIPT.ID List of IDs as Sub Value DOWNLOAD.SCRIPTS Selects given SST in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   h. RESULT.FILE.ID ALL DOWNLOAD.ALL Selects all RF, linked FV and linked SSFO in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   i. RESULT.FILE.ID ALL DOWNLOAD.RF Selects all RF in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   j. RESULT.FILE.ID List of IDs as Sub Value DOWNLOAD.ALL Selects given RF, linked FV and linked SSFO in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   k. RESULT.FILE.ID List of IDs as Sub Value DOWNLOAD.RF Selects given RF in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   l. FIELD.VALUE.ID ALL DOWNLOAD.FV Selects all FV in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   m. FIELD.VALUE.ID List of IDs as Sub Value DOWNLOAD.FV Selects given FV in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   n. SSFO.ID ALL DOWNLOAD.SSFO Selects all SSFO in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p>   o. SSFO.ID List of IDs as Sub Value DOWNLOAD.SSFO Selects given SSFO in Repository (grepos)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   BLANK BLANK DOWNLOAD.FROM.MASTER Transfers all the selected records to the respective files in User Area</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any valid description that describes the action.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWNLOAD.DIR.PATH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWNLOAD.IP.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the IP Address of the Destination User Area while downloading scripts from the Repository. The fields DOWNLOAD.IP.ADDR does not have any meaning while uploading scripts to Repository. The inputs are required to be furnished in the Repository area during Selection Activity while downloading scripts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

