<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SCRIPT.INTERFACE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Seat Scripts can be copied from various areas by the respective unit testers in to a Stage area where they are maintained. For doing such upload or while downloading scripts from a Master area to our unit area for testing, the SCRIPT.INTERFACE utility can be used.</p>
            <p>  The Scripts to be uploaded can be Selected using selection criteria and the SELECTED.IDS can be uploaded.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the operand to be used with the associated selection field, the operands used are EQ,LK and UL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value of the selection field to be checked while doing selection criteria.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field from the Seat Scripts template to be used for making the selection criteria while copying the scripts during upload/download. The fields that are used from seat scripts are ALL, BASE.RELEASE, PRODUCT.GROUP, PRODUCT.CODE, REGRESSION.CYCLE, SCRIPT.GROUP, APPLICATION, FUNCTION, SCRIPT.ID, FLD.NAME, SEAT.ID, COMPANY.CODE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTED.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Refer to the selected Script ID’s that were selected while doing a Selection of Scripts during the Action SELECT.SCRIPTS which would be further used during Upload of scripts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This refers to the Action that has to be performed for the selected scripts. The various actions that could be performed are SELECT.SCRIPTS, UPLOAD, DOWNLOAD, EXTRACT.REPORT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FTP.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No Input field that will get updated by the System with a description of the FTP login status when an incorrect login name or password is given in the Script Interface Parameter file. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERFACE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the identification of a record created under this file. Any Alphanumeric characters are allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No input field updated by the system with the Description of the status of the UPLOAD/DOWNLOAD being performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

