<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SCRIPT.INTERFACE.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This Application holds the Pre defined details of Upload and Download areas for Script Interface. The details include the area Name, Password and the path of the directory to which the Script records has to be uploaded and downloaded respectively.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No-input field released with the Username of the upload area</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.IP.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No-input field that is released with the Server IP address of the upload area</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERFACE.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the parameter file that holds the details of Upload and downloads areas. The only record and the allowed ID for this is SCRIPT.INTERFACE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.PATH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No-input field released with the Upload path to which the scripts were to be copied.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.PASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No-input field released with the Password of the upload area</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWNLOAD.IP.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No-input field released with the Server IP address of the download area</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWNLOAD.PASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No-input field released with the Password of the Download area</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWNLOAD.PATH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No-input field released with the download path to which the scripts were to be copied.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWNLOAD.USER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No-input field released with the Username of the Download area</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

