<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SEAT.SCRIPT.FIELD.VALUES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Application to define the fields with their expected results for the system to check the data against the actual values created during upload.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FLD.BASE.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the Base Release of the script, which is updated from the SEAT.SCRIPTS record.This field can have any Alphanumeric characters </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCRIPT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Can be a valid ID specified in the field FLD.DEFN.ID of application SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES. Also , can be of the form SYSTEM*FILE.NAME*RECORD.ID*COB.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPECTED.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It should be in any of the following formats:</p>
            <p>     1. Accepts values within brackets i.e. (150000) means that the expected result is the difference of the previous value and the current value of that field. Example, CLOSING.BAL.NOM field in SECURITY.POSITION which is a cumulative value and not an absolute one.</p>
            <p>     2. Values enclosed by "~"</p>
            <p>     For example:</p>
            <p>     FIELD.NAME: TRANSACTION.IDS</p>
            <p>     EXPECTED.VALUE: ~DXTRA0033500004.100322.1 250~</p>
            <p>     What ever is present between ~ needs to be located in the FIELD.NAME</p>
            <p>     This field can have a maximum of 35 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.RECORDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the number of instances of this record in the file that are similar to the field values defined.</p>
            <p>This field can have any Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>No-Input Field with a maximum of 16 characters. Will contain the mnemonic of the file . </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.MODIFIED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will get populated with the Date on which the SEAT.SCRIPT.FIELD.VALUES reocrd was modified and uploaded to the master. This is an NOINPUT field. </p>
            <p>Only Dates can be defined as value for this field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the RECORD ID during the upload. No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Actual value during getting updated during upload. No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONCAT.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field can be set to 'Y', when we needs to check the TABLE type files,such that we can ignore the checks for standard selection Table type template files. </p>
            <p>This field can be set to 'Y' or 'N' as value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will get updated with the Date on which the SEAT.SCRIPT.FIELD.VALUES record was created and uploaded to the master. This is an NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Only Dates can be defined as value for this field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value can be "Y" or null. Once "Y" is entered  while cross validation stage if the EXPECTED.VALUE field is blank it will copy the ACTUAL.VALUE to EXPECTED.VALUE field.</p>
            <p>  Up to 16 characters of input will be accepted, leading spaces, trailing spaces and duplicated embedded spaces will be removed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESULT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. Incase of any error this field will be populated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>A Valid field name, which hold the script in OFS Syntax. Refers to the field name and the field, multi-value or sub-value position.</p>
            <p>   Multi value or sub value positions can be in  the format FIELD.NAME:FIELD.VALUE</p>
            <p>   For example:</p>
            <p>   FIELD.NAME: TX.PRICE:(TRANSACTION.IDS:DXTRA0033500004.100322.1 250):1 </p>
            <p>   Which means that the multi-value position for TX.PRICE needs to be picked up by locating DXTRA0033500004.100322.1 250 in the field TRANSACTION.IDS. The bracket is  only for clarity</p>
            <p>   Up to 65 characters of input will be accepted, leading spaces, trailing spaces and</p>
            <p>   duplicated embedded spaces will be removed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.TAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No input field that will get updated with value as NEW when a Script is uploaded in to the Master area.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free text as description.</p>
            <p>  Between 3 and 35 characters allowed, no special editing will be done.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDEX.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field has to be set if the field sepcified in the FIELD.NAME is to be used as a selection criteria.When a field values with index fields set to Yes is attached to SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES, the REC.ID.MAP on the result files needs to be set to 'INDEX'.</p>
            <p>This field can be set to 'Y' or 'N' as value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>RESULT.FILE.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
