<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SEAT.AUTO.COMPARE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a verify template which is used to create a comparison routine. The details of the comparison defined are picked fron this template and on verification, a subroutine will be generated accordingly to execute the comparisons.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FILE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should be a valid ID for the file specified. The file id should be specified within double quotes. Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESULT.ACTUAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value in this will be accepted only if the value in the field OPERATION is SUM. Value should be specified if a range is to be summed up . Should be of the form – Start Position : End Position , where Start &amp; End positions are numbers delimited by ‘:’. Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLD.TO.FIND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value in this will be accepted only if the value in the field OPERATION is FIND. A valid field name of the file where system will try to match the given value to retrieve the position. Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the image to be picked. Values allowed are BEFORE, AFTER based on which the image is picked. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used,If a range is to be summed up.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEAT.DEF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any id with Alpha - numeric values. The comparison routine will be formed with this ID in TEST.BP. Upto 35 characters are allowed with a minimum of 3 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Mandatory field. The operand number that stores the value in the variable OPER followed by Operand.No in the routine.Upto 10 characters are allowed.  Eg: OPER1, OPER2 are various operands used in the generated routine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the comparison operation on the expressions.The values currently allowed are EQ,NE,GT,GE,LT,LE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESULT.EXP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should contain the expected result. The user can give values within quotes or can use any EXP.NUMBER (Numeric) as the expected result.Will be returned for updating the SEAT.RESULTS. Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The values allowed are FIRST,LAST,SUM,MAX,MIN or FIND.FIRST – Get the first value in the field.</p>
            <p> LAST – Get the last value in the field.</p>
            <p> SUM – Get the sum of the values in the field.</p>
            <p> MAX – Get the maximum value in the field.</p>
            <p> MIN – Get the minimum value in the field.</p>
            <p> FIND – Here we can do three types of FIND</p>
            <p> a) To simply get the position – We can give a value to be compared in the field VAL.TO.FIND and any of these values ‘NO’, ‘AL’, ‘AR’, ‘AN’, ‘DL’, ‘DR’, ‘DN’  in the field FLD.TO.FIND. System will then return the position accordingly.</p>
            <p> b) To get the value of a matching position – Here we give a value to be compared (VAL.TO.FIND) as well as a field where we have to compare (FLD.TO.FIND). On matching, system will get the value from the same position in the field FIELD.NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPARE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid Comparison Name. Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONNECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value that can be given is EXTN. Setting EXTN implies that the current operand number expects some value which is derived in the following multi values. In case we are unable to define a operand completely in a single multi-value set, the value can be derived from the extended multi-value sets with same operand number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This should have a numeric value that is an expression number which is formed by various operands. Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field should contain the expression number to be compared. It should be a valid EXP.NUMBER which is defined already .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPER.OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The values allowed are ADD and SUBT.Operation that can be performed on the operands. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAL.TO.FIND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value in this will be accepted only if the value in the field OPERATION is FIND. The value which is to be searched in FLD.TO.FIND is to be entered in this field.User can even give a hard-coded value within double quotes.Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should be a valid file name. Mandatory input . Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPER.PART.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Corresponding Operand Number that forms this expression . Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid field name in the file.Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESULT.REASON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reason for the failure can be written in words here.Upto 35 characters are allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULT.ID.OPER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Possible values are ADD and SUBT. This field is used if many id's are chosen. In case more than one record is processed, then we have to specify here the relation between them – to Add or Subtract</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

