<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application stores all the scripts that constitute a scenario. It stores the Common Regression Test Bed on which the scenarios to be regressed and also the result files meant for the Regression Test Bed. It also stores the outcome of the scenario when the scripts are regressed. Thus, records the activity associated with the scripts under each scenario. There will be one record per scenario.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESULT.FILES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the ID of SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES that has to be considered for validating the results. </p>
            <p>   Validation:</p>
            <p>   The contents shall be a valid record in SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES. Populated by the system when a record is created in SEAT.SCRIPT.RESULT.FILES with the same ID as that of SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY. Generally shall be the ID of the SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY. But when separate result files need to be defined for different test bases,  can contain a suffix that is a valid record in SCRIPT.TESTBASE.  The suffix, if present, will be validated against the contents in TEST.BASE field. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUFFIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>System updated field. Multi-value Field.  Whenever a record in SEAT.SCRIPTS is authorized, this field will be populated with the suffix of the SEAT.SCRIPTS record. </p>
            <p />
            <p>   For example : If the SEAT.SCRIPTS SCRPT100920502503-201 is uploaded system will update the value 201 in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Initially will be input by the user with ACTIVE. If any error is encountered during Regression Run, will be updated with ERROR.  Scripts with Status equal to ACTIVE will only be considered for upload.  The Status is applicable for all the scripts under the ID. There is no provision to select single scripts. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Will be updated only for the first error in the script sequence. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid values are:</p>
            <p>  ACTIVE – Will be considered for single or bulk upload</p>
            <p>  PENDING, ANALYSIS, HOLD – Indicates that product teams are working on the Scenario and therefore, the scripts will NOT be considered for upload</p>
            <p>  ERROR – Indicates the scenario has encountered an error.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  REG.SETUP – A status indicates that the error is on account of Regression Static Base.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  REG.ERROR – A status indicates that the error is not anything to do with the scripts or results. It is Regression error and therefore needs to be resolved by Regression team before next upload.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>A free text filed provided for recording resolution of an error.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPONENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use to update the Components exercised by the System when the Scenario is executed. A valid entry in EB.COMPONENT table.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any meaningful description that describes the scenario.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.TRACE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the details of error that was encountered while execution the script. Whenever an error is encountered, contents will be appended if the CURRENT.RELEASE field in SYSTEM Record in SPF file indicates that it is build. Will be overwritten otherwise.  Error will indicate whether the error has been encountered during upload or during result check.</p>
            <p>   Noinput field. Updated by system.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTIONALITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid record in SEAT.FUNCTIONALITY.COMPONENT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEST.BASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid record in SEAT.TESTBASE. Indicates the test base, for which the scenario has been created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCRIPT.ACTIVITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>System updated when a Seat Script is authorized. The ID shall be a valid record in SEAT.SCRIPTS without the suffix.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   For example: If the SEAT.SCRIPTS SCRPT100920502503-201 is authorised and it is first script in the scenario system will update the ID as SCRPT100920502503.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>PRODUCT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
