<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SEAT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>SEAT means System Engineering Automated Testing.It is is available for testing both technical and functional aspects of T24.The overall objective is to build an Automated Testing System is that,which helps to manage the testing inputs (Scripts) and Evaluate the test results by:</p>
            <p />
            <p> Setting-up and managing a library of Test Cases (SEAT Scripts) which can be injected on every T24 build (any shipment from System Engineering).</p>
            <p> And</p>
            <p> Call test routines (on the technical infrastructure available from SEAT) to evaluate the results for each transaction generated out of SEAT scripts. These test routines would be self assessing (checks the test results and updates exceptions in a file)</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description about the routine. Accepts any alpha numeric characters with a minimum of 3 to 32 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUTINE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid inputs are SPECIFIC or GENERIC. Indicates the type of the routine. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RTN.BASE.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should contain the base release from which the routine can be executed. Should be of the format Rxx. Eg: R08.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEAT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of test (routine to call) . Accepts any alpha numeric characters and a maximum of 60 characters may be entered</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.TESTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this is defined then this test is actually a group of SEAT.IDs to be invoked. If not defined then this is an actual test – routine to call . Accepts any alpha numeric characters and a maximum of 32 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

