<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SEAT.FUNCTIONALITY.COMPONENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The application contains names of virtual test bases. A virtual test base is a set of static scripts that are run on top of Test Base with Stand Alone Static set up.  Several such Test Bases can be created for each component or a group of components which can be uploaded on Static Test Base on Stand Alone basis. For example, if one decides to regress the component on ACCOUNT CLOSURE, a record ACCOUNT.CLOSURE can be created in the application. Then create a set of scripts with necessary static data (which can run independently on a Common Regression Test Bed) and mark them as ACCOUNT.CLOSURE in the field FUNCITIONALITY .ID of the application SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY.  This will help select all the scripts pertaining to the referred to functionality and use them for Regression. </p>
            <p> To be read in conjunction with SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY Application</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates a valid record in SEAT.PRODUCT.GROUP</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPONENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the component that the functionality comprises. A valid entry in EB.COMPONENT Table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A meaningful description which describes the functionality component</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTIONALITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free Text . Will be used in SEAT.SCRIPT.ACTIVITY  to indicate which functionality that the designated scenario seeks to cover.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTIONALITY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>A two digit number that describes the ID. This two digits number may be used as a part of Script ID so that scripts for this functionality can be identified. No validation with Script ID envisaged.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

