<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SEAT.EVENT.MANAGER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>SEAT.EVENT.MANAGER is a table to specify SEAT ids to manage events that could happen for a contract. An event could mean any function/COB job that affects the contract. Basically it is an API for SEAT to decide on the routines that needs to be called for each transaction depending on the function/COB process.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SEAT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will hold the SEAT ID, if more than one routine needs to be triggered, then a scenario id (with a prefix ‘SID.’) can be created in SEAT with the sub test routines attached. Mandatory field, up to 60 characters of input will be accepted, leading spaces, trailing spaces and duplicated embedded spaces will be removed .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any id – typically should describe the type of transaction input.  Mandatory field, up to 35 characters of input will be accepted, leading spaces, trailing spaces and duplicated embedded spaces will be removed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the description about the event created. Mandatory field, up to 35 characters of input will be accepted, leading spaces, trailing spaces and duplicated embedded spaces will be removed .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Can be a valid function INPUT, INPUT-AUTH, INPUT-MOD, AUTH-MOD, INPUT-DEL, REV-DEL, REV-AUTH, AUTH-REV or a COB process name. COB Process name should in the format PROCESS*JOB.NAME for e.g. BNK/LD.END.OF.DAY*LD.END.OF.DAY4. Mandatory field, up to 60 characters of input will be accepted, leading spaces, trailing spaces and duplicated embedded spaces will be removed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JOB.ID.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>For COB jobs, the job id need not necessarily be the contract id – it could be a related id. For example for an loan contract – the id to the cob job could either be an LD.ID or a LMM.ACCOUNT.BALANCES id. This routine can be specified optionally to build such ids for the job. If this routine is not specified – the contract.id would be passed to the job. Up to 35 characters of input will be accepted, leading spaces, trailing spaces and duplicated embedded spaces will be removed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

