<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>SEAT.PERFORMANCE.SUMMARY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The Seat Performance Summary is an verify template, developed to take the Seat Performance report This report can be generated when SEAT is set with the PERFORMANCE option. i.e the OP.CONSOL field in SPF is set to 'PERFORMANCE' option</p>
            <p>With the help of SEAT.PERFORMANCE.SUMMARY, we can generate reports like File Details, Program Details, Total Regression Summary, Compiler Rating Summary, Seat routines count, Used seat routines, Seat scripts count, Worst 100 records, Best 100 records.With the help of these reports, we can get the complete details about the routines and files regressed in Regression Cycle.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PERFORMANCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the unique ID to identify the records through which the reports are generated.</p>
            <p>Any Alphanumeric characters are allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUMMARY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field SUMMARY.TYPE refers to the type of report, that we are going to 
generate using Performance Summary application.This is an mandatory field. Only the following options can used to generate seat performance summary report.</p>
            <p>1. REG.FILES.STATIC - This option is used to create records in REG.FILES.SUMMARY application with the fields TOTAL.READS, TOTAL.UPDATES set to '0' for all the files in available in the SYSTEM. </p>
            <p>2. REG.FILES.DETAILS - This option will updates the following fields TOTAL.READS, TOTAL.UPDATES, NO.OF.READS, NO.OF.WRITES, NO.OF.DELETES, READ.PROGRAMS, WRITE.PROGRAMS, DELETE.PROGRAMS in the records already created in REG.FILES.SUMMARY application to give the complete details about the files regressed in each Regression Cycle.</p>
            <p>3. REG.PROGRAMS.STATIC - This option is used to create records in REG.PROGRAMS.SUMMARY application with the fields PRODUCT, PROGRAM.TYPE, TOTAL.CALLS for all the programs/routines in available in the SYSTEM. </p>
            <p>4. REG.PROGRAMS.DETAILS - This option will updates the fields CALLED.FROM.APPS and also increment the TOTAL.CALLS field in the records already created in REG.PROGRAMS.SUMMARY application, gives the complete details about the programs/routines regressed in each Regression Cycle. </p>
            <p>5. REGRESSION.SUMMARY - This option is used to generate report 'PROGRAMS.SUMMARY' which gives the details about number of Programs/routines available in the System and that has been regressed in the Regression cycle.Similarly it also creates a report called 'FILES.SUMMARY', which gives the details about the total number of files available in the system and that has been regressed in each Regression cycle.</p>
            <p>6. COMPILER.RATING.SUMMARY - THis option is used to generate a report called 'COMPILER.RATING', which holds the details about all the routines in the system along with this compiler ratings.</p>
            <p>7. WORST.100 - This option is used to generate reports WOSRT.IO, AVERAGE.IO which holds the  worst 100 (Transaction/Process) across applications based on the TOTAL.IO in seat results file and average IO of that 100 records. </p>
            <p>8. TOTAL.SEAT.ROUTINES - This option generates reports called 'TOTAL.SEAT.ROUTINES, TOTAL.SEAT.ROUTINES.PRODUCT', which holds all the STEST routines and that available under each product group.</p>
            <p>9. USED.SEAT.ROUTINES - This option is used to generate reports USED.SEAT.ROUTINES.PRODUCT and USED.SEAT.ROUTINES, which gives the details about number of routines triggered in each product group and the routines itself.</p>
            <p>10. SEAT.SCRIPTS.COUNT - This is used to generate the report 'SST.COUNT.MODULE', which holds the counts of number of scripts available under each product and in each script group. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

