<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>UI.CREATE.SCRIPTS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table when defined with the details of Mapping record, defaults the objects to be created which when verified along with the object values will create the necessary Scripts compatible to be from a QTP Session.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DATATABLE.PATH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the path of the excel when the values required for the objects needs to be taken from an external source excel.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.ITERATIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts a numeric value and hold the number of Iterations the Script needs to be run.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the standard Functions that are available and will be applied to the script being created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the Transaction ID of the application for which Script is being created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the standard field name of the application defined in the APPLN.NAME and will be defaulted when an application name is entered and validated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALIDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field when defined with a value YES would include a validate operation to be performed for the application in the Script being generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a Standard Descriptive field that holds the description of the Workflow being scripted for.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UI.SCRIPT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID field that holds the Script ID with the format UISCRXXXXXXXXXX.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OBJ.MAP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds a UI.OBJ.MAPPING ID for which Scripts will be created.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the a Valid T24 Version name for the defined Application name.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the values for the Fields defined or can be defined to be picked from an Excel.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.OPER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be defined with the Selection criteria operand for Enquiry type of Mapping .Input not allowed for Object mappings other than Enquiry.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field holds the name of the Enquiry while creating               Enquiry Scripts.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLN.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the name of a standard T24 Application name.Input is allowed for Contract type of Mapping for which Application names are mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPTURE.IMAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPTURE.IMG.PATH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATED.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the Author name of the Script.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OBJECT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the standard object names that would be defaulted for the given Field names as per the Mapping being defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCRIPT.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the Script Group to which the created Script belongs to.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

