<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SE</product>
<table>UI.SCRIPT.CHECKS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows to define various checks related to Objects in the Browser Screen relating to an application for checking Enrichments, Overrides,defaulted field values,Comparison of Field values etc.</p>
            <p>In the defined workflow in UI.CREATE.SCRIPTS template,Script Checks can be defined with sequence no for the Contract type of Mapping alone. For E.g. When we have defined CONTRACT type of Mapping in second Multivalue for the UI Script ID UISCR0000000001, UI.SCRIPT.CHECKS can be created for UISCR0000000001-02 with checks.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>UI.SCR.CHKS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Refers to the ID of UI.SCRIPT.CHECKS application.  The ID of this holds the ID of UI.CREATE.SCRIPTS application along with a Sequence No, where the Sequence number refers to the multi value number of the UI.CREATE.SCRIPTS record for which a Contract type of Mapping is defined. Error message for Invalid ID would be thrown when the sequence no defined is for other than Contract type of mapping scenarios.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the No of options that a particular field can have if defined as a default for the defined Field name.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The expected Override Message is entered and at runtime the script will measure the Overrides produced and measure it against the content in this field exactly, a true match will result in a pass and a mismatch will result in a failure both of which will be registered by QTP. This field allows the use of a wildcard “*” at the end of the expected Override to allow any content after the selected string to be allowed as a pass.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Error in the Result field must be selected in order to check whether the expected  error message is occured at runtime of the script.A true match will result in a pass and a mismatch will result in a failure both of which will be handled by internal functions and displayed by QTP Results.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENRICHMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field is used to define the enrichment value for the field name defined which would be checked to have populated correctly in the Screen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the description of the UI Object that would be used in identifying the object class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.DEFINED.FUNCTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field is used to define a User defined VB Function that can be included in the Script for the Browser Screen when a validate is being performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESULT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Mandatory field with two options, the Commit option is used with a script that is expected to commit successfully, a positive test case if you will, this will then test to run a check on the Txn.Complete message. The Error option is used when a test wants to measure error messages produced in a script that does not commits successfully and used the next field Err.Message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPARE.FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be input with a valid field which would be checked with its value at runtime with the value of the field defined in Field name.The matching values will result in a pass otherwise a fail will be registered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the field value that needs to be checked for the field name given while the script is being run.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Descriptive field that holds the description of the checks for the scripts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.HEADERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field is used to define the Enquiry Headers that would be used by internal functions to check for the existence of appropriate Headers of the enquiry to have present on the screen. While creating Enquiry Scripts, these Headers will be populated by default in INAU record which upon verification can be authorised.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

