<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LI.LIMIT.DEFINE.PRIORITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p>This Application is used to setup the order in which group and individual limits of the customer are to be utilised when a transaction is done for the customer.
</p>
        <p>When there is no priority defined then Individual limit will have first priority and group limits will be utilised in the order they have created.
</p>
        <p>Customer can be a part of one or more groups with multiple customers in such case priority to the customer can be set using this application. During recalculation, allocation of the limits will be done according to the priority of the customer in ascending order.
</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to define the priority of the customer, Group Limits Utilisation will recalculate based on this Priority.
</p>
        <p>When there is no priority denoted for the customer then default priority will be customers sorted in ascending order.
</p>
        <p>Validations:
</p>
        <p>Any numeric Value up to three digits.
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Customer to whom priority has to be defined
</p>
        <p>Validations:
</p>
        <p>Valid Customer key who is a part of LIMIT.SHARING.GROUP
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to define the order in which Group and Individual limits have to be utilised when a transaction is done for the customer.
</p>
        <p>Validations:
</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Valid reference from LIMIT.SHARING.GROUP in which customer is a part or the keyword “OWN” is accepted.
</p>
            <p value="2">The keyword “OWN” is to indicate that the individual Limit is not prioritised first as default; it will be used based on the priority specified here.
</p>
            <p value="3">Duplication not allowed.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t><field>CUSTOMER.NO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
