<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LI.RISK.COLLAT.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to set up the parameters required to print the customer risk collateral report. </p>
            <p>This file contains information like risk codes, risk exposure percentages, narratives, collateral codes, narratives &amp; percentages, posting restrict for collateral accounts and forex limit product code. The order in which the risk codes and collateral codes are input in this file decides the order in which the codes will be printed in the reports. </p>
            <p>Functions (I)nput, (C)opy, (L)ist, (P)rint, (R)eversal and (S)ee functions are available. </p>
            <p>This file should contain only one record with  record id as "SYSTEM". </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.RISK.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields RISK.CODE to LL.RISK.NARR form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique identifier for the parameters required for the Risk Collateral Report. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 type A (alphanumeric characters). (Mandatory input.)  Allowed value - "SYSTEM".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the risk code to be printed. </p>
            <p>This risk code is associated with fields Risk Percentage &amp; Risk Narr. While printing the Risk Collateral report for each customer, the risk codes are printed in the order as they appear in this record. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:      Valid limit products should end with 00. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input.)  Multi value field associated with RISK.PERCENTAGE to RISK.NARR.</p>
            <p>Should either be a valid product code defined in LIMIT REFERENCE file or should be one of the following codes:        a)  ODNL - Indicates overdrafts for accounts not connected                  with Limits        b)  ULFX - Unrealised loss for FOREX.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.COLAT.NAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Fields COLLAT.CODE to LL.COLAT.NAR form a related multi value set. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.PROD.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the product code(s) associated with FOREX limits. </p>
            <p>While processing the limit files, FOREX product codes need to be processed differently from other products. This field identifies the product codes associated with FOREX. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-4 numeric characters ending with 00.  Multi value field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record id in the file LIMIT.REFERENCE.</p>
            <p>Must end with 00.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Percentage to be applied to the risk amount under this particular risk code while calculating Net exposure for any customer. </p>
            <p>This field indicates the percentage to be applied to the risk amount calculated under the risk code specified in RISK.CODE in order to arrive at the Net exposure amount across all risk codes for any customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 3 numeric characters in the range between 0 &amp; 100.  Multi value field associated with RISK.CODE and with RISK.NARR.  (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the narrative to be printed for the corresponding risk code (RISK.CODE). </p>
            <p>While printing the Customer Risk Collateral report, the narrative corresponding to each risk code is picked up from this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 32 type a (alphanumeric) characters.  Multi value field associated with language. Associated with field RISK.CODE to RISK.PERCENTAGE.  (Mandatory Input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLAT.NAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the narrative to be printed for the corresponding COLLAT code. </p>
            <p>While printing the Customer Risk Collateral report, the narrative corresponding to each Collat code (COLLAT.CODE) is picked up from this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 32 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multi value field associated with language. Associated with field COLLAT.CODE to COLLAT.PRCNTG. (Mandatory Input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLAT.ACCT.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the posting restriction which identifies collateral accounts. </p>
            <p>Collateral accounts are identified by using this field. </p>
            <p>Those accounts whose posting restriction field matches with any one of the values specified in this field are considered as collaterals. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid id of the POSTING.RESTRICT file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLAT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Collat code to be printed. </p>
            <p>This Collat code is associated with fields Collat Percentage &amp; Collat Narr. While printing the RISK Collateral report for each customer, the Collat codes are printed in the order as they appear in this record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input.)  Multi value field associated with COLLAT.PRCNTG to COLLAT.NARR.</p>
            <p>Should either be a valid collateral code defined in LIMIT COLLATERAL file or should be one of the following codes:        a)   CLIL - Indicates Collateral accounts associated with                   limits.        b)   CLNL - Collateral accounts that do not have any                   corresponding limit reference.        c)   CRIL - Accounts with positive balances But are not                   collateral and associated with limits.        d)   CRNL - Accounts with positive balances which are not                   collateral and do not have any limit links.        Note: Limit product codes 9700, 9800 &amp; 9900 are also             considered as valid collateral codes. But in order to             distinguish from collateral codes of the same values,             these codes should be entered as 97LL, 98LL or 99LL             respectively.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLAT.PRCNTG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Percentage to be applied to the Collat amount under this particular Collat code while calculating Net collateral for any customer. </p>
            <p>This field indicates the percentage to be applied to the Collat amount calculated under the Collat code specified in COLLAT.CODE in order to arrive at the Net Collateral amount across all COLLAT codes for any customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 3 numeric characters in the range between 0 &amp; 100.  Multi value field associated with COLLAT.CODE and with COLLAT.NARR. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

