<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.CROSS.USAGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This live table is updated for each PRODUCT Limit input for a Liability Customer in a Cross Limit structure. It is  used by </p>
            <p>T24</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />for creating/modifying new Limit records.  <p /><p>This table is with a ID of  'Liability Customer ID.PRODUCT Limit Reference ID'. </p><p /><p>In this table for each PRODUCT Limit (based on sequence no.), it  records   the CROSS  and SUB-PRODUCT Limits defined  as well as the next CROSS Limit that could be input. </p><p /><p>It also records  the next  Sequence No. that could be used while inputting a new  PRODUCT Limit.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SEQ.NOS.USED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Sequence nos. used for SUB-PRODUCT Limits in a Cross Limit structure.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System updated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NXT.PROD.LINK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.SEQ.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Sequence Number for the PRODUCT Limit in a Cross Limit structure.</p>
            <p>For example, if the Record ID is 500101.1800 and the value of PRODUCT.SEQ.NO.is 01, then the associated fields would store details for the PRODUCT  Limit 500101.1800.01.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System updated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.LIMITS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the IDs of  SUB-PRODUCT Limits used in a Cross Limit structure.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>System     updated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NXT.CROSS.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ID of the next CROSS Limit that could be  input   in a Cross Limit structure. </p>
            <p>For example, if the Record ID is 500101.1800,  value of  PRODUCT.SEQ.NO .is 01, and NXT.CROSS.LIMIT is 500101.1803.01, then the next CROSS Limit that could be input in the Cross Limit structure for the PRODUCT limit 500101.1800.01 would be 500101.1803.01. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System updated field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CROSS.LIMITS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the IDs of CROSS Limits used in a Cross Limit structure.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System updated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID  is of the format "Liability Customer ID.PRODUCT Limit Reference ID" for a PRODUCT Limit input in a Cross Limit structure.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System updated field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.PROD.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.SEQ.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the next sequence no. for input of a  PRODUCT Limit  in a Cross Limit structure for the PRODUCT  Limit specified in the record ID.</p>
            <p>For example, if the Record ID is 500101.1800 and the value of  NEXT.SEQ.NO.is 05, then the next PRODUCT Limit that would  be allowed to be  input in the Cross Limit structure would be 500101.1800.05.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System updated field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

