<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.RANGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used to define ranges or lists of currency or company codes. The data specified can be used to restrict the use of particular limit records. </p>
            <p>Records can be defined for either COMPANY or CURRENCY, and may be specified as a list of values, or a series of ranges. These records can be utilised on the LIMIT record in the fields ALLOWED.CCY, RESTRICTED.CCY, ALLOWED.COMP, RESTRICTED.COMP. </p>
            <p>It will allow setting up of "standard", often used or vitual views as a help or short cut in the Limit definition process. (eg. certain limits may be valid only for EEC currencies, so a record grouping the currencies in question can be defined). </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System field, no input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the start value for a range of values. </p>
            <p>This field together with END.VALUE allows ranges of CURRENCY or COMPANY codes to be specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-9 alpha numeric characters Multi value field Optional Input</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as COMPANY, the value can be input as the 2-3 character company mnemonic, or the full 9 character company code.</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as COMPANY, the company should be a financial company. Branches are not allowed.</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as CURRENCY, the value can be input in standard currency format.</p>
            <p>The value must be greater than the END.VALUE in the last multi value set.</p>
            <p>Both DISCR.VALUE and a range of values (using START.VALUE and END.VALUE) cannot be specified together.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System field, no input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the key to LIMIT.RANGE file. </p>
            <p>LIMIT.RANGE records cannot be reversed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-20 Alpha-numeric characters Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMP.OR.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the record is to define CURRENCY or COMPANY codes. </p>
            <p>This field cannot be changed once the record is authorised. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>CURRENCY or COMPANY or any abbreviation thereof. Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the record. </p>
            <p>This field will be used for the screen enrichment of the LIMIT.RANGE key specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 35 Alpha-numeric characters. Multi language field Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISCR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Discrete values of COMPANY or CURRENCY codes. </p>
            <p>This field defines discrete values of either CURRENCY or COMPANY (whichever is defined in COMP.OR.CCY). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-9 Alphanumeric characters Multi value field Optional input</p>
            <p>No duplicate codes allowed</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as COMPANY, the value can be input as the 2-3 character company mnemonic, or the full 9 character company code. The company code must exist on the COMPANY file.</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as COMPANY, the company should be a financial company. Branches are not allowed.</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as CURRENCY, the value can be input in standard currency format, and must exist on the CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>Both DISCR.VALUE and a range of values (using START.VALUE and END.VALUE) cannot be specified together.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the end value for a range of values. </p>
            <p>This field together with START.VALUE allows ranges of CURRENCY or COMPANY codes to be specified. </p>
            <p>Reserved for future use. Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-9 Alpha numeric characters. Multi value field Optional Input System field, no input. FIELD7   RESERVED1 System field, no input</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as COMPANY, the value can be input as the 2-3 character company mnemonic, or the full 9 character company code.</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as COMPANY, the company should be a financial company. Branches are not allowed.</p>
            <p>If COMP.OR.CCY is specified as CURRENCY, the value can be input in standard currency format.</p>
            <p>The value must be greater than or equal to the associated START.VALUE in the multi value set.</p>
            <p>Both DISCR.VALUE and a range of values (using START.VALUE and END.VALUE) cannot be specified together. FIELD6   RESERVED2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

