<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Within this file are defined parameters which determine the way in which the Limit system operates. These are as follows: </p>
            <p>1.         An indicator to specify whether Foreign Exchange            contracts are, or are not, to be netted before Limit            comparison. </p>
            <p>2.         A 'number of days' to define how many days prior to Limit            Expiry Date and Limit Review Date the approach of these            events is to be reported. </p>
            <p>3.         A date and cycle to indicate when the first revaluation            will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>4.         A date and cycle to indicate when a full Central Liability            report (including those Liability numbers which did not            move) need to be produced in the back-end process. </p>
            <p>5.         A date and cycle to indicate when the Commodity,            Country and Currency reports must be produced. </p>
            <p>6.         A number of days (administrative extension days) which            defines the maximum number of days by which the expiry            date of a limit can be "administratively" extended before            a new expiry date is reassigned to the limit. 7.         The Limit product definition according to the specific            requirements of the Bank.  The most important feature of            this file is that it allows the user, for each Financial            Application, to define the precise rules applicable to his            environment.  In this way, the Limit verification process            can be established by the user according to his own set            of rules without any program maintenance. </p>
            <p>8.         The product group definition which will allow the user to            specify which are the different products which in his            opinion must be part of the Commodity, Country and            Currency exposure. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXT.LIMIT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The limit reference for correspondent banks for the above application. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No two applications can share the same reference.</p>
            <p>Numeric field with a maximum length of 5.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.CURRENCY.EXP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Date and Cycle to indicate when the first full Currency exposure report will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency code.  Input may be a date followed by a cycle or the cycle by itself in which case the system will automatically generate the next report date. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Input of a frequency without a date is allowed.</p>
            <p>Input of a date without a frequency is not allowed.</p>
            <p>The following frequency formats are allowed:- W followed by 1 to 9 (e.g. W3 - every 3 weeks) D (Daily) M followed by 01 to 99 followed by 1 to 31 (e.g. M0309 - every 3 months on the 9th). T (twice a month).</p>
            <p>If a date is not input, it is calculated depending on the current date as follows:- D     -  Today Wn    -  Yesterday + 7 * n days T     -  15th of current month if today is less than the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month. Mnndd -  Day number dd in current month + nn months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPIRIES.REPORTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines how many days prior to Limit EXPIRY DATE the approach of this event is to be reported. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters in the range 1 to 99. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.MULTIPLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Included in G14.0.00)</p>
            <p>When this field is set to yes then at the time of inputting a contract for the customer, the validation would check for all the possible matches, find whether there are any Limit records in existance.  If only one is available then it will be defaulted at the LIMIT.REFERENCE of the contract.  If there are more than one, the user is shown the choices thorough a drop-down list attached to the field LIMIT.REFERENCE in respective contract (eg: LD Contract). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed Values are Yes, No or NULL</p>
            <p>Default is NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMODITY.EXP.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Date and Cycle to indicate when the first Commodity exposure report will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency code.  Input may be a date followed by a cycle or the cycle by itself in which case the system will automatically generate the next report date. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Input of a frequency without a date is allowed.</p>
            <p>Input of a date without a frequency is not allowed.</p>
            <p>The following frequency formats are allowed:- W followed by 1 to 9 (e.g. W3 - every 3 weeks) D (Daily) M followed by 01 to 99 followed by 1 to 31 (e.g. M0309 - every 3 months on the 9th). T (twice a month).</p>
            <p>If a date is not input, it is calculated depending on the current date as follows:- D     -  Today Wn    -  Yesterday + 7 * n days T     -  15th of current month if today is less than the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month. Mnndd -  Day number dd in current month + nn months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.OPERANDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>(added from G14.0.00)</p>
            <p>Specifies the type of DECISION which the user wants to perform on the field defined in the previous field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The following values will be accepted: EQ = Equal  LK = Like  GE     = Greater or Equal  LT = Less than   LE = Less or     Equal   UL = Unlike   GT = Greater than   NE =     Not Equal </p>
            <p>Multivalue field associated with fields 44.1  to 47.1</p>
            <p> Input of  EQ only is allowed if the hard-coded filter values are     used</p>
            <p>The hard coded filter values are CHECK.EXPIRED, CHECK.AVAILABLE.FUNDS,     CHECKAVAILABLE.MARKER, CHECK.DRAW.DATE, CHECK.CUST.RESTRICT,     CHECK.CURRENCY.RESTRICT, CHECK.COMPANY.RESTRICT</p>
            <p>For any relevant field from LIMIT application is used in the field     FILTER, then any operand compatible to the field can be used </p>
            <p>Default value: None.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.OUTSTANDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether, or not, Foreign Exchange  contracts are netted before comparison with the respective Limit. </p>
            <p>If 'no netting' is chosen, the full value of the transaction is compared with the Limit to ensure that the transaction will not cause an excess. If 'netting' is chosen, the System will net transactions in opposite sense which involve the same two currencies, which are for the same Liability Number and which mature on the same date. </p>
            <p>For example, suppose the following two transactions are in the System:- </p>
            <p>      Buy  USD 100,000   Sell        GBP  70,000   Value   31/12/86       Sell GBP  35,000   Buy         USD  50,000   Value   31/12/86 </p>
            <p>If 'no netting' is requested, and the Limit is 150,000 US Dollars, after the first transaction, 50,000 US Dollars is available.  After the second transaction, the Limit is reduced by the US Dollar equivalent (according to the latest on-line middle rate) of 35,000 GB Pounds.  If this gives a figure of 50,000 US Dollars, the Limit availability is reduced to zero. </p>
            <p>If 'netting' is specified, the second transaction is subtracted from the first (100,000 US Dollars minus the middle rate equivalent of 35,000 GB Pounds), giving a net equivalent value of 50,000 US Dollars. This is then subtracted from the Limit to give an available figure of 100,000 US Dollars. </p>
            <p>It should be noted that the Limit System always uses the same side of Foreign Exchange transactions (the bought side) for all calculations. Apart from the currency, the sold side is always ignored. </p>
            <p>Note: It is important to note that the value of this field must be defined at installation.  Once the value has been  authorised, it can only be changed through LIMIT.CHANGE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>N for no netting or   Y for netting. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Application for which the user wants to create specific Limit products. Only Financial Type Applications will be allowed in this field. </p>
            <p>For all Financial Applications (eg Loans, Money Market, Accounts, Foreign Exchange etc), T24 allows the user to define the Limit products according to his own requirements. The definition of these various Limit products will be done by Application using the association of the multivalue Fields 13 to 18. Whenever Market conditions change or the Bank's management decides to reorganise their Limit control, a simple maintenance in this table will automatically allow and take care of such changes in the Limit verification process. </p>
            <p>It is also possible to specify a suffix after the application separated by a "-" character. This will allow sub-products to be defined for a particular application, so that more than 1 limit refererence can be defined for an application. </p>
            <p>For example the application SL.SYNDICATED.LOANS may require 2 limit references, for the underwritten portion and the agent participation. The following could be defined: </p>
            <p>APPLICATION SL.SYNDICATED.LOANS PRODUCT NO 4000 </p>
            <p>This is the overall for the SL application and will default 4000 as the limit reference </p>
            <p>APPLICATION SL.SYNDICATED.LOANS-UNDERWRITE PRODUCT.NO 4100 </p>
            <p>The reference 4100 will be used for undewritten limits </p>
            <p>APPLICATION SL.SYNDICATED.LOANS-AGENT PRODUCT.NO 4200 </p>
            <p>The reference 4200 will be used for the AGENT portion. </p>
            <p>The order for defaulting is as follows: 1 APPLICATION-suffix with specific conditions 2 APPLICATION-suffix default 3 APPLICATION with specific conditions 4 APPLICATION default </p>
            <p>The suffix used by applications when defaulting limit references is hard coded if required. To find if an application requires a suffix consult the application documentation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any valid Application name (1 to 25 characters) where the         PGM.TYPE has a suffic equal to '.NOH' ie that it         represents a 'Financial' application. Multivalue field         associated with Fields 14 to 18.</p>
            <p>The Application entered in this field must be a valid         Application in PGM.FILE.</p>
            <p>The PGM.TYPE of the Application (except ACCOUNT) must         have a suffix of '.NOH' ie it must relate to an         Application with financial figures.</p>
            <p>At least a 'Default' definition will be mandatory for         each Application entered in this multivalue field. The         default of an Application will be recognised by the fact         that the PRODUCT NO has been entered in Field 14.1 while         the Fields 15.1.1 to 18.1.1 have been left blank.</p>
            <p>Duplicates of the same Application name will only be         allowed when the fields 'DECIS FIELD' to 'DECISION TO '         have been defined with different values.</p>
            <p>A suffix may be supplied separated by a "-"         character. When supplied a default condition must exist         for the suffix, as well as a definition for the         application without suffix as the overall default.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.REV.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the Review Frequency on the LIMIT requires an associated frequency or not. </p>
            <p>Entry in this field will currently have no effect in the system, it will be activated at a later date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or N (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Included from G14.0.00)</p>
            <p>Specifies the value, or start of a range of values, with which the contents of the field indicated in Filter (Field 44.1) are to be compared.</p>
            <p>Note: The values input in this field and the next must be in agreement with the Format rules of the element specified in Field 44.1 FILTER  FIELD. If, for example, the input in FILTER field is from the hard-coded values as below, then only YES will be allowed in this field:</p>
            <p>CHECK.EXPIRED,     CHECK.AVAILABLE.FUNDS, CHECK.AVAILABLE.MARKER, CHECK.DRAW.DATE, CHECK.CUST.RESTRICT, CHECK.CURRENCY.RESTRICT, CHECK.COMPANY.RESTRICT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters Multivalue field associated with Fields     44 to 47.    </p>
            <p> Input should be YES  when FILTER field above has been defined with     any one of the hard-coded values mentioned above   </p>
            <p>Otherwise input should be compatible with the fields of LIMIT     record.    </p>
            <p> Default value: None   </p>
            <p>Input must begin and/or end with 3 dots when DECISION = 'LK' or 'UL'.   </p>
            <p>Input for the other FILTER values (eg GE, EQ,LE, etc) will be checked     according to the rules defined in the corresponding APPLICATION. </p>
            <p> It must be     noted, however, that no check will be performed for the Local reference     fields.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.FID.DEPOSIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default Limit Reference to be used for Money Market fiduciary deposits. </p>
            <p>If no specific fid deposit product is defined for Money Market Fid deposits, this will be used as the default. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 or 4 digit Limit Reference</p>
            <p>Must exist on LIMIT REFERENCE with a Value of 'DP' in FX.OR.TIME.BAND.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field introduced in G13.2</p>
            <p>Routine for processing the  outstanding calculation of  the Forex sub-product Limit reference specified in the associated field LIMIT.REFERENCE. </p>
            <p>If the associated LIMIT.REFERENCE field is Null, then the specified Routine will be used for calculating the outstanding for all FX sub-product Limit references.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only the following core routine will be allowed:</p>
            <p>          CALC.FX.PROFIT.LOSS (From G13.2)</p>
            <p>          FX.LIMIT.NETTING.I (From G14.1)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the end of a range of values with which the contents of the field indicated in FILTER (Field 44.1) are to be compared.</p>
            <p>Note: The values input in this field and the previous one must be in agreement with the format rules of the element specified in Field 44.1 FILTER. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters Multivalue field associated with Fields     44 to 47.    </p>
            <p> Optional input when DECISION = 'EQ' or 'NE'; otherwise input not     allowed.   </p>
            <p>The value entered into this field must be greater than the value entered     in the field DECISION FR.   </p>
            <p>It may only be input if corresponding Data comparison (Field 45.1 FILTER)     contains EQ (Equal) or NE (Not Equal to).</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COU.PROD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies which country limit products are part of the group defined in the previous field. </p>
            <p>Note:      The check of duplicates and no mix is only done at the            sub-value level.  It is possible, for example, to define            LOANS, MONEY MARKET and as a 3rd Product Group            'LOANS + MONEY MARKET'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 4 numeric LIMIT REFERENCE ID. Sub value field. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Input must be a valid ID on the LIMIT.REFERENCE file.</p>
            <p>Duplicates will not be allowed.</p>
            <p>Mix of Product No and Sub Product No will not be allowed i.e. it is possible to define 100 or 101, 102 etc... but not both.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field introduced in G13.2</p>
            <p />
            <p>The Forex Limit Reference ID for which the outstanding processing would be done as per routine attached  in the  field FX.ROUTINE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The field     could be null, in which case the attached routine would apply to all     FX  sub-product Limit References.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid      Fx Limit.Reference ID with field FX.OR.TIME.BAND set to FX.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Only     sub-product Limit References are allowed. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Duplicate     values are not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Limit product number (ie LIMIT.REFERENCE number) for which the user wants to define a Limit control within the Application entered in the previous field. </p>
            <p>For all Financial Applications (eg Loans, Money Market,            Accounts, Foreign Exchange etc), T24 allows the            user to define the Limit products according to his own            requirements.  The definition of these various Limit            products will be done by Application using the association            of the multivalue Fields 13 to 18.  Whenever Market            conditions change  or the Bank's management decides to            reorganise their Limit control, a simple maintenance in            this table will automatically allow and take care of such            changes in the Limit verification process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 to 4 numeric characters Subvalue field. Input mandatory when the field APPLICATION has been defined; otherwise not allowed. No default value</p>
            <p>The PRODUCT.NO must be a valid ID on the LIMIT.REFERENCE file.</p>
            <p>Input in this field will only be allowed when the APPLICATION has been defined in Field 13.1.</p>
            <p>This table will allow the input of a valid product number eg 100,200 ... 9600 or a valid sub-product number eg 101, 102, 103 etc.</p>
            <p>Definition of product numbers together with sub-product numbers will not be allowed.  Either the user chooses to enter 101,102, 103 etc... or, 100, 200 ... 9600.</p>
            <p>The product or sub-product number will be checked in connection with application and field FX.OR.TIME. BAND in the LIMIT.REFERENCE table as follows:  .   The application 'FOREX' must have the field FX.OR.TIME. BAND' with a value = to 'FX'. .   The application 'ACCOUNT' must have the field 'FX.OR.TIME. BAND' without input. .   The application FD.FIDUCIARY must have the field FX.OR.TIME.BAND with a value of 'IN' or 'TB'. -   The application FD.FID.ORDER must have the field 'FX.OR.TIME.BAND' with a value of 'DP' .   Other Applications must have the field 'FX.OR.TIME.BAND' with a value equal to 'TB' (i.e. Time band possible) or null.</p>
            <p>For  Limit References in a Cross Limit structure, only the    SUB-PRODUCT Limit References  (value of CROSS.LIMIT is PROD in the   LIMIT.REFERENCE record) would be allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.LIMIT.APP</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>A valid application in </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MAX.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Field Added in G14.1)</p>
            <p>This field indicates which amount (INTERNAL or ADVISED) mentioned in the LIMIT is to be considered for calculation of  UNUTIL.LIMIT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Accepted Values are INTERNAL and ADVISED</p>
            <p>Default is INTERNAL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.DEPOSIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default Limit Reference to be used for Deposit contacts in Money Market and Loans and Deposits. </p>
            <p>If no specific deposit product is defined for Money Market or Loans and Deposits, this will be used as the default rather than the default specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 or 4 digit LIMIT Reference (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on LIMIT REFERENCE with a Value of 'DP' in FX.OR.TIME.BAND.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.CLL.REPORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Date and Cycle to indicate when the first full Central Liability Ledger report (i.e. including the non moved Liability numbers) will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency code.  Input may be a date followed by a cycle or the cycle by itself in which case the system will automatically generate the next report date. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Input of a frequency without a date is allowed.</p>
            <p>Input of a date without a frequency is not allowed.</p>
            <p>The following frequency formats are allowed:- W followed by 1 to 9 (e.g. W3 - every 3 weeks) D (Daily) M followed by 01 to 99 followed by 1 to 31 (e.g. M0309 - every 3 months on the 9th). T (twice a month).</p>
            <p>If a date is not input, it is calculated depending on the current date as follows:- D     -  Today Wn    -  Yesterday + 7 * n days T     -  15th of current month if today is less than The 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month. Mnndd -  Day number dd in current month + nn months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the user wants rates specified in the field CONVERT. RATE in limit references to be effective in the revaluation of limit outstanding when the limit and transaction are in different currencies. A value of 'Yes' in this field will mean that the the limit outstanding will be revalued online and in batch processing using the rate type specified in the field CONVERT. RATE in LIMIT. REFERENCE. When the value is  'No' the limit outstanding will be revalued at mid rate irrespective of any rate type specified in the field CONVERT. RATE in LIMIT. REFERENCE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory.</p>
            <p>Value allowed Yes or No.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFLT.NOSTRO.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Idenfifies the limit reference which will be assigned to nostro balances for inclusion in country, commodity and currency reporting. </p>
            <p>Processing for country, commodity and currency exposure reporting is based on outstandings reported in the limit main file. To include nostro accounts in these reports a default or "dummy" limit reference is required. </p>
            <p>Please note that any valid LIMIT REFERENCE ID is accepted, but the reference number used should logically be the one for nostros. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 4 numeric valid LIMIT.REFERENCE id. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.PRODUCT.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies a mnemonic to group together various currency limit products.  These groups will then be input in the LIMIT.CURRENCY file to specify the content of the Currency exposure report. </p>
            <p>In the LIMIT.CURRENCY file, the user will be requested to enter one or various of these groups to specify what type of limit product must be included in the currency exposure report. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-15 characters type MNEMONIC. Multivalue field. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>The user will be forced to define at least one group.</p>
            <p>Duplicates are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.PRODUCT.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies a mnemonic to group together various commodity limit products.  These groups will then be input in the LIMIT.COMMODITY file to specify the content of the commodity exposure report. </p>
            <p>In the LIMIT.COMMODITY file, the user will be requested to enter one or various of these groups to specify what type of limit product must be included in the commodity exposure report. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-15 characters type MNEMONIC. Multivalue field. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>The user will be forced to define at least one group.</p>
            <p>Duplicates are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>(Included from G14.0.00)</p>
            <p>When more than one limit is available to the customer, then this field is used to filter out the limits that can be used based on the certain conditions.  </p>
            <p>There are some hard coded filter conditions such as:</p>
            <p>CHECK.EXPIRED: If this is given, then from the available limits to the customer, the expired limits will be filtered out.</p>
            <p>CHECK.AVAILABLE.MARKER: If this is given, then from the available limits to the customer, the limits where the AVAILABLE.MARKER is set to NO will be filtered out.</p>
            <p>CHECK.DRAW.DATE: If this is given, then from the available limits to the customer, the limits which had crossed LAST.DRAW.DATE will be filtered out</p>
            <p>CHECK.CUSTOMER.RESTRICT:  If this is given, then  the available limits to the customer will be checked for ALLOWED.CUST and RESTRICTED.CUST fields and filter out the limits accordingly</p>
            <p>CHECK.CURRENCY.RESTRICT: If this is given, then  the available limits to the customer will be checked for ALLOWED.CCY and RESTRICTED.CCY fields and filter out the limits accordingly.</p>
            <p>CHECK.COMPANY.RESTRICT: If this is given, then  the available limits to the customer will be checked for ALLOWED.COMP and RESTRICTED.COMP fields and filter out the limits accordingly</p>
            <p>Apart from the above hard coded filter fields, we can use any of the fields in LIMIT application in this field for filtering out the LIMIT record of the customer that we wish to use for the transaction.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Associated Multi-value fields from 44.1 to 47.1</p>
            <p>Default value is Null</p>
            <p>The above Hard-coded values can be given as it is shown</p>
            <p>Apart from these, any relevant field from LIMIT record can be used</p>
            <p>Default is blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.EXP.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Date and Cycle to indicate when the first Currency exposure report will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency code.  Input may be a date followed by a cycle or the cycle by itself in which case the system will automatically generate the next report date. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Input of a frequency without a date is allowed.</p>
            <p>Input of a date without a frequency is not allowed.</p>
            <p>The following frequency formats are allowed:- W followed by 1 to 9 (e.g. W3 - every 3 weeks) D (Daily) M followed by 01 to 99 followed by 1 to 31 (e.g. M0309 - every 3 months on the 9th). T (twice a month).</p>
            <p>If a date is not input, it is calculated depending on the current date as follows:- D     -  Today Wn    -  Yesterday + 7 * n days T     -  15th of current month if today is less than the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month. Mnndd -  Day number dd in current month + nn months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of DECISION which the user wants to perform on the field defined in the previous field. </p>
            <p>For all Financial Applications (eg Loans, Money Market,            Accounts, Foreign Exchange etc), T24 allows the            user to define the Limit products according to his own            requirements.  The definition of these various Limit            products will be done by Application using the association            of the multivalue Fields 13 to 18.  Whenever Market            conditions change  or the Bank's management decides to            reorganise their Limit control, a simple maintenance in            this table will automatically allow and take care of such            changes in the Limit verification process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The following values will be accepted: EQ = EqualLK = Like GE = Greater or EqualLT = Less than LE = Less or Equal UL = Unlike GT = Greater than  NE = Not Equal Multivalue field associated with fields 13 to 18. Input mandatory when input has been done in DECIS FIELD; otherwise input not allowed.  Default value: None.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECISION.FR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value, or start of a range of values, with which the contents of the field indicated in DECIS.FIELD (Field 15.1.1) are to be compared. </p>
            <p>For all Financial Applications (eg Loans, Money Market,            Accounts, Foreign Exchange etc), T24 allows the            user to define the Limit products according to his own            requirements.  The definition of these various Limit            products will be done by Application using the association            of the multivalue Fields 13 to 18.  Whenever Market            conditions change  or the Bank's management decides to            reorganise their Limit control, a simple maintenance in            this table will automatically allow and take care of such            changes in the Limit verification process. </p>
            <p>Note:           The values input in this field and the next must be                 in agreement with the Format rules of the element                 specified in Field 15.1.1 DECIS FIELD.  If, for                 example,  the input in DECIS FIELD corresponds                 to a category code, a maximum input of 5 numeric                 characters will be allowed in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters Multivalue field associated with Fields 13 to 18. Input mandatory when DECISION has been defined. Otherwise input not allowed. Default value:  None</p>
            <p>Input must begin and/or end with 3 dots when DECISION = 'LK' or 'UL'.</p>
            <p>Input for the other DECISION values (eg GE, EQ,LE, etc) will be checked according to the rules defined in the corresponding APPLICATION.  It must be noted, however, that no check will be performed for the Local reference fields.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.LIMIT.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The routine to be run to update the correspondent bank limits table for the above application. LIMIT.CHECK invokes this routine.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should have a valid entry in PGM.FILE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECIS.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies, together with fields 16-18, which condition(s) have to be met by a financial transaction to be verified and checked under the limit PRODUCT.NO (field 14.1) specified for the corresponding APPLICATION (Field 13.1). </p>
            <p>For all Financial Applications (eg Loans, Money Market,Accounts, Foreign Exchange etc), T24 allows the user to define the Limit products according to his own requirements. The definition of these various Limit products will be done by Application using the association of the multivalue Fields 13 to 18. Whenever Market conditions change or the Bank's management decides to reorganise their Limit control, a simple maintenance in this table will automatically allow and take care of such changes in the Limit verification process. </p>
            <p>Note: The LIMIT PARAMETER table allows the user to define both 'AND' and 'OR' conditions: </p>
            <p>. The 'AND' condition will be specified by the expansion of the associated sub-value fields 15.1.1 - 18.1.1. If, for example, the user wants to define a specific Limit checking for Money Market transactions with a category code in the range 21075-21079 AND the currency equal to USD, the following input will then be performed in this table: </p>
            <p>Field Number Input </p>
            <p>13.1 Application MM.MONEY.MARKET 14.1 Product 201 15.1.1 Decis Field CATEGORY 16.1.1 Decision EQ 17.1.1 Decision FR 21075 18.1.1 Decision TO 21079 15.1.2 Decis Field CURRENCY 16.1.2 Decision EQ 17.1.2 Decision FR USD 18.1.2 Decision TO - </p>
            <p>. The 'OR' condition will be specified by the expansion of the complete set of multivalue fields (13.1 to 18.1.1). If, for example, the user wants to define the same specific Limit checking for Money Market transactions which have either the category code in the range 21075 to 21079 OR the currency code equal to USD, the following input will then be performed in this table: </p>
            <p>Field Number Input </p>
            <p>13.1 Application MM.MONEY.MARKET 14.1 Product 201 15.1.1 Decis Field CATEGORY 16.1.1 Decision EQ 17.1.1 Decision FR 21075 18.1.1 Decision TO 21079 13.2 Application MM.MONEY.MARKET 14.2 Product 201 15.2.1 Decis Field CURRENCY 16.2.1 Decision EQ 17.2.1 Decision FR USD 18.2.1 Decision TO - </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 40 alpha numeric characters in the format: "FIELD         NAME / FIELD NAME" 'Field Number "-" Multi         Value "." Sub value /Field Number "-"         Multi Value "." Sub Value' Multivalue field         associated with Fields 13 to 18. Input mandatory when         APPLICATION has been defined; otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p>The field name input must correspond to a valid field         name within the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the         APPLICATION defined in field 13.1. Field names may be         defined as SYS or USR fields in STANDARD.SELCTION and         must be of TYPE "D"</p>
            <p>The field name must be input with the multi value/sub-number         when the user wants to specify a special multi value/sub-field.         Multi and sub values should be entered in the format         FIELD NAME - Multi value . Sub Value E.g LOCAL.REF-13.1         LOCAL.REF-1</p>
            <p>Input of 2 field names separated by a '/' is possible         when both fields are of 'D' type or the 2nd field is         numeric (to define call/notice maturity).</p>
            <p>When 2 field names are input, the lst field has to be a         Takedown value date, the 2nd one a Maturity date and the         following input fields can deal with the difference of         these 2 fields in calendar days.</p>
            <p>If input, the 2 date fields must be different (e.g. VALUE.DATE/VALUE.DATE         will not be accepted).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.COMMODITY.EXP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Date and Cycle to indicate when the first full Commodity exposure report will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency code.  Input may be a date followed by a cycle or the cycle by itself in which case the system will automatically generate the next report date. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Input of a frequency without a date is allowed.</p>
            <p>Input of a date without a frequency is not allowed.</p>
            <p>The following frequency formats are allowed:- W followed by 1 to 9 (e.g. W3 - every 3 weeks) D (Daily) M followed by 01 to 99 followed by 1 to 31 (e.g. M0309 - every 3 months on the 9th). T (twice a month).</p>
            <p>If a date is not input, it is calculated depending on the current date as follows:- D     -  Today Wn    -  Yesterday + 7 * n days T     -  15th of current month if today is less than he 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month. Mnndd -  Day number dd in current month + nn months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVALUATION.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Date and Cycle to indicate when the first revaluation will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency code.  Input may be a date followed by a cycle or the cycle by itself in which case the system will automatically generate the next revaluation date. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Input of a frequency without a date is allowed.</p>
            <p>Input of a date without a frequency is not allowed.</p>
            <p>The following frequency formats are allowed:- W followed by 1 to 9 (e.g. W3 - every 3 weeks) D (Daily) M followed by 01 to 99 followed by 1 to 31 (e.g. M0309 - every 3 months on the 9th). T (twice a month)</p>
            <p>If a date is not input, it is calculated depending on the current date as follows:- D     -  Today Wn    -  Yesterday + 7 * n days T     -  15th of current month if today is less than the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month. Mnndd -  Day number dd in current month + nn months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECISION.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the end of a range of values with which the contents of the field indicated in DECIS FIELD (Field 15.1.1) are to be compared. </p>
            <p>For all Financial Applications (eg Loans, Money Market,            Accounts, Foreign Exchange etc), T24 allows the            user to define the Limit products according to his own            requirements.  The definition of these various Limit            products will be done by Application using the association            of the multivalue Fields 13 to 18.  Whenever Market            conditions change  or the Bank's management decides to            reorganise their Limit control, a simple maintenance in            this table will automatically take care of such changes in            the Limit verification procedure. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:      The values input in this field and the previous one must            be in agreement with the format rules of the element            specified in Field 15.1.1 DECIS FIELD.  If, for example,            the input in DECIS FIELD corresponds to a category            code, a maximum input of 5 numeric characters will be            allowed in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters Multivalue field associated with Fields 13 to 18. Optional input when DECISION = 'EQ' or 'NE'; otherwise input not allowed.</p>
            <p>The value entered into this field must be greater than the value entered in the field DECISION FR.</p>
            <p>It may only be input if corresponding Data comparison (Field 16.1.1 DECISION) contains EQ (Equal) or NE (Not Equal to).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVIEWS.REPORTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines how many days prior to Limit REVIEW DATE the approach of this event is to be reported. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters in the range 1 to 99. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.EXP.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Date and Cycle to indicate when the first Country report will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency code.  Input may be a date followed by a cycle or the cycle by itself in which case the system will automatically generate the next report date. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Input of a frequency without a date is allowed.</p>
            <p>Input of a date without a frequency is not allowed.</p>
            <p>The following frequency formats are allowed:- W followed by 1 to 9 (e.g. W3 - every 3 weeks) D (Daily) M followed by 01 to 99 followed by 1 to 31 (e.g. M0309 - every 3 months on the 9th). T (twice a month).</p>
            <p>If a date is not input, it is calculated depending on the current date as follows:- D     -  Today Wn    -  Yesterday + 7 * n days T     -  15th of current month if today is less than the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month. Mnndd -  Day number dd in current month + nn months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the default LIMIT.CURRENCY (Field 1 in LIMIT file) in which all amount fields will be denominated for all limits which are system generated (default limits). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric character currency code or     3 character SWIFT Currency code. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the CURRENCY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARAMETER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an identifier for the record.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be SYSTEM. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The default Limit Reference to be used for Money Market Fiduciary Placements for information. </p>
            <p>If no specific information product is defined for Money Market Fiduciary Placements, this will be used as the default rather than the default specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 or 4 digit LIMIT REFERENCE (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>Must exist on LIMIT REFERENCE with a value of 'IN' in FX.OR.TIME.BAND.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED11</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ACCT.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Idenfifies the limit reference which will be assigned to overdraft balances for inclusion in country-  commodity- and currency reporting. </p>
            <p>Processing for country-, commodity- and currency exposure reporting is based on outstandings reported in the limit main file.   To include overdrafts in cash accounts in these reports a default or "dummy" limit reference is required. </p>
            <p>Please note that any valid LIMIT REFERENCE ID is accepted, but the reference number used should logically be the one for overdrafts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 4 numeric LIMIT REFERENCE ID. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Input must be a valid ID on the LIMIT.REFERENCE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BATCH.STAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.PROD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies which commodity limit products are part of the group defined in the previous field. </p>
            <p>Note:      The check of duplicates and no mix is only done at the            sub-value level.  It is possible, for example, to define            LOANS, MONEY MARKET and as a 3rd Product Group            'LOANS + MONEY MARKET'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 4 numeric LIMIT REFERENCE ID. Sub value field. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Input must be a valid ID on the LIMIT.REFERENCE file.</p>
            <p>Duplicates will not be allowed.</p>
            <p>Mix of Product No and Sub Product No will not be allowed i.e. it is possible to define 100 or 101, 102 etc... but not both.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ADVISED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field, when set denotes that the advised limit will be defaulted. A value of NULL indicates that there is no default processing. There are also two options; INTERNAL and MAXIMUM.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Where INTERNAL is set, it will default to the INTERNAL         amount.</p>
            <p>Where MAXIMUM is set, it will deafult to the MAXIMUM         amount. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.PROD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies which currency limit products are part of the group defined in the previous field. </p>
            <p>Note:      The check of duplicates and no mix is only done at the            sub-value level.  It is possible, for example, to define            LOANS, MONEY MARKET and as a 3rd Product Group            'LOANS + MONEY MARKET'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 4 numeric LIMIT REFERENCE ID. Sub value field. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Input must be a valid ID on the LIMIT.REFERENCE file.</p>
            <p>Duplicates will not be allowed.</p>
            <p>Mix of Product No and Sub Product No will not be allowed i.e. it is possible to define 100 or 101, 102 etc... but not both.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCS.LIMIT.SWEEP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that sweeping of unutilised accounts into contingent accounts, where specified, should be applied during end of day.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Y or N only allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.COUNTRY.EXP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Date and Cycle to indicate when the first full Country exposure report will occur and at what frequency thereafter. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 frequency code.  Input may be a date followed by a cycle or the cycle by itself in which case the system will automatically generate the next report date. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Input of a frequency without a date is allowed.</p>
            <p>Input of a date without a frequency is not allowed.</p>
            <p>The following frequency formats are allowed:- W followed by 1 to 9 (e.g. W3 - every 3 weeks) D (Daily) M followed by 01 to 99 followed by 1 to 31 (e.g. M0309 - every 3 months on the 9th). T (twice a month).</p>
            <p>If a date is not input, it is calculated depending on the current date as follows:- D     -  Today Wn    -  Yesterday + 7 * n days T     -  15th of current month if today is less than the 15th, otherwise the last day of the current month. Mnndd -  Day number dd in current month + nn months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COU.PRODUCT.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies a mnemonic to group together various country limit products.  These groups will then be input in the LIMIT.COUNTRY file to specify the content of the country exposure report. </p>
            <p>In the LIMIT.COUNTRY file, the user will be requested to enter one or various of these groups to specify what type of limit product must be included in the country exposure report. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-15 characters type MNEMONIC. Multivalue field. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>The user will be forced to define at least one group.</p>
            <p>Duplicates are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOCATE.ONLINE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to say whether notional reallocation has to be done for group limits while running enquiries. </p>
        <p>Value YES is set to run notional reallocation, when NO is set reallocation will not be done; enquiries will display the data without reallocation.
</p>
        <p>Validations:
</p>
        <p>Option field, Values YES or NO is accepted.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.CREDIT.LINE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Parameter setup to switch on Group Limits, Only if this field is set to YES, system will allow inputting LIMIT.SHARING.GROUP.</p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Option field, Values YES or NO is accepted.</p>
            <p value="2">	NOCHANGE field.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDITIONAL.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates if additional checking is required. There are three possible values ADVISED,INTERNAL and BOTH.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Where ADVISED is set, the amount will be checked against         the ADVISED limit.</p>
            <p>Where INTERNAL is set, the amount will be checked against         the INTERNAL limit.</p>
            <p>Where BOTH is set, the amount will be checked against         both the ADVISED and the INTERNAL limits.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADM.EXTENSION.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum number of days by which the user may extend the expiry date in the LIMIT file by entering an extension date in ADM EXTENSION DATE. </p>
            <p>The number of days defined in this field will be used by            the LIMIT file to check that the ADM EXTENSION DATE            of a specific limit does not exceed the EXPIRY.DATE by            a number of days greater than the one defined here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 numeric characters in the range 1 to 360. Optional Input.  Default value: None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOW.UNUTIL.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether unutilised amount differences that would result in a credit to the UNUTIL.ACCT are allowed. In other words, if a limit is exceeded, if the flag is set to Y then overall balance of contingent account may become credit. If flag set to N then when limit is fully utilised contingent account balace reaches zero. If limit is exceeded contingent account remains at Zero.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Yes or No allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t><field>GRP.CREDIT.LIMIT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>GRP.ALLOC.ONLINE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
