<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.COUNTRY.GRP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this file is to allow the definition of Country Groupings. The file Limit Country can then be used to define Limits for Country Groups as well as for individual Countries. </p>
            <p>For instance, suppose that it is required to keep track of outstandings in South America. This file is used to define 'South America' by linking together the Country Codes which make up that group. Having defined South America, a Limit is then entered to the Limit Country file for South America (and if necessary by Application within South America). The system will then keep track of outstandings for this grouping, by means of overnight reporting. </p>
            <p>It is possible to define any group of Countries as a Country Group. If a user wishes to define South Africa, for instance, as part of Europe, this is perfectly possible. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>K.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines those Countries which make up a Country Group. </p>
            <p>Each country which is part of the country grouping, must be entered to this multi value field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 character Country Code. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Duplicate Country Codes are not allowed.</p>
            <p>The input code must be a valid entry on the Country table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.GROUP.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name by which the country grouping will be known to the Limits system. Each Country Group must have a unique name. </p>
            <p>As long as it is unique, any combination of characters can be used to identify a country grouping. Obviously, it is best to make the identifier as meaningful as possible. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Country Group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type AA (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Description of the group that the countries detailed in the field or fields COUNTRY.CODE now belong to.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 min -10 max Character length alphanumeric or numeric description</p>
            <p>A country code can only appear once in the in such a group</p>
            <p>For example a country group could be set up as:</p>
            <p />
            <p>SOUTHEAST.ASIA</p>
            <p>This may consist of the following countries:</p>
            <p>ID&amp;#9;Indonesia</p>
            <p>MY&amp;#9;Malaysia</p>
            <p>TH&amp;#9; Thailand</p>
            <p>KR&amp;#9;Republic of Korea</p>
            <p>GROUP&amp;#9;not defined</p>
            <p>As this record is not defined the following valid record could also be defined</p>
            <p>ASEAN</p>
            <p>ID&amp;#9;Indonesia</p>
            <p>VN&amp;#9;Vietnam</p>
            <p>TH&amp;#9;Thailand</p>
            <p>GROUP&amp;#9;not defined</p>
            <p>However if the GROUP was defined on both the above records as USGAAP the validation would not allow both records to exist as ID and TH are common countries to both records.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

