<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.COMMODITY.GRP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this file is to allow the definition of Commodity (Industry) Groupings.  The file LIMIT.COMMODITY can then be used to define Limits for Commodity Groups as well as for individual Commodities. </p>
            <p>For instance, suppose that it is required to keep track of outstandings in the Energy Industry.  This file is used to define the 'Energy' group by linking together the various Industry Codes, (e.g. Coal, Gas, Oil etc.) which make up that group.  Having defined the 'Energy' group, a Limit is then entered to the Limit Commodity file for the Energy Group (and if necessary by Application within this group).  The system will then keep track of outstandings for this grouping, by means of overnight reporting. </p>
            <p>It is possible to define any group of Industries as a Commodity Group. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>K.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMODITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes those Commodities (industry codes) which make up a Commodity Group. </p>
            <p>Each industry which is part of the Commodity grouping, must be entered to this multi value field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric character Industry Code. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Duplicate Industry Codes are not allowed.</p>
            <p>The input code must be a valid entry on the Industry table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMODITY.GRP.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the key by which the Commodity grouping will be known to the Limits system.  Each Commodity Group must have a unique reference ID. </p>
            <p>As long as it is unique, any combination of characters can be used to identify a country grouping.  Obviously, it is best to make the identification as meaningful as possible. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Commodity Group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type AA (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>LIMIT.COMODITY.GRP GROUP</p>
            <p>Description of the group that the countries detailed in the field or fields COUNTRY.CODE now belong to.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1 min -10 max Character length alphanumeric or numeric description</p>
            <p>A commodity code can only appear once in the in such a group</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

