<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.COMMODITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this file is to define Limits by Commodity (Industry) Type.  Although this file is maintained on-line, the System does not attempt to provide real-time information about Commodity Limit utilisation.  Instead, a report which shows all of the Commodity Limits and the corresponding utilisation is produced at a frequency as defined on the LIMIT.PARAMETER table. </p>
            <p>If it is necessary to define Limits for a group of commodities, then the Commodity grouping is specified by the LIMIT.COMMODITY.GRP table. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REPRT.LIMIT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the Limit Amount contained in the last Commodity exposure report produced. </p>
            <p>This field will always be the same as the LIMIT AMOUNT (Field 5) except if this one has been changed since the date on which the last commodity exposure report has been run.  When the next Commodity exposure report is produced, it will then be the same again. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Amount Format. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 13.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.PROD.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the Product Group identification contained in the last Commodity exposure report produced. </p>
            <p>This field will always be the same as the PRODUCT GROUP (Field 3) except if this one has been changed since the date on which the last commodity exposure report has been run.  When the next Commodity exposure report is produced, it will then be the same again. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 17 characters type MNEMONIC. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 13.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency in which the Limit is denominated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 character SWIFT code or     1-3 numeric character Currency code. Multivalue field associated with Fields 3 to 13. (Mandatory input when PRODUCT GROUP has been defined; otherwise not allowed).</p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the CURRENCY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the total value of transactions, as at the production date of the last Commodity exposure report in the Currency specified by Field 12 for the corresponding Product Group. </p>
            <p>During the overnight run, the total value of transactions for each Commodity Limit are totalled by Currency. Each Currency in which there are Outstandings has an entry in this field and the total Outstanding Amount for the Currency is held in associated Field 10.  All these amounts are converted at the appropriate CURRENCY table middle rate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters. Sub-value field associated with Field 7 and multivalue Fields 2 to 8. (Display only. Cannot be input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the Currency code contained in the last Commodity exposure report produced. </p>
            <p>This field will always be the same as the LIMIT CURRENCY (Field 4) except if this one has been changed since the date on which the last commodity exposure report has been run.  When the next Commodity exposure report is produced, it will then be the same again. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 characters SWIFT code. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 13.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency in which the Outstandings in associated Field 10 are denominated. </p>
            <p>During the overnight run, the total value of transactions for each Commodity Limit are totalled by Currency. Each Currency in which there are Outstandings has an entry in this field and the total Outstanding Amount for the Currency is held in associated Field 10.  All these amounts are converted at the appropriate CURRENCY table middle rate. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 SWIFT characters. Sub-value field associated with Field 13 and multivalue Fields 3 to 13. (Display only.  This field cannot be input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines, for the Commodity, or Group of Commodities, the Limit amount applicable to the Product Group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters. Multivalue field associated with Fields 3 to 13. (Mandatory input when PRODUCT GROUP defined; otherwise not allowed).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPRT.OUTSTANDG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays in the currency indicated in field 8 the total Outstanding amount contained in the last printed Commodity exposure report for the corresponding product group. </p>
            <p>The details, in the original currency, of this amount will be displayed in fields 12 and 13. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Amount Format. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 13.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Limit Product Group(s) which is(are) to be part of the Commodity exposure. </p>
            <p>The definition of the Product Groups in the LIMIT.COMMODITY table allows the user to identify the different products which, according to his own criteria, must be part of the Commodity exposure limit control. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 17 characters type MNEMONIC. Multivalue field associated with Fields 4 to 13. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Input must be a valid Product Group on the LIMIT.PARAMETER table.</p>
            <p>Duplicated Product Groups are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPRT.AVAILABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays in the currency indicated in field 8 the total Available amount contained in the last printed Commodity exposure report for the corresponding product group. </p>
            <p>The amount will represent the difference between REPRT LIMIT AMT (Field 9) and REPRT OUTSTANDG (Field 10). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Amount Format. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 13.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMODITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines a unique key for each type of Commodity for which a Limit or Limits are to be maintained. </p>
            <p>A Limit commodity record can be keyed into the System for each Commodity (Industry) or Commodity group for which Limits are to be kept. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 4 numeric character Industry Code or     3 to 15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters to identify a valid commodity group. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>If the Input is up to 4 numeric characters, it must be a valid INDUSTRY code.</p>
            <p>If the input is more than 2 characters type SS, it must be the code of a valid entry on the LIMIT COMMODITY GRP table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains a description of the Commodity Limit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRADE.COMMODITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows a status to be associated with a Commodity Limit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters CUSTOMER.STATUS code. (Optional Input; No Default value).</p>
            <p>Any input must be a valid code on the CUSTOMER.STATUS table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRADE.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows a status to be associated with the Product Group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters CUSTOMER.STATUS code. (Optional input; No Default value).</p>
            <p>Any input must be a valid code on the CUSTOMER.STATUS table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

