<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.CROSS.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This application is used to specify the parameters for Limit References which could be used as PRODUCT Limit References in a Cross Limit structure. In this application it could be possible to specify the maximum value of a CROSS Limit Reference under a PRODUCT Limit Reference. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LINKED.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value of a PRODUCT Limit Reference in a Cross Limit structure. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A PRODUCT</p>
            <p />Limit Reference in<p />a Cross Limit structure should be first defined as a record key in the application <p>LIMIT.CROSS.PARAM before the Limit Reference records are input for that Cross Limit structure.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>The value should end with '00' and should be of length only 3 or 4 digits     (i.e. Global Product values are not allowed).</p><p>LIMIT.REFERENCE record for the value specified should not exist.</p><p>LIMIT.REFERENCE records with values in the range of  'x01' to 'x99'     (in case the ID is 3 digits) and with values in the range 'xy01' to 'xy99'     (in case the ID is 4 digits) should not exist.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOP.CROSS.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum value of a CROSS Limit Reference for the PRODUCT  Limit Reference specified in the ID of the record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>For  example, </p>
            <p>Record ID: 1800 (a PRODUCT Limit Reference in a Cross Limit structure)</p>
            <p>Value of TOP.CROSS.REF: 1840</p>
            <p>All Limit References with values in the range 1801 to 1840 could be used as CROSS Limit References, and Limit References with values in the range 1841 to 1899 could be used as SUB-PRODUCT Limit References.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be in the range of  'x09' to 'x99' where 'x'  is the     first digit if the Record ID is with 3 digits, and should be in the range     of  'xy09' to 'xy99' where 'xy' are the first two digits  if the     Record ID is with 4  digits</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

