<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.NETTING.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Introduced in G14.1. </p>
            <p>This table specifies the parameters for use by the Core routine </p>
            <p>FX.LIMIT.NETTING.I, </p><p>(attached in the field FX.ROUTINE of LIMIT.PARAMETER) while processing the outstanding of a FX Limit.</p> 
            <p>Default SYSTEM record setup will be used. Netting will be carried out for All customers.</p>
            <p>Having only Counter Party level setup will make netting to happen only for specific counter party.</p>
            <p>SYSTEM setup allowed to reverse when NET.OUTSTANDING is set 'N' in the LIMIT.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>If SYSTEM and Counter Party level setup exists, Counter party level setup will take precedence.</p>
            
            </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RECALC.ONLINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Introduced in G14.1.</p>
            <p>Specifies whether all  outstanding transactions need to be revalued on-line,  while processing  the outstanding of  a FX Limit using the core routine FX.LIMIT.NETTING.I.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid values are YES or NO.</p>
            <p>Default value is YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPL.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Introduced in G14.1.</p>
            <p>Specifies the Percentage to be applied on Replacement Value (Customer Loss), while calculating the Limit outstanding using the Core routine FX.LIMIT.NETTING.I.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A positive number.</p>
            <p>Default value is 100.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.USED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Introduced in G14.1.</p>
            <p>Specifies whether Forward or Spot rates are to be used for  calculating the Profit/Loss, while processing the outstanding of a FX Limit using the Core routine FX.LIMIT.NETTING.I.</p>
            <p>If FWD or SPOT, then Forward or Spot rates respectively  would be used for calculating the Profit/Loss of Forward Contracts.</p>
            <p>Profit/Loss of Spot Contracts would be always calculated using the Spot Rates irrespective of the value in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Valid values are FWD or SPOT.</p>
            <p>Default value is FWD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Introduced in G14.1. </p>
            <p>Specifies the Percentage to be applied on Customer Profit, while calculating the Limit outstanding using the Core routine FX.LIMIT.NETTING.I.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A positive     number.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Default     value is 0.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Introduced in G14.1.</p>
            <p>Description of the Record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 35 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of the LIMIT.NETTING.PARAM Record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be SYSTEM or  the ID of  a valid CUSTOMER Record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Introduced in G14.1.</p>
            <p>Specifies the FX Limit Reference for which the parameters in the associated fields would apply while processing the Limit Outstanding using the core routine FX.LIMIT.NETTING.I.</p>
            <p>If the value is ALL, then the parameters in the associated fields would apply to all remaining  FX Limit Sub-Product  References, not explicitly specified here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid      Fx Limit.Reference ID with field FX.OR.TIME.BAND set to FX.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Only     sub-product Limit References are allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Duplicate     values are not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Associated     with the fields LIMIT.REFERENCE to RATE.USED. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Default     value is ALL.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The value     ALL </p>
            <p>is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETTING.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Introduced in G14.1.</p>
            <p>Specifies the type of Netting to be used, while processing the Limit Outstanding using the core routine FX.LIMIT.NETTING.I.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid values are MULTI, NONE and PAIRED.</p>
            <p>Default value is NONE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

