<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LI</product>
<table>LIMIT.CURRENCY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this file is to define Limits by Currency.  Although this file is maintained on-line, the System does not attempt to provide real-time information about Currency Limit utilisation. Instead, a report which shows all of the Currency Limits and the use made of each is produced at a frequency as defined on the LIMIT.PARAMETER table. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REPRT.OUTSTANDG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays in the currency indicated in the ID the total Outstanding amount contained in the last printed Currency exposure report for the corresponding product group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Amount Format. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 9.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Limit Product Group(s) which is(are) to be part of the Currency exposure. </p>
            <p>The definition of the Product Groups in the LIMIT.CURRENCY table allows the user to identify the different products which, according to his own criteria, must be part of the Currency exposure limit control. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 17 characters type MNEMONIC. Multivalue field associated with Fields 4 to 9. (Mandatory input).</p>
            <p>Input must be a valid Product Group on the LIMIT.PARAMETER table.</p>
            <p>Duplicated Product Groups are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines, for the Currency, the Limit amount applicable to the Product Group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters. Multivalue field associated with Fields 3 to 9. (Mandatory input when PRODUCT GROUP defined; otherwise not allowed).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPRT.AVAILABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays in the currency indicated in the ID the total Available amount contained in the last printed Currency exposure report for the corresponding product group. </p>
            <p>The amount will represent the difference between REPRT LIMIT AMT (Field 7) and REPRT OUTSTANDG (Field 8). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Amount Format. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 9.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.PROD.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the Product Group identification contained in the last Currency exposure report produced. </p>
            <p>This field will always be the same as the PRODUCT GROUP (Field 3) except if this one has been changed since the date on which the last currency exposure report has been run.  When the next Currency exposure report is produced, it will then be the same again. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 17 characters type MNEMONIC. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 9.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPRT.LIMIT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Displays the Limit Amount contained in the last Currency exposure report produced. </p>
            <p>This field will always be the same as the LIMIT AMOUNT (Field 4) except if this one has been changed since the date on which the last currency exposure report has been run.  When the next Currency exposure report is produced, it will then be the same again. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Amount Format. System generated field. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 9.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a unique key for each Currency for which a Limit, or Limits, are to be held. </p>
            <p>A Currency Limit record can be keyed into the System for each Currency for which Limits are to be kept. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 numeric character Currency Code or     3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character SWIFT Code. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Input in this field must refer to a valid code on the CURRENCY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains a free format description of the Currency Limit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRADE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows a status to be associated with a Currency Limit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters CUSTOMER.STATUS code. (Optional Input; No Default value).</p>
            <p>Any input must be a valid code on the CUSTOMER.STATUS table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRADE.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows a status to be associated with the Product Group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters CUSTOMER.STATUS code. Multivalue field associated with fields 3 to 9. (Optional input; No Default value).</p>
            <p>Any input must be a valid code on the CUSTOMER.STATUS table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

