<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LD</product>
<table>LD.GROUP.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p> It is possible to stipulate customer/ customer-group specific conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> When inputting an LD contract where the customer (or customer group) has an entry in the LD.GROUP.CONDITION application and if the category input has been defined in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION application, then entering individual values for interest, commission and charges becomes redundant as the system will default these values making use of the entries in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION and LD.GROUP.CONDITION. The user, may however, wish to input values at the deal level, by overriding the default values.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FIXED.CONTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Entries in this field can be YES or</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Example: Say, in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21065 stipulates a fixed interest of 8% on all USD contracts. If a particular group (say GRPA) has an entry of 2 in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD loan to a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 6% (8%-2%). The same would apply for deposit contracts also.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SPREAD.LOAN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default spread to be applied to loan type contracts for a specific customer or group. The value can be positive or negative as this value can be used to increase or decrease the end user rate.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In usage the bank may wish to set a floating rate record to be the generally available rate for customer loans and use the values here to soften the rates by deducting a small amount, thereby reducing the rate to the user. However, it is just as valid to use the standard rate record as the base rate and add a spread to this to provide client rates.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Whichever is used the system will work out the end spread as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p>BASIC.INTEREST + LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION(INTEREST.SPREAD) + LD.GROUP.CONDITION(INT.SPREAD.LOAN)</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 1: Say in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21050 stipulates an interest key for all USD contracts. This key corresponds to a rate of 5% in the BASIC.INTEREST table. If a particular group (say GRPA) has an entry of 0.5 in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN field in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD loan taken by a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 5.5% (5% +0.5%).</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 2: Say in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21051 stipulates an interest key for all USD contracts and a spread of 0.75%. This key corresponds to a rate of 5% in the BASIC.INTEREST table so general loans are going to get 5.75% interest. If a particular group (say GRPB) has an entry of -0.5 in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN field in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD loan given to a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 5.25% (5% +0.75% -0.5%), thereby getting a lower rate than the general loans.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>Cannot be greater than 100. </p>
            <p>Negative values allowed but cannot exceed -100</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Indicates the customer group or individual customer for whom customerlevel spread and charge stipulations are being made.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Validations</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> For     customer groups, the group should first have been defined in     APPL.GEN.CONDITION</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> For     individual customers, the ID should be the customer number preceded by C-</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This NOINPUT field is currently not used. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Forms part of the associated multi-value set CHARGE.TYPE to CHRG.FLT.AMT. Input in this field must be an entry in the LMM.CHARGE.CONDITIONS application.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Validation</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHRG.FLT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Forms part of an associated sub-value set from CHARGE.CCY to CHARGE.FLT.AMT. For every CHARGE.CCY specified it is possible to stipulate a flat amount for the customer/customer-group specified in the ID.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Validation</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Should     be a numeric input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Input     in this field is prohibited if there is an input in the CHARGE.PERC field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SPREAD.DEP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default spread to be applied to deposit type contracts for a specific customer or group. The value can be positive or negative as this value can be used to increase or decrease the end user rate.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In usage the bank may wish to set a floating rate record to be the generally available rate for customer deposits and use the values here to soften the rates by adding a premium, thereby increasing the rate to the user. However, it is just as valid to use the standard rate record as the base rate and deduct a spread from this to provide client rates.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Whichever is used the system will work out the end spread as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p>BASIC.INTEREST + LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION(INTEREST.SPREAD) + LD.GROUP.CONDITION(INT.SPREAD.DEP)</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 1: Say in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21006 stipulates an interest key for all USD contracts. This key corresponds to a rate of 5% in the BASIC.INTEREST table. If a particular group (say GRPA) has an entry of 0.5 in the INT.SPREAD.DEP field in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD deposit taken from a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 5.5% (5%+0.5%).</p>
            <p />
            <p>Example 2: Say in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21005 stipulates an interest key for all USD contracts and a negative spread of 0.75%. This key corresponds to a rate of 5% in the BASIC.INTEREST table so general deposits are going to get 4.25% interest. If a particular group (say GRPB) has an entry of 0.5 in the INT.SPREAD.DEP field in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD deposit taken from a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 4.75% (5% -0.75% +0.5%), thereby getting a better rate than the general deposits.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>Cannot be greater than 100. </p>
            <p>Negative values allowed but cannot exceed -100</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc>
        <p>Default spread to be applied to loan type contracts for a specific customer or group. The value can be positive or negative as this value can be used to increase or decrease the end user rate. In usage the bank may wish to set a floating rate record to be the generally available rate for customer loans and use the values here to soften the rates by deducting a small amount, thereby reducing the rate to the user. However, it is just as valid to use the standard rate record as the base rate and add a spread to this to provide client rates. Whichever is used the system will work out the end spread as follows: BASIC.INTEREST + LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION(INTEREST.SPREAD) + LD.GROUP.CONDITION(INT.SPREAD.LOAN) Example 1: Say in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21050 stipulates an interest key for all USD contracts. This key corresponds to a rate of 5% in the BASIC.INTEREST table. If a particular group (say GRPA) has an entry of 0.5 in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN field in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD loan taken by a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 5.5% (5% +0.5%). Example 2: Say in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21051 stipulates an interest key for all USD contracts and a spread of 0.75%. This key corresponds to a rate of 5% in the BASIC.INTEREST table so general loans are going to get 5.75% interest. If a particular group (say GRPB) has an entry of -0.5 in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN field in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD loan given to a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 5.25% (5% +0.75% -0.5%), thereby getting a lower rate than the general loans. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional Input Cannot be greater than 100. Negative values allowed but cannot exceed -10.</p>
        <p>APPLY.CURR.LOANS</p>
        <p>Inputs in this field can be YES or NO. If set to '"YES", it would mean that any changes in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN or INT.SPREAD.DEP fields would be applicable to the customer/customer-group specified in the ID, for existing floating rate contract. Validation For this field to be changed from NO to YES, a change should first be made in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN or INT.SPREAD.DEP field.</p>
        <p>CHARGE.CCY</p>
        <p>Forms part of an associated sub-value set from CHARGE.CCY to CHARGE.FLT.AMT. For every CHARGE.TYPE specified it is possible to stipulate the various currencies for which the charge would be applicable. Validation Input in this field must be a valid entry in the CURRENCY table If the CHARGE.TYPE is linked to an entry in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE/FT.CHARGE.TYPE, an entry for CHARGE.CCY would also have to exist in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE/ FT.CHARGE.TYPE for that particular charge, for this field to be recognized Could be set to for all currencies or to REST for all currencies not specifically defined. However REST can be input only if at least one currency has been defined for that charge.</p>
        <p>CHARGE.PERC</p>
        <p>Forms part of an associated sub-value set from CHARGE.CCY to CHARGE.FLT.AMT. For every currency defined in CHARGE.CCY, this field can be used to define whether only a certain percentage of charges in that currency would be applicable to the customer/customer-group in the ID. Validation Should be a numeric input Cannot be a negative value or a value greater than 100 Input in this field is prohibited if there is an input in CHARGE.FLT.AMT field.</p>
        <p>CHARGE.TYPE</p>
        <p>Forms part of the associated multi-value set CHARGE.TYPE to CHRG.FLT.AMT. Input in this field must be an entry in the LMM.CHARGE.CONDITIONS application. Validation Must b.</p>
        <p>CHRG.FLT.AMT</p>
        <p>Forms part of an associated sub-value set from CHARGE.CCY to CHARGE.FLT.AMT. For every CHARGE.CCY specified it is possible to stipulate a flat amount for the customer/customer-group specified in the ID. Validation Should be a numeric input Input in this field is prohibited if there is an input in the CHARGE.PERC field.</p>
        <p>EXCHANGE.SPREAD</p>
        <p>This NOINPUT field is currently not used.</p>
        <p>FIXED.CONTRACT</p>
        <p>Entries in this field can be YES or Example: Say, in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21065 stipulates a fixed interest of 8% on all USD contracts. If a particular group (say GRPA) has an entry of 2 in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD loan to a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 6% (8%-2%). The same would apply for deposit contracts also.</p>
        <p>GROUP.ID</p>
        <p>Indicates the customer group or individual customer for whom customerlevel spread and charge stipulations are being made. Validations For customer groups, the group should first have been defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION For individual customers, the ID should be the customer number preceded by C.</p>
        <p>INT.SPREAD.DEP</p>
        <p>Default spread to be applied to deposit type contracts for a specific customer or group. The value can be positive or negative as this value can be used to increase or decrease the end user rate. In usage the bank may wish to set a floating rate record to be the generally available rate for customer deposits and use the values here to soften the rates by adding a premium, thereby increasing the rate to the user. However, it is just as valid to use the standard rate record as the base rate and deduct a spread from this to provide client rates. Whichever is used the system will work out the end spread as follows: BASIC.INTEREST + LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION(INTEREST.SPREAD) + LD.GROUP.CONDITION(INT.SPREAD.DEP) Example 1: Say in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21006 stipulates an interest key for all USD contracts. This key corresponds to a rate of 5% in the BASIC.INTEREST table. If a particular group (say GRPA) has an entry of 0.5 in the INT.SPREAD.DEP field in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD deposit taken from a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 5.5% (5%+0.5%). Example 2: Say in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION the category 21005 stipulates an interest key for all USD contracts and a negative spread of 0.75%. This key corresponds to a rate of 5% in the BASIC.INTEREST table so general deposits are going to get 4.25% interest. If a particular group (say GRPB) has an entry of 0.5 in the INT.SPREAD.DEP field in LD.GROUP.CONDITION, this would mean that a USD deposit taken from a customer falling in GRPA would be at a defaulted rate of 4.75% (5% -0.75% +0.5%), thereby getting a better rate than the general deposits. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional Input Cannot be greater than 100. Negative values allowed but cannot exceed -100</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLY.CURR.LOANS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Inputs in this field can be YES or NO. If set to '"YES", it would mean that any changes in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN or INT.SPREAD.DEP fields would be applicable to the customer/customer-group specified in the ID, for existing floating rate contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Validation</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> For     this field to be changed from NO to YES, a change should first     be made in the INT.SPREAD.LOAN or INT.SPREAD.DEP field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Forms part of an associated sub-value set from CHARGE.CCY to CHARGE.FLT.AMT. For every CHARGE.TYPE specified it is possible to stipulate the various currencies for which the charge would be applicable.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Validation</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Input     in this field must be a valid entry in the CURRENCY table</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> If     the CHARGE.TYPE is linked to an entry in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE/FT.CHARGE.TYPE,     an entry for CHARGE.CCY would also have to exist in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE/     FT.CHARGE.TYPE for that particular charge, for this field to be recognized </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Could     be set to   for all currencies or to REST for all currencies not     specifically defined. However REST can be input only if at least one     currency has been defined for that charge.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PERC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Forms part of an associated sub-value set from CHARGE.CCY to CHARGE.FLT.AMT. For every currency defined in CHARGE.CCY, this field can be used to define whether only a certain percentage of charges in that currency would be applicable to the customer/customer-group in the ID.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Validation</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Should     be a numeric input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Cannot     be a negative value or a value greater than 100</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Input     in this field is prohibited if there is an input in CHARGE.FLT.AMT field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

