<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>LD</product>
<table>PM.LD.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table allows the user to define the parameters governing the rules for the handling of the allocation of PM.POSN.CLASS keys according to the Category code in the Loans and Deposits record. </p>
            <p>The position management activities for Loans and Deposits are pre-defined and cannot be changed. </p>
            <p>There are a set of fields covering the category code ranges and the PM.POSN.CLASS activities, which are expanded together for each "range". </p>
            <p>The category code ranges are split to provide a deposit (Liability) range and a loan (asset) range for each set of PM.POSN.CLASS activities. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>POS.FWD.VAR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the position class used to reflect future interest payments (i.e not the next scheduled payment) for variable interest contracts. </p>
            <p>The next interest payment will always be shown as a cash flow movement, if this field is defined, the later interest payaments will be passed with this position class reference. If not defined, the future movements are also reflecteed as cash flow movements. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input First 2 characters must be LD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PM.MAX.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where Position Management (PM) is being actively used and the LD module is installed this record controls how the two modules interact.</p>
            <p>In cases where it is common to enter long term loans i.e 10 years or more you may wish to set this value to limit the updates sent to PM to a more reasonable period.</p>
            <p>For example if you want to enter a 25 year term loan with monthly settlements of Interest and/or Commission you can limit the number of months of info sent to PM. It is unlikely you would use PM information (broken down on a monthly basis) that far in advance, and to avoid the overhead at input time you can set this field to say 60 (representing 60 months).</p>
            <p>If you do require this level of information contact Temenos on advice on system settings which may need tuning.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p>Must be a number between 1 and 999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.PPL.DEC.CSH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is obsolete at 14.2.0 </p>
            <p>Specified the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the principal decrease cash activity. The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the Principal Decrease, entered on the deal,for the date of the decrease. This activity is a cash activity. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Obsolete</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.FEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the activity for fee payments. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the fee payment on the date that the fees are paid. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXFE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 12.1 and fields 14.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the activity for charge payments. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the charges payment on the date of the charges payment </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXCH. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 11.1 and fields 13.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.INT.CAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the interest activity for when interest is to be capitalised rather than paid away. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the interest movement on interest due date and is used when interest is to be capitalised rather than paid away. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXIC. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 10.1 and fields 12.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether the position Management module is to include all interest payments for the life of a contract or for just the current interest period.. </p>
            <p>If this field is null then only the current interest period           movements will be shown. </p>
            <p>          If this field is VARIABLE then all the interest movements           for LD contracts not of interest type 1 will be shown. </p>
            <p>          If this field is FIXED then all the interest movements for           LD contracts of interest type 1 will be shown. </p>
            <p>          If this field is BOTH then all the interest movements for LD           contracts of all interest types will be shown. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Can take any of the following values, FIXED VARIABLE BOTH or null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.PPL.INC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the principal increase activity. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the Principal Increase movement for the date of the increase. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXPI. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 14.1 and fields 16.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the commission activity. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the commission movement on commission due date or maturity date of the contract. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXCM. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 13.1 and fields 15.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the interest movements beyond the current interest period for contracts of interest type 1. </p>
            <p>If the value in field 28 SHOW FWD INT is BOTH or FIXED then this field is mandatory. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXFI. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Optional input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 21.1 and fields 23.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.TAX.PRIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the activity covering tax on principal payment. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the Tax on Principal movement for the date of the tax payment. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXPT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 19.1 and fields 21.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the principal activity for the start of the deal. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the prinicpal movement on value (Start) date of the deal. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXST. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 5.1 and fields 7.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.FWD.FIX.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the position class used to reflect future interest payments (i.e not the next scheduled payment) for fixed interest contracts. </p>
            <p>The next interest payment will always be shown as a cash flow movement, if this field is defined, the later interest payaments will be passed with this position class reference. If not defined, the future movements are also reflecteed as cash flow movements. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input First 2 characters must be LD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GM.DATE.SFX</field>
<desc>
            <p>For internal use only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 character. Value = "8"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.PRIN.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is obsolete at 14.2.0 </p>
            <p>Specified the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the principal repayment cash activity. The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the Principal repayment by the dates on the schedules.    This activity is classed as a cash activity and there is one for each principal repayment date except for the one on the maturity date when the POS.MAT.CASH field is used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Obsolete</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHOW.FWD.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whethere interest and commission events are to be projected into the future. </p>
            <p>The next interest and commission movement will always be shown in the Position Management system. Subsequent events will not be included unless this field is defined. It may contain the following values: </p>
            <p>   BOTH     - Show fixed and variable rate contract future payments    VARIABLE - Show only future payments for variable interest contracts    FIXED    - Show only future interest and commission payaments for fixed               rate contracts. </p>
            <p>A fixed rate contract is a contract where INT.RATE.TYPE = 1, all other types are termed variable. Commission may only be fixed rate. </p>
            <p>Future interest and commission movements will be shown using the position class defined in POS.FWD.FIX.INT, POS.FWD.VAR.INT or POS.FWD.COMM if defined, otherwaise the movements will be reflected as cash flows in the same way as the first interest or commission payment. </p>
            <p>Future interest is calculateed using the current interest rate for all contracts. If a contract is of interest rate type PERIODIC AUTOMATIC, the current rate will be used, unless the field PROJECT.R.TYPE is set to YES in the LMM.INSTALL.CONDS table. In this case the future rate will be projected on R schedule dates using the current setting of the PERIODIC.INTEREST table. This can be recalcualted on the period specified in FWD.R.TYPE.FQU. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input First 2 characters must be LD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-language field allowing the user to specify a description for the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>35 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is obsolete at 14.2.0 </p>
            <p>Specified the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the interest activity as at the next interest date. The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the interest movement on interest due date or maturity date if there is no interest due date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Obsolete</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.PRIN.GAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the principal repayment gap activity. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the Principal repayment by the dates on the schedules.    This activity is classed as a gap activity. </p>
            <p>If there are no rate change schedules/date then there is separate activity raised for each repayment date.  Otherwise activities are only raised up to the rate charge schedule/date.  The activity for this date contains outstanding balance as at this date. The recommended value for this field is LDXPG. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 18.1 and fields 20.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.TAX.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the activity covering tax on interest payment. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the Tax on Interest payment on interest due date or maturity date. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXIT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 20.1 and fields 22.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.MAT.GAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the principal gap activity for the maturity of the deal. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the prinicpal movement on maturity date of the deal and is used as a gap activity. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXMG. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 7.1 and fields 9.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.TAX.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the activity covering tax on commission payment. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the Tax on Commission payment on the date the commission is due or the maturity date. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXCT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 21.1 and fields 23.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.PPL.DEC.GAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the principal decrease gap activity. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the Principal Decrease, entered on the deal, for the date of the decrease. This activity is a gap activity. </p>
            <p>This activity is for a special decrease, the repayment schedules use the fields POS.PRIN.CASH and POS.PRIN.GAP. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXDG. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 16.1 and fields 18.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.FWD.FIX.CAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the future interest activity (i.e not the next interest scheduled event) for when interest is to be capitalised rather than paid away and the contract is of FIXed interest type. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the interest movement on interest due date and is used when interest is to be capitalised rather than paid away. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 10.1 and fields 12.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.FWD.VAR.CAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the future interest activity (i.e not the next interest scheduled event) for when interest is to be capitalised rather than paid away and the contract is of VARiable interest type. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the interest movement on interest due date and is used when interest is to be capitalised rather than paid away. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 10.1 and fields 12.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PM.LD.PARAM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the 'ID' of the record which can only be SYSTEM. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.MAT.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is obsolete at 14.2.0 </p>
            <p>Specified the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the principal cash activity for the maturity of the deal. The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the prinicpal movement on maturity date of the deal and is used as a cash activity. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Obsolete</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.FWD.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the future commission (i.e not the NEXT commission schedule) activity. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the commission movement on commission due date or maturity date of the contract. </p>
            <p>The initial commission movement will be passed only as a cash flow movement. If this field is defined the subsequent movements will be pasased using this position class. If not the future movements will also be raised as cash flow movements. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Optional input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 13.1 and fields 15.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.ROWS</field>
<desc>
            <p>For internal use only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 alphanumeric characters. Value = "21"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.TYPE.TO.USE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the user to indicate whether the deal interest rate or the MIS interest rate is to be used in the Gap activities. </p>
            <p>If this field is left blank the deal interest rate is used.  If MIS entered then the MIS interest rate is used.  This refers to the rate to be used in Position Class activities that can be used for Interest mismatch gap positions. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alphanumeric characters. Multivalue field in association with fields 2.1 to 24.1. Field must be either blank or MIS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the interest movements beyond the current interest period for contracts of interest type NOT EQUAL to 1. </p>
            <p>If the value in field 28 SHOW FWD INT is BOTH or VARIABLE then this field is mandatory. </p>
            <p>The recommended value for this field is LDXVI. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Optional input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 21.1 and fields 23.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.CHARGE.CAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the activity for capitalised charge payments. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the charges payment on the date of the charges payment. </p>
            <p>Charges which are not capitalised will be passed into PM as cash flow movements using the underlying CHRG.LIQ.ACCT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input. Multivalue field associated with fields 2.1 to 11.1 and fields 13.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS'</p>
            <p>The first two digits must be LD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.INT.DISC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is obsolete at 14.2.0 </p>
            <p>Specified the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the discount interest activity. The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to Category Code on the deal.  The ranges are contained in fields CATEG.DEP.ST to CATEG.DEP.END and CATEG.LOAN.ST to CATEG.LOAN.END.  The position class is the one used to identify the discount movement on value (start) date of the deal and is used when interest is being taken up front. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Obsolete</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEG.DEP.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category code to identify the End of the Deposit Category Code Range. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to the category code on the deal.  This field contains the end category code for the deposit range. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters Multivalue associated group with field 2.1 and fields 4.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>If the start Deposit category code not blank then end code cannot be blank.</p>
            <p>Category code must be within the range 21001 to 21049.</p>
            <p>Category Code must be greater than associated start deposit category code (field CATEG.DEP.ST).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEG.DEP.ST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category Code to identify the start of the Deposit Category code range. </p>
            <p>The position Class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to the category code on the deal.  This field contains the start category code for the deposit range. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters. Multivalue associated group with fields 3.1 to 25.1</p>
            <p>Category code must be in the range 21001 to 21049</p>
            <p>Category code must be greater than preceeding end deposit category code (field CATEG.DEP.END).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEG.LOAN.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category code to identify the End of the Loan Category Code Range. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to the category code on the deal.  This field contains the end category code for the loan range. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters Multivalue associated group with fields 2.1 to 4.1 and fields 6.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>Category code must be within the range 21050 to 21074.</p>
            <p>Category Code must be greater than the associated start loan category code (field CATEG.LOAN.ST).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEG.LOAN.ST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category code to identify the Start of the Loan Category Code Range. </p>
            <p>The position class for Loans and Deposits can be allocated according to the category code on the deal.  This field contains the start category code for the loan range. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters Multivalue associated group with fields 2.1 to 3.1 and fields 5.1 to 25.1.</p>
            <p>Category code must be within the range 21050 to 21074.</p>
            <p>Category Code must be greater than preceeding end loan category code (field CATEG.LOAN.END).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>REAL.FX.CLASS</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
