<t24help>
<header>
<product>ACHFRM</product>
<title> </title>
<table>ACH.CLEARING.PARAMETER</table>
 </header>
 <overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This application is used to determine how various entries and records for ACH are posted and the set up required for the process of clearing to happen. The table aids in defining the paths where the various files, carring incoming, outgoing and returned entries are posted.</p>
<p>The table also provides details about the routing numbers or ABA numbers used for the bank.</p>
<p>This record is referred for all the type of processing, outward, inward and returns in order to update the entries and related tables. </p>
</ovdesc>
<ovimage>
</ovimage>
 </overview>
 <menu>
<t><field>
ID
</field>
<desc>
<p>ID can be anything upto a length of 35 characters.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
DESCRIPTION
</field>
<desc>
<p>A multi language description of the ACH clearing process set up.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Standard Multivalued Language field.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
CHECK.TYPE
</field>
<desc>
<p>Describes the types of check or verification process the entries have to undergo before posting them in the system. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multivalue set used to define all the parameters required for the verification processes like AML, etc</p>
<p>Upto 35 characters</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
CHECK.LEVELS
</field>
<desc>
<p>The field is used in validating the level or stages of the process the entries undergo during the AML verification process or any other interface involved. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field associated with CHECK.TYPE, upto 2 numeric characters</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
RETRY
</field>
<desc>
<p>Reserved for future use</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
RESPONSE.PATH
</field>
<desc>
<p>The field denotes the path in which the results of the check process mentioned in the CHECK.TYPE field are posted. Say in case of AML, the entries after the AML verification process carrying the details of the legitimacy of the customer is posted in the path mentioned here. This is then taken up for further processing by the other services that are run subsequently. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field associated with CHECK.TYPE </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
RESPONSE.TIME
</field>
<desc>
<p>The field indicates the time within which the response from the AML verification process is received.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field associated with CHECK.TYPE , standart TIME format</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
ADDENDA.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>Denotes the position of the addenda in the incoming file which is used to process the entries with addenda records and to merge them as required by the NACHA rules. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Upto 10 characters</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
CCY.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is not used currently.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
AMOUNT.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>Denotes the position of the amount in the incoming file which is used to process the entries.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Upto 10 characters</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
FCY.ALLOWED
</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is not used currently.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
FILE.DR.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>For the trailer records, that is the records with the file type indicator '9', the total credit or debit made for the file has to be displayed. This field is used to retrieve the information of the position of the total debit for the file to be used as control for validation. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>The position of the variable followed by a ',' followed by the length of the same</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
FILE.CR.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>For the trailer records, that is the records with the file type indicator '9', the total credit or debit made for the file has to be displayed. This field is used to retrieve the information of the position of the total credit for the file to be used as control for validation. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>The position of the variable followed by ',' followed by the length of the same</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
BATCH.DR.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is not used currently.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
BATCH.CR.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is not used currently.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
DETAIL.CLASS.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>The SEC type code is available in the batch header records, that is the record with the file type indicator '5'. In order to retrieve the same from the incoming file, the position of the class code is mentioned in this field. </p>
<p>Validation rule:</p>
<p>The position of the variable followed by ',' followed by the length of the same</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
BATCH.CLASS.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is not used currently.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
TXN.CODE.POS
</field>
<desc>
<p>The type of the transaction, say if it is debit or credit determines the totals of the batch or the file. The transaction codes are then validated against the lookup table. The position of this code is retrived and updated in this field. </p>
<p>Validation rule:</p>
<p>The position of the variable followed by ',' followed by the length of the same</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
VALUE.DATE.IN
</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is not used currently.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
OUR.RTN.NUMBER
</field>
<desc>
<p>The field carries the routing number of the bank mentioned in the field ROUTING.COMPANY. </p>
<p>Multi value field, Upto 9 characters</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
ROUTING.COMPANY
</field>
<desc>
<p>Company code to which the OUR.RTN.NUMBER mentioned above belongs to. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value associated with OUR.RTN.NUMBER</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
FED.RESERVE.NUMBER
</field>
<desc>
<p>Carries the identification number of the Federal Reserve Bank.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field, upto 10 characters</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
CONTRA.ACCT
</field>
<desc>
<p>Identifies the account which is used for clearing. </p>
<p>Validatin Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field, upto 16 characters</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
SUSPENSE.ACCT
</field>
<desc>
<p>Identifies the account number which is used in case of entries that is routed through other banks.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value set associated woth CONTRA.ACCT, upto 16 characters allowed</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
CONTRA.COMPANY
</field>
<desc>
<p>The company to which the contra and the suspense account belong. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value set associated woth CONTRA.ACCT, upto 10 characters allowed</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
AC.ENTRY.ID
</field>
<desc>
<p>Carries the key of the table, AC.ENTRY.PARAM that is referred for raising entries for ACH. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Upto 10 characters</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
FT.SEL.CONDITION
</field>
<desc>
<p>Reserved for future use</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
COMPANY.PATH
</field>
<desc>
<p>Defines the path of the company for which the below various paths for the files is configured. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field,  type - file path</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
INWARD.FILE.PATH
</field>
<desc>
<p>Defines the path of file in which the inward entries are available. When the service corresponding to inward processing is run, the path given is referred to in order to fetch the incoming file to be processed.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field associated with COMPANY.PATH,  type - file path</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
OUTWARD.FILE.PATH
</field>
<desc>
<p>Defines the path of file in which the outward entries are available. When the service corresponding to outward processing is run, the entries to be sent out in the NACHA complaint file structure are posted in the path given.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field associated with COMPANY.PATH,  type - file path</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
RETURN.FILE.PATH
</field>
<desc>
<p>Defines the path of file in which the entries returned are available. When the service to  processing the entries is run, the entries found to be flawed are to be returned to the originator and this is posted as per the NACHA complaint file structure in the path given.</p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field associated with COMPANY.PATH,  type - file path</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t><field>
ROUTED.TXNS.PATH
</field>
<desc>
<p>Defines the path of file in which the entries rotued through other banks are available. </p>
<p>Validation Rule:</p>
<p>Multi value field associated with COMPANY.PATH,  type - file path</p>
</desc>
</t>
</menu> 
</t24help>