<t24help>
  <header>
    <product>ACHFRM</product>
    <title>ACH Message</title>
    <table>ACH.MESSAGE</table>
  </header>
  <overview>
    <ovdesc>
      <p>The table is used to hold details related to addenda for all the sec class codes which have addenda records available.</p>
      <p>The table specifies the number of addenda records available for the sec class code and the fields that are mandatory when the message type has an addenda record. </p>
      <p>It also holds the default values to be updated in the fields captured in the table while creating an ACH.ADDENDA record </p>
    </ovdesc>
    <ovimage>
    </ovimage>
  </overview>
  <menu>
    <t>
      <field>ID</field>
      <desc>
        <p>ID can only be a valid type of sec class code. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p></p>        
        <p>Maximum length is 3</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
   <t>
      <field>ADDENDA.FIELD.OR.COUNT</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Field to capture the name of the field in ACH.ADDENDA that will have to be input for the class code. </p>
		<p>The total addenda count will be considered from the count of the multi-values in the ACH.ADDENDA record for the field mentioned in this table.</p>
		<p>Instead of the field based count, a number can also be input here, in which case the system will check if there are that many addenda fields updated in the ACH.ADDENDA table while generating outward transactions</p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>No validation</p>               
      </desc>
    </t>
	<t>
      <field>ORDER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>The field carries the value upto 3 character as per the addenda records available.  </p>
		<p>The first digit denotes the RECORD.TYPE.CODE and the last two digits denote the ADDENDA.TYPE.CODE for the particular sec class code. </p>
		<p>When more than one addenda record is available, this can be multi valued.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
		 <p></p>
        <p>Multivalue field, upto 3 characters</p>               
      </desc>
    </t>
	<t>
      <field>OPTIONAL.ORDER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is an optional field used for the SEC codes having optional addenda apart from the mandatory ones mentioned in the field ORDER.</p>		
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
		 <p></p>
        <p>Multivalue field, upto 3 characters</p>               
      </desc>
    </t>
	<t>
      <field>SEQUENCE</field>
      <desc>	
        <p>For every value mentioned in the field ORDER, the SEQ.FLD.MAP, PROPERTY and DEFAULT.VAL have to be mentioned.</p>			
		<p>This field carries the values given in the field ORDER.</p>			
        <p>Validation Rules</p>	
		 <p></p>	
        <p>Multivalue field, upto 3 characters</p>               	
      </desc>	
    </t>	
	<t>	
      <field>ADD.SEQ.FIELD.RTN</field>	
      <desc>		
        <p>Allows attaching any routines for manipulating the sequence number to be populated while generating the outward file.</p>				
		<p>Wherever the sequence number generation is different for a Sec class code, a routine can be attached to this field to generate the sequence number.</p>	
		<p>The routine attached should accept single argument.</p>	
        <p>Validation Rules</p>		
		 <p></p>		
        <p>Multivalue field associated with SEQUENCE and must be a valid API, upto 35 characters</p>               		
      </desc>		
    </t>		
	<t>	
      <field>SEQ.FLD.MAP</field>	
      <desc>		
        <p>The sub value set from SEQ.FLD.MAP to DEFAULT.VAL holds the value required to be displayed in ACH.ADDENDA.</p>				
		<p>The field SEQ.FLD.MAP should be a valid field name from the application ACH.ADDENDA.</p>			
        <p>Validation Rules</p>		
		 <p></p>		
        <p>Multivalue field associated with SEQUENCE</p>               		
      </desc>		
    </t>			
	<t>	
      <field>PROPERTY</field>	
      <desc>		
        <p>This field is used to validate if the field mentioned in SEQ.FLD.MAP is mandatory, required or optional.</p>				
		<p>Possible values are M, R, O</p>	
		<p>M - Mandatory</p>
		<p>R - Required</p>
	    <p>O - Optional</p> 		
        <p>Validation Rules</p>		
		 <p></p>		
        <p>Multivalue field associated with SEQUENCE</p>               		
		<p>When the field is set to M or R, while validating the ACH.ADDENDA record system will check if a value exists for this field, else system will thow 'INPUT MISSING' error message</p>
      </desc>		
    </t>		
	<t>	
      <field>FIELD.NO</field>	
      <desc>		
        <p> This field specifies the position of the field taken from the standard selection record of ACH.ADDENDA.</p>				
		<p>For internal use</p>			
        <p>Validation Rules</p>		
		 <p></p>		
        <p>No input field.</p>               				
      </desc>		
    </t>	
	<t>	
      <field>DEFAULT.VAL</field>	
      <desc>		
        <p>This is an optional field used to update the ACH.ADDENDA version with default values.</p>				
		<p>In case the SEQ.FLD.MAP field is given mandatory or required, this field is checked for default values to be populated.</p>			
		<p>If values are not available, an error is thrown.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>		
        <p>No validation.</p>               				
      </desc>		
    </t>		
	<t>	
      <field>DET.SEQ.FIELD.RTN</field>	
      <desc>		
        <p>Allows attaching any routines for manipulating the sequence number to be populated while generating the Detail records (prefixed 6) in outward file. </p>				
		<p>The general logic will be available in the outward generation service. </p>			
        <p>Wherever the sequence number generation is different for a Sec class code, a routine can be attached here. </p>		
		<p>The routine attached should accept single argument.</p>
		 <p></p>		
        <p>Multivalue field associated with SEQUENCE and must be a valid API, upto 35 characters</p>               				
      </desc>		
    </t>			
  </menu>
</t24help>