<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.CONTRACT.MASTER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds the contract definitions of all of the contract types tradable in the derivatives module.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MIN.PRICE.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>To avoid potentially infinite small price fluctuations, an exchange limits the minimum amount by which prices may change. This is movement conventionally known as the "Tick".</p>
            <p>    The tick size of a 3-month Short Sterling Contract is 0.01; therefore the quote will change by 0.01 tick.</p>
            <p>    e.g. 93.95, 93.96, 93.97 and so on.</p>
            <p>    The minimum price movement does not necessarily move by the tick size, as half and quarter price movements are now practiced in the markets of today.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 11 numeric characters available, expressed in the         same format as price</p>
            <p>    Mandatory field</p>
            <p>    Multi-valued set by price band</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.EXPIRY.PRI</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal price defaulted from EXPIRY.PRI field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Regarding the Risk country: The problem here is similar to that of the risk currency. Many instruments are issued in a tax haven and will have this as security country. The security country has tax implications, it is relevant when it comes to Double Tax Treaties and will cause a certain withholding tax. It is also relevant for the Swiss stamp duty calculation. But when Japanese Company decides to issue a Eurobond in London, the risk country will most probably be Japan in such a case. Many unit trusts are issued in Guernsey, in British Virgin Islands or in the Bermudas, but the underlying instruments come from other countries. Also it should be possible to open artificial countries such as Europe or World as risk countries. It can be estimated that about 20 % of instruments have different risk- and security countries in a security database. For this reason the security country is not generally applicable for asset management decisions.</p>
            <p>    On RISK.COUNTRY field a drop down list will be made available showing valid entries from the T24 application COUNTRY.</p>
            <p>    Each position in clients portfolio must be attributed a risk currency and risk country back office users will update this information to correctly show where the risk for an instrument lies.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    If No input this field would default to the contract         currency.</p>
            <p>    Country from the T24 application COUNTRY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The full description of the contract</p>
            <p>    Eg. Long Gilt, 3-Month Short Sterling, etc&amp;#133;</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 Alpha characters Multi-value field</p>
            <p>    Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The valid maturity days for the delivery period defined in MONTHS.FWD.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 date formula characters available</p>
            <p>    Unless MATURITY.TYPE is populated by 'DAILY' or 'OTHER'         this field is NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTIAL.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Attached with if the type of contract is an OPTION otherwise no input field. It defines whether a partial delivery is allowed for the contract or not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 characters</p>
            <p>    No Input unless CONTRACT.TYPE = &amp;#145;OPTION&amp;#146;. Input         must be YES/NO</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAR.MARGIN.CALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is defaulted from the EXCHANGE.MASTER if not populated</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 25 alpha characters</p>
            <p>    Default from EXCHANGE.MASTER Null.</p>
            <p>    Must be a valid record in DX.MARGIN.CALC with TYPE =         "VARIATION"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.SPOT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the SPOT.DATE</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc&amp;#133;., will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Date Format characters available. (YYYYMMDD)</p>
            <p>    This is part of a multi-set field with OVR.MONTH.YEAR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.ALLOWED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Choose from the drop down menu YES or NO to confirm contracts traded are allowed to settle/close out with other contracts or left open as a held position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 Alpha character allowed.</p>
            <p>    If this field is left Null it will default information         from DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER.</p>
            <p>    Input is YES/NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIRST.DELIVERY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Delivery date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    In the case of cash settled contracts, the delivery day is known as the 'final settlement day'.</p>
            <p>    e.g.</p>
            <p>    Italian Government Bond : delivery must be notified on the specified notice day</p>
            <p>    Long Gilts : delivery can be notified by the seller of the contract, on any day in a specified delivery period.(from the start of the delivery month to the expiry day)</p>
            <p>    For Options, unless cash settlement applies, the delivery day is the day on which the underlying instrument must be delivered, if the contract has been exercised.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 date format characters available.</p>
            <p>    Date Formula "+3WE,-1BD" = 3</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RND.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Rounding factor is an optional input with the following restrictions on the integer and fractional part :</p>
            <p>    1.    The fraction is restricted to the Strike price scale i.e. &lt; scale factor</p>
            <p>    2.    Unless the Price Scale  factor is 100, integer part cannot be used</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.MONTHS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maturity/Delivery months are generally set to meet the needs of the underlying cash market. A traded contract has a specified delivery month set by the relative exchange within the contract specifications. This field is used to populate the said month for that period.</p>
            <p>    The drop down menu allows the choice of numeric (1-12) or alpha ALL to populate this field. The numeric of 1-12 represents the twelve calendar months.</p>
            <p>    e.g. 3-month Short Sterling :</p>
            <p>    March, June, September, December and two serial months, such that 22 delivery months are available for trading, with the nearest 3 delivery months being consecutive calendar months.</p>
            <p>    This equates to, trading 3 months consecutively and then quarterly up to 22 periods.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 alpha or numeric characters Available</p>
            <p>    Enrich with month abbreviation from REMTEXT</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.YEAR.MONTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the year and month delivery date.</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc&amp;#133;., will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 alpha/numeric characters available.(YYYYMM)</p>
            <p>    This is a multi-set field with OVR.LAST.TRADE, OVR.FIRST.NOTICE,         OVR.LAST.NOTICE, OVR.FIRST.DLV, OVR.LAST.DLV, OVR.SPOT.DATE,         and OVR.DEC.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.PERIODS</field>
<desc>
            <p>For contracts where the available maturity months are quoted as</p>
            <p>    e.g. LIFFE Cocoa Futures - maturity on March, May, July, September, December cycle such that 10 trading months are available:</p>
            <p>    AVAIL.MONTHS = 10</p>
            <p>    MONTHS.FORWARD = OPEN</p>
            <p>    MATURITY.MONTHS = 03,05,07,09,12</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 characters</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.AMORT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the Amortisation Date.</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc&amp;#133; will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Date Format characters available. (YYYYMMDD)</p>
            <p>    This is part of a multi-set field with OVR.MONTH.YEAR</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.EXPIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Select YES to enable system expiry of options when process routine is included as part of End of Exchange processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input must be either YES or NO or blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORT.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amortise; accounting procedure that gradually reduces the cost value of a limited life or intangible asset through periodic charges to income.</p>
            <p>    The number of days that the profit or loss should be amortised over.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contract maturity type as set on the contract specifications by the relative exchange. Choose from the drop down menu, DAILY, MONTHLY, OTHER.</p>
            <p>    MATURITY.TYPE is part of the setup for trading periods on a contract specified to the relative exchange. This field works in conjunction with AVAILABLE PERIODS, MONTHS FORWARD, MATURITY MONTHS AND MATURITY DAYS</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 7 Alpha characters available</p>
            <p>    Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This records holds details pertaining to each instrument that is supposed to be trading. On input of DX.TRADE details will be updated from this record once the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER id is input and validation is taking place when a manual input of price, lot, trade dates / month etc are input.</p>
            <p>    This record hold the information on whether it is a FUTURE, OPTION or STOCK. STOCK and FUTURE behave same way it is only for internal classification.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    numeric value upto 12 characters.</p>
            <p>    mandatory input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RATE.CONTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to differentiate, whether this is an Interest rate based contract or a normal contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input allowed YES or NO</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    If</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.POST.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Time in contract lifecycle when commissions/charges applied to a trade should be charged.</p>
            <p>    TRADE charges applied on-line immediately trade verified.</p>
            <p>    SETTLEMENT charges applied when trade closed-out, matured or exercised/expired (option trades only).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 10 alpha characters</p>
            <p>    If left Null will default from DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
            <p>    Input must be either TRADE/SETTLEMENT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADING.OPEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Open trading time of the exchange as listed by contract according to the trading sessions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 5 numeric characters in TIME format</p>
            <p>    Input as HHMM or HH:MM</p>
            <p>    Multi-value field and set for multiple trading sessions,         part of TRADING.CLOSE, EXCHANGE.SESSION and EXCH-MNEMONIC</p>
            <p>    Quoted in Exchange's local time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.SCALE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The scale of which the price is denominated in.</p>
            <p>    ie. Decimal prices are in 100's. e.g. Short Sterling Future 94.59</p>
            <p>    Fraction's could be in 32</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 Numeric characters available.</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
            <p>    Defaults to 100</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED13</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADING.CLOSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Closing trading time of the exchange as listed by contract according to the trading sessions.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 5 numeric characters in TIME format</p>
            <p>    Input as HHMM or HH:MM</p>
            <p>    Multi-value set for multiple trading sessions, part of         TRADING.OPEN</p>
            <p>    Quoted in Exchange's local time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The nominal or Trading unit of the contract, specified according to the contract specifications set by the relative Exchange per trading Lot, Tonne etc&amp;#133;..</p>
            <p>    e.g. 3-month Short Sterling (LIFFE) ; Trading unit of 500,000 per lot</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 16 Numeric characters available</p>
            <p>    Default to 1 if Null</p>
            <p>    Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNITS.OF.MEASURE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The units of measure in which the contract specification is set too, by the relative exchange.</p>
            <p>    E.g. Tonnes, Bushels, Lots, etc&amp;#133;.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 Alpha characters available</p>
            <p>    Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPIRY.PRI</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price offset from strike price for expiring options.</p>
            <p>    Some exchanges specify for certain contracts a price difference where the option will automatically be exercised when they are so much "in the money" (in profit). Conversely there may be a margin where an option is "out of the money" (in loss, i.e. negative profit) but some customers may still wish to exercise. For this reason exchanges may stipulate a greater degree of loss before an option is automatically expired.</p>
            <p>    An option is out of the money, and will therefore be expired if.</p>
            <p>    For a call option (buying at the strike price):-</p>
            <p>    Market price of underlying - strike price GT (&gt;) EXPIRY.PRI</p>
            <p>    For put option (selling at the strike price):-</p>
            <p>    Strike price - market price of underlying GT (&gt;) EXPIRY.PRI</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Must be valid price scale and minimum price movement for         the underlying asset / product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifier of a price interface known to T24. Can be an actual interface or TRADE to define T24 trade entry price format.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Must be a valid Price set in DX PRICE SOURCE</p>
            <p>    Multi value set with Price Set</p>
            <p>    15 Alpha</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies an alternative easy means of referencing the Contract.</p>
            <p>    Like the ID, the Mnemonic must be unique across T24.</p>
            <p>    Care should be taken when assigning Mnemonics to Contracts and some rules should ideally be defined across the bank to allow easy identification of the Customers by their Mnemonics.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    3-10 type MNE (Uppercase alpha or numeric, first         character alpha, or ".") characters.</p>
            <p>    Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.TOLERANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The price variance allowed from the official market price, populated to the field in percentage terms.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 numeric characters available</p>
            <p>    2 Multi-value set by price band.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREM.POST.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the numeric entry for the number of Offset days is required to post an accounting entry.</p>
            <p>    'n' (being the numeric in days).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 numeric characters</p>
            <p>    If field is Null &amp;#150; will default from DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Populate this field for reporting purposes. The field allows for Regulatory, Internal, or other reporting requirements on this contract to the appropriate body/department.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 15 alpha characters</p>
            <p>    DX.GEN.DATA will contain the information for the         Regulatory Body, Internal Department or other reporting         requirements, which will populate this field.</p>
            <p>    Multi-valued set with GEN,DATA.CODE AND GEN.DATA.LIMIT.</p>
            <p>    If not populated this field will default to the         information contained in GEN.DATA.NAME in EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Trading spot date</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 date format characters available.</p>
            <p>    Date Formula "+3WE,-1BD" = 3</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.VALID.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the last date that this contract can be traded.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.DEC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the Declaration Date.</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc&amp;#133; will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Date Format characters available. (YYYYMMDD)</p>
            <p>    This is part of a multi-set field with OVR.MONTH.YEAR</p>
            <p>    No Input unless CONTRACT.TYPE = &amp;#145;OPTION&amp;#146;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.LAST.NTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the Last Notice Date.</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc&amp;#133;., will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Date Format characters available.(YYYYMMDD)</p>
            <p>    This is part of a multi-set field with OVR.MONTH.YEAR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.LAST.TRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the Last Trade Date.</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc&amp;#133;., will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Date Format characters available.(YYYYMMDD)</p>
            <p>    This is part of a multi-set field with OVR.MONTH.YEAR</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds override messages generated during input of this record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXER.PRI.MEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price offset from strike price when exercising for customers who are exchange members.</p>
            <p>    Some exchanges specify for certain contracts a price difference where the option will automatically be exercised when they are so much "in the money" (in profit). This may be to take into account the additional costs of exercising the option.</p>
            <p>    Therefore for exchange members, an option is in the money, and will therefore be exercised if.</p>
            <p>    For a call option (buying at the strike price):-</p>
            <p>    Market price of underlying - strike price GE (&gt;=) EXER.PRI.MEM</p>
            <p>    For a put option (selling at the strike price):-</p>
            <p>    Strike price - market price of underlying GE (&gt;=) EXER.PRI.MEM</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Must be valid price scale and minimum price movement for         the underlying asset / product.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Delivery method for specified contract at maturity</p>
            <p>    CASH - Delivery of cash equivalent to contract realized value</p>
            <p>    PHYSICAL - Physical delivery of underlying instrument</p>
            <p>    NONE - No delivery method specified (defaults to NONE)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 alpha characters</p>
            <p>    This is a mandatory field</p>
            <p>    Default is NONE</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULT.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price multiplication factor. Defaults to 1 if null.</p>
            <p>    Example: LIFFE 3 Month Short Sterling contract price quoted ref full year&amp;#146;s interest- MULT.FACTOR = 0.25</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 11 characters</p>
            <p>    No Change field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Details of the contract specification currency are entered in this field as set by the relative exchange. This is the user-defined alpha currency code</p>
            <p>    This field contains the currency code and is entered in Alpha format. This code comprises of three alpha characters as defined in the currency table. It is recommended to use the standard SWIFT currency code, which is the internationally recognised convention for currency codes. The following are examples of ISO/SWIFT codes:</p>
            <p>    - USD = US Dollars - GBP = Pounds Sterling - DEM = Deutsche Marks - FRF = French Francs</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">    3 characters  </p>
                <p value="2">Corresponds to a record id on the         Currency table.</p>
                <p value="3" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">    Non Mandatory Input</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rate for the financial bond future, expressed in terms of percentage. The rate must be as published by the exchange.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input allowed only for BOND futures.</p>
            <p>    Mandatory when financial bond future contract class is defined in PM.DX.PARAMETER for PM processing.</p>
            <p>    No change after authorization.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The last day on which notice can be given that physical delivery is intended, or expected, on a futures contract</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 date format characters available.</p>
            <p>    Date Formula "+3WE,-1BD" = 3</p>
            <p>    No Input if MATURITY TYPE = DAILY or OTHER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVERAGE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Average Price</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE.INTERVAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The valid Strike price interval on an Option contract. Quoted in the contract Currency.</p>
            <p>    e.g. exercise Price Intervals for 3-month Short Sterling Option</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    0.25 (i.e 0.25%); 94.00, 94.25, 94.50</p>
            <p>    Therefore                 the interval movements are 0.25</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 14 numeric characters</p>
            <p>    No Input unless CONTRACT.TYPE = "OPTION"</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.LAST.DELIV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the Last Delivery Date.</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc&amp;#133;., will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Date Format characters available.(YYYYMMDD)</p>
            <p>    This is part of a multi-set field with OVR.MONTH.YEAR</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.UNIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The unit of measure relative to which the price is quoted.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 10 alpha characters available</p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
            <p>    For Future Use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREM.POST.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the choice of when the premium should be posted to an account. Choose from the drop down menu of "TRADE", "SETTLEMENT" ".</p>
            <p>    TRADE; The premium will be paid or received in full on the trade date.</p>
            <p>    SETTLEMENT; The premium will be posted on the day of settlement, close/expiry of the trade.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 10 alpha characters</p>
            <p>    If field is left Null - will default from DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIFE.UNDERLYING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the original life of the underlying instrument for this derivative in days ,or months or years. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input allowed only when INT.RATE.CONTRACT is set to “YES” .</p>
            <p>    Should be specified in number of days or month  or years. Eg :- 20D, 5M, 2Y and so on.</p>
            <p>    Mandatory when financial bond or interest rate future contract class is defined in     PM.DX.PARAMETER for PM processing.</p>
            <p>    No change after authorization.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the risk level of this particular product.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input as per virtual table RISK.LEVEL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Limit related to reporting/regulatory procedure named in GEN.DATA.NAME</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 11 numeric characters available.</p>
            <p>    Multi-value set with GEN.DATA.NAME</p>
            <p>    If not populated this field will default to the         information contained in GEN.DATA.NAME in EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.EXER.PRI.NON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal price defaulted from EXER.PRI.NON field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field requires the name of the Exchange on which this contract is traded.</p>
            <p>    eg. LIFFE, EUREX, CBOT etc&amp;#133;&amp;#133;</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 10 characters (Mnemonic or Numeric Id of the         Exchange)</p>
            <p>    Must be a valid ID/Mnemonic on DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
            <p>    Mandatory input</p>
            <p>    No change</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>B2B.CO.OK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines at the contract master level whether the trades covered by this contract master record can undergo back to back closeout</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Defaults from      DX.CONTRACT.CLASS but can be amended manually</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the type of rounding method to be applied, which can be one of the following:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    STANDARD - It will round either upwards or downwards whichever is nearer integer, to the required number of decimal places</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    UP               -  It will round upwards to the required number of decimal places</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    DOWN        -  It will round downwards to the required number of decimal places</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input can be STANDARD, UP or DOWN, default being STANDARD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of option traded, normal (vanilla) or Exotic.</p>
            <p>    Exotic; Digital, Currency, etc&amp;#133;..</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    This multivalue set will contain a list of valid option.types for this contract.code Or ALL. This is linked to a record in</p>
            <p>    DX.OPTION.TYPE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 alpha characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.SET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies a price set that holds prices for this contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Must be a valid Price set in DX PRICE SET</p>
            <p>    Multi-value set with Price Source</p>
            <p>    15 Alpha</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RISK.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the Risk Currency, the most frequent examples are unit trusts. A German Fund Administration might decide to issue a US equity fund, and, because it might be more convenient for the investors, might issue and price the units in Euro. The legal security currency is Euro. But if the Dollar changes its value to the Euro, this will have an impact on the market value of this fund because the underlying equities are mostly exposed to the USD. Another example is a European Bond Fund quoted in Sterling and issued in the UK. The risk currency in such a case could be Euro, but could as well be artificial like 'European currency'. Another example is a German Certificate of a US company. It is issued in Germany, priced in Euro, but the risk currency is not Euro but USD.  Apart from the asset type breakdown, within the field of asset management, the risk currency is usually considered to be one of the most important attributes of an instrument. As a general rule about 10 % of all instruments have a different security and risk currency.</p>
            <p>    On RISK.CURRENCY field a drop down list will be made available showing valid entries from the T24 application currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Default to trade currency if no input</p>
            <p>    Taken from theT24 applicationn"CURRENCY"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of contract that has been traded on an exchange.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">    Mandatory input</p>
                <p value="2">    Up to 10 Alphabetic characters </p>
                <p value="3">    Input must be one of the following: OPTION/FUTURE</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNDERLYING</field>
<desc>
            <p>The financial instrument, equity or commodity upon which a futures or options contract is based.</p>
            <p>    These may be a specific instrument, as in the case of stock options, or maybe a notional instrument, as in the case of the Euro Bund futures.</p>
            <p>    In the case of many Options, such as the Long Gilt and Euro Bond options on LIFFE, the underlying instrument is a corresponding futures contract.</p>
            <p>    This field requires to be set as 'OTHER' for Interest rate Caps, Floors and Swaptions</p>
            <p>    If underlying is cash Delivery currency field is mandatory</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 12 Alpha characters</p>
            <p>    Input must be a valid record on either DX.CONTRACT.MASTER         or SECURITY.MASTER, or 'CASH' or 'OTHER'</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The basis on which the price for this contract is quoted.</p>
            <p>    Choose from the drop down menu of INTEREST or NORMAL.</p>
            <p>    e.g. 3-month Short Sterling; 100-Libor rate = Quote Price, therefore is interest rate based.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Alpha characters available</p>
            <p>    Default to NORMAL</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.EXER.PRI.MEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal price defaulted from EXER.PRI.MEM field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TICK.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Derived from the "Tick Size" is the "Tick Value". Since the contract has a fixed size the smallest price movement can be given a monetary value.</p>
            <p>    e.g.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 11 numeric characters</p>
            <p>    Mandatory field</p>
            <p>    Multi-valued set by price band</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.FMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The display format of the price for the relevant price interface quoted by the quote vendor.</p>
            <p>    There must be an entry for PRICE.SOURCE 'TRADE' which represents the format that the price can be entered in on DX.TRADE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 20 PFMT Alpha Numeric characters available</p>
            <p>    Must have an entry for 'TRADE'</p>
            <p>    Multi-value set with PRICE SOURCE</p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.FIRST.DELIV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the First Delivery Date.</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc., will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Date Format characters available.(YYYYMMDD)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    This is part of a multi-set field with OVR.MONTH.YEAR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.ASSIGNMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The routine used for automatic assignment of options. For exchange regulated contracts, the routine must meet any rules governing the assigment of options. See application DX.CO.ASSIGN.AUTO for details on running automatic assignment.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input must be a valid record on DX.OBJECT.LIBRARY</p>
            <p>    25 Alpha</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.CONT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the id of the new contract master record created on corporate action, which supersedes this contract master record</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    No input field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXER.PRI.NON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price offset from strike price when exercising for customers who are not exchange members.</p>
            <p>    Some exchanges specify for certain contracts a price difference where the option will automatically be exercised when they are so much "in the money" (in profit). This may be to take into account the additional costs of exercising the option.</p>
            <p>    Therefore for non exchange members, an option is in the money, and will therefore be exercised if.</p>
            <p>    For a call option (buying at the strike price):-</p>
            <p>    Market price of underlying - strike price GE (&gt;=) EXER.PRI.NON</p>
            <p>    For a put option (selling at the strike price):-</p>
            <p>    Strike price - market price of underlying GE (&gt;=) EXER.PRI.NON</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Must be valid price scale and minimum price movement for         the underlying asset / product</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIRST.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The first notice period</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 date format characters available.</p>
            <p>    Date Formula "+3WE,-1BD" = 3</p>
            <p>    No Input if MATURITY TYPE = DAILY or OTHER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.PRICE.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Main price data such as the price basis (INTEREST for interest-rate basis prices, NORMAL otherwise) are same for all prices on a contract, but in same cases values like tick size and value may vary when the contract price falls within different bands. This is catered for by mulvaluing the PRICE.BAND to INT.PRICE.BAND set.</p>
            <p>    The value is calculated by price band / tick size x tick value. This is a system generated field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 11 character</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    No Input field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The code for the relevant price of the contract on the relevant exchange or price vendor system, the "Ticker Symbol". This can be left as to "LOOK UP" which allows DX.PRICE.INTERFACE to determine the format.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 20 Alpha characters available</p>
            <p>    Multi-value set with PRICE SOURCE</p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVERAGE.DPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    1 Numeric character allowed</p>
            <p>    Default to '2' if not populated/null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TICK.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The unit of quotation allowed is conventionally known as the "TICK". To avoid potentially infinitely small price fluctuations, the relative exchange, limits the minimum amount by which prices may change. This is set within the contract specification as the tick size.</p>
            <p>    The tick size for a 3-month Short Sterling future is 0.01.</p>
            <p>    The tick size for a 3-month Short Sterling option to a level of 7 price units is 0.005</p>
            <p>    The tick size for a 3-month Eurodollar futures is 1/32.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 11 Numeric characters available</p>
            <p>    Mandatory field</p>
            <p>    Multi-value set with Price Band</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE.SCALE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Basis of the strike price for this contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 11 numeric characters available</p>
            <p>    NO INPUT unless CONTRACT.TYPE is OPTION</p>
            <p>    Default to PRICE.SCALE</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEC.TIME.CALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The latest time on the expiration date on which the Seller must accept notice of Exercise as specified in a confirmation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 5 characters in TIME format</p>
            <p>    No Input unless CONTRACT.TYPE = &amp;#145;OPTION&amp;#146;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field requires the Code Identifier provided by an Exchange for clearing and reporting purposes. No input is required if it does not differ from the T24 mnemonic.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 10 Alpha characters long.</p>
            <p>    Default to mnemonic if NULL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>In addition to specifying a delivery cycle, contracts also specify the precise time when trading in a particular delivery month will cease. This will generally relate to a particular business day in the month. It follows that this does not necessarily tie into the last business day of the month.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    e.g. The 3</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 date format characters available.</p>
            <p>    Date Formula "+3WE,-1BD" = 3</p>
            <p>    No Input if MATURITY.TYPE = DAILY or OTHER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.FIRST.NTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the use of a manual input date to override the field populated by a formula used to calculate the First Notice Date.</p>
            <p>    When populated, the date formula in the previously populated LAST.TRADE, FIRST NOTICE, etc&amp;#133;., will not be used in the fixing and calculation routine for this contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 8 Date Format characters available.(YYYYMMDD)</p>
            <p>    This is part of a multi-set field with OVR.MONTH.YEAR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.EXPIRY.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of business days after the specified option declaration date to delay system expiring of options. This is to allow an additional period after the declaration date when automatic assignment of options can take place.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Integer value</p>
            <p>    Must be less than PRICE.DAYS for EOE.PRICE.SET on DX.PARAMETER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.IND.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Alternate Index Id releated to the listed ALT.IND.NAME.</p>
            <p>    The contents of this field will be validated against using the routine identified in the DX.PARAMETER record when the list of ALT.IND.NAMES is taken from.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    No Input Field</p>
            <p>    Input defaults from DX.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>    35 Alpha</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.IND.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies a list of possible alternate ID Names thar can be used to identify this contract in the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    No Input Field</p>
            <p>    Input defaults from DX.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>    35 Alpha</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amortise; accounting procedure that gradually reduces the cost value of a limited life or intangible asset through periodic charges to income.</p>
            <p>    The start date that the amortisation should occur from.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 Date Format Characters</p>
            <p>    Input as a Date Format</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.DELIVERY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Last day on which, for a given futures or options contract, delivery can take place.</p>
            <p>    In the case of cash settled contracts, the delivery day is known as the 'final settlement day'.</p>
            <p>    e.g. below</p>
            <p>    Long Gilts and some Commodity Contracts: delivery can be notified by the seller of the contract, on any day in a specified delivery period.(from the Start/First of the delivery month to the Expiry/Last day)</p>
            <p>    For Options, unless cash settlement applies, the delivery day is the day on which the underlying instrument must be delivered, if the contract has been exercised.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 date format characters available.</p>
            <p>    Date Formula "+3WE,-1BD" = 3</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of instruments being traded on the relative exchange.</p>
            <p>    e.g. Bond, Interest Rate, Metals, Softs, Stock Index and so on,.</p>
            <p>If the Contract Class selected has a Contract Type as FX-OPTION, currency fields and price definition fields will become NOINPUT for FX-OTC options.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>    Up to 15 Alpha characters available</p>
            <p>    Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.PRICE.CALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>THIS FIELD IS NO LONGER USED</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Eg : Australian Bills &amp; Bonds on the SFE</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.BAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Some contracts are subject to a price band, specified on the contract specification set by the relative Exchange. This field works in conjunction with Tick Size, Tick Value, and Minimum Price Movement.</p>
            <p>    An example of price band contract is the 3 Month Short Sterling Option;</p>
            <p>    &lt;7(note not equal too) price units the Tick Size is 0.01, Tick Value is 12.50(6.25 1/2 tick) and the minimum price movement is 0.005</p>
            <p>    &gt;7 price units the Tick Size is 0.01, Tick Value is 12.50 and the minimum price movement is 0.01</p>
            <p>    This equates; the movement up to 7 price units will be per half tick and above 7 price units per one tick.</p>
            <p>    The set is then multi-valued where the,</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 16 characters available in "CURRENCY'"         format or Alpha "OPEN" for no price band.</p>
            <p>    Multi-value Set with Tick Size, Tick Value, Minimum Price         Movement and Price Tolerance.</p>
            <p>    Price Band, field is shown as an "Up Too"         figure.</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifier code used by the Regulatory Body, Internal or other reporting system for this contract</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 15 alpha characters.</p>
            <p>    Multi-value set with GEN.DATA.NAME</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Last Date by which a customer may exercise an option. The exercise date (European Options) or last exercise date (American Options) for this contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 35 date format characters</p>
            <p>    No Input unless CONTRACT.TYPE = "OPTION"</p>
            <p>    Date Formula "+3WE,-1BD" = 3</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED14</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.STYLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rule of settlement of an option according to the type populated in this field, choose from the drop down menu:</p>
            <p>    AMERICAN; An option that may be exercised at any time prior to its expiry date</p>
            <p>    EUROPEAN; An option that may only be exercised on its expiry date.</p>
            <p>    CARRIBEAN:</p>
            <p>    A type of option that can only be exercised on predetermined dates, usually every month.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 10 alpha characters available</p>
            <p>    No Input unless CONTRACT.TYPE is "OPTION"</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.CONTROL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the percentage margin allowable on this Contract.</p>
            <p>    If not entered, the margin allowed for the "SUB.ASSET.TYPE" will be used.</p>
            <p>    Example: 70 = 70% Margin (Contract is worth 70% actual value for Client valuation purposes).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 5 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>    Must exist on the MARGIN.CONTROL file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MONTHS.FWD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The available months forward to trade according to the contract specifications set by the relative exchange.</p>
            <p>    e.g. 3-month Short Sterling :</p>
            <p>    March, June, September, December and two serial months, such that 22 delivery months are available for trading, with the nearest 3 delivery months being consecutive calendar months.</p>
            <p>    This equates to, trading 3 months consecutively and then quarterly up to 22 periods.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 4 Alpha characters available</p>
            <p>    OPEN (Infinite availability) can be used to populate the         field or if Null it will default to the field from DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
            <p>    Multi-value set with MATURITY MONTHS, MATURITY DAYS</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency to be delivered on maturity of the contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 CCY character available</p>
            <p>    No Input if DELVERY.METHOD is Not CASH</p>
            <p>    Mandatory if DELIVERY.METHOD is CASH.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTINGENT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value per lot to be used in calculating the off-balance sheet liability/asset posting to be made when contract traded.</p>
            <p>    If left blank, system will use 'contract value' i.e. internal price per lot to make posting.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 19 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INIT.MARGIN.CALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is defaulted from the EXCHANGE.MASTER if not populated</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 25 alpha characters</p>
            <p>    Default from EXCHANGE.MASTER if Null.</p>
            <p>    Must be a valid record in DX.MARGIN.CALC with TYPE =         "INITIAL"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.EXERCISE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Select YES to enable system exercise of options when process routine is included as part of End of Exchange processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input must be either YES or NO or blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ASSET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the group of like Contracts, which are reported together.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    1-5 Alphanumeric characters &amp;#150; code must exist on the         SUB.ASSET.TYPE table.</p>
            <p>    Mandatory Input</p>
            <p>    No Change Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEC.TIME.PUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The latest time on the expiration date on which the Seller must accept notice of Exercise as specified in a confirmation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 5 characters in TIME format</p>
            <p>    No Input unless CONTRACT.TYPE = &amp;#145;OPTION&amp;#146;</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.POST.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Days offset to apply settlement postings</p>
            <p>    Validation</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input defaults from DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
            <p>    No Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.POST.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of days offset from charge posting date to actually generate postings.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 characters</p>
            <p>    If left null will default from DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the name of the Contract in a more descriptive form, and will be used for on-line enrichments in any field where a Contract ID or Mnemonic has been input.</p>
            <p>    A clear and unique identification of the Contract must be entered in this field. When entering or displaying data where a Contract ID or Mnemonic is involved, the content of this field will be used as the enrichment of the Contract number/Mnemonic.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    3-35 characters. Multi value field</p>
            <p>    Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.DPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of decimal places for the price quote. This also changes the number of decimal places in the multi-value set of Price Band.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    1 Numeric character allowed</p>
            <p>    Default number of decimals from the CURRENCY if NULL.</p>
            <p>    Reformat the other prices e.g. PRICE BAND</p>
            <p>    No Change field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.DPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Decimal places for the CONTRACT SIZE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    1 Numeric character allowed</p>
            <p>    Default to '0' if not populated/null</p>
            <p>    No Change Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on value provided in this field update to table DX.CONTRACT.DATES happens. Options allowed to this field are CALC.ONLY, TABLE.CALC.UPDATE and TABLE.ONLY.</p>
            <p>When set to CALC.ONLY or NULL system always calculates the dates based on the formules provided to date fields.</p>
            <p>When set to TABLE.CALC.UPDATE system referes to the formulae in dates field and calculates the date and updates to DX.CONTRACT.DATES.</p>
            <p> When set to TABLE.ONLY user has to manually update the DX.CONTRACT.DATES from where the dates are considered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUPPRESS.UNDERLYING</field>
<desc>
            <p>When set to YES will suppress the creation of underlying during closeout process. Defaults with value set in SUPPRESS.UNDERLYING field of DX.PARAMETER. Can be changed for individual contract level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 3 characters</p>
            <p>    YES or NO are allowed values</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KICKIN.EXPIRE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When set to YES and the exotic event triggered the exotic trade should get automatically expired by DX.CO.EXPIRE.MANUAL. This value set here can be overwritten at  trade level.</p>
            <p>
               <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Upto 3 alphanumeric values</p>
            <p>        Valid inputs are either YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOSS.MARGIN.CNTRL</field>
<desc>
            <p>    Indicates the percentage loss margin allowable on this Contract.</p>
            <p>    If not entered, the margin allowed for the "SUB.ASSET.TYPE" will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 5 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>    Must exist on the MARGIN.CONTROL file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The settlement mode of the option contract is specified in this field. The option can be physically settled (Delivery/Receipt of the underlying takes place )or Cash settled (The cash difference is settled). Possible values are PHYSICAL or CASH. NULL value would by default use physical settlement</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLE.INSTRUMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The alternative settlement instrument for equity option when not given settled with equity in UNDERLYING field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.PAYOUT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the delivery method is cash, and value given in this field then the payout for an cash option to happen in this currency else Forex trade gets created. The currency should be different from trade and delivery currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MTM.REQUIRED</field>
<desc>
            <p>When set to YES alone Mark-to-Market (MTM) entry is posted.This gets defaulted from DX.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MTM.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The allowed values are PROFIT.LOSS and OPTION.VALUE. When set to PROFIT.LOSS the difference between trade and market cost is posted. When set as OPTION.VALUE the entire market cost is posted on the first day.This gets defaulted from DX.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MTM.DIFFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The allowed values are ADJUST and REBOOK. When set to ADJUST the difference between pevious day and todays MTM amount is posted as entry. Whereas when set to REBOOK the previously posted MTM is reversed and the new MTM amount is posted.This gets defaulted from DX.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MTM.SPEC</field>
<desc>
            <p>When MTM.SPEC is set to YES, instead of raising the internal account entry based on ACCOUNT.CLASS category SPEC entry is raised.This gets defaulted from DX.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FTT.EXEMPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When set to YES it means the Financial Transaction Tax is exempted for the contract. This gets defaulted at trade level which can be overwritten.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DOMICILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid Country code can be specified. The field is for information purpose.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

