<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.CUSTOMER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INTERNAL.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the frequency a particular report is to be produced for internal purposes. The type of reports are detailed in INTERNAL.REPS.</p>
            <p>Note : This is a default frequency it is to be used in conjunction with the multi valued INTERNAL.REPS field to define the various reports required by a particular client, and the frequency of those reports.</p>
            <p>By defining internal and external reports the user is able to print all external reports on high quality statement paper (possibly pre-printed for this precise purpose). Different printers can be attributed to these reports to avoid unnecessary paper and time wastage.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 17 alpha characters available</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid frequency on the frequency table</p>
            <p>Multi-value set with INTERNAL.REPS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Investment Exchanges available to populate this field. Use SHORT.NAME from DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER or 'ALL' for all possible exchanges.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 10 numeric characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If in DX.PARAMETER field ALLOW.ALL.EXCH is populated with 'Y' (YES), then this field will default to 'ALL' if left null/blank.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field is a mandatory input field if ALLOW.ALL.EXCH is not populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a Multi-value set with TRADING.ALLOWED, SPEC.OR.HEDGE, EXCH.MEMBER, MARG.WEIGHTING, CONTRACT and TRADE.CON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field illustrates the capacity in which a client is acting. A client may well act in one or all of these capacities, hence the multi valued field to cater for this eventuality. Only 'CUSTOMER', 'BROKER', 'COUNTERPARTY'and 'EXCHANGE' may be entered.</p>
            <p>CUSTOMER would either Own-book or a customer of the bank.(Portfolio's would be required).</p>
            <p>BROKER someone who executes or clears trades on behalf of the bank/customer. This does not require any portfolio's to be set up.</p>
            <p>COUNTERPARTY This is used in the same way as Broker although portfolio's can be set-up.</p>
            <p>EXCHANGE if an Exchange member then the Exchange on which the user has membership need to be set-up in DX.CUSTOMER (For Future Use)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 12 alpha characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be one of the following: CUSTOMER,         BROKER,COUNTERPARTY, EXCHANGE</p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.ACC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Currency for MARGIN.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 3 CCY Format alpha characters</p>
            <p>Default from MARGIN.ACCOUNT is MARGIN.ACCOUNT entered         first.</p>
            <p>Do not allow duplicate currencies in the multivalue set.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPEC.OR.HEDGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Speculative or Hedge trading, the type of business this customer trades within the market of the Investment Exchanges. Choose from the drop down menu of SPECULATOR, HEDGE or &lt;BLANK&gt;.</p>
            <p>Speculative: Dealing in a commodity or financial asset with a view to obtaining a profit on the prospective change in the market value of the item in question</p>
            <p>Hedge: Dealing in a commodity or financial transaction, tending to the opposite effect of another transaction engaged to minimize a potential loss on the latter.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 10 alpha characters available</p>
            <p>If this field is not populated it will default to being &lt;BLANK&gt;.</p>
            <p>Part of a Multi-value set with EXCHANGE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID for the special account used for margin payments and postings separate from the customers main account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 16 accounting characters</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid ACCOUNT on file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Minimum Balance controlled by 'Maintenance Margin'</p>
            <p />
            <p>If MARGIN.ACC.CCY has been entered first, the user should         validate to ensure account currency is the same as MARGIN.ACC.CCY</p>
            <p>If MARGIN.ACC.CCY is blank, populate MARGIN.ACC.CCY with         account currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADING.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The trading status of the customer, a Regulatory Classification. Choose from the drop down menu 'HOUSE'_'SEGREGATED'_'RESERVED'</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 10 alpha characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input must be one of the following : HOUSE/SEGREGATED/RESERVED</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Group(s) this customer is a part off.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 Alpha characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid ID on DX.GROUPING</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the statement frequency desired by the client (monthly, quarterly, half-yearly etc). While this frequency may be superceded at SEC.ACC.MASTER level, this is where the default statement frequency for the customer should be recorded.</p>
            <p>At SEC.ACC.MASTER level the user can store different frequencies for the reports requested within this file. Thus a client with more than one security account can have the reports printed at different intervals.</p>
            <p>Example: B = Next working day. Format is date BSNSS</p>
            <p>Note : This is a default frequency and is to be used in conjunction with the multi-value EXTERNAL.REPS field to define the various reports required by a particular client and the frequency of those reports.</p>
            <p>By defining internal and external reports the user is able to print all external reports on high quality statement paper (possibly pre-printed for this precise purpose). Different printers can be attributed to these reports to avoid unnecessary paper and time wastage.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>17 characters frequency code. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid frequency on the frequency tables.</p>
            <p>Multi-value set with EXTERNAL.REPS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.SETT.NAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any added text settlement instructions for information purposes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 alpha characters of free text allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.MEMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Is this customer a member of the relative Investment Exchange of Exchanges? Choose from the drop down menu of CLEARING, NONE or TRADING.</p>
            <p>CLEARING; This allows the members to clear all trades through the Clearing House appointed by the Investment Exchange.</p>
            <p>TRADING; This allows the members to only trade on the Investment Exchange without the clearing facility.</p>
            <p>NONE; This customer is of neither stature above, neither a member of any Investment Exchange nor Clearing House.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 8 alpha characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The Customer must exist on a file in EXCHANGE.MEMBERSHIP</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Part of a Multi-value set with EXCHANGE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Sub Multi-value field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input must be one of the following : TRADING/CLEARING/NONE/BOTH</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Default is NONE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARG.WEIGHTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for the 'Bump-UP-Factor' or additional margin requirement from a customer of whom we the bank/broker do not have the utmost confidence in. The figure is calculated in percentage terms.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 5 numeric characters available</p>
            <p>Range of 0-999</p>
            <p>Part of a Multi-value set with EXCHANGE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORTING.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Currency used for this customer when reporting during revaluation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 3 CCY characters available</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Defaulted from SEC.ACC.MASTER                 portfolio 1. If no portfolio exists then default                 from the COMPANY&amp;#146;s local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AU.CT.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows this user to define how a customer wishes to automatically closeout different classes of contract.</p>
            <p>For example, for all BOND class contracts they may wish to use first in first out (FIFO) processing. And for all others last in first out(LIFO)</p>
            <p>There in multivalue one the user should setup BOND and in multivalue two ALL with FIFO and LIFO associated with these items.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a vaild DX.CONTRACT.CLASS or "ALL"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AU.SETT.DELAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines how long after a trade takes place a trade can be automatically closed out, dependant on the current DX.CONTRACT.CLASS</p>
            <p>For example, a customer may have chosen to hold there BOND positions for three days after trade date before any action is taken on them, or the user may use this to for high risk clients whos position are often in dispute.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional</p>
            <p>Numeric</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AU.SETT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defined how a customer wishes to have the trades automatically closedout for a particular DX.CONTRACT.CLASS, the user may choose to enter a DX.CLOSEOUT.METHOD or leave the item blank.</p>
            <p>If the user leaves this field blank then for the chosen DX.CONTRACT.CLASS no automatic closeouts will take place.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid DX.CLOSEOUT.METHOD</p>
            <p>Optional.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the record key to this DX.CUSTOMER record.  This will be identical to the corresponding CUSTOMER record key.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERN.REPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-value field used to record the reports, valuations, etc. required by internal sources (i.e. the account executives).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 5 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-value set with INTERNAL.FREQ</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERN.REPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>While STATEMENT.FREQ dictates when and how often a client desires a report or statement, this multi value field records the various types of reports and statements requested.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 5 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-value set with EXTERNAL.FREQ</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Type(s) of combined equity statement required by the customer. Choose from the drop down menu 'BOTH'_'DAILY'_'MONTHLY'_'NONE'</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 7 Alpha characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input must be one of the following : BOTH/DAILY/MONTHLY/NONE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>CLR.BROKER</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>BROKER.REMITTANCE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>BROKER.FTT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
