<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.CO.ASSIGN.AUTO</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines the contract currency.</p>
        <p>The option trade is selected based on the contract currency.</p>
        <p>Validation Rule:</p>
        <p>Must be a valid currency in CURRENCY table and is a mandatory field for FX-OTC options.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.CCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines the delivery currency.</p>
        <p>The option trade is selected based on the delivery currency.</p>
        <p>Validation Rule:
</p>
        <p>Must be a valid currency in CURRENCY table and is a mandatory field for FX-OTC options.
</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The STRIKE.PRICE of the trades to be assigned.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECLARATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The declaration date calculated from DX.CONTRACT.MASTER date formula.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    NOINPUT</p>
            <p>    Display date format, e.g 24 JAN 2000</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contract code of the option to be expired</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Should be valid for DX.CONTRACT.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STRIKE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Intenal strike price defaulted from STRIKE field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maturity / delivery month of the option to be expired.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 11 characters in DATE format </p>
            <p>   The field CONTRACT.CODE must be populated prior to this         field </p>
            <p>    Must be in the format: MONTHLY TRADES = Month/Year e.g.         SEP00 </p>
            <p>    DAILY TRADES = Day/Month/Year e.g. 15SEP00 </p>
            <p>    Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the Override messages which the user agreed to during Input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the Override, the full text of the actual Override Message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNAUTH.AUTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>If set as AUTHORISED this field will create all close out records with status of authorised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    One         of AUTHORISED or UNAUTHORISED or blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.ASSIGN.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total number of lots which must be assigned to customers found selling this option.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Integer value</p>
            <p>    Must be equal or less than total number of oustanding         open sell lots.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This application allows the automatic assignment of options to customers who are on primary side of a trade and have sold the option concerned. The user enters the option details (contract code, maturity, strike and call or put) and the number of lots to be assigned. The process of selecting customers is determined by the routine defined in AUTO.ASSIGNMENT field in DX.CONTRACT.MASTER for the option contract.</p>
            <p>    The assignment process is activated when the record is Authorised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Key consisting of DXCOASNAT prefix followd by julian date         and a sequence number</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALL.PUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Select CALL or PUT for option series.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Should be one of CALL or PUT</p>
            <p>    Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSEOUT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key of the associated DX.CLOSEOUT record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.STYLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The OPTION.STYLE from the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER e.g. AMERICAN.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>The operand field is used to select the trades based on the strike quote provided. Available operands are EQ, GE and LE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE.QUOTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the strike price in the quote currency which is STRIKE.QUOTE in trade.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the market price of the security at the time of exercise.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.SETTLE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the delivery currency for the options with underlying as SECURITY.MASTER when the SETTLEMENT.METHOD is CASH.</p>
            <p>The exchange rate between this currency and contract currency is defined in DLV.CCY.RATE field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DLV.CCY.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the exchange rate between trade currency and settlement currecny.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLE.INSTRUMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The alternate settlement instrument which is settled on exercise.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.INSTR.CONT.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contract size of the alternate settlement instrument which is mandatory when settled using alternate underlying.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.INSTR.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The price of the alternate settlement instrument which is mandatory when settled using alternate underlying.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency in which the SPOT.EXCHANGE.RATE is quoted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the current exchange rate between the currency pairs of an FX option quoted in the QUOTE.CCY i.e base currency being the strike quote currency for generic FX-OTC options and delivery currency for fx options.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.PAYOUT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency in which the payout is to be made for FX options.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.PAYOUT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the exchange rate between QUOTE.CCY and FX.PAYOUT.CCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds DX.TRANSACTION reference which gets selected based on the conditions given in selection fields.Value to the field gets defaulted only when SETTLEMENT.METHOD in contract master is set to CASH.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the delivery currency for equity options cash payout and FX.PAYOUT.CCY for fx options cash payout.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the cash payout amount calculated in settlement account currency. i.e in the SETTLEMENT.CCY field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

