<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.CO.CONTROL.HIST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Closeouts (or settlements) are used to match opposing buy and sell positions within the same contract to effectively close the open positions and realise any profit or loss due. </p>
            <p>Once the settlement has occurred the position will be closed-out and any profit/loss will be realised. Commission and charges also due to be paid at settlement time will also be posted.</p>
            <p>Within the derivatives module there are three methods of closing out trades;</p>
            <p />
            <p>The first involves matching opposing buy and sell positions within the same contract to effectively close the open positions and realise any profit or loss due. </p>
            <p>The second form of closeout occurs when a position is held until maturity. This also results in a position being closed and subsequent cash or physical delivery taking place, this is also known as a "cash" or "maturity" settlement. In this case the open trades are in effect settled against a pseudo trade. For futures this trade would be performed at the EDSP (Exchange Delivery Settlement Price). For options no psuedo trades are created, for trades where premium was not paid a trade the trades/transactions are closed out against each other on the same way as a manual closeout, where the premium has already been paid these are Cash Settled against the Original Premium Price.</p>
            <p>Automatic settlement is performed by entering a series of selection criteria into the DX.CO.AUTO.INPUT application. Using the selection criteria the system will attempt to create a closeout or a series of closeout records which match lots again lot. The method by which the system does this can be setup in the DX.CLOSEOUT.METHOD application and each customers closeout method can be defined on their DX.CUSTOMER record. If no method is defined then no         automatic settlement will be performed. </p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.REV</field>
<desc>
            <p>If set to "YES" then reversals are not allowed for this closeout.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multivalued list of trades in this closeout.</p>
            <p>This may include PSEUDO trades. These trades do not exist on the DX.TRADE files and only exist as part of an individual maturity style closeout.   </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Mutlivalued list of trade transactions, from the DX.TRANSACTION file, that are associated with this closeout.</p>
            <p>This may include PSEUDO transactions. </p>
            <p>N.B. These transactions do not exist on the DX.TRANSACTION files and only exist as part of a individual maturity style closeout.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT.TCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax Amount in trade currency.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price at maturity of the contracts traded and associated with this closeout. For 'OPTION' trades, this is the Maturity 'PREMIUM' price.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Only applicable for option close outs.</p>
            <p>The price at which an option holder has the right to buy (Call Options) or sell (Put Options) the underlying instrument, or to cash-settle the option if appropriate, to exercise the option.</p>
            <p>All trades and transaction associated with this closeout will have the same Strike Price</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total value of the lots sold, stored in the closeout currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DET.RES03</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.MATURITY.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maturity price in standard T24 derivatives internal price format.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEST.CUST.PORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid id from the CUSTOMER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customer for who the close out occurred. May be the Bank's own book or an external customer or broker</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid T24 customer.</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid record within the DX.CUSTOMER and CUSTOMER File. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DET.RES05</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STRIKE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the strike price in internal format for T24 calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Commission Curreny - not currently used</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.BUY.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The buy value of each transaction in the close out.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total Commission - not currently used</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.CPARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid id from the CUSTOMER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Contract code for this closeout.  All transactions and trades associated with this Closeout will be of this contract type.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Set to YES if fee is required else set to NO</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Upto 3 alphanumeric values</p>
            <p>Valid inputs are either YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.REV.REASON</field>
<desc>
            <p>If BLOCK.REV is set to yes then this field explains why</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The delivery period or prompt date of the contract transacted. All transactions associated with this closeout will have matching maturity dates.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.PANDL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total value of the profit and loss for this closeout. The figure is held in the CURRENCY currecy.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Tax Code for the side of the trade that was closed out.</p>
            <p>This is a key to a record on the TXN.TAX.CODE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tax amount in account currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The status of this close out. Maybe one of the following</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>RUNNING. The closeout is currently taking place.</p>
            <p />
            <p>ACTIVE. The closeout has occurred. I.e the trades have been matched and the close out is now waiting for authorisation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>DELETED. The closeout has         been reversed/bust</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Only applicable for option close outs.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The option type of the trades/transactions which constiute this closout</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only CALL or PUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.SELL.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The sell value of each transaction in the close out.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>How the close out was created.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>MANUAL - As part of a manual/maturity closeout from using a series of selection criteria.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>AUTOMATIC - The automatic closeout of a customer or a customers positions.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>SYSTEM - A system closeout carried out under instruction of the end of day or end of exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>BACK2BACK - Back to back closeout triggered for a secondary customer</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>MANUAL, AUTOMATIC, SYSTEM or BACK2BACK</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEST.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the internal recipient customer</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Upto 10 numeric values</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in CUSTOMER application</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DET.RES01</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>An valid ID from the DX.DIARY application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DET.RES02</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.BNK.ADD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The address of the customers bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the profit or loss created by this close out.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUY.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total value of the lots bought, stored in the closeout currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The </p>
            <p>type of trades that are being closed out.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FUTURE - A futures contract STOCK - A stock contract OPTION - An Options Contract</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>O.C</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Sub mulitivalued list corresponding to the lots in DET.LOTS indicating whether these lots were opening or closing a position. </p>
            <p>(Phase 2 development)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.TRADED</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the price at which the trade is being done</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Upto 19 numeric values</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.BUY.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of buy lots in each transaction that is being closed out.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The automatic settlement type selected by the system for this closeout.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must exisit on the DX.CLOSEOUT.METHOD field</p>
            <p>Must be defined as the closeout method for this customer.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.BNK.NME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the customers bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INP.MAT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The delivery period or prompt date of the contract transacted, in the format entered by the user. All transactions associated with this closeout will have matching maturity dates.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRI.HEDGE.TRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will can be set to HEDGE or TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Account over which financial entries relating to the customer for the closeout, are to be passed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Set to YES if a transfer advice is to be produced else set to NO</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Upto 3 alphanumeric values</p>
            <p>Valid inputs are either YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>B2B.CO.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field holds the list of ids of closeout records created for a secondary customer during back to back closeout processing. This field will be updated only in the closeout records relating to Primary Customers </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>B2B.PAR.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field gets updated only in the closeout records relating to secondary customers. This holds the parent closeout record id in relation to which this BACK2BACK closeout record got created</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEST.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Specifies the external recipient customer portfolio reference if any</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Upto 18 alphanumeric values</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field identifies the type of close out.</p>
            <p />
            <p>SETTLEMENT - A closeout matching lot against lot(MANUAL/AUTOMATIC/SYSTEM).</p>
            <p />
            <p>MATURITY - A Manual settlement maturing individual trades (MANUAL).</p>
            <p />
            <p>EXERCISE - The Exercising of an Option (MANUAL/AUTOMATIC/SYSTEM).</p>
            <p />
            <p>EXPIRY - The Expiry of a Option (MANUAL/AUTOMATIC/SYSTEM).</p>
            <p />
            <p>ASSIGNMENT - The Assignment of an Option (MANUAL/AUTOMATIC).</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIXING - The Fixing of a IRS Option (MANUAL)</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Can only be one of the following : </p>
            <p>SETTLEMENT, MATURITY, EXERCISE, EXPIRY or ASSIGNMENT</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total number of lots being closed out by this closeout.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.BNK.SORT.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The sort code of the customers bank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The portfolio for which this closeout is taking place. In the case of brokers this will be the same as there customer no.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must exist as a valid portfolio on SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tax type applied to the side of the trade that was closed out.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DET.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Sub mulitvalued list of the number of lots corresponding to the following types of trade, for commission purposes.  Only used if the TYPE of closeout is SETTLEMENT. </p>
            <p>(Phase 2 development.)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The records held within this file are created using the closeout input feeds from the closeout enquiries.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This must be a vaild key held on the DX.CLOSEOUT file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Key Format DXCOyydddnnnnn eg DXCO0100200077</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.SELL.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of sell lots in each transaction that are being closed out. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DET.RES04</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHILD.TRADE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds ids of DX.TRADE records created as part of an EXERCISE.  Held so that if the closeout is reversed, these trades are also reversed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>D.S</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Sub mulitivalued list corresponding to the lots on DET.LOTS indicating whether these lots were DAY trades or SCRATCH trades. </p>
            <p />
            <p>(Phase 2 development)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>None</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

