<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.DEFAULT.CPARTY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows the user to setup a default counterparty for a trade based on the contract class of the product being traded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>For example,</p>
            <p>OTC FX trades are mostly traded between the customer and the banks own book therefore the use could set the module up to default the banks own book portfolio as the default counterparty for all OTC FX deals.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SELL.OPEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the customer/portfolio id for this counterparty which is to be defaulted when a contract within this contract class is sold to open the position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the Override messages which the user agreed to during Input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the Override, the full text of the actual Override Message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.CLOSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the customer/portfolio id for this counterparty which is to be defaulted when a contract within this contract class is sold to close the position.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUY.CLOSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the customer/portfolio id for this counterparty which is to be defaulted when a contract within this contract class is bought to close the position.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUY.OPEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the customer/portfolio id for this counterparty which is to be defaulted when a contract within this contract class is bought to open the position.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to a valid record in the DX.CONTRACT.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DX.DEFAULT.CPARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to a valid record in the DX.CONTRACT.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

