<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application defines setup specific to a particular derivatives exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p> An exchange is any entity through which you can trade a product, or alternatively a grouping device for OTC trades.</p>
            <p />
            <p> For example all OTC trades should be traded on a OTC exchange setup in T24.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Keys to this table are numeric.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STREET.TOWN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Postal Address for the Exchange (Street and Town)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies an alternative means of referencing the Exchange as an alternative to the numeric key (ID).</p>
            <p> Like the ID, the Mnemonic must be unique within the T24 Derivatives module and additionally must not be the name of a strategy entered in the system.</p>
            <p> Note : The field allows the user to use either the numeric key or this mnemonic when entering exchange information in the system.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 3-10 characters, type MNE - Uppercase alpha or numeric,         first character alpha, or ".".</p>
            <p> Mandatory input,</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for Future Use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INIT.MARGIN.CALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>The deposit required by the clearing-house from clearing members as protection against default on futures or options contracts that they trade.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 8 alpha characters</p>
            <p> This must be a valid record in DX.MARGIN.CALC with         MARGIN.TYPE as "INITIAL".</p>
            <p> Mandatory input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREM.POST.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults the Premium Post Offset for Options Contracts traded on this Exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This is the numeric entry for the number of Offset days is required to post an accounting entry.</p>
            <p />
            <p>'n' (being the numeric in days).</p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:  When creating new Options Contracts on DX.CONTRACT.MASTER, if the corresponding field is not explicitly set, it will default to this value, otherwise the value input into the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER record will be used.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADING.OPEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Open Trading Time of the exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 5 numeric characters in TIME format</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input as HHMM or HH:MM</p>
            <p />
            <p>Quoted in Exchange's local time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved For Future Use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifier code used by the Regulatory Body, Internal or other reporting system for this Exchange</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 15 alpha characters available.</p>
            <p> Multi-value set with GEN.DATA.NAME</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.ALLOWED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults whether or not to allow Settlement of Contracts traded on this Exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Choose from the drop down menu YES or NO to confirm contracts traded are allowed to settle/close out with other contracts or left open as a held position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:  When creating new contracts on DX.CONTRACT.MASTER, if the corresponding field is not explicitly set, it will default to this value, otherwise the value input into the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER record will be used.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVN.POSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADING.CLOSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Close Trading Time of the exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 5 numeric characters in TIME format</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input as HHMM or HH:MM</p>
            <p />
            <p>Quoted in Exchange's local time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREM.POST.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults Premium Post Time for Options Contracts traded on this Exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field allows the choice of when the premium should be posted to an account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>TRADE: The premium will be paid or received in full on the trade date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>SETTLEMENT: The premium will be posted on the day of settlement, close/expiry of the trade.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:  When creating new Options Contracts on DX.CONTRACT.MASTER, if the corresponding field is not explicitly set, it will default to this value, otherwise the value input into the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER record will be used.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Is this an Investment Exchange traded product or is it an OTC (Over The Counter) traded product. Choose from the drop down menu of "NORMAL" OR "OTC".</p>
            <p> Exchange Traded (NORMAL); Products governed by rules set by an exchange, defined contract specifications, dates fixed, no counterparty risk, margin requirement and subject to regulation.</p>
            <p> OTC; Tailored products according to customer needs, limited, risky with no margin requirement and less actively regulated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 6 alpha characters available</p>
            <p> Input must be NORMAL/OTC</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the Exchange</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIRM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Identifier code for the Firm/Bank assigned by an exchange to members. This allows for the capture and reporting of products traded on this exchange.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 6 alpha characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETT.GROSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether Initial Margin Calculations on this Exchange should be nett or gross.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Default is NETT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REMOTE.TRADING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to store information about Remote Trading on this Exchange.</p>
            <p>Information only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.SESSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds any trading 'sessions' during the exchange day for trading certain products.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEG.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a segregated Customer associated with the Exchange, which can be used to record trades transacted directly with the Exchange.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAR.MARGIN.CALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults the Variation Margin Calculation Method for Contracts traded on this Exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This is the default Method to use for Variation Margin calculations, and should be a valid record on DX.MARGIN.CALC. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:  When creating new contracts on DX.CONTRACT.MASTER, if the corresponding field is not explicitly set, it will default to this value, otherwise the value input into the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER record will be used.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REGION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Region to which the Exchange belongs (REGION code).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HOUSE.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the status of that the bank is holding a house customer status with the particular exchange.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be defined as &amp;#145;EXCHANGE&amp;#146; in DX.CUSTOMER</p>
            <p> 10 Alpha</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a Customer associated with the Exchange, which can be used to record trades transacted directly with the Exchange.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Mnemonic by which the Exchange is known.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MUTUAL.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Does this Investment Exchange have links with others to allow fungibility on some of its products? Populate this field with the Investment Exchange the product relates too.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Up to 10 alpha characters</p>
            <p> Multi-value field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Short name for this Exchange</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ELEC.TRADING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to store information about Electronic Trading on this Exchange.</p>
            <p>Information only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETT.POST.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults the Settlement Postings Offset for Contracts traded on this Exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Days offset to apply settlement postings</p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:  When creating new contracts on DX.CONTRACT.MASTER, if the corresponding field is not explicitly set, it will default to this value, otherwise the value input into the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER record will be used.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds override messages that have been produced and accepted on input of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Populate this field for reporting purposes. The field allows for Regulatory, Internal, or other reporting requirements on this Exchange to the appropriate body/department.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 15 alpha characters</p>
            <p> DX.GEN.DATA will contain the information for the         Regulatory Body, Internal Department or other reporting         requirements, which will populate this field.</p>
            <p> Multi-valued set with GEN,DATA.CODE AND GEN.DATA.LIMIT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADING.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes which days of the week the Exchange is open for trading.</p>
            <p>Normally this is not required, as it would match the HOLIDAY table for the region.  However, for some exchanges, there may be unusual trading day rules, which can then be defined here.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVRESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for Future Use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.MONTHS.FWD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The available months forward to trade according to the contract specifications set by the relative exchange</p>
            <p> Open is suggested for this field as in CONTRACT.MASTER this field is populated to the contract specification related to the Contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 4 Alpha characters available)</p>
            <p> If not populated this field will default to 'OPEN'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Certain Regulatory Bodies require reports only when a certain limit is reached in the number of lots dealt. The limit lot set by this body is populated in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 11 numeric characters</p>
            <p> Multi-value set with GEN.DATA.NAME</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.POST.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is where the number of Offset days is required if the CHG.POST.TIME is populated with "TRADE + n".</p>
            <p> 'n' being the numeric in days.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Up to 3 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.POST.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults the Premium Post Offset for Contracts traded on this Exchange.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Time in contract lifecycle when commissions/charges applied to a trade should be charged.</p>
            <p />
            <p>TRADE charges applied on-line immediately trade verified.</p>
            <p />
            <p>SETTLEMENT charges applied when trade closed-out, matured or exercised/expired (option trades only).</p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:  When creating new contracts on DX.CONTRACT.MASTER, if the corresponding field is not explicitly set, it will default to this value, otherwise the value input into the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER record will be used.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEARING.HOUSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to hold details of the Clearing House for this Exchange.</p>
            <p>Information only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Country in which the Exchange is located (COUNTRY code).</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CUT.OFF.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used in conjunction with the field DAY.TRADE. 
            The Exchange cut off time is stored in this field. This time is expressed based on the server time zone.
             If the exchange is located in a different time zone, then the time needs to be converted to server time and updated here. 
             This cut off time would be used for creating a consolidated trade for multiple partial fills. Fills happening after the cut off time will be considered for the next day’s trade. .</p>

        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DAY.TRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used in conjunction with the field CUT.OFF.TIME. When set to YES , multiple fills before the cut off time, will be consolidated and a single trade will be created.
             The trade price would be weighted average price of each fill. The consolidated trade would be created at the cut off time. If the fill (execution) happens after the cut off time, 
             then that fill be considered for the next day’s consolidated trade. If the order is fully filled before the cut off time, then the consolidated trade would be created immediately.
              The consolidation would be broker wise in case of a multiple broker scenario, i.e. only fills of a particular broker would be consolidated, therefore the number of trades would be equal to the number of brokers.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values are YES and NO.</p>

            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This table gives the details of exchange on which trades can be done. This will have the trading dates, trading hours, maring calculation strategies, settlement criteria to trade on it etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Numeric - 10 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

