<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.MARGIN.CALC</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This Application allows the user to setup any number of margining methods to be used in the revaluation suite. Each method can be associated with a revaluation/margin method black box routine. (See the Manual)</p>
            <p>This application allows the user to define a number of extra parameters of there choice to be passed into the black box routine as well as a series of extra factors to apply to any results being produced by a black box.</p>
            <p>For example;</p>
            <p />
            <p>NO.IM - Used in order to skip producing any Initial         margin for a group of trades. </p>
            <p>NO.VM - Used in order to skip producing any Variation         margin for a group of trades. </p>
            <p>STAND.IM - Provides the standard Initial Margin         Calculation. </p>
            <p>STAND.VM - Provides the standard Varitaion Margin         Calculation. </p>
            <p>ENHANCED - Provides an enhanced Initial Margin         Calculation. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p />
            <p>DX.REVAL.DET.</p>
            <p>DX.RV.DET.HIST</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINTENANCE.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional percentage maintenance margin calculation factor. Only input if calculation type is INITIAL.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 5 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.RECORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies which of the listed relevent records the system should pass into the revaluation black box routine (PROGRAM.NAME) that is associated with this routine.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Can be CUSTOMER, DX.CONTRACT.MASTER,DX.CUSTOMER,DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER,DX.MARGIN.CALC,DX.PARAMETER,         DX.POSITION,SECC.ACC.MASTER (Limited to 10 multivalue         items)</p>
            <p>No Duplicates are allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Percentage factor to be applied to an initial margin fot the corresponding contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 5 characters </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the type of margin that will be calculated by the routine specified in the PROGRAM.NAME field.</p>
            <p>This maybe be either INITIAL (also known as DEPOSITS) or VARIATION (also known as PROFIT/LOSS)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 9 characters</p>
            <p>Mandatory Field</p>
            <p>Input must be either : INITIAL /VARIATION</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds any override messages generated on input to this record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>System-generated field only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contract code for an additional factor. This field should allow the entry of a mnemonic as well as the number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 12 characters, input must be a valid record the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER         Application</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Please enter a descriptive name for the margin calculation method. This is used for reporting purposes only.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters</p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROGRAM.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field define the name of the routine that will be called from the remargin process in order to calculate the margins for any contracts that are specified to use this margin calculation method. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 characters</p>
            <p>Mandatory Field</p>
            <p>Input must exist as a valid record on PGM.FILE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDON.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines a percentage increase or reduction that will be applied to all margin figures calculated by this routine. </p>
            <p>If no value is entered then the calculation will default to 100%. i.e. the margin figure calculated will remain unchanged.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 5 characters</p>
            <p>Numeric value</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A brief description of the margin calculation being used.</p>
            <p>For example;</p>
            <p />
            <p>NO.IM - Used in order to skip producing any Initial         margin for a group of trades.</p>
            <p>NO.VM - Used in order to skip producing any Variation         margin for a group of trades.</p>
            <p>STAND.IM - Provides the standard Initial Margin         Calculation.</p>
            <p>STAND.VM - Provides the standard Varitaion Margin         Calculation.</p>
            <p>ENHANCED - Provides an enhanced Initial Margin         Calculation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>8 Characters</p>
            <p>Alphanumeric</p>
            <p>DX.REVAL.DET. file </p>
            <p>DX.RV.DET.HIST file </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONS.DATA.ITEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This allows the user to associate a data name (variable) to a piece of data to be passed to a particular revaluation black box. Such as</p>
            <p>CONS.DATA.NAME : RISK.FACTOR CONS.DATA.ITEM: 35</p>
            <p>When processing the black box the box is provided with the information that RISK.FACTOR = 35.</p>
            <p>This information can be extracted from a common array called R.RVC.DATA by locating the text in array position DX.RVD.DATA.NAME, this will identify where in the DX.RVD.DATA.ITEM position the data value is stored.</p>
            <p>This field also has a number of online substitutions available.</p>
            <p />
            <p>!TODAY - Provides the current bank date in internal T24 format, e.g. 20020205.</p>
            <p>!NWD - Provides the next working day of the current company in internal T24 format, e.g. 20020206.</p>
            <p>!LWD - Provides the last working day of the current company in internal T24 format, e.g. 20020204.</p>
            <p>!WHO - Provides the ID of the current operator, e.g. TRAIN01.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>35 Characters Alphanumeric</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONS.DATA.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This allows the user to associate a data name (variable) to a piece of data to be passed to a particular revaluation black box. Such as</p>
            <p>CONS.DATA.NAME : RISK.FACTOR CONS.DATA.ITEM: 35</p>
            <p>When processing the black box the box is provided with the information that RISK.FACTOR = 35.</p>
            <p>This information can be extracted from a common array called R.RVC.DATA by locating the text in array position DX.RVD.DATA.NAME, this will identify where in the DX.RVD.DATA.ITEM position the data value is stored.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>35 Characters Alphanumeric</p>
            <p>No Duplicates</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

