<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.MARGIN.RATES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STRADDLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate to apply to both way deals</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 15 numerical characters</p>
            <p>No Input unless APPLY.STRADDLE.RATE is set to                 &amp;#145;YES&amp;#146;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate to apply to lots involved in a qualifying time (maturity) spread.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 15 numerical characters</p>
            <p>No Input unless APPLY.SPREAD.RATE is set to         &amp;#145;YES&amp;#146;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>DX.MARGIN.RATS will allow the entry of initial margin rates for various trades. These rates will be used, as required, by various initial margin calculation routines.</p>
            <p>Margin can be defined for Contract class level, Contract leve, Contract group level or customer level.</p>
            <p>example : CU100055 customer 100015; CGINT2 is for contract group INT2; CT100 for contract 100; CCBONDS for contract class BONDS. This can also be given in combinations of one or more combinations each separated with a '-' sign.</p>
            <p>On input the classification of type will be charged to '---' .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>two alphabets</p>
            <p>should be CC,CG,CT,CU to identify the classification. </p>
            <p>Should be a valid ID in the respective files.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should be a numerical value. no decimals allowed</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 15 numerical characters</p>
            <p>No Input unless APPLY.SPOT.RATE is set to &amp;#145;YES&amp;#146;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of margin rate to be applied.</p>
            <p>Either flat rate or percentage of contract value.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 10 characters</p>
            <p>Input must be either RATE/PERCENTAGE</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Minimum margin amount to be taken on a single trade. If the calculated margin amount is less than this then this amount will l be charged as the margin for that particular trade.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 15 numerical characters </p>
            <p>Input should be an amount not a rate or                 percentage</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds any override messages created on input to this record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>System-generated field only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLY.SPOT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>spot rate applicable for calculating margin</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input must be YES/NO</p>
            <p>If left Null, field will default to NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLY.SPREAD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should the system apply a special margin rate to trades that form a time (maturity) spread.</p>
            <p>If YES, the rate input in SPREAD will be applied to the number of lots involved in a valid spread</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input must be either YES/NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLY.STRADDLE.RTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Should the system apply a special margin rate for both way trades in a straddle.</p>
            <p>If YES, the rate input in this field then the system will use the same rate for buy and sell of the transactions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be either YES/NOThis is a samle help text.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate to apply to lots not involved in any spread, spot or straddle calculations.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 15 numerical characters</p>
            <p>Mandatory Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

