<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.MARKET.PRICE.HISTORY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the method for interest calculation.</p>
            <p>Should be a valid record in INTEREST.BASIS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UND.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Underlying Price / Exchange price of the two currencies.</p>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field whose value is populated from DX.TRADE.</p>
            <p>The type of option defined.</p>
            <p>It holds two values either CALL or PUT based on the trade.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.SET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Its gets value from DX.PRICE.SET.</p>
            <p>CLOSING - END OF EXCHANGE: Prices are updated during the end of exchange processing.</p>
            <p>CURRENT - ON-LINE: Prices can be updated online using a verify application DX.RV.CHECK.PRICES.</p>
            <p>If the revaluation occurs during End of Exchange then PRICE.SET holds the value CLOSING.</p>
            <p>If the revaluation occurs Online then PRICE.SET holds the value CURRENT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STRIKE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.TRADE.</p>
            <p>The price is calculated as Internal number of ticks * tick value for strike price.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The new price in which revaluation should be done.</p>
            <p>This is used internally as the price as which to calculate the internal price.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VOLATILITY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to DX.VOLATALITY.</p>
            <p>The key for this file is CONTRACT.CODE-MATURITY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the user field value.</p>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current system date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>It holds the quote currency price in which revaluation should be done.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VEGA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the rate of change of the value with respect to the volatility of the underlying asset.</p>
            <p>Greek value generated as part of the option pricing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The User Field Price is a NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Record id of the transaction being priced.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>It is the contract currency of the trade.</p>
            <p>Its value is populated from DX.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.TRADE.</p>
            <p>It is the internal price in standard T24 price format.</p>
            <p>Its value is calculated as</p>
            <p>INT.PRICE = Internal number of ticks * tick value for Futures price or Option premium.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The secondary internal rate for the secondary customer.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RHO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The rate at which the price of a derivative changes relative to a change in the risk-free rate of interest.</p>
            <p>Rho measures the sensitivity of an option or options portfolio to a change in interest rate.</p>
            <p>Values are available for both Call and Put options.</p>
            <p>Greek value generated as part of the option pricing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Populate this field for reporting purposes. The field allows for Regulatory, Internal, or other reporting requirements on the contract to the appropriate body/department.</p>
            <p>Value populated from DX.CONTRACT.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The internal rate for the primary customer.</p>
            <p>Indicates whether the contract is a interest rate contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to this DX.MARKET.PRICE record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The record key comprises the following attributes:</p>
            <p />
            <p>price set * exotic type (if applicable) / contract / currency / maturity date / call or put (only for options) / strike price (only for options) * exotic option data, delimited by '/' (for exotic options only).</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the quoted price in which valuation should be done.</p>
            <p>If QUOTE.CCY is Null then it takes the PRICE.CCY whose value is defined in the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.APP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>It specifies the source application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is NOINPUT field whose value is got from the DX.TRADE.</p>
            <p>The delivery period or prompt date of the contract transacted.</p>
            <p>The date must be greater than the Trade Date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price source describes the type of pricing model to be used for revaluation.</p>
            <p>Its value should be a valid record in DX.PRICE.SOURCE.</p>
            <p>The price source is also setup in DX.CONTRACT.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.DPS</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is NOINPUT field whose value is got from the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER.</p>
            <p>The number of decimal places for the price quote. This also changes the number of decimal places in the    multi-value set of Price Band.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UND.INT.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Underlying Internal Price.</p>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifier code used by the Regulatory Body, Internal or other reporting system for the contract.</p>
            <p>Value populated from DX.CONTRACT.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current system time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELTA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the rate of change of the option price with respect to the underlying asset.</p>
            <p>Greek value generated as part of the option pricing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>The User Field Name gets value from DX.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THETA</field>
<desc>
            <p>A measure of the rate of decline in the value of an option due to the passage of time.</p>
            <p>Theta can also be referred to as the time decay on the value of an option.</p>
            <p>Theta is part of the group of measures known as the "Greeks" which is used in options pricing.</p>
            <p>Values are available for both Call and Put options.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GAMMA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the rate of change of the delta with respect to the underlying asset.</p>
            <p>Greek value generated as part of the option pricing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.TRADE.</p>
            <p>It accepts three values namely : FUTURE,OPTION,STOCK.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME.TO.EXPIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>It denotes the time to mature the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VOLATILITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>A variable in option pricing formulas showing the extent to which the return of the underlying asset will       fluctuate between now and the option's expiration.</p>
            <p>Values are available for both Call and Put options.</p>
            <p>Used to input the volatilities to be used by the option pricing models.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.TRADE.</p>
            <p>It is the External Strike Price.</p>
            <p>The price at which an option holder has the right to buy (Call Options) or sell (Put Options) the underlying       instrument, or to cash-settle the option if appropriate, to exercise the option.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.UNITS</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.CONTRACT.MASTER whose contract is traded.</p>
            <p>The unit of measure relative to which the price is quoted.</p>
            <p>It is used for price related description.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>QUOTE.EXC</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>The rate of exchange between the price currency and the quote currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field whose value is got from the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER.</p>
            <p>It is the contract specification currency as set by the relative exchange. This is the user-defined alpha currency code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.DATA.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Limit related to reporting/regulatory procedure named in GEN.DATA.NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.IND.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The alternate index id related to ALT.IND.NAME.</p>
            <p>Its value is got from DX.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.IND.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Represents the alternate index name.</p>
            <p>Identifies the alternate for contracts in this system. i.e. CUSIP, ISIN etc.</p>
            <p>Identifies a list of possible alternate ID names that can be used to identify the the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALL.PUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is NOINPUT field whose value is got from DX.TRADE.</p>
            <p>It holds single value either CALL or PUT based on the trade.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>The Contract CODE for the trade, as per the information in DX.CONTRACT.MASTER.</p>
            <p>Its value should be a valid record in DX.CONTRACT.MASTER.</p>
            <p>Gets value from DX.TRADE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>DELIVERY.CCY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>OPTION.STYLE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
