<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>  
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.PORTFOLIO.MARGIN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a live file which gets updated when NETTING.REQD is set to YES in DX.PARAMETER.</p> 
            <p>Netting for individual portfolio gets updated here.</p>
            <p>The exposure for covered calls and exotics that are not in live are not considered for netting.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a valid portfolio id</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the reference currency of the portfolio</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETTING.FMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the netting key under which the exposure of different contracts gets updated.</p>
            <p>The format is UNDERLYING*STRIKE.PRICE*MATURITY.DAYS*CONTRACT.CURRENCY*DELIVERY.CURRENCY*EXOTIC.FIELD.NAMES.VALUES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the netted exposure for CALL type of contracts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the netted exposure for PUT type of contracts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSURE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Gets updated with the minimum negative exposure value among CALL and PUT.</p>
            <p>When the exposure are positive then zero gets updated.</p>
            <p>The value updated here is in trade currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The EXPOSURE value is updated in reference currency of the portfolio.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALL.TRANSACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated with the transaction references whose exposures are netted in CALL field. This is an sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PUT.TRANSACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated with the transaction references whose exposures are netted in PUT field. This is an sub-value field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.EXPOSURE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sum of EXP.REFERENCE is updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIRST.MATURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated with first maturating contracts maturity date which is used in netting with respect to maturity date.</p>
            <p>For example when 100 days is provided in MATURITY.DAYS field of DX.PARAMETER then 100 days from this FIRST.MATURITY are netted together.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>PORTFOLIO.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
