<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.REP.POSITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds all of the positions held in T24 for products tradeable in the DX module.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        The key is complex, details of the structure of this key can be found in the Derivatives manual.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OPTION.STYLE</field>
<desc>
        <p>A NOINPUT field which holds the first character of option style value in DX.TRADE.</p>
        <p>This will hold the value either ‘A’ for American, ‘E’ for European or ‘C’ for Carribean options</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.BASE.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of lots traded prior to any closeout or corporate action taking place.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for Exotic Options processing.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        The field holds a list of user defined name of fields/parameter that define the uniqueness of the exotic position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUY.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total number of lots bought in this contract for this position</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The positon type of this position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        FUTURE or OPTION</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REGION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Region code which applies to this position - this will have been defined in the relevant DX.EXCHANGE.MASTER record in the REGION field.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Regions exist to segregate a Region within a Country where the public holidays differ from other parts of the Country.</p>
            <p />
            <p> This enables a separate HOLIDAY table to be defined for the Region, to allow delivery to be controlled within the T24 system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAR.MAR.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the variation margin payable.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.CO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date(s) of closeouts affecting this transaction,</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ONLINE.YNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>I.CMF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for T24 internal use only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VAR.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The variation margin payable.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the DX customer group to which the customer belongs.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This information is taken from the DX.CUSTOMER record for this customer and is a valid entry on the DX.GROUPING file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is used as part of the valuation engine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FAR.PVD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date of the furthest out of all of the premium currently paid or pending for the position from a value dated perspective.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Foreign Exchange positions, this is the currency that this position will deliver at exercise/assignment time.</p>
            <p>        This will be a valid entry on the CURRENCY application.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.PV.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value date for the premiun payment for this transaction based on the trade date (TX.TRADE.DATE + TX.PREM.OFFSET)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>I.TXNF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for T24 internal use only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNR.PL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unrealised P&amp;L currently on this position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Updated after a DX valuation has taken place.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for Exotic Options processing.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        The field holds a list of user defined fields/parameter values that define the uniqueness of the exotic position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.ORIG.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The original number of lots of this contract traded on the transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.CO.PV.LT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The no.of lots of the closeouts affecting this transaction based on if the TRADE.DATE + TX.CO.OFFSET has passed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FAR.CO.PV.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date of the furthest out of all of the closeouts currently active or pending for the position from a valuedated perspective.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The traded currency of the position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This will be a valid entry on the CURRENCY application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This information is also part of the key.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.PVD.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated no. of lots based on if the TX.PV.DATE for this transaction has passed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the value date of this position, it could be in past, today or future.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for NON-STOP (NS) product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Number of lots bought or sold (FWD.BUY.SELL) pending entry as live transaction (FWD.TXN) on the next working day (FWD.DATE).</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal strike price for OPTION type positions. This field is populated from the DX.TRANSACTION record field INT.STRIKE and holds the T24 internal strike price for the option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.SET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the exotic option type of the transaction &amp; contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This is used as part of the key and is taken from the DX.TRANSACTION record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This will exist as a valid record in the DX.OPTION.TYPE application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of lots traded on this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.CO.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id(s) of closeouts affecting this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.OPEN.CLOSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This specifies the open or close status of transaction . This is used in the new average price method OPENING</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        Either OPEN/CLOSE allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the exchange on which the contract of this position would be traded.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.CO.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of lots of closeouts affecting this transaction,</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contract class of the position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This will be a valid entry on the DX.CONTRACT.CLASS application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PVD.NET.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated net position. (Long or Short)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for Exotic Options processing.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        As part of the  list of user defined fields/parameter that define the uniqueness of the exotic position this defines which of these fields are part of the position &amp; price keys.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.BUY.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of lots traded for this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maturity period of the position</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OWN.BOOK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the own book portfolio to which this portfolio belongs.</p>
            <p>        It identifies is this position is an own book position.</p>
            <p>        This data is taken from the DX.TRANSACTION OWN.BOOK field, which is taken from the DEALER.DESK field on SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NXT.PVD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date of the next due date out of all of the premium currently paid or pending for the position from a value dated perspective.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of lots of this position that have been closed out.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.SELL.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Weighted average of external price for sell positions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FST.PVD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date of the first out of all of the premium currently paid or pending for the position from a value dated perspective.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FAR.CO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date of the furthest out of all of the closeouts currently active or pending for the position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.CO.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated offset(s) of closeouts affecting this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.BUY.SELL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for NON-STOP (NS) product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Indicates a BUY or a SELL of a specified number of lots (FWD.LOTS) which will be entered into system on the next working day (FWD.DATE) as a live transaction (FWD.TXN). </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REP.POSITION.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the position. This key is complex.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customer holding the position</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PVD.BUY.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated buy positions</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.BUY.SELL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Was this transaction a BUY or a SELL transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>I.TRDF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for T24 internal use only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTITLEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to any entitlements currently affecting these trades/positions.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNR.PL.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unrealised P&amp;L currency on this position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Updated after a DX valuation has taken place.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.PVD.SELL.LT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated sold no. of lots based on if the TX.PV.DATE for this transaction has passed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.NET.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>The net cost of this transaction updated with DX.TX.NET.COST field from DX.TRANSACTION.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALL.PUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Type of OPTION trade.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        CALL or PUT</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.SELL.IPRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Weighted average of internal price for sell positions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for Exotic Options processing.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        The field holds a list of user defined fields/parameter that define the uniqueness of the exotic position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.IPRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The DX internal price of this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Net lots for this position, long or short.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The T24 Portfolio holding the position</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contract that is being traded. This will be a valid DX.CONTRACT.MASTER id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for NON-STOP (NS) product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Forward transaction reference for buy or sell (FWD.BUY.SELL) of a specified number of lots (FWD.LOTS) in this position to be entered on the next working day (FWD.DATE) onto the system as a live transaction (FWD.TXN).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COB.PRICE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to the price record used to price this position.  This will be a valid DX.MARKET.PRICE id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.CO.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Type of closeout affecting this transaction, e.g. ASSIGNMENT, EXERCISE, EXTERNAL, EXPIRY, FIXING, MATURITY or SETTLEMENT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PVD.SELL.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated sell position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELL.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total number of Sold Lots for this position</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>All transaction ID's for this position</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The traded price of this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.PREM.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>The premium payment offset for this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXT.STRIKE.PRI</field>
<desc>
            <p>Strike price for OPTION type position in external format. This field is populated from the DX.TRANSACTION record field STRIKE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>I.DAC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is for T24 internal use only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.PVD.BUY.LT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated bought no. of lots based on if the TX.PV.DATE for this transaction has passed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.CO.PV.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value date of the closeouts affecting this transaction based on the TRADE.DATE + TX.CO.OFFSET</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.PV.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of lots of this position that have been closed out based on the value date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.PVD.SIGN.LT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated no. of lots based on if the TX.PV.DATE for this transaction has passed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        A signed figure. -ve for short / +ve for long.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.SELL.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The no. of lots of this contract sold on this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TX.TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The trade date for this transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for NON-STOP (NS) product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Usually next working day, date at which forward transaction (FWD.TXN) for buy or sell (FWD.BUY.SELL) of a specified number of lots (FWD.LOTS) will be entered into system as live transaction (FWD.TXN).</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.BUY.IPRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Weighted average of internal price for buy positions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.BUY.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Weighted average of external price for buy positions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.IPRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average traded price for this position based on the setup for the contract.</p>
            <p>        This is expressed in DX internal format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average traded price for this position based on the setup for the contract.</p>
            <p>        This is expressed in external format.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

