<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.REVAL.DET.ENHANCED</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FULL.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate to apply to lots not involved in any spread, spot or straddle calculations.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPREAD.PAIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The lots paired by spread.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid DX.MARGIN.RATES key.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPREAD.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of lots that the spread rate has been applied to.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETT.GROSS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin calcualted NETT or GROSS</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRADD.MNTHS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maturity months of the lots that were paired using the straddle strategy.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINT.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Bump up factor applied to the maintenance margin.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAINT.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The calcualated Maintenance margin amount</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPREAD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate to apply to lots involved in a qualifying time (maturity) spread.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate to apply to lots that mature on the same day.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of lots that the Full rate has been applied to.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INITIAL.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The calculated Initial Margin amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRADDLE.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of lots that straddle rate has been applied to.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPREAD.MNTHS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maturity months of the lots that were paired by spread.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IM.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Bump up factor applied to the initial margin.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRADDLE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin rate to apply to both way deals.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of margin rate to be applied. Either flat rate or percentage of contract value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAND.IM.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to this DX.REVAL.DET.ENHANCED record.</p>
            <p>This takes the format DX.TRANSACTION key * exchange * currency * customer</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.LOTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of lots that spot rate has been applied to</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRADD.PAIR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The lots that were paired using the straddle strategy.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Minimum margin amount to be taken on a single trade. If the calculated margin amount is less than this then this amount will be charged as the margin for that particular trade.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Bump up factor to be applied to initial margin at contract level.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This contract breaks the detailed revaluation data down into contract by contract figures relating to initial margin.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.IM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the total initial margin calculated for this contract, on this exchange, in this currency for this customer/group./portfolio.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.FACTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Bump up factor to be applied to initial margin at exchange level.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

