<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.REP.POS.ACTIVITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is a repository of event based information and links to the application records driving the events. This  holds information related to a DX. REP. POSITION record. However, it will hold the information based on the activity that takes place for the position based on DX.EVENT.TYPEs. </p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ENTITLEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the link to the DX. ENTITLEMENT record which holds details of the effect of diary event on this position</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for Exotic Options processing.</p>
            <p>The field holds a list of user defined name of fields/parameter that define the uniqueness of the exotic position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.OF.EXCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the link to the End of Exchange processing which calculated margin for this position </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DX.TX.ACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is linked to DX. TXN. ACTIVITY record that relates to this entry. This is populated only when REPORTING is set to YES</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the link to the constituent transaction which was caused by trade based event</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for Exotic Options processing.</p>
            <p>The field holds a list of user defined fields/parameter values that define the uniqueness of the exotic position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Portfolio holding the position or the portfolio against which this side of the contract is being traded.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This denotes the transactional event that has occurred</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>There should be a valid DX. EVENT. TYPE record for this event</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORD.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is linked to the constituent DX. TRANSACTION record for the relevant DX. ORDER, which was caused by the order based event</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is linked to the Order which caused an Order based event</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the exotic option type of the transaction &amp; contract.</p>
            <p>This is used as part of the key and is taken from the DX.TRANSACTION record.</p>
            <p>This will exist as a valid record in the DX.OPTION.TYPE application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REP.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time at which the event occurred</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Taken from System time</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EOE.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the link to the DX.TRANSACTION record generated at the end of exchange processing which calculated margin for this position</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STRIKE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal strike price for OPTION type positions. This field is populated from the DX.TRANSACTION record field INT.STRIKE and holds the T24 internal strike price for the option.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RPA.ACTIVITY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to this DX.REP.POS.ACTIVITY record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the link to the diary event that has affected this position</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INACTIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>INACTIVE - This field is here as a placeholder - if the DX.SOD.RPA.TIDY job is active, the contents of this field will be changed to 'YES' in the corresponding DX.REP.POS.ACT.HIST record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REP.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the event has occurred</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Taken from System date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is obtained from the field Trade. date from the relevant DX. TRADE or DX. ORDER record. In case of Closeout, it displays the date on which the Closeout record is authorised</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the link to the DX. TRADE which caused the trade based event</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for Exotic Options processing.</p>
            <p>As part of the  list of user defined fields/parameter that define the uniqueness of the exotic position this defines which of these fields are part of the position &amp; price keys.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.FLD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for Exotic Options processing.</p>
            <p>The field holds a list of user defined fields/parameter that define the uniqueness of the exotic position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.CUST.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the Portfolio ID of the Customer and is linked to the Customer Activity file DX.TXN.ACT.CUST</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORTING.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This denotes whether this transaction is required for reporting purposes</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Can be YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maturity date for the contract transacted.  Held in yyyymm format for monthly maturity types or yyyymmdd for daily maturity types.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DX.REP.POS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This provides a link to the last maintained copy of the position with value obtained from ID of relevant DX. REP.POS. LAST record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customer holding the position or involved in this side of the deal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNQ.ENTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a unique key used to differentiate transaction events and prevent duplication of entries</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREM.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the date on which option premium becomes payable and is linked to the field PREM.VAL.DATE in DX.TRANSACTION</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STRIKE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Options contracts only - strike price, held in external format. This field is populated from the DX.TRANSACTION record field STRIKE and holds the T24 strike price for the option.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to the DX.CONTRACT.MASTER record which holds definition of the contract being traded.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the date on which the relevant DX. EVENT.TYPE  is authorised </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALL.PUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for options trades only - denotes whether this is a CALL or PUT option.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSEOUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>For closed out or partially closed out deals - key for the DX.CLOSEOUT record which has closed out lots against this side of the deal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>For closed out or partially closed out deals - key for the DX.TRANSACTION record which has closed out lots against this side of the deal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

