<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DX</product>
<table>DX.VARIATION.MARGIN.DETS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a live table which gets updated with variation margin details on each revaluation when VM.REV.TYPE in parameter record is set to INDIVIDUAL. </p>
            
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VM.DETS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Variation margin ID reference is held against VM.DETS.ID field. ID is of format 'TRADE ID.PORTFOLIO'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which revaluation had happended.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the account number on which the margin entries are posted. Updated from VAR.ACCOUNT from DX.TRANSACTION record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency for variation margin. Updated from VAR.MAR.CCY field of DX.TRANSACTION record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MARGIN.REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Margin amount in customer reference currency. Updated from VAR.MAR.REF.CCY of DX.TRANSACTION record</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valuation amount posted as margin on the date updated in DATE field. Updated from VAR.MARGIN field of DX.TRANSACTION record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EXC.RATE.VM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Is the rate of exchange between variation margin currency and local currency used for variation margin posting. Updated from VM.EXC.RATE of DX.TRANSACTION record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EXC.RATE.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Is the exchange rate between the customer reference currency and trade currency. Updated from EX.RATE.REF of DX.TRANSACTION record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EXC.RATE.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Is the rate of exchange between trade currency and customer account currency. Fields from DATE until EXC.RATE.ACC are associated multivalue fields. Updated from EX.RATE.ACC of DX.TRANSACTION record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>TRADE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated with value 'RNA' when the reversal trade is authorised. This status is used by COB job DX.POST.VM.INDIV.ENTRIES to post reversal variation margin entries during COB or by online service DX.RV.SERVICE. </p>
        </desc>
</t>

</menu>
</t24help>

