<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DC</product>
<table>DC.ADVICES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file has only one record 'DC.ADVICES' and is used to control the printing of advices from within the DATA.CAPTURE module. </p>
            <p>The production of advices is requested via input in a LOCAL.REF field at the transaction level during DATA.CAPTURE input. This item specifies which of the DATA.CAPTURE LOCAL.REF fields is to be used to request the production of an advice and that which will subsequently record the delivery reference for the advice produced. </p>
            <p>This record will need to be set up before delivery messages from data.capture can be produced. The prerequisite for entering this record is that the DATA.CAPTURE record on the LOCAL.REF.TABLE file is present. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RES3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RES2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DC.ADVICE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input must be "DC.ADVICES". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10 alpha characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the additional element which has been defined locally for the advice generation in Data Capture. </p>
            <p>This field gives the multivalue position within the LOCAL.REF field within DATA.CAPTURE that will contain the delivery reference if an advice was requested (see 'LOCAL.REF.USED'). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alpha characters.  Single value field.  No change allowed to this field after validation.</p>
            <p>Field number entered must be defined on LOCAL.REF.TABLE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF.USED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally for the advice facility in Data Capture. </p>
            <p>This field gives the multivalue position within the LOCAL.REF field that will be used to request an advice from within a DATA.CAPTURE transaction. An input of 'Y' in this LOCAL.REF field when entering a DATA.CAPTURE item will trigger the delivery processing. </p>
            <p>Example:   LOCAL.REF.USED = 1 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alpha characters.  Single value field.  No change allowed to this field after validation.</p>
            <p>Field number entered must be defined on LOCAL.REF.TABLE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RES1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

