<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DC</product>
<table>DC.BATCH.CONTROL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is an internal file automatically updated within the Data Capture Application.  It controls for each open batch the items pending authorisation, the items (i.e. entry number) which have been used as well as the current total debit and credit both in local currency and foreign currency.  For each batch which has been 'adjusted' by means of the automatic balancing facility, a corresponding update will also be done in this file.  The information contained in the file is as follows for each 'open' batch: </p>
            <p>      -    List of items not yet authorised.       -    List of items used.       -    Local currency amount Debit.       -    Local currency amount Credit.       -    Foreign currency amount Debit       -    Foreign currency amount Credit       -    Record status: </p>
            <p>           - IAUT              which means that all the items (entries) of the batch have              been authorised but the batch is not yet in balance. </p>
            <p>           - INAU              which means that all the items (entries) of the batch are              still in an unauthorised status. </p>
            <p>           - IPAU              which means that some of the items (entries) of the batch              have been authorised while other are still in an unauthorised              status.  The batch is 'partially' authorised. </p>
            <p>      -    Company identification       -    Adjustment flag (ADJUST, TRY ADJ or Nothing).       -    Adjustment amount       -    Adjustment Item number. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEPT.BATCH.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the ID field for this application. It holds the ID details of particular Department and its Batch entered in DATA.CAPTURE. It's sturcuture will be like 'DCYYJJJDDDDBBB'. EX: DC012340001001.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FCY.AMOUNT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total of all credit amount transactions with in a batch in foreign currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEMS.ON.HOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the sequence number of items that has been kept in hold status in a batch. This field will be updated when DC.BALANCED flag is set in ACCOUNT.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTINGENT.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be populated from DATA.CAPTURE record. Sets the value in this field based on CONTINGENT.ACCT in DATA.CAPTURE to identify the type of batch (contingent/non contingent).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1 : NO INPUT</p>
            <p>Rule 2 : Y or N</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNBALANCED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the user information of the DATA.CAPTURE entered. This field will be updated when DC.BALANCED flag is set to "YES" in ACCOUNT.PARAMETER and When DC is not balanced.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LCY.AMOUNT.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total of all debit amount transactions with in a batch in local currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPARTMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEMS.NOT.AUTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the sequence number of items in a batch that are still not authorized. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1 : NO INPUT</p>
            <p>Rule 2 : Sequence number of the batch</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The NET of all credit and debit amount transactions with in a batch in local currency. This field will be updated when DC.BALANCED flag is set to "YES" in ACCOUNT.PARAMETER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The NET of all credit and debit amount transactions with in a batch in foreign currency. This field will be updated when DC.BALANCED flag is set to "YES" in ACCOUNT.PARAMETER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OF.ITEMS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNTING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be populated by the system from DATA.CAPTURE application. This field specifies on which date accounting should take place.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUST.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>SYSTEM updated field. Will hold the adjustment amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUST.ITEM</field>
<desc>
            <p>SYSTEM updated field. Will hold the adjustment item.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BATCH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field stores the list of all users who has entered the DATA.CAPTURE record. This field will be updated if DC.BALANCED FLAG in ACCOUNT.PARAMETER is set. This field ensures there will be no INPUTTER/AUTHORIZER conflict.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1 : NO INPUT</p>
            <p>Rule 2 : INPUTTERS from DATA.CAPTURE record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>SYSTEM updated field. Will hold either "ADJUST" OR "TRY.ADJ </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEMS.USED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the sequence number of items that has been used in a batch.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FCY.AMOUNT.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total of all debit amount transactions with in a batch in foreign currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the company to which the DATA.CAPTURE belongs to.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1 : NO INPUT</p>
            <p>Rule 2 : ID.COMPANY OF THE DATA.CAPTURE RECORD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LCY.AMOUNT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total of all credit amount transactions with in a batch in local currency</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1 : NO INPUT</p>
            <p>Rule 2 : Amount from DATA.CAPTURE record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Company code of the companies present in batch entries for mixed batches. System updated no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LCY.AMT.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total local currency amount of all debit entries for this company in this batch. System updated no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LCY.AMT.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total local currency amount of all credit entries for this company in this batch. System updated no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FCY.AMT.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total foreign currency amount of all debit entries for this company in this batch. System updated no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FCY.AMT.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total foreign currency amount of all credit entries for this company in this batch. System updated no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

