<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.AXIS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application will allow the user to define an axis and its contents (Member field, defining the grouping of assets, e.g. stocks, bonds, cash) and list the elements belonging to each group at the asset or sub asset type level. These will be used to define the composition of a matrix. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Example for AXIS = CURRENCY</p>
            <p />
            <p>    MEMBER = North America, Europe, Asia, Other</p>
            <p />
            <p>    CCY EQ USD    -&gt; North America</p>
            <p />
            <p>    CCY EQ CAD    -&gt; North America</p>
            <p />
            <p>    CCY EQ EUR    -&gt; Europe</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MBR.LABEL</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    Member name that will appear on the heading of a grid comparison. This field is modified to allow the user to enter the member label in various languages. If blank, MEMBER is display.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p>    0 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.MEMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    Sub valued field contains the member to which the entity belongs.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Must be a       valid member defined in the MEMBER field above</p>
            <p />
            <p>    1 - 12 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>    Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MEMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    Multi-valued field used to define the different elements of the axis , i.e., the column or row headings of a grid. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    The members are defined using the entities that have been created. When a user re-balances a portfolio each position in the portfolio will be assigned to a member by matching its characteristics with the characteristics defined in the entity and axis.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    The       input of the space char and the label TOTAL are prohibited</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Mandatory input</p>
            <p />
            <p>    1 - 12 alphanumeric       characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LABEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>A short description of the axis.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the Override messages which the user agreed to during Input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the Override, the full text of the actual Override Message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Operand apply on entity</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Multi-valued field associated with the ENTITY and VALUE fields.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    ENTITY, OPERAND and VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Input must       be either 'EQ' or 'NE'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AXIS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    Unique reference which identifies the AXIS record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Mandatory       input</p>
            <p />
            <p>    1       - 12 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Must       be unique as an ID record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    Describes the AXIS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the AXIS in various languages.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    0 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIRECT.ALLOC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the list of members set up as a direct allocation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    No Input. Updated by system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTITY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    Contains the id of the entity.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Multi-valued field associated with the OPERAND and VALUE fields. Defines rules to allocate analysis positions to member.  Allocation is to the first entity which applies to the instrument.</p>
            <p>    An entity is a term used to describe the ways we can look at instruments. It is the segment or cell of a matrix. e.g. an asset type, currency, modified duration, sector. </p>
            <p>    ENTITY, OPERAND and VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Must be a       valid record in AM.ENTITY</p>
            <p>    Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    Multi-valued field contains the value to use as a selection criteria for the entity. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    ENTITY, OPERAND and VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank. Defining sub-values mean a logical OR function.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    0 - 30 alphanumeric characters long free text</p>
            <p>    Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.PCT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    Contains the strategic allocation corresponding to a MEMBER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Total of       this sub-valued field throughout each TO.MEMBER sub-valued field must be       100%</p>
            <p>    1 - 6 alphanumeric characters </p>
            <p>    Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBR.ALLOCATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the allocation mode.</p>
            <p>    DIRECT means that the MEMBER field contains the actual modelling position code (usually the internal security code). If this is used, the position allocation is done directly to the corresponding member. You do not have to set up a rule for that member.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    RULES or blank indicates that the allocation is done using rules describe with fields ENTITY, OPERAND, VALUE, TO.MEMBER, TO.PCT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>AUTOMATIC When an item is allocated to a MEMBER which has its MBR.ALLOCATION set as AUTOMATIC the MEMBER will be replaced with the entity value.</p>
            <p>This allows for a dynamic member list, hence if the entity returns the currency we would dynamically generate member labels for each currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    DIRECT type members are process before RULES.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    DIRECT, RULES or AUTOMATIC</p>
            <p>    Optional input. Blank is processed as RULES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

