<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.BREAKDOWN.SELECT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Parameter table to select portfolios for which breakdown facility is availed. Only the portfolios identified with this set up will have various breakdown entities like flow capture and historic breakdown information recorded.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SELECT.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the associated multi value forming the selection criteria for selecting portfolios availing breakdown facility. </p>
            <p>Valid Operands - EQ NE LIKE</p>
            <p />GT LT UNLIKE. <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory Input when the BREAK.SELECT field is Set to SELECT LIST</p><p>Value is any one of the valid operands.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.JOIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field is an associated multi-value for forming the selection criteria  for the dynamic selection of portfolios availing breakdown facility . The field is used to </p>
            <p>d</p>
            <p>efine Join conditions for Multiple select statement .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Vaild values are boolean operands AND and OR</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AM.BREAKDOWN.SELECT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of AM.BREAKDOWN.SELECT should be a valid company id.        </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid company id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BREAK.SELECT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if the breakdown facility is applicable to all or only for selected portfolios.</p>
            <p>ALL - The breakdown facility is available for all the portfolios under the given company.</p>
            <p>SELECTED - The user can specify the list of portoflios for which the breakdown facility is available. The portfolios are recorded manually in the Field SEL.PORTFOLIO.</p>
            <p>SELECTED.LIST - Allows the user to specify a Dynamic selection criteria to select the list of portfolios availing breakdown facility .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Any of three Options.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Portfolio's for which Breakdown facility is available. Activated when BREAK.SELECT is set to SELECTED</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Portfolio ids.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input when BREAK.SELECT is set to SELECTED.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field is an associated multi value forming the selection criteria for the dynamic selection of portfolios. </p>
            <p>Value corresponding to the select field and operand.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field when the BREAK.SELECT field is set to SELECT LIST.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field should contain a valid field name or a field no. of SEC.ACC.MASTER. The field forms the start of the associated multi value containing the selection criteria for selecting the list of portfolios availing breakdown facility.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Valid field name or field no. of  the     SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
            <p>      Mandatory field when the BREAK.SELECT is     set to SELECT LIST .</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

