<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.BUILD.MODEL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FILTER.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is associated with the FILTER.OPERAND and FILTER.VALUE fields.</p>
            <p>Contains the field to be filtered from the SECURITY.MASTER application to build the model.</p>
            <p>FILTER.FIELD, FILTER.OPERAND and FILTER.VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.OPR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the filter criteria invoked by the fields FILTER.FIELD and FILTER.VALUE. </p>
            <p>FILTER.OPERAND, FILTER.FIELD and FILTER.VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.MEMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the member for the axis to be rebuilt. It is mandatory if the CALCULATION.TYPE is ABSOLUTE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RUN.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT Field.</p>
            <p>This field is used to display the information about the run when the record is verified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.EXISTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the Matrix Specified in the MATRIX field already exists and this field is set to YES then the matrix specified gets rebuilt.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATRIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Gets defaulted same as the ID of the AM.BUILD.MODEL. </p>
            <p>ID of the Matrix which is created in IHLD status in AM.MATRIX after verifying the AM.BUILD.MODEL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the id of the entity.</p>
            <p>Defines rules to allocate analysis positions to member.</p>
            <p>An entity is a term used to describe the ways we can look at instruments. It is the segment or cell of a matrix. 
     e.g. an asset type, currency, modified duration, sector.</p>
            <p>Mandatory if the MBR.ALLOCATION is set to RULES.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in AM.ENTITY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODEL.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference to the Model.</p>
            <p>Maximum of 10 characters can be specified</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEMPLATE.AXIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the ID of the AM.AXIS.</p>
            <p>If the value sets in this field then the system analyses the portfolio's holdings on this axis before generating the model..</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AXIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the axis that will be used in the axis rebuilt process. Gets defaulted same as the ID of the AM.BUILD.MODEL.</p>
            <p>The AM.AXIS gets created in IHLD status..</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The CALCULATION.TYPE can be either ABSOLUTE or RELATIVE</p>
            <p>If ABSOLUTE is given then OTHER.MEMBER field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEVIATION.MAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field that contains the maximum tolerance variation above the target percentage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEVIATION.MIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field that contains the minimum tolerance variation below the target percentage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the field value to be filtered from the SECURITY.MASTER record</p>
            <p>FILTER.VALUE, FILTER.FIELD and FILTER.OPERAND fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MBR.ALLOCATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the allocation mode.</p>
            <p>DIRECT means that the MEMBER field contains the actual modelling position code (usually the internal security code). If this is used, the position allocation is done directly to the corresponding member. You do not have to set up a rule for that member.</p>
            <p>RULES indicates that the allocation is done using rules describe with fields ENTITY.</p>
            <p>DIRECT type members are process before RULES..</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the portfolio being processed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Define nature of each cell. Depending of the nature of cell, rebalancing tool have different process to generate proposed orders.</p>
            <p>Blank : Rebalancing tool doesn't process this cell.</p>
            <p>MOD : "Model portfolio" Rebalancing tool get directly the security set for this cell. Assign to cell who define exactly the security.</p>
            <p>RCD : "Recommendation" Rebalancing tool used recommended stock list to proposed orders. Assign to cells who securities with criteria (asset, currency, industry sector ...).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only MOD, RCD, can be entered.</p>
            <p>Cannot be set on a total cell. A total cell cannot be rebalance.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

