<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.COMPOSITE.HIST.DETAIL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This file contains the calculation details for Portfolios included in composites</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>It's structure is : 1 record per composite, per month and portfolio.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This file is monthly updated by a batch job called AM.COMP.HIST.DET.UPD and is used for composite reporting.</p>
            <p>See also files : AM.COMPOSITE.HIST, AM.COMPOSITE.HIST.EXCL and AM.COMPOSITE.YEARLY.HIST   </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>W.MD.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the portfolios weighted monthly performance based on the modified dietz calculation method, in relationship to the composite it is attached too. The weighting used is the PORT.W.BEGIN.MONTH figure.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MONTHLY.MD.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the monthly performance of the portfolio using the modified dietz calculation method.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MONTHLY.DAILY.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the monthly performance of the portfolio using the daily calculation method.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORT.W.BEG.MONTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the weight of this portfolio in the composite. It is based on its market value at the start of the composite calculation period against the total market value of all the portfolios included in the composite.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Portfolio id </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Alphanumeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.MONTHLY.MD.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the monthly performance of the portfolio using the Modified Dietz calculation method on gross figures. The formula used is :</p>
            <p>Modif.Perf = (Per 1/ Per 2) * 100</p>
            <p>Per 1 = End.Value - Begin.Value - Netflow - Grossflow</p>
            <p>Per 2 = Begin.Value + Avg.Cap.Inv</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUSION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the code of exclusion from monthly composite performance calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>W.DAILY.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the portfolios weighted monthly performance based on the daily calculation method, in relationship to the composite it is attached too. The weighting used is the PORT.W.BEGIN.MONTH figure.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.W.DAILY.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the portfoilio's weighted monthly performance based on the daily calculation method on gross figures. The weighting used is the Port.W.Beg.Month value.</p>
            <p>W.Daily.Perf = Beg.Value * Daily.Perf</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FEE.PAYING.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This flag indicates if the portfolio is fee paying or not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Alpha field, accepted characters are Y or N, generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.STATUS.FLG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the inclusion or exclusion flag defined in the AM.COMP.HIST.DET.WORK file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUSION.LOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the log of exclusion reason for this portfolio and the date when the exclusion event has occurred.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUSION.TEXTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the comments given by the user in AM.COMP.HIST.DET.WORK</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AM.COMP.HIST.DET.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.STATUS.FLG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the inclusion or exclusion flag defined in the AM.COMP.HIST.DET.WORK file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEG.MONTH.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The detailed beginning market value is the market value for the portfolio detailed in the PORTFOLIO_ID, based on the reference currency of the portfolio on the 1st day of the month for which the composite performance calculation is being made.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.MONTH.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total end market value is the portfolio market value of the portfolio detailed in the PORTFOLIO.ID, based on the reference currency of the portfolio on the final day of the month for which the composite performance calculation is being made.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.W.MD.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the portfolio's weighted monthly performance based on the Modified Dietz calculation method on gross figures. The weighting used is the Port.W.Beg.Month value.</p>
            <p>Formula used :</p>
            <p>W.Modif.Perf = Beg.Value * Modif.Perf</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.MONTH.DAILY.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the monthly performance of the portfolio using the daily calculation method on gross figures. The formula used is :</p>
            <p>Daily.Perf = (P.Daily.Perf - 1) * 100</p>
            <p>P.Daily.Perf = Sum of P.Perf.End.Day taken from all the multivalue set of a Sc.Perf.Detail record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

