<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.COMPARE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows a user to select a particular portfolio or a group of portfolios from a criteria or several criteria and compare the holdings of a portfolio against the strategy contained in the investment program.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      It contains four principal functions:</p>
            <p>             - Select of portfolios to process, these selection process can either select the portfolio ID's desired or by selecting fields from the portfolio file (SAM) a selection of portfolios can be made based on the selected criteria and values chosen.</p>
            <p>             - Optional possibility to force the comparison engine to compare a portfolio or consolidate portfolio to any selected Matrix. Note orders cannot be generated when forcing a comparison, they can only be generated based on the  Investment Program linked to a portfolio (or to be precise to the matrix linked to this investment program.)</p>
            <p>             - Instructions buttons (flag Yes/No) to execute a selected process on each portfolio such as Compare, Rebalance, Edit .</p>
            <p>             - The ability to display the results of the comparison via context sensitive drilldown enquiries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      When a record is commited with the START flag set to yes a request is placed to process a bulk rebalancing by the AM.SC.MOVEMENT service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This application shares is layout with AM.COMPARE.DETAILS therefore some fields are not update in this applicaiton but are in AM.COMAPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RBL.ROUND.BUY</field>
<desc>
        <p>RBL.ROUND.BUY</p>
        <p>Specifies rounding rules to calculate the nominal of BUY orders, generated through rebalancing.
</p>
        <p>Automatically defaults the values  from RBL.ROUND.BUY field of AM.PARAMETER.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Accepts any one of the following values ‘UP’ or ‘DOWN’ or ‘CLOSER’
       </p>
        </p>
        <p class="div_1">
            <p class="Indent5Percent">
                <p style="list-style-type: circle;">
                    <p value="1"><b>UP:</b> The nominal is rounded to the closest round lot above the target. 
       </p>
                    <p value="2"><b>DOWN:</b> The nominal is rounded to the closest round lot below the target.
       </p>
                    <p value="3"><b>CLOSER:</b> The nominal is rounded up or down to the closest rounding lot depending  
       on whichever is closer to the target.
</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">If the value of RBL.ROUND.BUY in AM.PARAMETER is null then Rebalancing will consider the value given in ROUNDING.TYPE of AM.COMPARE or ROUNDING.TYPE of AM.PARAMETER</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RBL.ROUND.SELL</field>
<desc>
        <p>RBL.ROUND.SELL</p>
        <p>Specifies rounding rules to calculate the nominal of SELL orders, generated through rebalancing.
</p>
        <p>Automatically defaults the values  from RBL.ROUND.SELL field of AM.PARAMETER.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Accepts any one of the following values ‘UP’ or ‘DOWN’ or ‘CLOSER’
       </p>
        </p>
        <p class="div_1">
            <p class="div_1">
                <p style="list-style-type: circle;">
                    <p value="1"><b>UP:</b> The nominal is rounded to the closest round lot above the target. 
       </p>
                    <p value="2"><b>DOWN:</b> The nominal is rounded to the closest round lot below the target.
       </p>
                    <p value="3"><b>CLOSER:</b> The nominal is rounded up or down to the closest rounding lot depending  
       on whichever is closer to the target.
</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">If the value of RBL.ROUND.SELL in AM.PARAMETER is null then Rebalancing will consider the value given in ROUNDING.TYPE of AM.COMPARE or ROUNDING.TYPE of AM.PARAMETER</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.02</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.03</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.04</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.05</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.06</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.07</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.08</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.09</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANUAL.SELECTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the fields defined on the SEC.ACC.MASTER standard selection file, it is used as a selection criteria to select the portfolio(s).</p>
            <p />
            <p>      FIELD, OPERAND and VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHADOW.MODEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Creates a shadow model(Copy of a model prefixed with 'S-' ) based on the matrix specified in the INVESTMENT.PROGRAM.</p>
            <p> Accepts the values YES, NO and NULL.         </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">If the value is "Yes" then it creates the shadow model based on the matrix specified in the INVESTMENT.PROGRAM                    </p>
                <p value="2">If the value is "No" then it uses the matrix specified in the MATRIX field. </p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed for groups.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alphabetic</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIL.SUB.FUNC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains logical operators which is used to determine another sub-value of criteria.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Input must be either AND or OR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REASON.TYPE.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines why rebalancing is performed.</p>
            <p>Accepts a description that is deflated in AM.SCENARIO. </p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alphabetic	</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRITERIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>A valid AM.CRITERIA record to use a pre-defined selection configuration.</p>
            <p>	Accepts criteria record with file name as 'AM.GROUP.PORT' and 'ACCOUNT'</p>
            <p>The criteria entered depends on REBALANCE.LEVEL field.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alpha numeric.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.COMPARE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORD.GEN.HOW</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RAISE.CASH.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts a valid currency for raising cash.</p>
            <p>Holds a value only when SESSION.TYPE is ‘RAISE CASH’</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.SCENARIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: Used to process a clear on scenarios.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Only       "ALL", "BUY", "SELL", "FLOW" or       "FOREX" can be entered</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This process is not allowed in a mass comparison (CONSOLIDATE field set to YES)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPARE.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>A duplicate field which holds the COMPARE.CODE. </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEVIATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>No Longer Update - See AM.COMPARE.DETAILS for details</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.OUTBOUND</field>
<desc>
            <p>	Contains the number of cellular that are outbound in each grid of a compare process.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Numeric</p>
                <p value="2">NOINPUT field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBALANCE.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>	Accepts any one of the following values SEC.ACC.MASTER or AM.GROUP.PORT.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alphabetic</p>
                <p value="2">
                    <p>Mandatory field.</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.ACTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGH.VOLUME</field>
<desc>
            <p>YES/NO flag to choose whether to check high volume processing file as opposed to default order file when including pending orders in the valuation used as basis for the rebalancing process. This field only works if the routine SET.POSITION.OPEN.ORDER has been specified in AM.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAM.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOLIDATE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the common currency to be used and displayed in the consolidated comparison process of selected portfolios. </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Mandatory if CONSOLIDATE field is set to YES.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPARE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the COMPARE record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      The key may contain the following characters A-Z, AND 0-9, and "-"</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRICE.SET</field>
<desc>
            <p>An alternative set of prices to use. Defined in AM.PRICE.SET</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SVC.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The time at which the request to run a rebalancing session was requested.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SVC.MESG</field>
<desc>
            <p>A free-text message from the processing engine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATRIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: used to process consolidated comparison on selected portfolios.</p>
            <p>      It defines the common matrix process to be used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GENERATE.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: used to process the generating of orders.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a short description that describes the Modelling session, this should be used to clearly identify what the objectives of the comparison session are, so that they can be re-used at a later date. The field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the description in various languages.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.AXIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: Used to rebuild AM.AXIS.MEMBER concat file. This concat file is used by enquiry "Eligible list" and by rebalancing buying routine.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SVC.WHO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The user/process that has requested the rebalancing session.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBAL.SELL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: used to process rebalancing routine and proposed orders.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPARE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: Used to process comparison on selected portfolios.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.GRID.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>	Stores the group grid id.</p>
            <p>Associated multi-valued field along with the fields starting from SAM.CODE till the field SCENARIO.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alpha numeric</p>
                <p value="2">
                    <p>NOINPUT field</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIL.MAIN.FUNC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains logical operators which is used to determine another multi-value of criteria.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Input must be either AND or OR</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHECK.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Request constraints checking on all orders generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.OPR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the filter criteria invoked by the fields FILTER.FIELD and FILTER.VALUE. This selection sets the criteria that will dictate which portfolios will be selected.</p>
            <p>      FILTER.OPERAND, FILTER.FIELD and FILTER.VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCENARIO.LIST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the group id to which the portfolio belongs.</p>
            <p>Associated multi-valued field along with fields starting from the field SAM.CODE till the SCENARIO field.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alpha numeric</p>
                <p value="2">NOINPUT field</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the operator to be applied to the fields FIELD and VALUE. This selection sets the criteria that will dictate which portfolios will be selected.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      OPERAND, FIELD and VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUATE.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: used to launch an online valuation of portfolios.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies rounding of nominals.</p>
            <p />
            <p>                 UP: the nominal is to be rounded to the closest round lot above the target.</p>
            <p>                 DOWN: the nominal is to be rounded to the closest round lot below the target.</p>
            <p>                 CLOSER: the nominal is to be rounded up or down to the closest rounding lot depending on whichever is closer to the target.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SESSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A duplicate of COMPARE.CODE used as a unique rebalancing session ID&gt;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REASON.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts a valid code from AM.REASON.TYPE application.</p>
            <p>The short description of AM.REASON.TYPE is the encryption for this field.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alphanumeric	</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SAM.COUNTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of portfolios selected for processing.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Update after the service has processed the selection.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBAL.BUY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: Used to process rebalancing routine and proposed orders.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SVC.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the request to run a rebalancing session was requested.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the FILTER.OPERAND and FILTER.VALUE fields.</p>
            <p>      It defines the rules to select proposed orders stored in the scenario application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      FILTER.FIELD, FILTER.OPERAND and FILTER.VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ONLINE.COB</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the rebalancing request should be processed by an online service or during the close of buisiness.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RAISE.CASH.PORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds a portfolio whose security position is sold in order to raise cash.</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">When Rebalance level is GROUP, the portfolio must be a part of the rebalancing group.</p>
                <p value="2">When Rebalance level is Portfolio, the portfolio must be a part of the selection criteria.</p>
            </p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Holds a value only when SESSION.TYPE is ‘RAISE CASH’</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.DEVIATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>	Holds the average of differences from various cellular of each grid that belongs to a compare process.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Numeric</p>
                <p value="2">NOINPUT field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCENARIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the value to be compared to the SEC.ACC.MASTER field defined in row 3 FIELD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      VALUE, OPERAND and FIELD fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RAISE.CASH.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines the amount of cash raised by selling the securities. The amount will be raised by selling out the most preferred sell securities.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Holds a value only when SESSION.TYPE is ‘RAISE CASH’</p>
                <p value="2">Disallows negative value.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOLIDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: Used to process a consolidate comparison of portfolios. Need to set a matrix and a currency.</p>
            <p>	Input not allowed for groups</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alphabetic</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.CASH.OVERDRAFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>	Updated during the compare process.</p>
            <p> Holds the number of cells in the model that has an overdraft detected for each portfolio.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">NOINPUT field.</p>
                <p value="2">Numeric</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Set to "YES" ths will request a rebalancing session to be requested.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the field value to be filtered from the AM.SCENARIO record.</p>
            <p>      FILTER.VALUE, FILTER.FIELD and FILTER.OPERAND fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLY.FILTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Instruction button: used to process a filter on proposed orders</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AXIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the axis that will be used in the axis rebuilt process. If left blank, axis used by selected portfolios are rebuild.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.NDAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The portfolio valuation is based on the trade date + the projected cash at n days. Projected cash can be set from 0 to 5 days.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.OVERDRAFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>No Longer Update - See AM.COMPARE.DETAILS for details</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.PORTFOLIOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Portfolios to be excluded from this comparison.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCENARIO.SAVED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.ORD.GEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRID.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RBL.OUTPUT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRO.ERRORS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>If selected this will include open orders in the valuation for the portfolio. </p>
            <p />
            <p> It is only possible to select YES for this field if the parameter file is configured to allow open orders.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SESSION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of process to compare and rebalance portfolio.</p>
            <p>Accepts the values ‘RAISE CASH’ in addition to SECURITY, CURRENCY and HEDGING.</p>
            <p>When FILE.NAME is AM.GROUP.PORT, this field allows only ‘RAISE CASH’ and ‘SECURITY’</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alphabetic</p>
                <p value="2">
                    <p>	Field length increased from 8 to 10</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTBOUND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in this application see AM.COMPARE.DETAILS</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>PARENT.CHILD</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is used to generate parent child SEC.OPEN.ORDERS and will accept a value YES.</p>
<p> Parent order will be generated for each security and all the portfolio under that security will be individual child orders.</p>
<p> This field is allowed only for portfolio rebalancing and not for group rebalancing.</p>
                <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                </p>  
                <p>Alphabetical characters</p>          
</desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>PARENT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
<p>The parent reference provided in this field will form part of the common reference between parent and child.</p>

                <p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                </p>  
                <p>Alphabetical characters</p>          
                <p>A maximum of 21 characters may be entered</p>
</desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

