<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.CCY.HEDGE.WRK</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is maintained by the common build routine for the enquiries:</p>
            <p />
            <p>    AM.CCY.HEDGE.WRK.FORWARD.AMEND and AM.CCY.HEDGE.WRK.SWAP.AMEND</p>
            <p />
            <p>  These enquiries build a view of the table AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL summarised by exposed currency.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FWD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the forward rate that is to be used for the underlying AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records and their resultant FOREX deals.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field has been supplied as a convenience for local use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows for a trade date to be entered that is to be applied to all underlying AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field has been supplied as a convenience for local use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the spot rate that is to be used for the underlying AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records and their resultant FOREX deals.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field has been supplied as a convenience for local use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WORKFILE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID of the workfile record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field cannot be amended.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.FCTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the hedging factor that is to be applied to the underlying AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  On validation, the HEDGE.AMOUNT field will be populated with the appropriate amount that is to be hedged and all underlying </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows for a maturity date to be entered that is to be applied to all underlying AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field has been supplied as a convenience for local use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the reference currency of the Portfolio relating to the workfile record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field cannot be amended.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows for a value date to be entered that is to be applied to all underlying AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field has been supplied as a convenience for local use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the exposed currency for the workfile record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field cannot be amended.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows for the entry of a dealer reference.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field has been supplied as a convenience for local use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds a list of AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records that have been summarised to create a workfile record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field cannot be amended</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSED.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total exposed amount for currency hedging. This total is made up from the exposed totals from the underlying AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field cannot be amended.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID of the originating AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field cannot be amended.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total amount that is to be hedged for all underlying AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL records.</p>
            <p />
            <p> This field is populated when a hedging factor has been entered using on of the enquiries and the row has been commited.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

