<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.COMP.HIST.DET.WORK</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LAUNCH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field would record the latest  date of launch of Exclusion preparation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.MONTH.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the end value of the portfolio for the period indicated in the KEY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard AMT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUSION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain all the Exclusion codes that a portfolio satisfies (evaluates to true and excluded) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Field Format - 'A' (18) Multi Value Associated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUSION.LOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.STATUS.FLG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field records a manual status change affecting the portfolio within a specific composite.  It is updated only if the user wishes to overrule the system defined status in AUTO.STATUS.FLG</p>
            <p>Field MAN.STATUS.FLG will take priority to either Include or Exclude a portfolio for composite Performance. Field will be blank if there is no change to the Auto status suggested by system.  <p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the portfolio number.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUSION.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.EXCL.FLG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.STATUS.FLG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether a portfolio is either Included or Excluded for composite performance calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the field contains the status E (Exclude) and if the portfolio satisfies any of the exclusion rules defined at composite level, the performance of an excluded portfolio will not be considered while calculating  composite performance.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the field contains the status I (Include) and if the Portfolio does not satisfy any of the Exclusion rules specified at composite level, the performance of a portfolio with Include status will be considered for composite performance calculation.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEG.MONTH.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the begin value of the portfolio for the period indicated in the KEY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard AMT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMP.WORK.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID contains 3 parts which are the Composite Key , Performance Period specified as year month YYYYMM and the Portfolio No.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Field Format  -  'A' (35)     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

