<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL application allows the viewing and amendment of the proposed FOREX trades determined by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    The records created are a result of the processing of AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST records.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID of the detail record</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field canot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.FWD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the proposed forward rate to be used for FOREX orders</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This value will only be filled if an external user routine can provide this information.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the trade date that is to be used for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the exchange rate returned from an external system</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSED.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total exposure. This is calculated as the total exposed currency, forecast and position. </p>
            <p />
            <p> NOTE : The minimum cash amount is not included in this calculation as it only affects the calculation of the Spot leg of a Swap operation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This value is expressed in the exposure currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the customer ID identified by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ASS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of a multivalued set allowing restriction of portfolio valuation to specific asset/sub-asset combinations.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.BUY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the calculated forward amount to buy as expressed in the portfolio reference currency (REF.CCY)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a short description for the AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST record</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from equity dividends.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUIRE.RECALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds an indicator showing whether this detail record needs to be recalculated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.SELL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the calculated spot amount to sell as expressed in the portfolio reference currency (REF.CCY)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSED.CASH</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the cash value of the non-portfolio currency account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This value is expressed in the exposure currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the rounding parameter to be used to determine how amounts are to be rounded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUPON.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from bond coupons.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modiied.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.FLOW.ACTIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether forward flows are to be included in the valuation of currency accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID of the AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST record that was used by the cash management service to generate this detail record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LONG.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a longer description for the AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST record</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether the accounts identified by the traded currency will have excess cash swept into the counter currency account (a Sell operation) or will have a shortfall met by the transfer of funds from the traded currency account (a Buy operation)</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.THRESHOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the minimum amount that is to be transfered between accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.CASH.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the cash value beyond which a non-portfolio currency account is considered to be exposed ie portfolio accounts not in the portfolio base currency whose values are greater than this value will be considered for hedging.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This value is expressed in the system base currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSED.FCST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the value of any forward flows to be included.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This value is expressed in the exposure currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from interest payments from bonds.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from FOREX contract settlements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MM.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from money market repayments.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDEMPTION.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from bond redemptions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRITERIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a predefined criteria record from the AM.CRITERIA application. If present this criteria will be used to initially restrict the portfolios that are selected for sweeping.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.TRA.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the proposed amount to be traded in order to meet the actual hedging factor.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This value is expressed in the exposure currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REF.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the reference currency of the selected portfolio.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field canot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDERED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows whether thiss detail record has ben used to generate a FOREX trade</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HEDGE.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the portfolio ID identified by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.BUY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the calculated spot amount to buy as expressed in the exposure currency (EXPOSURE.CCY)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.SPOT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the proposed spot rate to be used for FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.AMENDED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds an indicator showing whether the values to be used for the creation of FOREX orders have been amended by an operator.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value date that is to be used for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.FWD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the actual forward rate that is to be used for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field is not mandatory however a value must be entered before a FOREX order can be placed. Normally this value would be obtained from the FOREX desk.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.HEDGE.FCTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the actual hedging factor that is to be used to determine the amount of the exposed currency that is to be hedged.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.SPOT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the actual spot rate that is to be used for resultinf FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field will default to be the same as the proposed spot rate but may be amended as necessary.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of a multivalued set allowing restriction of portfolio valuation to specific asset/sub-asset combinations.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.HEDGE.FCTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the proposed hedging factor.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    The value will always be 0.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSED.CASHBAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the total cash value of the non-portfolio currency account including any forecast forward flows.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This value is expressed in the exposure currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSURE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the exposure currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine if the value of open security orders are to be considered when valuing the accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSED.POSN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the value of security holdings.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This value is expressed in the exposure currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The use of this field has been depricated</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.SELL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the calculated forward amount to sell as expressed in the exposure currency (EXPOSURE.CCY)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain a running description of the progress of this detail record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    This field cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

