<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.CASH.MGMT.REQUEST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used by the AM.CASH.MANAGEMENT service and is populated whenever a change occurs that requires the assistance of the service.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Items written to this file are effectively trigger records and describe each action that the service is to perform. </p>
            <p />
            <p> Once the service has actioned each request, the trigger record is removed and when all records have been processed the service will terminate.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field automatically generated by the Request record.</p>
            <p>  This contains the type of request needed.</p>
            <p>  The Values are: </p>
            <p>   CLR - clear the details record.</p>
            <p>   BLD - Build the detail record.</p>
            <p>  ORDR - creates the order based on the source.</p>
            <p>  RCLC - recalculates the postfolios</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field automatically generated by the Request record</p>
            <p>    A flag to indicate that this detail record has been preselected for processing</p>
            <p>    The value used  YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field automatically generated by the Request record</p>
            <p>  Values Can be AMC, AML or AMH (Cash, Liquidity or Hedging) </p>
            <p>  - The addition of an A suffix here denotes that the request was generated automatically from an enquiry.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field automatically generated by the Request record</p>
            <p>  The ID of the originating request record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATETIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>NOINPUT field automatically generated by the Request record</p>
            <p>    The date and time that the request that generated this detail record was processed. </p>
            <p>    This should be in the format YYYYMMDDHHMMSS. All request generated by the processing of a request will have the same date and time stamp.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the AM.CASH.MGMT.REQUEST record.</p>
            <p>  The key to the file should consist of 3 parts as follows delimited by forward slashes "/" .</p>
            <p>   - Request type                                                                  </p>
            <p>   - The request application code which generated the record       </p>
            <p>   - The ID of the originating request record.                              </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

