<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.COMPOSITE.PORTFOLIO</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This file is a link file between Composites and Portfolios : it identifies the linked entities and contains information on the status of this link, such as its START.DATE and its PLUG.DATE.</p>
            <p>The multi-value structure of this file enables to create a new link between a composite and a portfolio when a previous link already exists.</p>
            <p> T</p>o enable the creation of a new link, the following rules are applied : <p /><p /><p>The previous existing link between this same composite     and same portfolio must be closed.</p><p /><p>And the systems checks also that Month+Year     (MMYYYY) of START.DATE of the new link is greater than Month+Year (MMYYYY)     of UNPLUG.DATE of previous link.</p><p /><p /><p /><p /></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>UNPLUG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The unplug date is part of a multi value set linked to the START.DATE. The unplug date is the last date from which a portfolio can be included in a composite performance. The unplug date is automatically calculated by the system based on a the CLOSE.DATE and the PLUG.DATE. The unplug date cannot be manually amended. </p>
            <p>e.g. if a portfolio is removed from a composite on the 16th July 2000 and the plug date is the 1st January 2000. The unplug date will be the 1st July 2000.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format, mandatory field generated by T24.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The unplug date must be greater than or equal to the plug date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the start date of the portfolio to composite link. A date prior to the current system date cannot be entered. This date is used to calculate the first month in which the portfolio can be included in the composite performance figures.  </p>
            <p>e.g.  Today is the 13th September 2001 and you enter 1st September 2001 the     system will return the error message "Start date is less than todays' date."</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format YYYYMMDD (Mandatory)</p>
            <p>The start date must be greater than or equal to the current date. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNPLUG.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The unplug narrative is part of a multi value set linked to the START.DATE. This field is treated as free text and can be used to detail why the portfolio is being removed from the composite.</p>
            <p>e.g. "The client has changed the investment strategy linked to this portfolio."</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Memo field (optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLUG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The plug date is part of a multi value set linked to the START.DATE. The plug date is the first date from which a portfolio can be included in a composite performance . The plug date is automatically calculated by the system based on the START.DATE entered and cannot be manually amended. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format, mandatory field generated by T24.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If a new multi value set is being created the new PLUG.DATE must be       greater than or equal to the previous UNPLUG.DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The close date is part of a multi value set linked to the START.DATE. This field details the date a portfolio is being removed from the composite. The close date is used to calculate the UNPLUG.DATE which will determine the last month a portfolio will be included in the composite calculation process.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format YYYYMMDD (optional)</p>
            <p>Must be equal to or greater than the PLUG.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMP.PORTFOLIO.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCL.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exclusion end date is part of a multi value set linked to the START.DATE. This field details the final date which will be applied to exclude a portfolio from the composite calculation process. The portfolio will be included in the composite calculations for the months starting at that date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format YYYYMMDD (optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PLUG.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>PLUG NARRATIVE: Free text which can be used to detail the reason why a portfolio is being removed from a composite.</p>
            <p>e.g. "Portfolios received investment of $1,000,000. Rebalancing the portfolio will take a week, therfore portfolio should excluded from the composite until rebalanced."</p>
            <p />
            <p>validation Rules</p>
            <p />
            <p>Memo field (optional)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

