<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.COMPOSITE.YEARLY.HIST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This file contains the composites yearly performance figures.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>It's structure is : 1 record per composite and per year.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This file is yearly updated, in january, by a batch job called AM.COMP.YLY.UPD.</p>
            <p>See also files : AM.COMPOSITE.HIST.DETAIL, AM.COMPOSITE.HIST and AM.COMPOSITE.HIST.EXCL</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>P.CP.RET.EQW.D</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.CP.RET.W.MD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sum of the portfolio's weighted Modified Dietz performance on gross values.</p>
            <p>Ret.W.Md = P.Cp.Ret.W.Md</p>
            <p>The value P.Cp.Ret.W.Md is taken from the AM.COMPOSITE.HIST record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CP.RET.W.MD</field>
<desc>
            <p> Sum of the portfolio weighted modified dietz performance. The cumulative modified dietz performance of all portfolios in the composite is weighted according to the portfolio market value of each portfolio against the total market value of all portfolios in the composite. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NB.PORTFOLIOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Numer of portfolios included in the composite at the end of the year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.END.M.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total end market value is the market value based on the reference currency of the composite of all portfolios included in the composite on the final day of the year (VALUATION.DATE) .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.N.FEE.PTF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the total number of non fee paying portfolios included in the composite at the end of the year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.CP.RET.W.D</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sum of the portfolio's weighted daily performance on gross values.</p>
            <p>Ret.W.D = P.Cp.Ret.W.D</p>
            <p>The value P.Cp.Ret.W.D is taken from the AM.COMPOSITE.HIST record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.BEG.M.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total beginning market value is the market value based on the reference currency of the composite, of all portfolios included in the composite on the 1st day of the year for which the composite performance calculation is being made.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.CP.RET.EQW.MD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the sum of the portfolio's equally weighted Modified Dietz performance on gross values.</p>
            <p>Ret.Eqw.Md = P.Cp.Ret.Eqw.Md</p>
            <p>The value P.Cp.Ret.Eqw.Md is taken from the AM.COMPOSITE.HIST record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The valuation date is the last day of the month for the composite performance calculation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format (mandatory field generated by T24. )</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AM.COMP.HIST.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CP.RET.EQW.D</field>
<desc>
            <p> Sum of the equally weighted daily performance. The cumulative daily performance of all portfolios in the composite is weighted equally over each portfolio. i.e. divided by the number of portfolios.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CP.RET.EQW.MD</field>
<desc>
            <p> Sum of the equally weighted modified dietz performance. The cumulative modified dietz performance of all portfolios in the composite is weighted equally over each portfolio. i.e. divided by the number of portfolios.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CP.RET.W.D</field>
<desc>
            <p> Sum of the portfolio weighted daily performance. The cumulative daily performance of all portfolios in the composite is weighted according to the portfolio market value of each portfolio against the total market value of all portfolios in the composite. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.D.PTF.V.END.M</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the total market value of all portfolios linked to composites at the end of the year.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Numeric field generated by T24.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

