<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.DYNAMIC.NODE.NAME</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds the list of active &amp; inactive models in the system along with the current validity date of the respective nodes (therefore which AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL record is current), together with the date the first instance of each node was created (this is defaulted onto the record when the AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL record is created) as well as the default description.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Validity date of the first instance of this node.  This will only be the same as the VALIDITY.DATE until the AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL record is copied either by the daily COB process or manually via AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL.COPY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALIDITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The highest validity date currently applicable to this node name.</p>
            <p>   Where multiple instances of the same node name exist  with different validity dates this field contains the highest or most forward VALIDITY.DATE in existance for this node name.  </p>
            <p>   Corresponds to the second part of the AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL id.</p>
            <p>   The AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL id takes the form NODE.NAME * VALIDITY.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of this node.  Set during record input to the most recent AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL record and defaults onto the description field of subsequent instance of the AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NODE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Corresponds to the first part of the AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL id.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    The AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL id takes the form NODE.NAME * VALIDITY.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Override messages generated during input of this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

