<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.ENTITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This file will allow user to define an entity and its extraction rules depending on the type of Application (Security, Account, Forex). I-descriptors fields can be used in the definition. </p>
            <p />
            <p>For example, with the entity currency CCY:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If     the currency is for an account (AC) then extract field CURRENCY     from the file ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If     the currency is for a security (SC) then extract field SECURITY.CURRENCY from the file SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If     the currency is for a loans and deposits (LD) transaction then extract field     CURRENCY from the file LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi valued field allowing to define multi selection for the same product code. Used for example in the case of the Foreign Exchange to specify if it is the buying ('BUY' input) or selling ('SELL' input) of foreign currency. Option must be set according to SET.POSITION routine. (see SET.POS.RTN field in AM.PARAMETER)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>0 - 5 alphanumeric characters free format text</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.PROC.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field accepts subroutine name to be processed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This should be a filename without the "Fxxx" prefix. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must exist in the STANDARD.SELECTION file </p>
            <p>0 - 25 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p> A pseudonym for an existing field. This type may be used
 if an existing field name is amended, the previous name
 should be defined as type P, the FIELD.NO should be set to
 the new name. This will then ensure that exsiting enquiries
 and versions still recognize the old name.
 A pseudonym will assume all the attributes of the field it
 is linked to in FIELD.NAME.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the ID of the PRODUCT code</p>
            <p>A PRODUCT code can be entered only once in the same record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Must exist as a PRODUCT id</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the ENTITY id.</p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the ENTITY in various languages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>0 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the ENTITY record. The entity application defined the positions that will be included in the entity by selecting instruments based on the values and fields from applications.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 characters. Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Must be unique as an ID record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a field name belong to the file contained in the FILE field associated. Can contain a constante string if FILE is not populate.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must exist in the file contained in the FILE field         associated</p>
            <p>0 - 30 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

