<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.GRID.FMT.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file will allow the user to define the formats used to display the results of the modeling comparison. (used by the AM.GRID.MASTER and AM.GRID enquiry).</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DISP.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sub-value field used to display a data on the line. Each sub-value contains a data element.</p>
            <p>The Header line allow only TITLE and SEPARATOR</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be either RELATIVE.MODEL.TARGET, RELATIVE.MODEL.MAX,   RELATIVE.MODEL.MIN, RELATIVE.DIFFERENCE, RELATIVE.REAL.WEIGHT,   ABSOLUTE.MODEL.TARGET, ABSOLUTE.MODEL.MAX, ABSOLUTE.MODEL.MIN,   ABSOLUTE.REAL.WEIGHT, ABSOLUTE.DIFFERENCE, VALUE, SEPARATOR or TITLE. </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique reference which identifies the GRID.FMT.PARAM record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>2 - 12 alphanumeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRID.FMT.PARAM.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to this record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Lets a user provide a short description about the formatting being used.  This multi lingual field can be used to provide a description of the parameter in various languages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISP.CHAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input allowed only for separator values. (DISP.VALUE field contains the value SEPARATOR).Any display characters can be defined in this field. E.g. "/", "#", etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>0 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISP.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Format applies to the value set in DISP.VALUE field (E.g.: "3L","5R1", etc.)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid format</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISP.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi-value field that is used to define each line that appears on screen. Each new multi-value defines a line. HEADER: this forces the lines to appear at the top of the screen and is used to show what the contents of the column will be. The values that appear will usually be axis members (e.g. the grid members).  DETAIL: this provides more information on what appears against each grid member. Within each cell of a grid multiple information can be shown, such as the minimum and maximum target weights.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must be either HEADER or DETAIL</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

