<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST is the main input and control routine for the cash management workflow that handles the tactical investment of liquidities. This workflow covers the short-term investment (disinvestment) of liquidities in securitised money-market instruments.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REDEMPTION.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from bond redemptions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.PORTFOLIOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the portfolios that needs to be excluded from Cash Mangement Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value date that is to be used for resulting security orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field defaults to the system date plus 2 days and must be greater or equal to the traded date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field is mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the rounding of the initial proposed nominal while capturing the sweep request.</p>
            <p>It should be a multiple of trading units given in SECURITY.MASTER application.</p>
            <p>This is applied only while capturing the request. This is not applied in case any amendments made to the intial proposed nominal.</p>
            <p>Rounding rule &amp; size are associated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.BALANCES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine whether only accounts with a short ballance ie a balance less than 0 be considered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Setting this field to Yes means that only accounts whose total value is short shall be processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Available options: Yes, No</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine if the value of open security orders are to be considered when valuing the accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Setting this to Yes will have the proposed purchase price of the securities removed from the value of the appropriate currency account..</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LONG.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a longer description for this AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SESSION.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the currency of the accounts to be swept. This currency will be used to identify the cash account that is to be examined.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The value entered here must exist in the CURRENCY application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.CASH.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the required target cash value that the session currency account should be adjusted through the buying or selling of the identified security.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALCULATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p> Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that any AM.LIQ.SWEEP.DETAIL records that have been flagged as requiring recalculation should be picked up and recalculated.</p>
            <p />
            <p> This field does not need to be used if the AM.PARAMETER field AUTO.RECALC.CM field is set to Yes</p>
            <p />
            <p> Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MM.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from money market repayments.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from FOREX contract settlements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables for rounding the initial proposed nominal while capturing the sweep request.</p>
            <p>This needs to be the valid  value from the EB.ROUNDING.RULE application.</p>
            <p>If the value is not given by the user, this field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
            <p>If the proposed nominal is manually amended then the rounding is not applied at order generation level.</p>
            <p>Rounding rule &amp; size are associated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds a security instrument ID which must be a valid record n the SEC.ACC.MASTER application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The currency of the security must match the session currency entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from equity dividends.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GENERATE.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that security orders should be created for all AM.LIQ.SWEEP.DETAIL records relating to this request. AM.LIQ.SWEEP.DETAIL records that are awaiting recalculation will not be processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a short description for this AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.FLOW.ACTIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether forward flows are to be included in the valuation of currency accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that the value of various forward flows should be included. The number of days for each flow type can be amended elsewhere in this application and default from values entered in the AM.PARAMETER application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p> Setting this to Yes starts the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ONLINE.VALUATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that any AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST records that have been flagged as requiring revaluation should be picked up and valuated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the trade date that is to be used for resulting security orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field defaults to the system date and must not be less than this date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field is mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from interest payments from bonds.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The contents of this field must be a valid field name from the SEC.ACC.MASTER application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The contents of this field must be a valid operand.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID of the AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST record. It will appear as SOURCE.ID on any related AM.LIQ.SWEEP.DETAIL records allowing these detail records to be associated with the parent request.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUILD.DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that the criteria and parameters entered in this application should be processed and relevent AM.SWEEP.DETAIL records should be created for the proposed sweeping FOREX trades.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Setting this to Yes informs the cash amnagement service that all existing AM.SWEEP.DETAIL records for this request should be deleted. This may not be set to Yes when the Recalculate field is set to Yes.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUPON.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from bond coupons.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRITERIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a predefined criteria record from the AM.CRITERIA application. If present this criteria will be used to initially restrict the portfolios that are selected for sweeping.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

