<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.MODEL.PORT.REBUILD</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PROPOSED.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Number of nominals to be bought or sold.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Current holding of the security in the portfolio.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Price currency of SECURITY.MASTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALIDITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the records in this application is built.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated with NET.OPEN.ORD.POS from SECURITY.POSITION. PROPOSED.NOMINAL would be reduced by open orders.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPOSED.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Market value of proposed nominal. Market price of security and exchange rate between portfolio reference currency and security price currency is given in AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL  If not given, the market price is obtained from SECURITY.MASTER application and exchange rate is obtained from CURRENCY application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Market value of current holding. Market price of security and exchange rate between portfolio reference currency and security price currency is given in AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL  If not given, the market price is obtained from SECURITY.MASTER application and exchange rate is obtained from CURRENCY application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROOT.NODE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.ABS.WEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Absolute Weight of proposed value. The weight of current holding with respect to overall portfolio value. This would be updated only if VALUE.TYPE is Percentage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid SECURITY.MASTER ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEGMENT.MEMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>SEGMENT.LABEL of AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL to which the proposal is related to.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TXFR.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the security transfer that was created by this modelling request.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.REL.WEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Relative weight of current holding. The weight is relative to node given in CHILD.NODE.ID. This would be updated only if VALUE.TYPE is Percentage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHILD.NODE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.REL.WEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Relative weight of proposed value. The weight is relative to node given in CHILD.NODE.ID. This would be updated only if VALUE.TYPE is Percentage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid SEC.ACC.MASTER ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.ABS.WEIGHT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Absolute Weight of current holding. The weight of current holding with respect to overall portfolio value. This would be updated only if VALUE.TYPE is Percentage.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to this record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Buy or Sell.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to overwrite system calculated value in the field ACTION.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.PROP.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to overwrite system calculated value in the field PROPOSED.NOMINAL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate between portfolio reference and security currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

