<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.PERFORMANCE.FEES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application contains the details of portfolio performance fees to be debited from the customer.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NOTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Its a free text.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUSTMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>It can accept a positive or negative value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.FEES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Sum of PF.FEES and ADJUSTMENT.AMT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid SEC.ACC.MASTER. Non editable.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUST.ACCRUAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value accepted is Yes or No.</p>
            <p>If Yes, the difference between ACCRUED.FEES and TOTAL.FEES would be posted as PL entries to bring the PL amount in sync with the amount debited from the customer.</p>
            <p>If the value is null then it gets defaulted from AM.PF.FEES.CONFIG.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AM.PERF.FEES.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Calculation date of performance fees. Non editable.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is initially set to Calculated and set to Posted if COB.POSTING is set after the posting window. </p>
            <p>User can hold the fees posting within or even after posting window by setting the status to Hold and can be posted anytime after posting window by setting the status to Reviewed. </p>
            <p>Once the status is set to Posted, the record cannot be edited. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.RATE.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>It contains the exchange rate between portfolio reference currency and local currency. Editable and defaulted to current mid rate. This is used to fees amount in local currency from portfolio's reference currency to update PL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.RATE.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>It contains the exchange rate between the account currency and portfolio reference currency</p>
            <p>Editable and default to current buy rate. The rate is used to convert performance fees into account currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PF.FEES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total performance fees calculated for this period.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Start date of this fees period. Non editable.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account number to debit total fees.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.FEES.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total fees accrued for this period in local currency. Non editable.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUED.FEES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total fees accrued for this period in reference currency. Non Editable</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

