<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Parameter table for asset management.</p>
            <p>Contains company level default values that must be set up for the Wealth Management  module to run correctly.</p>
            <p>One record must be created for each company running the Wealth Management  module.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEF.PORT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds a valid AM.PORT.TYPE record. </p>
            <p>Holds a value only when the field RBL.TO.DEF.PORT is set to ‘YES’. </p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory field when RBL.TO.DEF.PORT is set to ‘YES’.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MEMBER.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines whether Group / Portfolio rebalancing priorities are based on the priority in AM.AXIS (existing functionality) or AM.MATRIX.</p>
        <p>Validations:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Accepts any one of the value ‘AXIS’ or ’MATRIX’.</p>
            <p value="2">When the value is ‘AXIS’ - the grids are built considering the priority of the members from AM.AXIS</p>
            <p value="3">When the value is ‘MATRIX’ - the grids are built considering the priority of the members from AM. MATRIX.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RBL.ROUND.BUY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies rounding rules to calculate the nominal of BUY orders, that are generated through rebalancing.
</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>Accepts any one of the following values ‘UP’ or ‘DOWN’ or ‘CLOSER’
       </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"><b>UP:</b> The nominal is rounded to the closest round lot above the target. 
       </p>
            <p value="2"><b>DOWN:</b> The nominal is rounded to the closest round lot below the target.
       </p>
            <p value="3"><b>CLOSER:</b> The nominal is rounded up or down to the closest rounding lot depending  
       on whichever is closer to the target.
</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RBL.ROUND.SELL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies rounding rules to calculate the nominal of SELL orders, that are generated through rebalancing.
</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>Accepts any one of the following values ‘UP’ or ‘DOWN’ or ‘CLOSER’
       </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"><b>UP:</b> The nominal is rounded to the closest round lot above the target. 
       </p>
            <p value="2"><b>DOWN:</b> The nominal is rounded to the closest round lot below the target.
       </p>
            <p value="3"><b>CLOSER:</b> The nominal is rounded up or down to the closest rounding lot depending  
       on whichever is closer to the target.
</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RBL.TO.DEF.PORT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Accepts the value ‘YES’ or ‘NO’. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">If this field is set to 'Yes', then the system defaults all the orders to a portfolio that belongs to the port type, which is defined in DEF.PORT.TYPE in AM.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p value="2">If this field is set to 'No' then the group must have a portfolio with default port type.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.01</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.02</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.03</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.04</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.05</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.06</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.07</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.08</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.HEDGE.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A local routine to be called prior to the creation of FOREX deals resulting from Currency Hedging.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFS.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The OFS.SOURCE to use when creating OFS messages for wealth management applications.</p>
            <p>Currently used by the AM.DYN.POPULATE service to input the IHLD security orders that it generates.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SVEH.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Following fields are the essential fields which are copied from SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT to historic valuation file AM.VEH.MM.</p>
            <p>SECURITY.NO,  SHORT.NAME,  SECURITY.CCY,  NO.NOMINAL,  COST.PRICE</p>
            <p>MARKET.PRICE,  ESTIMATION,  ACCRUED.INT,  YIELD,  ESTIMTED.INCOME</p>
            <p>GR.COST.PRICE,  GR.YIELD,  APPLICATION,  VALUE.REF.CCY,  EX.RATE.PR.REF</p>
            <p>EX.RATE.PR.SEC,  EX.RATE.SEC.REF,  ACCR.INT.REF.CCY,  DURATION,  MKT.PRICE.DTE</p>
            <p>BOOK.PRICE,  GR.BOOK.COST,  DAYS.ACCRUED.INT,  CURRENT.YIELD,  ORIG.ACCR.DIV</p>
            <p>NET.ACCR.DIV,  REC.TAX.CUM.AMT,  REC.TAX.CUM.RESET</p>
            <p>Rest of the fields of SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT are optional and needs to be specified in this field to get it copied to historic valuation file AM.VEH.MM</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EOM.VALUATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to set month end valuation and performance of a portfolio, if month end falls on holiday.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Allowed values are EOM and LW AND EOM. Default value is EOM</p>
                <p value="2">If EOM - the valuation and performance does not generate on month end, if month end falls on a holiday.</p>
                <p value="3">If LW AND EOM - the valuation and performance does not generate on month end, if month end falls on a holiday. The last working day valuation and performance contains interest accrued till the last working day for products AC,SC,LD,MM and FD. A separate valuation and performance is generated on month end which has interest accrued till month end.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TXF.FEE.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the routine that is used for Fees Processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORD.EXPIRY.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of days orders generated in the SEC.OPEN.ORDERS will be valid for when generated from a Modelling session.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional       input</p>
                <p value="2">1 - 3 alphanumeric characters</p>
                <p value="3">The number of days input must be a numeric string and finish with a C or W       character</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.RBL.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the rebalancing method to be used for group rebalancing.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alphabetic</p>
                <p value="2">
                    <p>Accepts any one of the following values: ‘PRIORITY’ &amp; ‘PRORATA’</p>
                    <p style="list-style-type: circle;">
                        <p value="1">
                            <p>If ‘PRORITY’ is chosen, the positions are maximised based on portfolio priority given in AM.PORT.TYPE</p>
                        </p>
                        <p value="2">
                            <p>If ‘PRORATA’ is chosen, the maximisation of position will be pro-rated.</p>
                        </p>
                    </p>
                </p>
                <p value="3">
                    <p>Though prorate is chosen, portfolio without tax wrapper will not be prorated.</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VRT.DELIV.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The delivery instructions to be used for security transfers created during the rebalancing of virtual portfolios.</p>
            <p>Must a valid entry in the SC.DEL.INSTR table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
        <p>
            <p>COMPANY</p>
            <p>Specifies the COMPANY to which the user must be linked to in order to use the WEALTH MANAGEMENT application. This application must be set up before attempting to use the wealth management functions as the other Wealth Management  applications may use parameters from this file.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">ID must be based on 9 Alphanumeric characters in the format "CCGGGLLLL" where: </p>
            </p>
            <p class="Indent5Percent">
                <p style="list-style-type: circle;">
                    <p value="1">CC is a 2 alpha character COUNTRY code. </p>
                    <p value="2">GGG is a 3 numeric character COMPANY code. </p>
                    <p value="3">LLLL is a 4 numeric character local code or 2-3 numeric company mnemonic     characters or 2-3 uppercase alpha numeric company mnemonic characters.</p>
                </p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory Input</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBAL.BUY.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A portfolio modeling parameter that specifies the sub-routine which is used to launch the securities purchase process.</p>
            <p>The sub-routine returns the recommended securities and values to buy.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional       input</p>
                <p value="2">If not any sub-routine is entered then buy orders can't be generated.</p>
                <p value="3">Must       be a valid S type routine</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.CASH.MGMT.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A local routine to be called prior to the creation of FOREX deals resulting from Cash Sweeping.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RBL.OUTPUT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the order output style from rebalancing. </p>
            <p>By Default it uses high volume order processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOO.AGGREGATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field controls the default of the Depository from CUSTOMER.SECURITY/SEC.ACC.MASTER when the SEC.OPEN.ORDERs are created from Wealth rebalancing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LABEL.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>A portfolio modeling parameter that contains the label displayed in the totals row/column. This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the label TOTAL in various languages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">1 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text</p>
                <p value="2">Mandatory input</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAIN.DISP.FMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the format to be used to display in the main enquiry.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory input</p>
                <p value="2">Must be a valid AM.GRID.FMT record</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAIN.ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the main enquiry that will be invoked at first in comparison processing by the Context Enquiry Drill-down.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory input</p>
                <p value="2">Must be a valid enquiry</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a portfolio modeling parameter that specifies the company specific sub-routine to run when a comparison is run. More than 1 routine can be run by creating multi-value fields. The routines will be launched in the order of which they are set in the AM.PARAMETER file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional     input</p>
                <p value="2">35 character alphanumeric</p>
                <p value="3">Must be a valid S type routine</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVERT.SPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in backvalue operations and online valuations.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">If set as “NO” this flag will instruct the valuation(s) to include FX Spot deals as standard FX deals in the valuation.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.POS.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a currency modeling parameter that specifies the routine used to define how a currency positions should be determined. This routine is processed before a comparison is run and retrieves all the positions within a portfolio from the relevant T24 tables.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional input, if no routine is entered the currency modelling functions will not     be available.</p>
                <p value="2">Must be a valid S type routine</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUPON.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the default number of working days forward to be considered when calculating forward cash flow resulting from bond coupons.</p>
            <p>This field is used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIST.DURATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The HIST.DURATION defaults to 12. This means that the historical valuation data will be maintained on a 12 month rolling basis. This can be increased as per requirement, but decreasing is not permitted. </p>
            <p>For example, if the HIST.DURATION is increased to 20, historical valuation data will be maintained on a 20 month rolling basis and it cannot be reduced. </p>
            <p>Before increasing the duration in AM.PARAMETER the AM.CREATE.VEH.FILES Utility needs to be run to create the necessary containers.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIST.YEAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future developments.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.REVAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date field associated with back value transactions.  The date input will entail the valuation to be recalculated from this date. For doing the recalculation, BV.SELECT.DATE shall be taken into account and all BV transactions entered on or after BV.SELECT.DATE shall be selected for doing the recalculated valuation process.</p>
            <p>Validation rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is YES.</p>
                <p value="2">NOINPUT field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is NO.</p>
                <p value="3">Date should be greater than BV.SELECT.DATE.</p>
                <p value="4">Date should be greater than previously entered date, if any.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VEH.PTR.UPD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the date that the VEH.POINTER was last updated.</p>
            <p>No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIST.BACKUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future developments.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CM.ACCOUNT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This flag indicates whether the Cash Management applications will take the account balances from the Working Balance, the Online Actual Balance or from the portfolio Valuation.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">The default behaviour is to use the Working Balance.</p>
                <p value="2">Options are: 'Working', 'Online Actual' or 'Valuation'</p>
                <p value="3">If the field is left blank, working balance will be assumed.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDG.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a currency modeling parameter that specifies the company specific sub-routine to run when a comparison is run with a hedging matrix. More than one routine can be run by creating multi-value fields. The routines will be launched in the order of which they are set in the AM.PARAMETER file.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional input</p>
                <p value="2">35 character alphanumeric</p>
                <p value="3">Must be a valid S type routine</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADE.OR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the field is set to TRADE, a security transaction is considered to be a back value transaction if the TRADE.DATE of the transaction is less than today.</p>
            <p>If it is VALUE, a security transaction is considered to be a back value transaction if VALUE.DATE of the transaction is less than today.</p>
            <p>For other cash transactions, it is considered to be a back value transaction if the VALUE.DATE is less than today regardless of this field.</p>
            <p>Default is TRADE.</p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SVEH.APPLN</field>
<desc>
            <p>For each application specified in SVEH.APPLN, the list of fields to be maintained in SC.VEH.YYYYMM can be specified in SVEH.FIELD. The fields selected are the fields excluding those already maintained in SC.VEH.YYYYMM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CON.RATE.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies an external.local routine to be used to determine the actual exchange rates to be applied to FOREX trades generated by Cash Management processing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.TXN.UPD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with <b>BACKVALUE.UPD</b> field. Specifies when the back dated transactions are processed. </p>
            <p>Accepts three values ‘ONLINE’, ‘EOD’ and ‘OFF’.</p>
            <p><b>ONLINE</b> – In ONLINE, during COB, the actual re-calculation of Valuation and Performance figure does not take place.</p>
            <p> After running COB, user should launch the ONLINE.BACKVALUE.LAUNCH application to recalculate the values.  </p>
            <p class="note"><b>Note:</b> The Performance can be re-calculated online ONLY after a COB is run and the file BV.TRANSACTIONS is updated.</p>
            <p><b>EOD</b> – During COB, processes back dated transactions and recalculate all the valuations and performance figures.</p>
            <p><b>OFF</b> – Does not consider back dated transaction for back valuation.</p>
            <p>Value in this field will be populated in BV.SECURITY.TRANS, BV.CASH.TRANS and BV.CA.TRANS.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory field, if BACKVALUE.UPD field is YES.</p>
                <p value="2">
                    <p>If this value is given, the back dated transactions are processed, as if, they were input today and there will not be any Back value effect, though BACKVALUE.UPD is set to YES. </p>
                </p>
                <p value="3">
                    <p>If the BACKVALUE.UPD field is YES then this field is mandatory. </p>
                </p>
                <p value="4">If the BACKVALUE.UPD field is NO then input is not allowed in this field.</p>
            </p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.CASH.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds a default value as minimum cash amount, which is used in the cash management applications.</p>
            <p>AM.SWEEP.REQUEST - Account sweeping.</p>
            <p>AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST - Tactical investment of liquidities</p>
            <p>AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST - Currency hedging</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SET.POS.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a portfolio modeling parameter that specifies the routine used to define how a portfolios positions should be determined. This routine is processed before a comparison is run and retrieves all the positions within a portfolio from the relevant T24 tables.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional input,       if no routine is entered the portfolio modelling functions will not be       available.</p>
                <p value="2">Must be a valid S type routine</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOO.ORDER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value of this field is defaulted from the Order Type field on SEC.OPEN.ORDERs create from AM rebalancing</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with back value EXCHANGE RATE transactions. </p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>If the field is set to ONLINE or EOD then the back value transaction updates, related to exchange rate change are considered either ONLINE or at EOD processing.  </p>
            <p>If the field is set to OFF then the back value transaction updates for exchange rate change is ignored.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.TXF.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the SECURITY.TRANSFER Version record which is used to update SECURITY.TRANSFER through OFS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORD.VIOL.APPR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the following values ‘Partial’, ‘All’ and Null.</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">When ‘All’ is set, system checks whether all the violations are approved or accepted, else it raises an error.</p>
                <p value="2">When ‘Partial’ or ’Null’ is set, system generates orders for violations that are approved and ignores the rest.</p>
            </p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alphabetic	</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.FEE.RECALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DYN.MODEL.LIFESPAN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the number of days that inactive AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL records will remain in the live file, before archiving it to the history file. </p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>If set to zero or null then the inactive records remain indefinitely.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCK.SCE.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag indicates whether a lock must be done at the order level.If it is set to YES a lock is done at the Scenario order level.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatoryinput</p>
                <p value="2">Input must be either NO or YES</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REP.FLDS.UPD.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the routine that can be used to update the following fields during valuation processing.</p>
            <p>SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT REPORT.FLD1</p>
            <p>SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT REPORT.FLD2</p>
            <p>SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT REPORT.FLD3</p>
            <p>SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT REPORT.FLD4</p>
            <p>SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT REPORT.FLD5</p>
            <p>The routine defined here can be used to provide extra information into the valuation framework.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VRT.TRANS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The security transaction type to be used for security transfers created during the rebalancing of virtual portfolios.</p>
            <p>Must a valid entry in the SC.TRANS.TYPE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEC.PRICE.MONTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with back value transactions.  The number of months the  records in SC.BAK.VAL.PRICE.CHANGE file shall be retained before deletion. This is to enable the ONLINE BV  functionality  to retain PRICE.CHANGES for a required maximum period.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is YES.</p>
                <p value="2">No input field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is NO.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACKVALUE.UPD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This particular field is meant for activating the back value subsystem.</p>
            <p>If the field is set to YES then the back value transaction updates</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUATION.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a portfolio modeling parameter that specifies the routine used to value the portfolio.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This routine is launched when a user requests the Value portfolio instruction in the AM.COMPARE application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional       input</p>
            <p />
            <p>If no routine is       specified the portfolio valuation function will not be available.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid S type routine</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MM.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the default number of working days forward that are considered when calculating forward cash flow resulting from money market repayments.</p>
            <p>Used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDG.MASK.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a mask which defines the format of the date identifying the hedging cells.</p>
            <p>Hedging cells are made of a lead currency (fixed), an offset currency (floating) together with a maturity date. Field HDG.MASK.DATE allows defining the format in which this date is displayed.</p>
            <p>This mask allows identifying the day (D), month (M) and year (Y) in any order.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">D, M, or Y character</p>
                <p value="2">Mandatory input</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDG.POS.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a currency modeling parameter that specifies the routine used to define how a currency positions should be determined. This routine is processed before a comparison is run and retrieves all the positions within a portfolio from the relevant T24 tables.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional input, if no routine is entered the currency modelling functions will not     be available.</p>
                <p value="2">Must be a valid S type routine</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.EXTRACT.MONTHS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HDG.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Operational in a HEDGING modelling session.</p>
            <p>This message text is display on refresh of main grid enquiry (AM.GRID.MASTER.) to request operator on execution of linked routines.</p>
            <p>CCY.TXT and CCY.RTN fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the criteria in various languages.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">0 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MM.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the transaction codes to identify money market repayments from forward accounting entries.</p>
            <p>Used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.CA.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value recorded in the BX.TXN.UPD field.</p>
            <p>The BV.TRANSACTION fields (BV.SECURITY.TRANS, BV.CASH.TRANS and BV.CA.TRANS) are derived from the field BX.TXN.UPD.</p>
            <p>Validation rules:</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the transaction codes to identify FOREX contract settlement transactions from forward accounting entries.</p>
            <p>Used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the transaction codes to identify interest payments from forward accounting entries.</p>
            <p>Used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DURATION.APPLN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Duration is calculated on Bonds and displayed in SECURITY.SUPP. These settings allow consolidated duration enquiries to include CASH/MM/LD as well.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.SELECT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date field associated with back value transactions.</p>
            <p>Input of a date will entail selection of all BV transactions input on or after the date for BV recalculation. This is again based on the selection of earlier field namely, BV.SECURITY.PRICE, BV.EXCHNAGE.RATE ,BV.CASH.TRANS , BV.SECURITY.TRANS and BV.CA.TRANS.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is YES.</p>
                <p value="2">NOINPUT field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is NO.</p>
                <p value="3">Date should be less than  or equal to BV.REVAL.DATE.</p>
                <p value="4">Date should be greater than previously entered SELECT date, if any.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.VALUATE.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A group modelling parameter that specifies the routine to value the group. This routine is launched when a user requests the Value group in the AM.COMPARE application.</p>
            <p>If no routine is specified the group valuation function will not be available.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Accepts a valid subroutine.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.SECURITY.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with back value SECURITY.TRANSFER, SEC.TRADE and POSITION.TRANSFER transactions.  </p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is YES and BV.TXN.UPD is YES.</p>
                <p value="2">NOINPUT field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is YES and BV.TXN.UPD is NO.</p>
                <p value="3">No Change field after the first time input.</p>
                <p value="4">Field values ONLINE or EOD or OFF.</p>
                <p value="5">
                    <p>If the field is set to ONLINE or EOD then the back value transaction updates, related to the above  transactions will be considered either ONLINE or  at EOD processing.  </p>
                </p>
                <p value="6">
                    <p>If the field is set to OFF then the back value transaction updates for the above security transactions are ignored.</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.SECURITY.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with back value SECURITY.PRICE transactions. </p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory field if BACKVALUE.UPD is YES.</p>
                <p value="2">NOINPUT field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is NO.</p>
                <p value="3">No Change field after the first time input.</p>
                <p value="4">Field values ONLINE or EOD or OFF.</p>
                <p value="5">
                    <p>If the field is set to ONLINE or EOD then the back value transaction updates, related to security price change will be considered  either ONLINE or at EOD processing.  </p>
                </p>
                <p value="6">
                    <p>If the field is set to OFF then the back value transaction updates for security price change is ignored.</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.CASH.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with back value transactions.  </p>
            <p>Validation rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory field, if BACKVALUE.UPD and BV.TXN.UPD is YES.</p>
                <p value="2">NOINPUT field, if BACKVALUE.UPD is YES and BV.TXN.UPD is NO.</p>
                <p value="3">
                    <p>If the field is set to ONLINE or EOD - then the back value transaction updates related to cash transactions are  considered  either ONLINE or at EOD processing.  </p>
                </p>
                <p value="4">
                    <p>If the field is set to OFF - then the back value transaction updates for cash transactions are ignored.</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a currency modeling parameter that specifies the company specific sub-routine to run when a comparison is run with a currency matrix. More than one routine can be run by creating multi-value fields. The routines will be launched in the order of which they are set in the AM.PARAMETER file.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional input</p>
                <p value="2">35 character alphanumeric</p>
                <p value="3">Must be a valid S type routine</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANAGED.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future developments.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIST.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future developments.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONS.POS.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the routine used for constraints/positions.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.DURATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Cash is considered as having a fixed duration i.e. no. of days in the year = 365</p>
            <p>The value in this field is used as part of the duration calculation for MM/LD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONV.HIST.VAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates if conversion process is required to update valuation files during EURO conversion.</p>
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Field values YES or NO.</p>
                <p value="2">If the field is YES - AM.VEH and AM.INST.VEH is updated.</p>
                <p value="3">If the field is NO - AM.INST.PERF.DETAIL is updated.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the number of days from today allowing defining the value date of a SPOT contract. This parameter should be consistent with the SPOT.MARKET field defined in application FX.PARAMETERS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-2 numeric characters</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBAL.SELL.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A portfolio modeling parameter that specifies the sub-routine which is used to launch the securities sale process.</p>
            <p>The sub-routine returns the recommended securities and values to sell.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional       input</p>
                <p value="2">If not any sub-routine is entered then sell orders can't be generated.</p>
                <p value="3">Must be a valid S type routine</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the sub-enquiry that will be invoked when descending from the main enquiry by the Link Drill-down in comparison processing .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory       input</p>
                <p value="2">Must be a valid enquiry</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FEE.ADJUSTMENT.TYPE </field>
<desc>
        <p>Default Value is 'Adjust' and can be modified to 'REPOST'. </p>
        <p>Once set, cannot be modified. The value set here will get defaulted in SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.REBAL.APPL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether FOREX or FX.BULK.ORDER records are created, when generating FX orders, from the Modeling application. In both cases the records are generated in IHLD status.</p>
            <p>The FOREX records are generated in the portfolio company returned by means of GET.SAM.COMPANY routine. The latter is a user-defined routine that should pick up the company from a LOCAL.REF defined in SEC.ACC.MASTER</p>
            <p>The FX.BULK.ORDER option allows grouping orders generated from a list of selected SCENARIOs. The whole orders are created in the user company.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">FOREX or FX.BULK.ORDER</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Operational in a CURRENCY modelling session.</p>
            <p>This message text is display on refresh of main grid enquiry (AM.GRID.MASTER.) to request operator on execution of linked routines.</p>
            <p>CCY.TXT and CCY.RTN fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the criteria in various languages.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">0 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDEMPTION.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the default number of working days forward to be considered when calculating forward cash flow resulting from bond redemptions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VIRTUAL.BROKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The broker to be used by AM.DYN.POPULATE when creating SEC.TRADES.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry in AM.VIRTUAL.CUSTOMER.</p>
            <p>The CUSTOMER.SECURITY entry must have a type of BROKER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VIRTUAL.DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The depository to be used by AM.DYN.POPULATE when creating SEC.TRADES.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry in AM.VIRTUAL.CUSTOMER.</p>
            <p>The CUSTOMER.SECURITY entry must have a type of DEPOSITORY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the default number of working days forward to be considered when calculating forward cash flow resulting from equity dividends.</p>
            <p>Used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.SUMMARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This flag determines the operation of the Currency Hedging application.</p>
            <p>For normal use this is left blank.</p>
            <p>Set to YES if the processing of Currency Hedging Detail records is handled through the use of the AM.CCY.HEDGE.WRK file and associated enquiry.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RBL.ACT.CAT.EXCL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts a valid category.</p>
            <p>Account of this category will not be considered for group rebalancing.</p>
            <p>Account of this category will be considered for valuation.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Numeric</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECUR.DEPTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>A portfolio modelling parameter which defines the number of levels that will be built on a multi-dimensional grid.</p>
            <p>e.g. if the recursive depth is set to 2, the 3rd level of a matrix will not be built by the modelling application. Master grid (Asset Type) could have a linked matrix (Sectorial) set against it. This matrix (can also have a matrix linked to it (Geographic, 3rd level). The 3rd level matrix (Geographic) cannot be viewed when the grid is displayed as the recursive depth is set to 2.</p>
            <p>1st Level    2nd Level                    3rd Level</p>
            <p>Asset Type</p>
            <p>Equity        Sectorial    Banking   Technology</p>
            <p>Bond                                          Geographic</p>
            <p>Cash                                           USD</p>
            <p>Other</p>
            <p>Europe</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory     input</p>
                <p value="2">1     character alphanumeric can be entered</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLD.POS.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the routine used for AM.BUILD.MODEL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.REPORT.LOG</field>
<desc>
            <p>BV.REPORT.LOG gets updated only if this is set to 'ON' during backvalue price change.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VEH.POINTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Initially it holds the current month information.Gets updated as and when the Historic Duration is changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIST.PERIODIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future developments.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.SET.POS.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds a routine which defines how a group position is determined.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">
                    <p>Accepts a valid subroutine.</p>
                </p>
                <p value="2">Optional input, if no routine is entered then group modelling functions will not be available.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.TXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Operational in a SECURITY modelling session.</p>
            <p>This message text is display on refresh of main grid enquiry (AM.GRID.MASTER.) to request operator on execution of linked routines.</p>
            <p>MSG.TXT and RTN fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the criteria in various languages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">0 - 35 alphanumeric characters long free text</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RBL.ORDER.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows adding a routine which will be called to change the orders, prior to being written in the database.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Alpha numeric</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.OVERDRAFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a Portfolio Modelling parameter that contains the AM.AXIS Member name used to check for negative balances that are then identified as overdrawn cash accounts. This member name is used to count the number of cells with negative balances identified with this member name and report the number of cells in field 30.1 as CASH.OVERDRAFT cells.</p>
            <p>i.e. this field identifies how many of a clients different currency segments are overdrawn.</p>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">IMPORTANT NOTES:</p>
            <p>This function only verifies the gross value of a particular currency segment, if a client has a number of accounts in 1 particular currency and 1 of these is overdrawn no overdraft will be identified.</p>
            <p>This is not a multi value field therefore the same member name must be used in all the axis definitions where overdrawn cash positions need to be identified. The multi value, lingual MEMBER.LABEL field in AM.AXIS should be used to provide the correct labelling that should appear in reports and screens.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Optional input</p>
                <p value="2">0 - 12 alphanumeric characters</p>
                <p value="3">Must be a valid member in the AXIS file (no check)</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies rounding of nominals.</p>
            <p>UP: the nominal is to be rounded to the closest round lot above the target.</p>
            <p>DOWN: the nominal is to be rounded to the closest round lot below the target.</p>
            <p>CLOSER: the nominal is to be rounded up or down to the closest rounding lot depending on whichever is closer to the target.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DYN.MOD.NOM.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether dynamic model rebalancing will adhere to the trading units of the security when synchronizing a virtual portfolio.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Allowed Options are "Trading Unit", "Non Trading Unit" and null which defaults to Trading Unit.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HISTORIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the historical data of the SC.VALUATION.EXTRACT has to be maintained.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory.</p>
                <p value="2">Only YES or NO are allowed.</p>
                <p value="3">
                    <p>If set to YES, the file SC.VEH.YYYYMM(YYYY- Year &amp; MM - Month No.) is created and maintained.</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.COMPOSITE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the values: ONLINE or COB or OFF.</p>
            <p>By default its value is ONLINE.</p>
            <p>Based on this, value composite performance will calculate either in ONLINE or COB.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the transaction codes to identify equity dividends from forward accounting entries.</p>
            <p>Used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the default number of working days forward, that are considered while calculating forward cash flow, resulting from FOREX contract settlements.</p>
            <p>Used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.DISP.FMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the format to be used to display in the sub-enquiry.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Mandatory       input</p>
                <p value="2">Must be a valid       AM.GRID.FMT record</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the default number of working days forward that are considered, when calculating forward cash flow resulting from interest payments.</p>
            <p>Used by the cash management workflows begining AM.SWEEP.REQUEST, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.REQUEST or AM.CCY.HEDGE.REQUEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUED.INTEREST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Include/Exclude interest on month end in/from valuation and performance.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.CUT.OFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the R10 upgrade date. This is used to refer BV.ACCT.ACTIVITY before the CUT.OFF.DATE else it will refer ACCT.ACTIVITY after the CUT.OFF.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.RECALC.CM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether the Cash Management service is automatically started when a change is made to one of the detail records: AM.SWEEP.DETAIL, AM.LIQ.SWEEP.DETAIL or AM.CCY.HEDGE.DETAIL where the change would require the record being recalculated.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>If the field is set to YES then the Cash Management service is started as required.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AXIS.SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a portfolio modelling parameter and only SECURITY.MASTER or RECOMMENDATION can be entered. This defines the method used to decide which securities will appear in the eligible list and is used to build the axis concatenate file.</p>
            <p>The SECURITY.MASTER option will generate an eligible list based on all the securities in the SECURITY.MASTER file.</p>
            <p>The RECOMMENDATION option will generate an eligible list based on only those instruments in the AM.RECOMMENDATION file.</p>
            <p>This field is referred in AM.DYNAMIC.MODEL for random pick functionality</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>LABEL.DEF.MEM</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
