<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.SEGMENTS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Application used to define segments. Every record is configured as a segment representing a virtual grid and every grid will in turn contain set of instruments representing the segmented grid.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SEG.LBL.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>A descripton of the member, used in segmented valuation output.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.SEGMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is responsible for building the various segments. When 'Y' is input in this field and authorised the associated multi value consisting of the SEGMENT.LABEL and MEMBER.VALUE is built. Thus this field is responsible for building the virtual grid comprising a segment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEGMENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Record id specifying the segment.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEGMENT.LABEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Start of multi value associated set. Input field to specify the label for the segmented grid. This label is defaulted to the names of the members of the axes under the corresponding segment. The user may change the label if he wishes to</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEGMENT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>A short description of the segmentation scheme.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AXIS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is a multi value field which contains the axes whose members make up the segment. The field is linked to the application AM.AXIS..</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the description of the segment.   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.REBUILT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date (system date) and time last rebuilt</p>
            <p />
            <p> System generated field only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MEMBER.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field contains Member values from AM.AXIS. The values are  present in AXIS.CODE field of the corresponding AM.AXIS record. The field is a multi value associated with the field SEGMENT.LABEL. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

