<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.SWEEP.REQUEST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>AM.SWEEP.REQUEST is the main input and control routine for the cash management workflow that handles account sweeping. This workflow covers short balances as well as reallocating cash across currencies. This will usually be used as a post-process of securities rebalancing.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TRADED.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the currency of the accounts to be swept. This currency will to be used as the traded currency for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      The value entered here must exist in the CURRENCY application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Setting this to Yes starts the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.FLOW.ACTIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether forward flows are to be included in the valuation of currency accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that the value of various forward flows should be included. The number of days for each flow type can be amended elsewhere in this application and default from values entered in the AM.PARAMETER application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value date that is to be used for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field defaults to the system date plus 2 days and must be greater or equal to the traded date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field is mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.PORTFOLIOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the portfolios that needs to be excluded from Cash Mangement Process.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GENERATE.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that FOREX orders should be created for all AM.SWEEP.DETAIL records relating to this request. AM.SWEEP.DETAIL records that are awaiting recalculation will not be processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a short description for this AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from equity dividends.</p>
            <p>This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRITERIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a predefined criteria record from the AM.CRITERIA application. If present this criteria will be used to initially restrict the portfolios that are selected for sweeping.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALCULATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that any AM.SWEEP.DETAIL records that have been flagged as requiring recalculation should be picked up and recalculated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     This field does not need to be used if the AM.PARAMETER field AUTO.RECALC.CM field is set to Yes</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.THRESHOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the minimum amount that is to be transfered between accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This amount is expressed in terms of the TRADED.CCY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MM.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from money market repayments.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Up to 35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p> No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from FOREX contract settlements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the rounding of the initial proposed nominal while capturing the sweep request.</p>
            <p>It should be a multiple of trading units given in SECURITY.MASTER application.</p>
            <p>This is applied only while capturing the request. This is not applied in case any amendments made to the initial proposed nominal.</p>
            <p>Rounding rule &amp; size are associated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDEMPTION.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from bond redemptions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine if the value of open security orders are to be considered when valuing the accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Setting this to Yes will have the proposed purchase price of the securities removed from the value of the appropriate currency account..</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.CONVENTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether an external routine should be used to return a convention rate. The routine to be used is held in the CON.RATE.RTN FIELD in the AM.PARAMETER record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The default operation of the system will be to use an external routine if present. </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Setting this to No prevents the use of an external convention rate routine.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from interest payments from bonds.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p> The contents of this field must be a valid SEC.ACC.MASTER  record ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether the accounts identified by the traded currency will have excess cash swept into the counter currency account (a Sell operation) or will have a shortfall met by the transfer of funds from the traded currency account (a Buy operation)</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Available options: Buy, Sell</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      The contents of this field must be a valid field name from the SEC.ACC.MASTER application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID of the AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record. It will appear as SOURCE.ID on any related AM.SWEEP.DETAIL records allowing these detail records to be associated with the parent request.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      The contents of this field must be a valid operand.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables for rounding the initial proposed nominal while capturing the sweep request.</p>
            <p>This needs to be the valid  value from the EB.ROUNDING.RULE application.</p>
            <p>If the value is not given by the user, this field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
            <p>If the proposed nominal is manually amended then the rounding is not applied at order generation level.</p>
            <p>Rounding rule &amp; size are associated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the trade date that is to be used for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field defaults to the system date and must not be less than this date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field is mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.CASH.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the required target cash value that the traded currency account should be swept to by the transfer of funds between the traded currency account and the counter currency account within a portfolio.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      The operation type field determines whether the value of the traded currency account should be reduced or increased to this value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      In the case of a Sell operation, only accounts in excess of this value are processed with the excess being swept into the counter currency account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      In the case of a Buy operation, only accounts short of this value are processed with the shortfall being swept from the counter currency account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This amount is expressed in system base currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LONG.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a longer description for this AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ONLINE.VALUATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that any AM.SWEEP.REQUEST records that have been flagged as requiring revaluation should be picked up and valuated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUILD.DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that the criteria and parameters entered in this application should be processed and relevent AM.SWEEP.DETAIL records should be created for the proposed sweeping FOREX trades.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLEAR.DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the set of control fields which manage the cash management service</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Setting this to Yes informs the cash management service that all existing AM.SWEEP.DETAIL records for this request should be deleted. This may not be set to Yes when the Recalculate field is set to Yes.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTER.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the currency that is to be used as the counter currency for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      The value entered here must exist in the CURRENCY application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUPON.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from bond coupons.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      This field will default to the value from the same field in the relevant AM.PARAMETER record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

