<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.SWEEP.DETAIL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The AM.SWEEP.DETAIL APPLICATION allows the viewing and modification of records created by the cash management service from AM.SWEEP.REQUEST records. </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Each record contains details for a proposed FOREX transaction that will attempt to fulfill the desired sweeping action specified in the source AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a short description for this AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRITERIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a predefined criteria record from the AM.CRITERIA application. If present this criteria will be used to initially restrict the portfolios that are selected for sweeping.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWEEP.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the customer ID of the portfolio that contains the accounts to be swept.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.ACCT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds an account ID for the account that is to be the traded account for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.AMENDED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows whether the user amendable fields in this record do not match the proposed values</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.ORDERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to determine if the value of open security orders are to be considered when valuing the accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.CONVENTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether an external routine should be used to return a convention rate. The routine to be used is held in the CON.RATE.RTN FIELD in the AM.PARAMETER record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    The default operation of the system will be to use an external routine if present. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Setting this to No prevents the use of an external convention rate routine.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Available options: Yes, No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTERNAL.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a rate provided from an external system to be used instead of the T24 system proposed exchange rate.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVIDEND.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from equity dividends.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADED.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the trade date that is to be used for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value date that is to be used for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether the accounts identified by the traded currency will have excess cash swept into the counter currency account (a Sell operation) or will have a shortfall met by the transfer of funds from the traded currency account (a Buy operation)</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDEMPTION.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from bond redemptions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID of the AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record that was used to create this record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds a running progress narrative for this detail record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds details of overrides for this record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUIRE.RECALC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows whether changes to this recod mean that it must be recalculated before a FOREX order can be created from it. Records with this field set to Yes cannot be considered valid until they have been recalculated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from interest payments from bonds.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from FOREX contract settlements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.FLOW.ACTIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines whether forward flows are to be included in the valuation of currency accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.ACCT.FCST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the forecasted value of any forward flows.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This value is expressed in system base currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWEEP.PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the identified portfolio that contains the traded and counter currency accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRADED.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the currency of the accounts to be swept. This currency will to be used as the traded currency for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTER.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds an account ID for the account that is to be the counterparty account for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.ACCT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the cash value of the account to be traded. If the open orders flag is set to Yes then it will include the effect of open security orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This value is expressed in system base currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LONG.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can hold a longer description for this AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.TRA.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the proposed rate to be used for the FOREX order.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUPON.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from bond coupons.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.THRESHOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the minimum amount that is to be transfered between accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTER.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the currency that is to be used as the counter currency for resulting FOREX orders.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the ID of the originating AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.ACCT.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total value of the currency account to be compared with the min cash amount figure to determine the sweep action.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This value is expressed in system base currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.TRA.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the initially proposed traded amount for the FOREX order.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDERED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows whether this detail record has been used to generate a FOREX order.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.CASH.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the required target cash value that the traded currency account should be swept to by the transfer of funds between the traded currency account and the counter currency account within a portfolio.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MM.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the number of working days in the future to be included when checking for cash flows resulting from money market repayments.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the additional criteria field set that can be used to further restrict the selection of portfolios for processing by the cash management service.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.MIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the actual minimum amount to be used when determining the amount to be traded</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This value will default to the min cash amount figure entered on the AM.SWEEP.REQUEST record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Changes to this field will require that the record be recalculated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This value is expressed in system base currency.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.TRA.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the actual amount to be traded and will override the proposed traded amount</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This value is expressed in system base currency.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.TRA.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the actual rate to be used for the FOREX order.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CNT.ACCT.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the value of the counter currency account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This value is expressed in system base currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        This field is cannot be modified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

