<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>AM.VALUATION.EXT.GRP.CONS.LW</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>AM.VALUATION.EXT.GRP.CONS.LW will store the consolidated positions for various Groups defined in AM.GROUP.PORT application, for the last working day. This is a copy of the AM.VALUATION.EXT.GRP.CONS taken during batch.</p>
            <p>The following is the criteria for consolidating the various positions for each portfolio and populate the AM.VALUATION.EXTRACT.GROUP.CONS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />CASH<p /><p>Distinct currencies are consolidated separately</p><p /><p /><p />Money Market <p /><p>Distinct currencies are consolidated separately</p><p>Distinct maturities are consolidated separately</p><p /><p /><p />Fiduciary<p /><p>Notice and fixed fiduciaries are consolidated separately</p><p>Distinct rates are consolidated separately</p><p>Distinct currencies are consolidated separately</p><p>Distinct maturities are consolidated separately</p><p /><p /><p />FOREX<p /><p>Distinct maturities are consolidated separately</p><p>Distinct Couple currencies are consolidated separately</p><p /><p /><p />REPO <p>Distinct currencies are consolidated separately</p><p>Distinct security codes are consolidated separately</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>COST.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is populated in case of security position and contains the Weighted COST.PRICE of the security for the group, in the securuity currency</p>
            <p />
            <p>COST.PRICE = SUM(NOMINAL*COST.PRICE)/SUM(NOMINAL)</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />No input field <p /><p /><p />Automatically updated by the system whenever the Group Consolidation is performed <p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HELD.SINCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVE.GRP.CON.LW.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>AlphaNumeric Id which identifies the identifies the AM.VALUATION.EXT.GRP.CONS.LW.</p>
            <p>Each AM.VALUATION.EXT.GRP.CONS record is identified by the following components separated by a "*":</p>
            <p>1) Group ID</p>
            <p>This is a 3-10 alphanumeric Group Id identifying the group.</p>
            <p>2) Application system id</p>
            <p>This is a 2 Alphanumeric Product id.</p>
            <p>Positions 3 to 7 will be filled based on the Application System Id.</p>
            <p>3) Security Code</p>
            <p>This is used for Security Positions and Repos.</p>
            <p>4) Security Currency</p>
            <p>This is used for Cash, Money Market, Fiduciary, Forex and Repo.</p>
            <p>5) Maturity date</p>
            <p>This is used for Money market, Fiduciary and Forex.</p>
            <p>6) Interest Rate</p>
            <p>This is used for Fiduciary.</p>
            <p>7) Transaction type</p>
            <p>This is used for Fiduciary(NOTICE or FIXED) and Securities(Bond or Share).</p>
            <p>8) Sub Asset type</p>
            <p>9) Asset type</p>
            <p>10) Position Type</p>
            <p>This is based on the requirement whether the positive and negative posiitons should be consolidation seperately or combined for different products. The following values are possible : </p>
            <p>    P - Consolidated Positive Positions</p>
            <p>    N - Consolidated Negative positions</p>
            <p>    C - Consolidated Positive and Negative Positions together.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system whenever the Group Consolidation was       performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contents of this field varies depending on the module that the position is for. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />If the position is for an Account (AC) then this field will contain the consolidated ONLINE.ACTUAL.BAL balances from the Account records plus the value of any forward entries for those accounts generated by the Securities module for transactions that have updated the portfolio.<p /><p>If the position is for a Fiduciary Contract (FD) then this field will contain the consolidated principal amounts from the AMOUNT field on the underlying FD.FID.ORDER records for this group.</p><p /><p>If the position is for a FOREX contract the this field will Contain the consolidated amount bought (AMOUNT.BOUGHT) expressed in the currency CURRENCY.BOUGHT field from the original FOREX records .</p><p /><p>If the position is for a Money Market (MM) contract then this field will contain the consolidated principal amount from the PRINCIPAL field on the MM.MONEY.MARKET record that gave rise to the position. If the position is for a loan then the amount will have a negative   '-' symbol before it.</p><p /><p>If the position is for a security position (SC) then this field will contain the consolidated number of securities held by the Group. If the  security position is short then the figure will be preceded by a '-' sign.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No input field</p><p>Automatically updated by the system during batch process when the Group       Consolidation is performed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ESTIMATED.INCOME</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the position is a Money Market (MM) or a Fiduciary (FD) contract then this field represents theconsolidated annual income - i.e. contract amount multiplied by the interest rate.</p>
            <p>If the position is a Securities (SC) position then this field will represent an consolidated estimated annual income from the Interest Rate of the Security if it is a Bond or the PRICE.EARN.RATIO field on the SECURITY.SUPP record for the security if it is a share.</p>
            <p>This field is not updated if the position is for an account (AC), a Forex (FX) contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch when the Group     consolidation is performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEGIN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ASSET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUP.PR.YEAR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Security module : Specifies the number of coupons or interest payments a year .</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system whenever the Group Consolidation is       performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.AT.MATURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRP.VAL.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Valuation currency in which the consolidation was performed.</p>
            <p>During ONLINE, the consolidation can be performed on the currency of the user's choice. If the currency was not given by the user, then the Consolidation will be done on the currency given in AM.GROUP.PORT for this group.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input Field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch processing when the Group     consolidation is performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.COST.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARKET.PRICE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is a Security Position then this field contains the price of the security from the LAST.PRICE field on the SECURITY.MASTER record for the Security. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />No input field <p /><p /><p /><p />Automatically updated by the system whenever the Group Consolidation is performed <p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.ACCR.DIV</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ESTIMATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the value of the asset in the currency contained in the associated GRP.VAL.CURRENCY field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for an Account (AC) then this field will contain the consolidated ONLINE.ACTUAL.BAL balance from the Account records plus the value of any forward entries for this account generate by the Securities module for transactions that have updated the portfolio.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Fiduciary Contract (FD) then this field will contain the consolidated principal amount from the AMOUNT field on the underlying FD.FID.ORDER record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Forex contract (FX) then this field will contain the consolidated Estimated profit or loss of the Forex transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Money Market (MM) contract then this field will contain the consolidated principal amount from the PRINCIPAL field on the MM.MONEY.MARKET records that represent this Group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Security positin then this field will contain an consolidated estimated value of the security position calculated using the market price in the associated MARKET.PRICE field. If the security position is short then the figure will be preceded by a '-' sign.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the System during batch processing when the Group     Consolidation was performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DURATION</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Security module : Updated automatically with Duration of the Yield. These figures are updated automatically when the SC.CALC.YIELD routine is run during the end of day process.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system whenever the Group consolidation is       performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.TAX.CUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will hold the Recoverable Tax Amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard     T24 Amount (AMT) field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>V.DT.ESTIMATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the value of the asset in the currency ontained in the associated GRP.VAL.CURRENCY field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for an Account (AC) then this field will contain the consolidated ONLINE.ACTUAL.BAL balance from the Account records for the group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Fiduciary Contract (FD) then this field will contain the consolidated principal amount from the AMOUNT field on the underlying FD.FID.ORDER records for the group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Forex contract (FX) then this field will contain the estimated profit or loss of the Forex transactions that constitute this group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Money Market (MM) contract then this field will contain the consolidated principal amount from the PRINCIPAL field on the MM.MONEY.MARKET records of different positions that belong to this group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Security positin then this field will contain an consolidated estimated value of the security position calculated using the market price in the associated MARKET.PRICE field. If the security position is short then the figure will be preceded by a '-' sign. This figure will only include securities that have updated the security position via transactions that have settled before the next working day.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch processing when the Group     consolidation is performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.TAX.CUM.RESET</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will hold the Recoverable Tax Reset Amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard     T24 Amount (AMT) field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains a description of the particular asset. This is populated only in case of security positions. This will be the Short name Security. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />No input field  <p /><p /><p />Automatically updated by the system whenever the Group Consolidation is performed <p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Security module : Specifies the maturity date of the Security.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field.</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system whenever the group consolidation is     performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>V.DATE.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the consolidated value dated margin value of the different positions that constitute this group. If the position is a debit or a short position then this field will be equal to the associated V.DT.ESTIMATION field. Otherwise this field will contain a value calculated by multiplying the V.DT.ESTIMATION amount by the Margin Rate for the position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch processingwhen the Group     consolidation is performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTER.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is populated only in case of Forex positions. This field will contain either the amount sold (AMOUNT.SOLD) from the original FOREX record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch when the Group       consolidation is performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECURITY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.ACCR.DIV</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains a consolidated Margin value for the Group position. If the position is a debit or a short position then this field will be equal to the associated ESTIMATION field. Otherwise this field will contain a value calculated by multiplying the ESTIMATION amount by the Margin Rate for the position.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch processing when the Group     consolidation is performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVE.GRP.CON.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>AlphaNumeric Id which identifies the identifies the AM.VALUATION.EXT.GRP.CONS.LW.</p>
            <p>Each AM.VALUATION.EXT.GRP.CONS.LW record is identified by the following components separated by a "*":</p>
            <p>1) Group ID</p>
            <p>This is a 3-10 alphanumeric Group Id identifying the group.</p>
            <p>2) Application system id</p>
            <p>This is a 2 Alphanumeric Product id.</p>
            <p>Positions 3 to 7 will be filled based on the Application System Id.</p>
            <p>3) Security Code</p>
            <p>This is used for Security Positions and Repos.</p>
            <p>4) Security Currency</p>
            <p>This is used for Cash, Money Market, Fiduciary, Forex and Repo.</p>
            <p>5) Maturity date</p>
            <p>This is used for Money market, Fiduciary and Forex.</p>
            <p>6) Interest Rate</p>
            <p>This is used for Fiduciary.</p>
            <p>7) Transaction type</p>
            <p>This is used for Fiduciary(NOTICE or FIXED) and Securities(Bond or Share).</p>
            <p>8) Position Type</p>
            <p>This is based on the requirement whether the positive and negative posiitons should be consolidation seperately or combined for different products. The following values are possible : </p>
            <p>    P - Consolidated Positive Positions</p>
            <p>    N - Consolidated Negative positions</p>
            <p>    C - Consolidated Positive and Negative Positions together.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system whenever the Group Consolidation was       performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>V.DATE.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contents of this field varies depending on the module that the position is for.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position if for an Account (AC) then this field will contain the consolidated ONLINE.ACTUAL.BAL balance from the Account record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Fiduciary Contract (FD) then this field will contain the consolidated principal amount from the AMOUNT field on the underlying FD.FID.ORDER records for the group.</p>
            <p>If the position is for a FOREX contract the this field will Contain either the consolidated amount bought (AMOUNT.BOUGHT)  from the original FOREX record representing the bought side of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Money Market (MM) contract then this field will contain the consolidated principal amount from the PRINCIPAL field on the MM.MONEY.MARKET records that belong to this Group. If the position is for a loan then the amount will have a negative   '-' symbol before it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a security position (SC) then this field will contain the consolidated number of securities settled by the various positions belonging to this group at the current date. If the security position is short then the figure will be preceded by a '-' symbol.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch processing  when the     Group consolidation is performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.CST.EXC.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Date and Time on which the File AM.VALIUATION.EXT.GRP.CONS was last updated for this Group.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch processing when the Group     consolidation is performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUED.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the Consolidated amount of interest (income) that has been accrued for the Group but not yet been capitalised.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for an account (AC) then this field will contain the sum of the ACCR.CR.AMOUNT, ACCR.CR2.AMOUNT,    ACCR.DR.AMOUNT and ACCR.DR2.AMOUNT fields of all Account records for the group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position is for a Money Market (MM) contract then if the contract is a deposit then this field will contain the consolidated amount from the OUTS.CUR.ACC.I.PAY from the LMM.ACCOUNT.BALANCES records that represent this group. If the contract is a loan then this field will contain the OUTS.ACCRUED.INT field from the LMM.ACCOUNT.BALANCES records for the Group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position represents a Fiduciary contract (FD) then this field will be updated from the OTS.INTEREST field on the  FD.BALANCES record for all the contracts that constitute this Group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the position represents a FOREX (FX) contract or a Forward Rate Agreement then this field will contain 0.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If this position is for a Security then this field represents the consolidated amount of accrued interest for the Group.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No input field</p>
            <p>Automatically updated by the system during batch processing when the Group     Consolidation is performed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AM.GROUP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

