<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>ONLINE.BACKVALUE.LAUNCH</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SEL.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with SEL.FIELD and SEL.OPERAND.  Values can be input for selection, against SEL.FIELD and SEL.OPERAND to update the field PORTFOLIO.NO.</p>
            <p>Once the selection criteria is /are completed launching the preview is enabled so that all selected portfolios are displayed as an enquiry. </p>
            <p> These portfolios shall get appended in the record as selected portfolios on committing the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field, if SEL.FIELD is input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Values should be relevant to the selection criteria inputted in SEL.FIELD and SEL.OPERAND.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with SEC.ACC.MASTER fields.  Valid fields in SEC.ACC.MASTER can be used to define selection criteria to update the field PORTFOLIO.NO.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Field values check against STANDARD.SELECTION of SEC.ACC.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.MAIN.FUNC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with selection criteria.  Multiple selections can be input using AND or OR conditions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Field values AND or OR.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with selection criteria, manual input is allowed.  If selection criteria  is used then the field is No input field and system updates the portfolio numbers based on the selection criteria given.  If field is set to ALL then all the portfolios get selected.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field, if selection criteria is not defined.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid SEC.ACC.MASTER id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEL.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field associated with SEL.FIELD  Valid operands can be input for selection against SEL.FIELD and SEL.VALUE to update the field PORTFOLIO.NO. If the field selected is a alphanumeric field in SEC.ACCOUNT.MASTER , then GT, GE, LT and LE are not allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field, if SEL.FIELD is inputted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Field values are EQ, NE, GT, GE, LT, LE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field shows that the record has been processed or not. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Field value shows PROCESSED after the record has been verified.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRITERIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAUNCH.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date for which alone BV process need to be launched. Input of a date will entail the system to launch the BV process for the date entered and the valuation effect from BV.REVAL.DATE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid date less than today and should be greater than BV.SELECT.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAUNCH.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>@IDEnables user to launch Back value process on line in verify mode.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input of any numeric value shall be accepted.     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

