<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AM</product>
<table>SC.PERF.DETAIL.MAN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>IN.FLOW</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the sum of Inflows for a particular day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard Amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.C.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERF.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The ID is of the format Portfolio ID.YYYYMM</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The      first part of the Id has to be checked for a valid record in      SEC.ACC.MASTER.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Month      and Year should not be less than the date given in AM.PERF.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the      month and the date is less than the T24 Go Live date given in      AM.PERF.PARAMETER, it means that the application is being used as a      Take-on History. Check if a record exists for previous month. If it exists      populate the Begin value field with the last months end value. If the      month is January, last years December month value has to be populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the      month and date is greater than the T24 Go Live date given in      AM.PERF.PARAMETER, search for the record in SC.PERF.DETAIL and display it.      If a record does not exists the user should not be able to create a new      record. If a record exists the PERF.END.DAY field should become a No Input      field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will hold the Recoverable Tax Amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 AMT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MGTFEE.OUTFLOW</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the sum of Management Fees debited from the portfolio on that day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>It is used, according to AM.PERF.PARAMETER field value PERF.MGTFEES, to calculate Gross of Fees index (P.PERF.END.DAY)</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation rules :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERF.END.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the Performance Index (Net of fees) of the particular day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Decimal format.       </p>
            <p />
            <p>If the Application is used as a Take on History Tool :              If the user enters the value and if there is an mismatch between       the calculated value an override message is given.       </p>
            <p />
            <p>     If the Application is used as a Correction Tool :               This field becomes a NOINPUT field. The index for all multivalue        sets is calculated at the time committing.       </p>
            <p />
            <p>If the Begin Value of the record is not given by the user and if the previous       month record does not exist the begin value is calculated using       the formula :              Begin Value = (End Value - ( Inflow + Outflow)) / Perf.End.Day</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>P.PERF.END.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the Performance Index (Gross of fees) of the particular day.  <p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Standard Decimal format.       </p>
            <p />
            <p>     If the Application is used as a Take on History Tool :          If the user enters the value and if there is an mismatch between        the calculated value an override message is given.       </p>
            <p />
            <p>     If the Application is used as a Correction Tool :               This field becomes a NOINPUT field. The index for all multivalue        sets is calculated at the time of committing.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.DIVISOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUT.FLOW</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the sum Outflows for a particular day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SFKFEE.OUTFLOW</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the sum of Safekeeping Fees debited from the portfolio on that day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>It is used, according to AM.PERF.PARAMETER field value PERF.SFKFEES, to calculate Gross of Fees index (P.PERF.END.DAY)</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation rules :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.C.PERF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REMARKS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the reason for modifying the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.DIVISOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEGIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will contain the Begin Value of the portfolio for a particular month.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount format.     </p>
            <p />
            <p>If the Application is used as a Take On History Tool :</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) If the previous month's record exists, the Begin Value is populated with the previous              month's End Value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (2) If the previous month's record does not exist then the user is allowed to input              the Begin Value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (3) If the user does not enter the Begin Value the Begin Value is calculated when the              user enters the End Value.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the Application is used as a Correction Tool :</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) The Begin Value gets populated and the field becomes a Noinput field. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> This field contains the date on which the performance is calculated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date format.     </p>
            <p />
            <p>The Month and Year must be the same as given in the ID.     </p>
            <p />
            <p>The dates given in the multivalue sets must not be equal.     </p>
            <p />
            <p>The date given in one multivalue set must be less than the date given in the next multivalue set and greater than the date given in the previous multivalue set.     </p>
            <p />
            <p>If the given date is a Holiday an Override message is given.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIV.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field will hold the Dividend Accrual Amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 AMT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field contains the portfolio Value End Day for a particular Date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount format.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the End Value is not given, it       is calculated using the formula :              End Value = (Begin Value * Perf.End.Day) + Inflow + Outflow       </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

