<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>BALANCE.MOVEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is an internal file which holds average balance information for accounts and contract for use within the Management Information. </p>
            <p>  In addition, the refinancing information is held on here, as defined on the MI.PARAMETER "SYSTEM" record - and this information is used in the creation of cost of funds entries on the MI.COF.ENTRIES file. </p>
            <p>  Records on this file are produced and updated from the REBUILD.BAL.MVMT infromation, and information regarding run dates and the retention of the data is held on the MI.DATES file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>POST.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The true value dated balance of the account or contract on the date specified in the related field POST.VALUE.DATE, including the effect of any back valuations. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range VALUE.DATE to BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The opening balance for the contract or account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. The effect of any back - valuations will not effect the balance held on this field until the year and month in which the backvaluation was booked has been reached. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.KEY</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.AVG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average debit balance for the month is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will not effect the amount held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.CR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account was in credit (i.e. the balance was greater than zero) is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will be reflected in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.DR.AVG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average debit  book balance </p>
            <p>  (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.CLOSE.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The post adjusted closing balance for the contract or account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back - valuations  will effect the balance held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.TP.FCY</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE.COUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the number of entries with the Transaction Code specified in the corresponding TXN.CODE which have been processed during the month specified in ID field. </p>
            <p>  The multivalue associated group of fields TXN.CODE to TXN.AMT.TOTAL contain the number of entries and the total amount of entries with each different Transaction Code which have been processed during the month specified in ID field.  The group is repeated for each different Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  Note: The number and amount of any reversal entries are subtracted from       the figures in fields TXN.CODE.COUNT and TXN.AMT.TOTAL. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-6 numeric characters. Multivalue field associated with fields TXN.CODE and TXN.AMT.TOTAL (Internal file)</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSE.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The closing balance for the contract or account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. The effect of any back - valuations will not effect the balance held on this field until the year and month in which the backvaluation was booked has been reached. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.ZERO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account had a balance equal to zero is held in this field. Any back valued entries booked before the month in question has closed will be reflected in this day count. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the movement which has a value date held in the POST.VALUE.DATE field was booked on. If this field is blank then the movement was booked in the current or was booked before the month was closed (e.g. it was a pre closing adjustment). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 date field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range POST.VALUE.DATE to POST.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  Field range POST.BOOKING to POST.DR.MOVEMENT form a related sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFIN.RATE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The debit refinancing rate assigned to the record by the refinancing process as specified on the MI.PARAMETER 'SYSTEM' record, or from the LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS, MG.MORTGAGE or MM.MONEY.MARKET record. </p>
            <p>  The rate here is used to create the debit cost of funds entry, or may be used as the SOURCE.RATE.FIELD for MI.COLUMN records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 rate field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account was in debit (i.e. the balance was less than zero) is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will not effect this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.YRMONTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the BALANCE.MOVEMENT records. </p>
            <p>  The key to this file is composed of up to three parts, separated by a '*' </p>
            <p>  a) Contract ID  - The transaction reference or account number to which the                   BALANCE.MOVEMENT record refers to. For Securities, the                   key of the SC.TRADING.POSITION record is held in this                   field. </p>
            <p>  b) Year Month   - The year and month to which the record refers. </p>
            <p>  c) Currency     - For certain applications (e.g. FOREX) where multiple                   currencies may be involved, the currency of the record                   is held in the third part of the key. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.COF.RATE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>  Represents the Additional Cost of Funds  rate for debit  balances. The rate would be applied while MI.COF.ENTRIES are generated, on  the value of the field in BALANCE.MOVEMENT,   which is identified by  the field SOURCE.FIELD.DR of MI.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  This is a multivalue field associated with ADD.COF.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 rate field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.DR.AVG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average debit balance for the month is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will be reflected in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.OPEN.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The post adjusted opening balance for the contract or account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back - valuations  will effect the balance held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.DR.AVG.BAL.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average debit balance for the entire month is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  This field differs from the ADJ.DR.AVG.BAL field in that the debit balance for the month is divided by the total number of days in the month (according to the interest basis) to arrive at the figure held in this field, rather than dividing the debit balance by the total number of days in which the account was in debit. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back valuations booked before the month in question has closed will be reflected in the amount held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.AVG.BAL.YTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The balance of the account or contract on the date specified in the related field VALUE.DATE. </p>
            <p>  Back valuations will not appear on this balance until the month in which the back valuation was booked in is the same as the month for the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range VALUE.DATE to BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.OPEN.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The adjusted opening balance for the contract or account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back - valuations which were booked whilst the year and month specified in the key will effect the balance held in this field. However, any back - valuations which were booked once the year and month had closed will not be reflected in this balance until the year and month in which the backvaluation was booked has been reached. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRILL.ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.CR.AVG.BALMTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average credit balance for the entire month is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  This field differs from the ADJ.CR.AVG.BAL field in that the credit balance for the month is divided by the total number of days in the month (according to the interest basis) to arrive at the figure held in this field, rather than dividing the credit balance by the total number of days in which the account was in credit. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back valuations will be reflected in the amount held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the movement which has a value date held in the ADJ.VALUE.DATE was booked on. If this field is blank then the movement was booked in the current month. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 date field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range ADJ.VALUE.DATE to ADJ.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  Field range ADJ.BOOKING to ADJ.DR.MOVEMENT form a related sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.DR.AVG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average debit balance for the month is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations booked before the month in question has closed will be reflected in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            <p>  System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPEN.BD.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The opening balance for the  account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. This opening balance is based on the Booking Date/Accounting Date  of the entries in the Account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In case of entries with an Accounting Date, the balances would be updated only when the Post Closing (PC) Database are updated and the movement  would be reported against the date of the earliest PC Database updated.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.CR.AVG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average credit balance for the month is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations booked before the month in question has closed will be reflected in the amount held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.CLOSE.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The adjusted closing balance for the contract or account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. </p>
            <p>   The effect of any back - valuations which were booked whilst the year and month specified in the key will effect the balance held in this field. However, any back - valuations which were booked once the year and month had closed will not be reflected in this balance until the year and month in which the backvaluation was booked has been reached. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.BAL.YTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.ADJ.CR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.AVG.DR.BAL.YTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.MARKET.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the market value from SC.TRADING.POSITION and the value here is sum of the values in the fields CUR.COST.POSITION and REVAL.UNREAL.PL. This will get updated only SC contracts own book portfolio</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.CR.AVG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average credit book balance </p>
            <p>  (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.CR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account was in credit (i.e. the balance was greater than zero) is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations booked before the month in question has closed will be reflected in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the value date on which any balance movement has occurred for contract or account in the year month specified in the id of the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 date field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range POST.VALUE.DATE to POST.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COF.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the file on which the contract originated is held in this field, which is used extensively to perform the field joins specificied on the STANDARD.SELECTION record. </p>
            <p>  For Securities, this field should point to SC.TRADING.POSITION. </p>
            <p>  For Swaps, this field should point to SWAP.BALANCES. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customer to which the account specified in the key belongs. </p>
            <p>  OR </p>
            <p>  The customer of the contract specified in the key. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Must be a valid entry on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>  System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.CR.AVG.BAL.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average credit balance for the entire month is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  This field differs from the ADJ.CR.AVG.BAL field in that the credit balance for the month is divided by the total number of days in the month (according to the interest basis) to arrive at the figure held in this field, rather than dividing the credit balance by the total number of days in which the account was in credit. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back valuations booked before the month in question has closed will be reflected in the amount held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.CR.AVG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average credit balance for the month is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will be reflected in the amount held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.POST.DR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFIN.RATE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The credit refinancing rate assigned to the record by the refinancing process as specified on the MI.PARAMETER 'SYSTEM' record, or from the LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS / MM.MONEY.MARKET record. </p>
            <p>  The rate here is used to create the credit cost of funds entry, or may be used as the SOURCE.RATE.FIELD for MI.COLUMN records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 rate field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total credit movements for the associated value date held in VALUE.DATE which were booked in the current month. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range VALUE.DATE to BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.CR.BAL.YTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.CR.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total credit movements for the associated value date held in ADJ.VALUE.DATE which were booked on the date held in ADJ.BOOKING </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range ADJ.VALUE.DATE to ADJ.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  Field range ADJ.BOOKING to ADJ.DR.MVMT form a related sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>vCATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction reference or account number to which the BALANCE.MOVEMENT record refers to is held in this field. For Securities, the key of the SC.TRADING.POSITION record is held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value date on which a pre - closing back valued movement has taken place. </p>
            <p>  Any balance movements which take place in the current month also update this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 date field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range ADJ.VALUE.DATE to ADJ.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value date on which a balance movement in the current month has taken place. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 date field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range VALUE.DATE to BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.AVG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average credit balance for the month is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will not effect the amount held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.AVG.BAL.CAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount held in this field represents the average book balance </p>
            <p>  (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) </p>
            <p>  The average held in this field is calculated on a calendar basis, which is equivalent to a basis of 366/366.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.          </p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.          </p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.DR.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total debit movements for the associated booking  date held in BOOKING.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range BOOKING.DATE to     BOOK.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.POST.ZERO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.ZERO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the  account had a book balance (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) equal to zero is held in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.POST.CR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.CR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the  book balance (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) of the account was in credit  (i.e. greater  than zero) is held in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.CODE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount held in this field represents the average balance for the account or contract for the month specified in the key to the record. If the average balance calculation is run before the end of the month then this figure calculated from the beginning of the month up to todays date. Only entries booked in the month in question will effect this average balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. Internal file - system generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.AVG.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount held in this field represents the average balance for the account or contract for the month specified in the key to the record. If the average balance calculation is run before the end of the month then this figure calculated from the beginning of the month up to todays date. </p>
            <p>  All entries with value date in the month specified will effect this average balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. Internal file - system generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.DR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account was in debit (i.e. the balance was less than zero) is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations booked before the mont in question has closed will be reflected in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>  System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account was in credit (i.e. the balance was greater than zero) is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will not effect this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The balance of the account on the date specified in the related field BOOKING.DATE, as per the movements  reported in  BOOKING.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range BOOKING.DATE to     BOOK.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.AVG.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount held in this field represents the average balance for the account or contract for the month specified in the key of the record. If the average balance calcualtion is run before the end of the month then this figure calculcated from the beginning of the month up to todays date. </p>
            <p>  The average held in this field is dependent on the the INTEREST.BASIS of the record. </p>
            <p>  All entries with booked before the month specified has closed will effect this average balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. Internal file - system generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.DR.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total debit movements for the associated value date held in POST.VALUE.DATE which were booked on the date held in POST.BOOKING. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range POST.VALUE.DATE to POST.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  Field range POST.BOOKING to POST.DR.MVMT form a related sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.ZERO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account had a balance equal to zero is held in this field. Any back valued entries will be reflected in this day count. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.CR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.DR.BAL.YTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ZERO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account had a balance equal to zero is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will not effect this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.AVG.BAL.CAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount held in this field represents the average balance for the account or contract for the month specified in the key to the record. If the average balance calculation is run before the end of the month then this figure calculated from the beginning of the month up to todays date. </p>
            <p>  The average held in this field is calculated on a calender basis, which is equivalent to a basis of 366/366. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  All entries with value date in the month specified will effect this average balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. Internal file - system generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.DR.AVG.BAL.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average debit  book balance </p>
            <p>  (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.BAL.CAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount held in this field represents the average balance for the account or contract for the month specified in the key to the record. If the average balance calculation is run before the end of the month then this figure calculated from the beginning of the month up to todays date. </p>
            <p>  The average held in this field is calculated on a calender basis, which is equivalent to a basis of 366/366. </p>
            <p>  Only entries booked in the month in question will effect this average balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. Internal file - system generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.AVG.BAL.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average debit balance for the entire month is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  This field differs from the ADJ.DR.AVG.BAL field in that the debit balance for the month is divided by the total number of days in the month (according to the interest basis) to arrive at the figure held in this field, rather than dividing the debit balance by the total number of days in which the account was in debit. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back valuations will not effect the amount held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.DR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the contract or account was in debit (i.e. the balance was less than zero) is held in this field. The effect of any back valuations will be reflected in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 numeric field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range CR.DAYS to ZERO.DAYS form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.TP.LCY</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.COF.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>  Specifies the type of  Additional Cost of Funds.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Multi-valued field associated with the fields ADD.COF.RATE.DR, ADD.COF.RATE.CR, ADD.COF.DEPT</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Must be the ID of a valid record in the file     MI.COF.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the key of the Consolidation record  (in the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file) into which  the details of this contract are consolidated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Alphanumeric, as specified in the Consolidate Conditions file (CONSOLIDATE.COND). (Internal field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The booking  date on which a balance movement in the current month has taken place.</p>
            <p>  Entries with  an ACCOUNTING.DATE and updated to Post Closing (PC) Database would be reported against  the date of  the earliest Post Closing (PC) Database updated (i.e. earliest PC.PERIOD.END in the entries, provided the field PC.APPLIED=Y).    </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.   </p>
            <p>  Field range BOOKING.DATE to BOOK.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to     YES in MI.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>  The field would be updated only for Accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.AVG.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount held in this field represents the average book balance </p>
            <p>  (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.AVG.DR.BALYTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.AMT.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the total amount of entries with the Transaction Code specified in the corresponding TXN.CODE which have been processed during the month specified in ID field. </p>
            <p>  The multivalue associated group of fields TXN.CODE to TXN.AMT.TOTAL contain the number of entries and the total amount of entries with each different Transaction Code which have been processed during the month specified in ID field.  The group is repeated for each different Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  Note: The number and amount of any reversal entries are subtracted from the       figures in TXN.CODE.COUNT and TXN.AMT.TOTAL. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-6 numeric characters. Multivalue field associated with TXN.CODE and TXN.CODE.COUNT (Internal file)</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.ZERO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>vLCY.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.CR.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total credit  movements for the associated booking  date held in BOOKING.DATE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Field range BOOKING.DATE to     BOOK.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNDING.DEPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used within the Management Information module to define the profit centre which funded this contract. It is used in the generation of cost of funds entries, which in turn create MI.AUTO.ENTRY records to be included on the database. </p>
            <p>  The DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER set here is assigned during the refinancing process at the same time as the refinancing rates, as defined on the MI.PARAMETER record. </p>
            <p>  For the LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS and MM.MONEY.MARKET applications it is possible to set the FUNDING.DEPT on the underlying contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Must be the key to a valid record on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.DR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of days for the month that the  book balance (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) of the account was in debit (i.e. less than zero) is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.ADJ.ZERO.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.AVG.CR.BAL.YTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The interest day basis for the account or contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Must be a valid entry on the INTEREST.BASIS file.</p>
            <p>  System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.ADJ.DR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.AVG.BAL.CAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount held in this field represents the average balance for the account or contract for the month specified in the key of the record. If the average balance calcualtion is run before the end of the month then this figure calculcated from the beginning of the month up to todays date. </p>
            <p>  The average held in this field is calculated on a calender basis, which is equivalent to a basis of 366/366. </p>
            <p>  All entries with booked before the month specified has closed will effect this average balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. Internal file - system generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.DR.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total debit movements for the associated value date held in ADJ.VALUE.DATE which were booked on the date held in ADJ.BOOKING. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range ADJ.VALUE.DATE to ADJ.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  Field range ADJ.BOOKING to ADJ.DR.MVMT form a related sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.AVG.BAL.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average credit balance for the entire month is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  This field differs from the ADJ.CR.AVG.BAL field in that the credit balance for the month is divided by the total number of days in the month (according to the interest basis) to arrive at the figure held in this field, rather than dividing the credit balance by the total number of days in which the account was in credit. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back valuations will not be reflected in the amount held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.AVG.BAL.YTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.AVG.CR.BALYTD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total debit movements for the associated value date held in VALUE.DATE which were booked in the current month. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range VALUE.DATE to BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value dated balance of the account or contract on the date specified in the related field ADJ.VALUE.DATE, including the effect of any back valuations booked before the month in question has closed. </p>
            <p>  Any back valuations booked after the month in question has closed will effect this balance in the month last open month. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range VALUE.DATE to BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the system by which the Entry was generated and the file from which further details may be obtained. </p>
            <p>  The following is a list of possible codes and the corresponding files containing further details:- </p>
            <p>  SYSTEM.ID      APPLICATION </p>
            <p>  LCD            DRAWINGS LCM            LETTER.OF.CREDIT FDP            FD.FIDUCIARY FDO            FD.FID.ORDER SC             SC.TRADING.POSITION </p>
            <p>  Other system ids point to the standard files, e.g. MM points to the MM.MONEY.MARKET file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Up to 6 uppercase alpha characters. (Internal file)</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.CR.AVG.BAL.MTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average credit  book balance </p>
            <p>  (Fields: OPEN.BD.BALANCE and  BOOK.BALANCE) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 date field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.CR.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total credit movements for the associated value date held in POST.VALUE.DATE which were booked on the date held in POST.BOOKING. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  Field range POST.VALUE.DATE to POST.BALANCE form a related multi-value set.</p>
            <p>  Field range POST.BOOKING to POST.DR.MVMT form a related sub-value set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSE.BD.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The closing  balance for the  account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. This closing  balance is based on the Booking Date/Accounting Date  of the entries in the Account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In case of entries with an Accounting Date, the balances would be updated only when the Post Closing (PC) Database are updated and the movement  would be reported against the date of the earliest PC Database updated.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 amount field.     System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only if the field BUILD.BD.BALANCES is set to YES in MI.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>  The field would be updated     only for Accounts.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.DR.AVG.BALMTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The average debit balance for the entire month is held in this field. </p>
            <p>  This field differs from the ADJ.DR.AVG.BAL field in that the debit balance for the month is divided by the total number of days in the month (according to the interest basis) to arrive at the figure held in this field, rather than dividing the debit balance by the total number of days in which the account was in debit. </p>
            <p>  The effect of any back valuations will be reflected in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the account, or contract, specified in the id of the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  Must be a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p>  Standard T24 currency field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YTD.DR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Transaction Code of the entries for which the total number and amount are held in the corresponding TXN.CODE.COUNT and TXN.AMT.TOTAL. </p>
            <p>  The multivalue associated group of fields TXN.CODE to TXN.AMT.TOTAL contain the number of entries and the total amount of entries with each different Transaction Code which have been processed during the month specified in ID field.  The group is repeated for each different Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-3 numeric characters. Multivalue field associated with fields TXN.CODE.COUNT and TXN.AMT.TOTAL (Internal file)</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.DATE</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.COF.DEPT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Department which funded the Type of Additional Cost of     Funds. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  This is a multivalue field associated with     ADD.COF.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a  key to a valid record on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.COF.RATE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>  Represents the Additional Cost of Funds  rate for credit balances. The rate would be applied while MI.COF.ENTRIES are generated, on  the value of the field in BALANCE.MOVEMENT,   which is identified by  the field SOURCE.FIELD.CR of MI.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  This is a multivalue field associated with ADD.COF.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Standard T24 rate field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

