<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>BOOK.DATED.BALANCE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.DEBITS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies total amount of  debit   entries  for the Booking Date specified in the corresponding DAY.NO.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard amount format. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Multivalue field associated     with field range DAY.NO to BALANCE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPENING.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The opening balance for the  account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. This opening balance is based on the Booking Date/Accounting Date  of the entries in the Account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In case of entries with an Accounting Date, the balances would be updated only when the Post Closing (PC) Database are updated and the movement  would be reported against the date of the earliest PC Database updated.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount     field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.CREDITS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies total amount of  credit  entries  for the Booking Date specified in the corresponding DAY.NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard amount format. </p>
            <p>Multivalue field associated with field range DAY.NO to BALANCE. </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.NO.YEAR.MONTH</field>
<desc>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies Balance   for the Booking Date specified in the corresponding DAY.NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard amount format.</p>
            <p>Multivalue field associated     with field range DAY.NO to BALANCE. </p>
            <p>This is a NO INPUT field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLOSING.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The closing  balance for the  account for the month specified in the id of the record is held in this field. This closing  balance is based on the Booking Date/Accounting Date  of the entries in the Account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In case of entries with an Accounting Date, the balances would be updated only when the Post Closing (PC) Database are updated and the movement  would be reported against the date of the earliest PC Database updated.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 amount     field. System generated - this is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the booking  date of the entries which generated the credit and debit turnover and resulting balance in the corresponding field range TOTAL.CREDITS  to BALANCE.</p>
            <p>The multivalue associated group of field range DAY.NO to BALANCE contain the total amount of credit entries, the total amount of debit entries and the resulting Balance for each Booking  Date for which there have been entries. The group is repeated for each different Booking  Date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Entries with  an ACCOUNTING.DATE and updated to Post Closing (PC) Database would be reported against  the date of  the earliest Post Closing (PC) Database updated (i.e. earliest PC.PERIOD.END in the entries, provided the field PC.APPLIED=Y). </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2 numeric characters.  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

