<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.AUTO.ENTRY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>MI.AUTO.ENTRY is an internal file which contains details of MI Profit &amp; Loss entries generated by automatic processes.  (Manual MI P&amp;L Entries are input via the MI.ENTRY application) </p>
            <p>These entries are outside T24 core P&amp;L and so will not affect the T24 General Ledger.  They will only appear on MI reports. </p>
            <p>Entries are principally created in this file by the MI P&amp;L reallocation process.  Expenses and earnings for a department may be recharged to other departments, creating balancing entries in this file.  The rules for reallocation are set up in the Application MI.PL.ALLOCATION. </p>
            <p>This file may also be used to include P&amp;L from other sources into MI databases and reports.  Any P&amp;L entries must be in the correct format, and must be self-balancing. </p>
            <p>Entries will remain in this file until replaced by rerunning P&amp;L Allocation for the period, or until deleted once the MI retention period has passed.  The retention period is set in the application MI.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>Only the See, Print and List functions may be used in this Application. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OUR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Reference given to the transaction/deal by the Bank. </p>
            <p>P&amp;l Allocation will generate entries with this field copied from the original P&amp;L entry. </p>
            <p>If these entries are generated by the user from an external system, this field could be used to hold the id of the originating transaction. Alternatively, it could hold the id of the T24 transaction to reallocate the P&amp;L to, if this is known. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 16 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters, or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAL.MI.CATEG.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The SWIFT Currency Code of the Account or transaction on which the Profit or Loss was earned.  (Not necessary if the originating Account or transaction was in local Currency.) </p>
            <p>Where the Entry is generated from P&amp;L Allocation, this field is copied from the originating P&amp;L Entry </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 3 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters  Currency Code, or null.  (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory if currency not local</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of Profit and Loss updated by this Entry. </p>
            <p>If the Entry is for a Product type Profit and Loss Category (e.g. Commission), then the Product Category code is also stored in this record, in the field of the same name. </p>
            <p>For Entries to base level Profit and Loss Categories (e.g. Purchase of Goods), then the Profit and Loss Category code needs no further breakdown by Product Category. </p>
            <p>Note: 1) Profit and Loss Category codes are in the range 50000 - 69999. 2) Where the entry is generated from P&amp;L reallocation, this field is derived from the value of the 'allocate from' or 'allocate to' category code on the reallocation record.  This need not be the same as the category of the originating entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 5 numeric characters Category Code.  (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATED.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the actual run date on which this entry was generated.  This field is only used for Audit; the date used to determine which MI period the entry falls in is stored in the BOOKING.DATE field on this record. </p>
            <p>Where the Entry is generated from P&amp;L Allocation, this field contains the T24 date when Allocation was run.  This need not be the same as the booking date, or the date on which MI database build was last run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format.  (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p> A multivalue field containing a variable number of lines of 34 characters.  Narrative can be reported as additional description of the Entry, alongside standard transaction and reference text. </p>
            <p>Where the entry has been generated from  P&amp;L reallocation, this field will contain the narrative from the original P&amp;L entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 34 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Internal file, no user input.) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For P&amp;L allocation entries, this is derived from the original P&amp;L entry, and identifies the type of transaction for which P&amp;L is being reallocated. </p>
            <p>The transaction code can be used to reference narrative etc. held on T24 via the TRANSACTION application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>Must be a valid T24 transaction code (Internal file, no user input) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.MI.CATEG.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the MI.ENTRY.TYPE of the record which indicates the type of profit and loss entry being allocated or reallocated. The value in this field defaults to the value on the CATEGORY record for the PL.CATEGORY, or may specified elsewhere. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the MI.ENTRY.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.SYS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 24 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENT.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p> Identifies the system by which the Entry was generated  and the file from which further details may be obtained. </p>
            <p> The following is a list of possible codes and the  corresponding files containing further details:- </p>
            <p> SYSTEM ID       APPLICATION </p>
            <p>                 Foreign Exchange  FX              FOREX </p>
            <p>                 Funds Transfer  FT              FUNDS.TRANSFER </p>
            <p>                 Loans and Money Market  LD              LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS  MM              MM.MONEY.MARKET  MMP             MM.PAYMENT.ENTRY  MMR             MM.RECEIPT.ENTRY </p>
            <p> SYSTEM ID       APPLICATION </p>
            <p>                 Data Capture  DC              DATA.CAPTURE </p>
            <p>                 Securities  SC              SC.BUY.SELL  SC              FORWARD.TRADE  SC              POSITION.TRANSFER  SC              SECURITY.TRANSFER  SC              OPT.PURCHASE.SALES  SC              OPT.OPTION.TAKEUP  SCBD            REDEMPTION.BAL  SCBL            BOND.LENT.MASTER  SCCP            DIV.POST.CHECK  SCCI            CAPTL.INCREASE.DET  SCNI            NI.ADMIN.MASTER  SCSF            SAFEKEEP.DET  SCSD            STOCK.DIV.DET  Others          STMT.ENTRY </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-4 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PALCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency Market for Entry </p>
            <p>Where the Entry is generated as a result of P&amp;L Allocation, this field is copied from the originating P&amp;L entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 Character, Currency Market code (Internal file, no user input) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows whether the Entry was produced a result of netting several other potential entries. </p>
            <p>P&amp;L Reallocation takes existing P&amp;L and applies it to other departments, according to percentages set in the MI.PL.ALLOCATION Application.  The reallocation may be split between many departments, and may then itself be reallocated.  Thus there may be many entries in this file for each eligable P&amp;L entry. </p>
            <p>You can set an option in MI.PL.ALLOCATION to net similar entries.  Where this is set, a single entry is produced for the net amount, with this field set to 'Y'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 character -Y or Null (Internal file, no user input) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.AUTO.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p> A unique key to identify the Entry. </p>
            <p>The key is made up as follows: (a)        4 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st            December 1967. (b)        Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers            and (usually) 2 decimals.  If the time is an exact number            of seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted. (c)        Sequence number. </p>
            <p>If a transaction generates several Entries, all the Entries have parts (a) and (b) the same and are distinguished from each other by their Sequence numbers. </p>
            <p>P&amp;L Allocation will automatically generate a unique number for this field.  If you are generating the records from a user routine, you can guarantee a unique value by: - ensuring the key corresponds to the above definition - ensuring that only one process can generate records at a time - preferably by running the processes in MI.END.OF.DAY, before any databases are built. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>13 numeric characters or 16 characters consisting of 15 numeric characters with a decimal point after the 9th. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the run date on which MI takes as the date the P&amp;L of this entry was generated.  This date determines which database period the entry will be reported in. </p>
            <p>Where the entry is generated from P&amp;L Allocation, this date will be the same as the booking date of the original P&amp;L entry.  This is normally, but not necessarily the actual date at the time the original Entry was generated, e.g. if the previous day's business was still being processed after midnight, the actual date  changes, but the run date is still the previous day. </p>
            <p> Thus the reallocated P&amp;L will appear in MI with the same date as the original P&amp;L, even if P&amp;L allocation is run some time after the original P&amp;L was earned. </p>
            <p>The date on which the record was physically generated (ie the T24 date on which the reallocation was run) is stored for audit purposes in the field CREATED.ON. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of product the interest or commission has been earned on. </p>
            <p>For entries generated from P&amp;L allocation, it is derived from the product category of the originating P&amp;L entry.  Originating entries updating base  level types of Profit and Loss e.g. Purchase of Goods, have no product categories, and thus will leave this field blank. </p>
            <p> For interest and charges earned on Customers' Accounts  this field contains the Category code from the Account record.  For  Profit and Loss earned on other products, the Product Category is  entered in the originating transaction or generated by the originating  Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters Category code or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p> Identifies the Customer on whose behalf the transaction  generating the Profit or Loss was performed, or who  owns the Account on which the Profit or Loss was  earned. </p>
            <p> Not used for transactions where there was no Customer,  e.g. cashing travellers' cheques for non customers of  the Bank. </p>
            <p>Where the entry was generated from P&amp;L reallocation, this is copied from the original P&amp;L entry, to record the Customer for whom the original transaction was performed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric characters Customer code or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Department or account officer to which this Profit or Loss entry should be allocated. </p>
            <p>Where the entry has been generated from P&amp;L allocation, this will not always match the Account Officer on the originating P&amp;L entry. </p>
            <p>Reallocation is the process of reversing a portion of P&amp;L from the originating department, and allocating it to another.  Thus, the MI.AUTO.ENTRY will show: -For Debit entries, the Department/Account Officer from whom the P&amp;L is being taken.  This will match the originating entry -For Credit entries, the Department/Account Officer to whom the P&amp;L is being reallocated.  This will normally be different to the originating entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric characters Department Account Officer code. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to show Profit or Loss in foreign currency where appropriate.  For instance the Profit or loss may be earned on a Foreign Currency Account or a transaction in a foreign currency. </p>
            <p>AMOUNT.FCY contains the amount of the Entry in the currency specified in the CURRENCY field.  (it is not necessary in Entries where the originating Account or transaction was in local Currency.) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point (standard amount format, type AMT) signed, or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory if currency not local</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the Entry in local currency. </p>
            <p>(All Profit and Loss Entries are also expressed in Local Currency, even when they are the result of a foreign currency transaction, or interest and charges calculated on a foreign currency Account.) </p>
            <p>Where the Entry has been generated from P&amp;L Allocation, this field is calculated from the Local Currency amount of the original entry being reallocated, and the percentage set for reallocation in the MI.PL.ALLOCATION application. </p>
            <p>Where the NETTED field in this record is set to 'Y', the entry is a result of netting during P&amp;L Allocation.  This happens where : - netting has been requested in MI.PL.ALLOCATION, and - the Allocation process could otherwise produce several entries with similar characteristics. One Netted entry is created, with a Local currency amount equal to the sum of the individual entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-14 numeric characters plus decimal point (standard  amount format, type AMT), signed.  (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMENT.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify whether the MI.AUTO.ENTRY record is a debit or a credit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be 'DR' or 'CR' (Internal file, no user input) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Value Date for the Entry. </p>
            <p>Where the Entry is generated as a result of reallocating P&amp;L, this field contains the Value Date of the original P&amp;L (where a value date has been supplied). </p>
            <p>This field is not currently used by MI databases, as MI considers most P&amp;L entries to be non-value dating.  Where value dated P&amp;L is required, the MI.ENTRY application may be used to input P&amp;L adjustments manually.  Only MI.ENTRY records will be applied to the MI databases by value date, rather than booking date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format. (Internal file, no user input.) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to hold the Exchange rate where the Entry is shown in foreign currency.  It contains the Rate which was used to convert the Foreign currency amount to the local equivalent at the time of the originating transaction. </p>
            <p>Where P&amp;L Allocation has generated the Entry, this rate will be taken from the rate on the original P&amp;L entry.  This ensures that the local and foreign currency amounts for both original and reallocated P&amp;L are all consistent. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric characters and decimal point, (standard Rate format, type R), or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory if currency not local</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

