<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.BUDGET</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file contains the budget information for use within the MI application. </p>
            <p>Records on this file may not be created directly by the user, but are created by the MI.BUDGET.LINE application, either by the user at authorisation or by the MI system at the time of a database build. </p>
            <p>Records are removed from this file every time the MI.BUDGET.LINE record which created them is modified and authorised. When the MI.BUDGET.LINE record is reversed, the corresponding records are removed from this file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MI.BUDGET.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The unique key to the MI.BUDGET record consisting of ; </p>
            <p>COMPANY - The company for which the budget is set for. </p>
            <p>DATABASE - The database for which the budget will is to be used. </p>
            <p>PERIOD - The period to which the budget pertains </p>
            <p>MI.LINE - The area of the database on which the budget will appear. </p>
            <p>BUDGET.TYPE - The type of budget being setr </p>
            <p>CONSOLIDATE.COMPONENTS - The actual areas for which the budget is set for. </p>
            <p>Each part of the key id seperated by an underscore ('_'). </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual amount of the budget. This field is created via the MI.BUDGET.LINE file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field. No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

