<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.BUDGET.LINE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>MI.BUDGET.LINE is the file upon which budgets are set for use within Management Information. Records on this file may be created manually, but will usually be created with a status of HLD by verifying a record on the MI.BUDGET.CONTROL file. </p>
            <p>In addition to the normal T24 functions MI.BUDGET.LINE includes the following </p>
            <p>Verify    - Allows the download and upload of budgets to and from an             external source. </p>
            <p>Authorise - Previously created MI.BUDGET records will be removed.           - The system rebuild flag will be set unless the user rebuild             flag has been set.           - If the user rebuild flag is set then new MI.BUDGET records             will be created.           - The record will be sorted if the sort flag is set. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USR.REBUILD.BUDGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a record is authorised with this flag set to Y then MI.BUDGET records will be produced from this record. If this action is taken then the SYS.REBUILD.BUDGET flag will not be set to Y as the MI.BUDGET file is up to date with regards to this record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must either be Y or NO. Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The database period for which the amount specified in the field AMT pertains to. </p>
            <p>The fields BUDGET.FOR to ANNUAL.AMT form a related multi - value set. </p>
            <p>The fields DB.PERIOD to AMT form a related sub valued set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.LINE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to each MI.BUDGET.LINE record and is composed of four parts, separated by an underscore (_); </p>
            <p>Company - The budget for which the budget is being set. </p>
            <p>Database ID - The ID of the database for which the budget is being set. </p>
            <p>Budget Type - The type of budget being set. This allows multiple budgets to be set for each database. </p>
            <p>Year - The year for which the budget is being set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Company must be a valid record on the company file. Defaults to the current company if left blank.</p>
            <p>Database ID must be a valid record on the MI.DB.DEFINITION file.</p>
            <p>Budget Type must be a valid record on the MI.BUDGET.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>Year must be in the range 1950 to 2049.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.REBUILD.BUDGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whenever the MI.BUDGET.LINE record is authorised this field is set to 'Y' and the MI.BUDGET file cleared of any records which would have been created by the old record. </p>
            <p>This flag indicates that the MI.BUDGET records need to be created from this record. When the database specified in the key is built, the build routine will check this file for any records pertaining to the database with this flag set. </p>
            <p>If so the MI.BUDGET records will be created and this flag set to null. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System generated. No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOWN.LOAD.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the full Unix pathname of the file which will be downloaded to disk from the live file when the record is verified and the down load option taken. The user should ensure that he or she has sufficient access to the pathname specified to allow the record to be written. </p>
            <p>The record will be in a comma delimted format. The layout of the record should not be altered, although the contents of the record may. </p>
            <p>This record may then be transfered from the host machine to a PC and modified in a spreadsheet which has the ability to import comma delimited files. </p>
            <p>Once complete the record may be uploaded from disk using the upload option from the Verify function and is uploaded form the pathname specified in the UP.LOAD.FILE field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>YEAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SORT.BUDGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Whenever a record is authorised with this field set to Y the recorded is sorted by the BUDGET.FOR fields such that it is easier to locate a given BUDGET.FOR. </p>
            <p>Once the sort processing is complete this flag is re set to null. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must either be Y or NO. Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the budget to be set for the area specified in the related BUDGET.FOR field for the period specified in the related DB.PERIOD field. </p>
            <p>The fields BUDGET.FOR to ANNUAL.AMT form a related multi - value set. </p>
            <p>The fields DB.PERIOD to AMT form a related sub valued set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field. Negative amounts permitted, optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ANNUAL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Annual amount. An amount input into this field will be equally amortised across the periods for the year. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.FOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The area and report line for which the fields ENRICHMENT to ANNUAL.AMT are related. Data in this field is comprised of two parts; </p>
            <p>Consolidate Components - These specify the specific areas for which the                          budget is being set. </p>
            <p>Report Line            - The report line on which the budget will appear.                          The Report Line must be at the end of the data                          in this field. </p>
            <p>The fields BUDGET.FOR to ANNUAL.AMT form a related multi - value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Consolidation components must be valid records on the files to which they are related to as specified on the MI.DB.DEFINITION record. There maybe from zero to as many consolidation components as there are specified on the MI.DB.DEFINITION for the relevant database.</p>
            <p>Report Line must be a valid record on the MI.LINE file. Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UP.LOAD.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the full Unix pathname of the file which will be uploaded from disk onto the unathourised file when the record is verified and the up load option taken. The user should ensure that he or she has sufficient access to the pathname specified to allow the record to be read. </p>
            <p>Once complete, the record will have the status set to HLD. </p>
            <p>The file must be in a comma delimIted format otherwise unexpected results may occur. For this reason it is recommended that a template is created by down loading the record using the download option (again from the Verify function). </p>
            <p>The template will then be downloaded to the file which is specified in the field DOWN.LOAD.FILE. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENRICHMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This sub value field contains the enrichment for the related BUDGET.FOR field. There will be as many enrichment subvalues as there are consolidation components to allow for additional compoments to the BUDGET.FOR field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

