<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.COF.ENTRIES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to hold the Cost of Funds entries for use within the MI application. Records on this file are passed into the automatic generation of MI.AUTO.ENTRYs process, as defined on the application MI.AUTO.MAPPING, for inclusion within the MI databases. </p>
            <p>A record will exist on this file for each BALANCE.MOVEMENT record which has a debit balance and a debit refinancing rate, and a credit balance and a credit refinancing rate. Hence, each contract BALANCE.MOVEMENT record will usually produce one record on this file, while account BALANCE.MOVEMENTs may produce two. </p>
            <p>Each record on this file should produce two MI.AUTO.ENTRYs, one credit entry and one debit entry. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the SYSTEM.ID from the BALANCE.MOVEMENT record which produced the MI.COF.EMTRIES record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The TRANSACTION code to be used for debit entires created from this cost of funds entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUNDING.DEPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The funding department assigned to the BALANCE.MOVEMENT record which produced this cost of funds entry is held in this field. </p>
            <p>The funding department is set either on the the MI.PARAMETER 'SYSTEM' record at the same time that the refinancing rate is assigned to the record, or - in the case of contracts from the LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSISTS and the MM.MONEY.MARKETs aplpications - may be set on the underlying deal. </p>
            <p>The DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER defined in this field should be used as the ACCOUNTT.OFFICER for the balancing entry on which the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER defined in the above field ACCOUNT.OFFICER is used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The profit and loss category assigned to the cost of funds entry, as defined on the MI.PARAMETER 'SYSTEM' record, is held in this field. </p>
            <p>This value should be mapped into the PL.CATEGORY field on the MI.AUTO.ENTRY record via the MI.AUTO.MAPPING application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the CATGEORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where the cost of funds is shown in a currency other than the local currency, the exchange rate used to calculate the local currency equivalent is held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the CONTRACT.ID of the record which produced the MI.COF.ENTRIES record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.POSTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The year and month to which this cost of funds entry relates is held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The TRANSACTION code to be used for credit entires created from this cost of funds entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ACCOUNT.OFFICER of the BALANCE.MOVEMENT record is held in this field and should be used as one of the profit centres for the mapping of the ACCOUNT.OFFICER field on the MI.AUTO.ENTRY application, as defined on the MI.AUTO.MAPPING application. </p>
            <p>The opposite entry should use the ACCOUNT.OFFICER set in the complementary field, FUNDING.DEPT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Where the cost of funds was calculated in a currency other than the local currency, the contract currency amount of the cost of funds is held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The cost of funds amount, in local currency, is held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency in which the cost of funds amount was calculated is held in this field. </p>
            <p>This currency is taken from the currency defined on the BALANCE.MOVEMENT contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The product category of the account or contract which produced the cost of funds entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.COF.ENTRIES.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>A unique key by which the MI.COF.ENTRIES record may be identified. It is generated by the system, based on the date and time (in hundredths of a second) at which the transaction is input and a sequence number. </p>
            <p>The key is made up as follows: (a)        4 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st            December 1967. </p>
            <p>(b)        Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers            and (usually) 2 decimals.  If the time is an exact number            of seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted. </p>
            <p>(c)        Sequence number.            If a transaction generates several Entries, all the Entries            have parts (a) and (b) the same and are distinguished            from each other by their Sequence numbers. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>13 numeric characters or 16 characters consisting of 15 numeric characters with a decimal point after the 9th. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The MI.ENTRY.TYPE assigned to the cost of funds entry, as defined on the MI.PARAMETER 'SYSTEM' record, is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the MI.ENTRY.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The customer number from the BALANCE.MOVEMENT record which produced this cost of funds entry is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

