<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.COLUMN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table defines the columns that are available for use within the MI databases. </p>
            <p>Each record describes a single column. A column may be used in may databases, thus a column such as 'Interest income and expense' may be defined once and used department profitability databases, product profitability database, etc. </p>
            <p>The record defines the source records that are to be selected for inclusion in this column. For example if the column shows Commission Income then the record will specify which P&amp;L entries are to be included by referencing MI.SELECTION records. </p>
            <p>The record also defines the field on T24 where the data is found (indicating, for example, that the income figure in local currency is found in AMOUNT.LCY on the Catogory Entry table. </p>
            <p>The record also defines the characteristics of the resulting field such as its name, etc. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to be added into this column. </p>
            <p>The format of this field is either: </p>
            <p>          FILE.NAME&gt;FIELD.NAME      or   FILE.NAME </p>
            <p>A field name must be input for all column types other than record counts. </p>
            <p>Valid file names are: </p>
            <p>     File Name               Type </p>
            <p>     BALANCE.MOVEMENT        BALANCE.MOVEMENT      CATEG.ENTRY             ENTRY      MI.ENTRY                ENTRY      MI.AUTO.ENTRY           ENTRY      MI.BUDGET               BUDGET </p>
            <p>This is a multi-valued field to allow the same record to be used for more than one source file. Each source file may appear only once per column. e.g. </p>
            <p>     CATEG.ENTRY&gt;LCY.AMOUNT      MI.ENTRY&gt;LCY.AMOUNT      MI.AUTO.ENTRY&gt;LCY.AMOUNT </p>
            <p>Types of source file may not usually be mixed. Thus amounts from category entries cannot be merged with amounts from Balance Movements in a single column. The exception to this rule is for value type columns (VALUE and UNIQUE.VALUE) where the files can be mixed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>Must be in the format           FILE.NAME&gt;FIELD.NAME     or    FILE.NAME</p>
            <p>File name must be a valid Management Information source file.</p>
            <p>File name may appear only once</p>
            <p>Field must exist on the file.</p>
            <p>Files must be of the same 'type'. Valid types are:       Type                 File(s)      BALANCE.MOVEMENT     BALANCE.MOVEMENT      BUDGET               BUDGET      ENTRY                CATEG.ENTRY                          MI.ENTRY                          MI.AUTO.ENTRY  Thus a column may not contain information from MI.ENTRY mixed with BALANCE.MOVEMENT (except when the column type is VALUE or UNIQUE.VALUE).  This restriction is required because the Management Information databases may be built for one type of file at a time. For example a build can be run that brings the database fully up to date with P&amp;L entries but not Balance Movement. Columns have to be allocated to one type or another in order to simplify the process of rebuilding the database.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.RATE.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Short description </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum 20 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Selections used to match source records to this column. </p>
            <p>If the source record match the selection(s) specified here then the record will be included in this column. </p>
            <p>Selections are held on the MI.SELECTION application. </p>
            <p>For example if this column should contain commission income and there is an MI.SELECTION record defined as 'COMMISSION' which defines commission income record, then COMMISSION will be entered in this column. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>If entered must be a valid record on MI.SELECTION.</p>
            <p>Optional. If not specified then all source records will match this column.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.CONVERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used at present </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.COLUMN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of this column. </p>
            <p>May be any alphanumeric characters up to a maxumum of 12. </p>
            <p>Use a meaningfull, short, description. </p>
            <p>This will be used as the field name on Management Information database files and thus will be refenced in any reporting, Enquiry, etc. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the relationship between the selection parameters if there is more than one. </p>
            <p>  AND: The record is selected if it matches ALL the selection criteria </p>
            <p>  OR:  The record is selected if it matches ANY of the criteria </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be AND or OR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSOC.AMT.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Amount field associated with INT.RATE columns. </p>
            <p>If this column is calculating a weighted average rate, then this column must contain the field name that contains the principal amount to be used for weighting. </p>
            <p>For example if this column is calculating the average refinancing rate from Balance Movement records then field might contain AVERAGE.BAL. The resulting average would then be weighted by average balance. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory if column type is INT.RATE</p>
            <p>Must be an existing field on the source file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLUMN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of value the column holds. Valid column types are: </p>
            <p>ACCUMULATIVE    Accumulate ACCUM.LCY       Accumulate in local currency ACCUM.BCY       Accumulate in base currency BUDGET          Budget value INT.ACCR        Calculate accrual from this principal INT.ACCR.LCY    Calculate accrual from this principal in local ccy INT.ACCR.BCY    Calculate accrual from this principal in base ccy INT.RATE        Weighted average rate field COUNT           Record count UNIQUE.VALUE    Source value. If already present then ***MULT*** VALUE           Source value. If existing value different then ***MULTI*** </p>
            <p />
            <p>ACCUMULATIVE Values will be accumulated. Typically this will be used for balances in original currency, local currency P&amp;L etc. </p>
            <p>ACCUM.LCY Values will be accumulated and converted to local currency for the company being processed at the exchange rate prevailing at the end of the period. Typically this will be used for balance amounts when they need to be converted to local currency. The prevailing rate is extracted from the CURRENCY file and its history. </p>
            <p>ACCUM.BCY Values will be accumulated and converted to base currency, as defined on the MI.PARAMETER record, at the exchange rate prevailing at the end of the period. Typically this will be used for balance amounts when they need to be converted to local currency. The prevailing rate is extracted from the CURRENCY file and its history. </p>
            <p>BUDGET Budget value. Indicates that the incoming records is a budget. Budgets will always be accumulated. </p>
            <p>INT.ACCR Calculate an interest accrual amount. The principal will be the source field. The rate will be the contents of the SOURCE.RATE.FIELD on this records. The period and days in the year will be calulated based upon the INTERSEST.BASIS field. This column type can only be used with BALANCE.MOVEMENT source fields. </p>
            <p>INT.ACCR.LCY Same as INT.ACCR except the result is converted to local currency for the company being processed, at the exchange rate prevailing at the end of the period. </p>
            <p>INT.ACCR.BCY Same as INT.ACCR except the result is converted to base currency, as defined on the MI.PARAMETER record, at the exchange rate prevailing at the end of the period. </p>
            <p>INT.RATE Weighted average rate. The rate is taken from the source field. The princial used for weighting is taken from the ASSOC.AMT.FIELD on this record. </p>
            <p>COUNT Record count. Each record that matches the selection criteria for this column is counted. Note that if you wish to calculate the total number of records for this line then two COUNT columns will have to be created, one for Balance Movement and one for P&amp;L records. Budget records cannot be counted. </p>
            <p>UNIQUE.VALUE Source value will be placed into the column without accumulation. If the program detects a value already in the field then this will be overwritten with '***MULTI***'. </p>
            <p>VALUE Same as UNIQUE.VALUE except that '***MULTI***' will only be written if the existing value is different from the one about to be written. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Default is ACCUMULATE</p>
            <p>INT.RATE may only be specified if the source file is Balance Movement.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 30 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the column. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum 30 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.DISPLAY.FMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used at present </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

