<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.DB.DEFINITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table contains the main definition of each Management Information database. </p>
            <p>It specifies: </p>
            <p>- the records that are to be included in the database, </p>
            <p>- the columns that are to be maintained, </p>
            <p>- the line structure that is to be used, </p>
            <p>- what level of detail (consolidation) is the be kept in the database, </p>
            <p>- whether the database is monthly, quarterly, etc, </p>
            <p>- whether budgets are to be held for the database and, if so, at what level </p>
            <p>It also contains information on the last time the database was built. </p>
            <p>For example, the mi.db.definition record for the customer profitability (CP) database might state that all that only information for certain types of customer is to be included (identified by the sector of the customer) and that the customers id and the account officer responsible for the customer are to be passed forward to enable further analysis, and that columns are to be held showing average balance, interest income, and non-interest income. </p>
            <p>Upon authorisation of the mi.db.definition record the application will automatically create the new management information database (the mi.data.xxxx file) and its associated Standard Selection record. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Short description of the database. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory.</p>
            <p>20 characters max.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.COLUMN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REL.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The T24 file related to the consolidate.by field. </p>
            <p>For example if the consolidate.by is a customer id then the related file will be customer. This enables MI to obtain further information from T24 (such as full names and descriptions) as required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Must be a valid T24 application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.UPTO</field>
<desc>
            <p>For the build period specified in the BUILT.PERIOD field, the date up to which budget information was included in the database is held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields CO.CODE.ID to BUDGET.LAST form a related multi value set. Fields BUILT.PERIOD to BUDGET.LAST form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.LAST</field>
<desc>
            <p>For the build period specified in the BUILT.PERIOD field, the date on which the budget information was last included in the database is held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields CO.CODE.ID to BUDGET.LAST form a related multi value set. Fields BUILT.PERIOD to BUDGET.LAST form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The frequency at which the data is held. Valid frequencies are: </p>
            <p>ANNUAL QUARTERLY MONTHLY DAILY </p>
            <p>The database can be updated more or less frequently than that specified here but information will always be accumulated to this level. </p>
            <p>For example a MONTHLY database could be built each day. Figures would always be accumulated into complete months and during the month the database would contain the month to date figures. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory Valid values are: DAILY WEEKLY MONTHLY </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.UPTO</field>
<desc>
            <p>For the build period specified in the BUILT.PERIOD field, the date up to which profit and loss information was included in the database is held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields CO.CODE.ID to BUDGET.LAST form a related multi value set. Fields BUILT.PERIOD to BUDGET.LAST form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.CODE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the company code for which the partial build information held in the related multi value fields is related. </p>
            <p>Fields CO.CODE.ID to BUDGET.LAST form a related multi value field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.LAST.RUN</field>
<desc>
            <p>For the build period specified in the BUILT.PERIOD field, the date on which the profit and loss information was last included in the database is held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields CO.CODE.ID to BUDGET.LAST form a related multi value set. Fields BUILT.PERIOD to BUDGET.LAST form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.DATABASE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of this record and also of the management information database that will be created. </p>
            <p>The name selected should be meaningfull and a maximum of four characters. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Four characters maximum</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the database. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Thirty characters max.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>MI.SELECTION records that contain the selection for this database. </p>
            <p>Source records that match the selections will be included in the database. All others will be rejected. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Must exist on MI.SELECTION</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Lines to be maintained for this database. </p>
            <p>Must be a valid id on MI.REPORT.TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Must exist on MI.REPORT.TYPE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the relationship between the selection parameters if there is more than one. </p>
            <p>AND - the record is selected if it fulfils ALL the selection criteria </p>
            <p>OR - the record is selected if it fulfils ANY of the selection criteria </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Default is AND</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.FOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specific values for each budget criterion that will be used during the automatic generation of mi.budget.line records. </p>
            <p>Thus if you wish to budget for certain department/client combinations then these may be input here. </p>
            <p>Two special values may be input: </p>
            <p>  EXIST    will generate budgets for values that currently exist in the database </p>
            <p>  ALL      will generate budgets for values on the REL.FILE </p>
            <p />
            <p>Examples: </p>
            <p>If this database is being held at department and team level (consolidate.by of DEPARTMENT and TEAM and you wish to generate budgets for all department and team combinations that already exist on the database then the following should be input: </p>
            <p>  BUDGET.BY      DEPARTMENT   BUDGET.FOR     EXIST   BUDGET.BY      TEAM   BUDGET.FOR     EXIST </p>
            <p />
            <p>Using the the same database - if you wish to budget for all departments that exist on the database but only for certain teams then the following could be input. </p>
            <p>  BUDGET.BY      DEPARTMENT   BUDGET.FOR     EXIST   BUDGET.BY      TEAM   BUDGET.FOR     100            Forex team   BUDGET.FOR     102            Money Market team </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional</p>
            <p>Must exist on the REL.FILE for the budget field.</p>
            <p>EXIST or ALL may be specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDITIONAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Additional, specific budget records may be specified here. </p>
            <p>If the BUDGET.FOR mechanism is not able to specify certain, specific budget combinations then they may be manually input here. </p>
            <p>For example if the majority of budgets are being maintained just for departments then the budget.for field would contain just DEPARTMENT. However if few specific customers within a particular department are also to have budgets set then these specific combinations may be specified in the ADDITIONAL field. </p>
            <p>For example: </p>
            <p>CONSOLIDATE.BY  DEPARTMENT CONSOLIDATE.BY  CUSTOMER.NO BUDGET.BY       DEPARTMENT BUDGET.FOR      EXIST ADDITIONAL      400_12547 ADDITIONAL      400_12554 </p>
            <p>The system would then create 'empty' budget structures for all departments that existed on the database and two additional budgets for department 400 and customers 12547 and 12554. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional</p>
            <p>Fields must be in same sequence as consolidate.by and budget.by</p>
            <p>Fields must exist in the appropriate related file (REL.FILE)</p>
            <p>Fields must be separated by an underscore character (_)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.LAST.RUN</field>
<desc>
            <p>For the build period specified in the BUILT.PERIOD field, the date on which the BALANCE.MOVEMENT information was last included in the database is held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields CO.CODE.ID to BUDGET.LAST form a related multi value set. Fields BUILT.PERIOD to BUDGET.LAST form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.UPTO</field>
<desc>
            <p>For the build period specified in the BUILT.PERIOD field, the date up to which BALANCE.MOVEMENT information was included in the database is held in this field. </p>
            <p>Fields CO.CODE.ID to BUDGET.LAST form a related multi value set. Fields BUILT.PERIOD to BUDGET.LAST form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGET.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The level at which budgets are to be held for this database. </p>
            <p>The fields entered here must already have been specified as consolidate.by fields in this record and must be in the same sequence. </p>
            <p>Entry in this field will cause the budget generation facility to automatically generate budgets at this level. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Duplicates not allowed</p>
            <p>Must already bave been specified as a CONSOLIDATE.BY field on this database. Budgets can only be specified for data that is being held in the database.</p>
            <p>Must be in the same position in CONSOLIDATE.BY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLUMN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Columns to be maintained for this database. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>At least one column must be specified.</p>
            <p>Must exist on MI.COLUMN.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUILT.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The period for which the related partial build information is held in this field. When a database is built for this period the dates held in the related fields are used to determine build period of the database. </p>
            <p>Fields CO.CODE.ID to BUDGET.LAST form a related multi value set. Fields BUILT.PERIOD to BUDGET.LAST form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOLIDATE.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Consolidation key fields e.g. CUSTOMER.NO or DEPARTMENT. </p>
            <p>The database will be held at this level. </p>
            <p>Thus if DEPARTMENT is specified then the database will be held at department level. It will thus be possible to produce reports by department. </p>
            <p>If more than one CONSOLIDATE.BY field is specified then it will be possible to produce reports at one or both levels. This also enables a report to be produced at one level (e.g. department) and then further detailed analysis performed (such as at customer level) when required. </p>
            <p>Note that this can be an I-descriptor field enabling associated information such as an account officers department code to be included. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

