<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.ENTRY.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used within the MI module to determine the type of profit and loss entry being allocated or reallocated. Hence it only appears on profit and loss categories (ie categories greater than 49999). It appears as a field on the MI.ENTRY and MI.AUTO.ENTRY applications. </p>
            <p>The MI.ENTRY.TYPE of CATEG.ENTRYs is found as a default from the PL.CATEGORY and linking to the CATEGORY file to retrieve the MI.ENTRY.TYPE. </p>
            <p>Records on this file can not be reversed. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a language related field and holds a short description of the type of entry which this record relates to. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a language related field and is used to describe the type of entry which this record relates to. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 50 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement. </p>
            <p>As in the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to define in the MI.ENTRY.TYPE file up to 999 Local Elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified.  These Local Elements should be defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters as defined in the Local Table definition for this Local Reference field. Multivalue field. (Optional or Mandatory Input according to definition in LOCAL.TABLE for this Local Reference element)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.ENTRY.TYPE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to the records on this file and is a unique code used to specify the type of profit and loss entry being allocated or reallocated. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to four alphanumeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

