<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.ENTRY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>MI.ENTRY is an Application which allows you to input manual MI Profit and Loss entries for inclusion in MI databases. </p>
            <p>These entries are outside T24 core P&amp;L and so will not affect the T24 General Ledger.  They will only appear on MI reports. </p>
            <p>You can use this Application to input any simple P&amp;L entries which are not held on T24, but which you would like to report as part of your management information.  For instance, departmental staff costs, where payroll is held on another system. </p>
            <p>You can also use MI.ENTRY to make amendments to T24 P&amp;L entries.  For example, you can manually reallocate interest income earned on a deal, between the departments involved.  You may also want to see a 'value dated' view of certain T24 P&amp;L.  (T24 General Ledger views all P&amp;L entries as value-dating, ie all P&amp;L is reported against the day it was booked, regardless of when it was earned.)  P&amp;L input via MI.ENTRY can be value dated, allowing you to make P&amp;L adjustments which will be reflected in the MI reports for the period appropriate to the value date.  You only see value dated entries if you rebuild the MI database for the appropriate period. </p>
            <p>Unlike MI.AUTO.ENTRY, the P&amp;L entries input via this application do not have to balance.  However, if you are using the application to amend your view of T24 P&amp;L, you would probably want to check that these entries balance overall. </p>
            <p>Entries in this file may be reversed or amended, but you should bear in mind that these changes will only be applied to MI if the relevant database is rebuilt.  Entries will remain in this file until the MI retention period has passed, when they will be automatically deleted.  The retention period is set in the application MI.PARAMETER. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Value date for the entry. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The SWIFT Currency Code of the Account or transaction on which the Profit or Loss was earned.  (Not necessary if the originating Account or transaction was in local Currency.) </p>
            <p>Where the Entry is generated from P&amp;L Allocation, this field is copied from the originating P&amp;L Entry </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 3 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters  Currency Code, or null.  (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory if currency not local</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAL.MI.CATEG.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PALCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REAL.AMOUNT.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.MI.CATEG.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the run date on which MI takes as the date the P&amp;L of this entry was generated.  This date determines which database period the entry will be reported in. </p>
            <p>Where the entry is generated from P&amp;L Allocation, this date will be the same as the booking date of the original P&amp;L entry.  This is normally, but not necessarily the actual date at the time the original Entry was generated, e.g. if the previous day's business was still being processed after midnight, the actual date  changes, but the run date is still the previous day. </p>
            <p> Thus the reallocated P&amp;L will appear in MI with the same date as the original P&amp;L, even if P&amp;L allocation is run some time after the original P&amp;L was earned. </p>
            <p>The date on which the record was physically generated (ie the T24 date on which the reallocation was run) is stored for audit purposes in the field CREATED.ON. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Reference field can be used to store an external reference for the entry.  For instance, where the entry reflects an expense billed by another company, </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency Market for Entry </p>
            <p>Where the Entry is generated as a result of P&amp;L Allocation, this field is copied from the originating P&amp;L entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 Character, Currency Market code (Internal file, no user input) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of product the interest or commission has been earned on. </p>
            <p>For entries generated from P&amp;L allocation, it is derived from the product category of the originating P&amp;L entry.  Originating entries updating base  level types of Profit and Loss e.g. Purchase of Goods, have no product categories, and thus will leave this field blank. </p>
            <p> For interest and charges earned on Customers' Accounts  this field contains the Category code from the Account record.  For  Profit and Loss earned on other products, the Product Category is  entered in the originating transaction or generated by the originating  Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters Category code or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of Profit and Loss updated by this Entry. </p>
            <p>If the Entry is for a Product type Profit and Loss Category (e.g. Commission), then the Product Category code is also stored in this record, in the field of the same name. </p>
            <p>For Entries to base level Profit and Loss Categories (e.g. Purchase of Goods), then the Profit and Loss Category code needs no further breakdown by Product Category. </p>
            <p>Note: 1) Profit and Loss Category codes are in the range 50000 - 69999. 2) Where the entry is generated from P&amp;L reallocation, this field is derived from the value of the 'allocate from' or 'allocate to' category code on the reallocation record.  This need not be the same as the category of the originating entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 5 numeric characters Category Code.  (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REAL.AMOUNT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The T24 transaction code you wish to associate with this entry. </p>
            <p>The transaction code can be used to reference narrative etc. held on T24 via the TRANSACTION application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p>Must be a valid T24 transaction code Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p> A unique key to identify the Entry. </p>
            <p />
            <p> Represents the reference number which uniquely  identifies a particular contract. </p>
            <p> Every new deal must be automatically assigned a unique  contract number which will identify only that deal and no other.  The  system maintains a central indicator, on the Company record, which  determines whether new Contract numbers are to be automatically  generated by the system or whether it is to be input by the User. </p>
            <p> In the case of a Fiduciary Deposit, which automatically generates the  corresponding Fiduciary Placement, each of the deals will have separate  numbers.  The following is an example of how a Fiduciary Deposit and  its corresponding Fiduciary Placement would be numbered: </p>
            <p> MM 85 043 0 0123  =  Fiduciary Deposit  MM 85 043 9 0123  =  Fiduciary Placement </p>
            <p>Thus the second contract, which is system generated, is assigned a sequence number in the 90000 range to link it to its corresponding Fiduciary Deposit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>The key is a 10 digit number, prefixed with MI to represent Management Information, in the following format: MM YY DDD 99999 where: MI   = Management Information YY   = Current Year DDD  = Julian Day 99999 = Sequence Number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the MI.ENTRY.TYPE of the record which indicates the type of profit and loss entry being allocated or reallocated. The value in this field defaults to the value on the CATEGORY record for the PL.CATEGORY, or may be input seprately. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 alphanumeric characters. Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the MI.ENTRY.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the Override messages which the user agreed to during Input. </p>
            <p>During the validation stage of a Money Market contract, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly, for instance, that the interest payable account does not match the drawdown account. </p>
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the Override, the full text of the actual Override Message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field. Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p> Identifies the Customer on whose behalf the transaction  generating the Profit or Loss was performed, or who  owns the Account on which the Profit or Loss was  earned. </p>
            <p> Not used for transactions where there was no Customer,  e.g. cashing travellers' cheques for non customers of  the Bank. </p>
            <p>Where the entry was generated from P&amp;L reallocation, this is copied from the original P&amp;L entry, to record the Customer for whom the original transaction was performed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric characters Customer code or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRILL.ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify whether the MI..ENTRY record is a debit or a credit. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p> A multivalue field containing a variable number of lines of 34 characters.  Narrative can be reported as additional description of the Entry, alongside standard transaction and reference text. </p>
            <p>Where the entry has been generated from  P&amp;L reallocation, this field will contain the narrative from the original P&amp;L entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 34 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Internal file, no user input.) Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Department or account officer to which this Profit or Loss entry should be allocated. </p>
            <p>Where the entry has been generated from P&amp;L allocation, this will not always match the Account Officer on the originating P&amp;L entry. </p>
            <p>Reallocation is the process of reversing a portion of P&amp;L from the originating department, and allocating it to another.  Thus, the MI.AUTO.ENTRY will show: -For Debit entries, the Department/Account Officer from whom the P&amp;L is being taken.  This will match the originating entry -For Credit entries, the Department/Account Officer to whom the P&amp;L is being reallocated.  This will normally be different to the originating entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric characters Department Account Officer code. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to show Profit or Loss in foreign currency where appropriate.  For instance the Profit or loss may be earned on a Foreign Currency Account or a transaction in a foreign currency. </p>
            <p>AMOUNT.FCY contains the amount of the Entry in the currency specified in the CURRENCY field.  (it is not necessary in Entries where the originating Account or transaction was in local Currency.) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point (standard amount format, type AMT) signed, or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory if currency not local</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the Entry in local currency. </p>
            <p>(All Profit and Loss Entries are also expressed in Local Currency, even when they are the result of a foreign currency transaction, or interest and charges calculated on a foreign currency Account.) </p>
            <p>Where the Entry has been generated from P&amp;L Allocation, this field is calculated from the Local Currency amount of the original entry being reallocated, and the percentage set for reallocation in the MI.PL.ALLOCATION application. </p>
            <p>Where the NETTED field in this record is set to 'Y', the entry is a result of netting during P&amp;L Allocation.  This happens where : - netting has been requested in MI.PL.ALLOCATION, and - the Allocation process could otherwise produce several entries with similar characteristics. One Netted entry is created, with a Local currency amount equal to the sum of the individual entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-14 numeric characters plus decimal point (standard  amount format, type AMT), signed.  (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to hold the Exchange rate where the Entry is shown in foreign currency.  It contains the Rate which was used to convert the Foreign currency amount to the local equivalent at the time of the originating transaction. </p>
            <p>Where P&amp;L Allocation has generated the Entry, this rate will be taken from the rate on the original P&amp;L entry.  This ensures that the local and foreign currency amounts for both original and reallocated P&amp;L are all consistent. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric characters and decimal point, (standard Rate format, type R), or null. (Internal file, no user input.) Mandatory if currency not local</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

