<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.LINE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table defines the lines within an MI report database. </p>
            <p>Each record defines a single line on the file providing a narrative description and selection criteria that will be used to determine which T24 information is consolidated into this line. </p>
            <p>The id is the mi.report.type.id and the line number </p>
            <p>e.g. GMPR.0010 </p>
            <p>Lines should be allocated in ranges (see GROUP.LINE.FROM field on the MI.REPORT.TYPE table). For example the range of lines from 0001 to 0999 might be reserved for assets. This will enable structured reports to be easily produced. </p>
            <p>Allocate lines initally leaving gaps to enable new lines to be inserted at a later date. For example 0010, 0020, 0030. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>MI.SELECTION records that define the data to be included in this line. </p>
            <p>This is a multi-value set where the keys to MI.SELECTION records are held. Each source record will be compared to the MI.SELECTIONs specified here to see if it is to be selected for inclusion in this line. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on MI.SELECTION</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id of the mi.line record. e.g. </p>
            <p>GMPR0010 </p>
            <p>The first part must be alphameric and must be a valid report type as defined on MI.REPORT.TYPE. </p>
            <p>The second part must be numeric 4 digits. </p>
            <p>Line records should be specified in ranges as defined on the MI.REPORT.TYPE record to enable simple reporting laer. </p>
            <p>It is recommended that line gaps are left during the initial set up of lines to enable later insertion of new lines. e.g. </p>
            <p>GMPR0010  Sources - interest bearing GMPR0020  Sources - non-interest bearing </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>First part must consist of valid report type as specified on MI.REPORT.TYPE.</p>
            <p>Second part must consist of four numerics.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates how the selection records are to be processed when more than one selection is specified. </p>
            <p>If OR is specified then the source will be selected if it satisfies one or more of the selections. </p>
            <p>If AND is specified then the source will be selected if it satisfies all the selections. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
            <p>And or Or. Default is Or.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The priority sequence for this line record. </p>
            <p>9 = highest priority. Compare to this record first. 1 = lowest priority. Compare to this record last. </p>
            <p>Indicates to MI the sequence in line records are to be compared to source records to see of ths source is to be selected for this line. </p>
            <p>Input to this field should not usually be required because the MI application will make its own estimate based upon the complexity of the selection records. See the helptext for INT.SEL.PRIORITY for further details. </p>
            <p>Only allowed if values are to be allocated to only one line in the report (i.e. if unique.selection on the report type record is set to Y or blank). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Numeric 1-9. Default is 5.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Short description of this line. </p>
            <p>To be used for printing on reports and enquiries. </p>
            <p>Mutli-valued for multi-languages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum 30 characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUDGETED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Y indicates that budgets are to be held for this line. </p>
            <p>This will cause empty budgets to be automatically generated for this line when mi.budget.control is run. </p>
            <p>For example if budgets are to be held for line ABCD0010 'Commission earned' but not for line ABCD0800 'Current account balances' then only the former would have the BUDGETED field set to Y. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Yes or No. Default is Yes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of this line. </p>
            <p>This may be used later for printing on reports and enquiries. </p>
            <p>Multi-valued to enable input of different languages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum 50 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is maintained by the system. It contains the description of the line group into which this line falls. </p>
            <p>Line groups are defined on MI.REPORT.TYPE and break up the final repor structure into groups to enable subtotalling. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input allowed. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SEL.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Internal selection priority. </p>
            <p>This is a system generated field containing the full, internal selection priority for this record. </p>
            <p>When a database is specified as having unique.selection then each item of T24 data will be added into one and only one line, however it is possible that an item of data will match the selection criteria for more than one line. </p>
            <p>For example we have two lines - Current Accounts and Current Accounts for Banks. A current account for a bank could be placed in either line - it is both a current account and a banks current account. Obviously we want to choose the latter but how do we ensure that MI understands our intentions? </p>
            <p>MI offers a mechanism called Selection Priority. </p>
            <p>Firstly there is a field on the line description (mi.line) where we may input the lines priority. In the case of the above example, we could give the line Current Accounts for Banks a higher priority than Current Accounts. MI would then check the lines in priority sequence. Finding a match against Current Accounts for Banks it would allocate the item to this line and look no further. We have achieved a correct result. </p>
            <p>However allocating a manual selection priority to all lines would prove tedious. Consequently MI offers an automatic facility to default the selection priority based upon an analysis of how specific the definition of the selections are. Again in the above example, Current Accounts for Banks is a more specific selection than just Current Accounts and records would be compared to this first. The same result would have been achieved as when the priorities were allocated manually. </p>
            <p>MIs determines how specific a selection is by analysing the number of different operands and fields used in the selection. This process is described in more detail below. </p>
            <p>MI holds the sequence in which it will check lines in the field int.sel.priority on mi.line. This field consists of two parts: the selection.priority as input by the user and an analysis of the relative specificity of the selection parameters for the line. </p>
            <p>MI determines the relative priority of lines by analysing the mi.selection records that the mi.line record refers to. It examines three factors: </p>
            <p>- The number of different source fields used in the selection records - The number of different operands used on those fields - The relative priority of those operands (see the table below) </p>
            <p>For example if MI is presented with two lines with the following selections: </p>
            <p>Line 1 - PRODCAT EQ 1000 Line 2 - PRODCAT EQ 1000 AND CURRENCY EQ USD </p>
            <p>it will assign data to line 2 if it matches. Only if it does not match here will it check against line 1. </p>
            <p>MI holds its assessment of the relative priority of each line in the field internal selection priority on the mi.line record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

