<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.PL.ALLOCATION.2</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>MI.PL.ALLOCATION.2 ================== </p>
            <p>This application is similar to the MI.PL.ALLOCATION application in that the file contains records which are used by the Management Information module to reallocate profit and loss. </p>
            <p>However, additional features have been added to this application to allow for more complex allocation to be carried out if required, and the underlying way in which the selection is specified is different. </p>
            <p>SELECTION </p>
            <p>Each record on this file represents a 'RULE' against which various types of P &amp; L entry may be checked against. A list of the rules for each type of entry is held on the CATEGORY file and the MI.CATEG.GROUP file. </p>
            <p>The selection process for each rule is specified using the MI.SELECTION method (not just the Department / Account Officer of the incoming record) to allow  more powerful selections. </p>
            <p>BANDING </p>
            <p>The concept of banding has been introduced to this allocation process to provide further flexibility. Refer to field level helptext for details. </p>
            <p>NETTING </p>
            <p>Netting is also available in the same way as in the MI.PL.ALLOCATION application. </p>
            <p>When the allocation process is run, records on the CATEG.ENTRY file are read and MI.AUTO.ENTRY records are produced. </p>
            <p>The allocation process may be run during the end of day processing or on line. The on line processing is triggered via the MI.BUILD.DATABASE file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TO.ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If an MI.ENTRY.TYPE is required to be allocated on the 'to' record (ie the record which posts a credit for the percentage of the incoming allocation amount to the Department / Account Officer set in the field TO.DAO) then the value in this field is used in preference to any default found from either the CATEGORY file or the MI.CATEG.GROUP file. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION (field 2) to FROM.DAO (field13) form a related multi value group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the MI.ENTRY.TYPE table. Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether MI.AUTO.ENTRY records should be netted when they are created. If this flag is set to VALUE then entries which have the same : </p>
            <p>CATEGORY ACCOUNT.OFFICER PRODUCT.CATEGORY BOOKING.DATE VALUE.DATE CURRENCY </p>
            <p>Will be netted together if the account officer from which the entries were created are the same, e.g. takes into account the value date and booking date of the incoming records. </p>
            <p>When this flag is set to MONTHLY the value.date is set to the end of the month it had value in and the booki date will be set to the system date on which the allocation was run. This option provides for a higher level of netting and will result in fewer records. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION (field 2) to FROM.DAO (field13) form a related multi value group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Only Input of VALUE, MONTHLY or NONE will be excepted.</p>
            <p>Optional Input. Defaults to NONE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>The operand which applies to the MI.SELECTION records specified in the related field SELECTION is set here. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION to FROM.DAO form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must either be AND or OR. Defaults to AND.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If an MI.ENTRY.TYPE is required to be allocated on the 'from' record (ie the balancing record which posts a debit for a percentage of the incoming allocation amount to the Department / Account Officer on the incoming record OR as set in the field FROM.DAO) then the value in this field is used in preference to any default found from either the CATEGORY file or the MI.CATEG.GROUP file. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION (field 2) to FROM.DAO (field13) form a related multi value group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the MI.ENTRY.TYPE table. Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.DAO</field>
<desc>
            <p>By default the Department / Account Officer set on the 'from' record (ie the debit record) is that on the incoming source file. </p>
            <p>If there is a value present in this field it will be used in preference to the default value. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION (field 2) to FROM.DAO (field13) form a related multi value group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 4 numeric characters. Optional Input.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the percentage of the allocation amount (refer to the fields BAND.AMOUNT and BAND.PERCENT for details) to be credited to the Department / Account Officer specified in the field TO.DAO. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION to FROM.DAO form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>Fields TO.DAO to PERCENT form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to three numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.DAO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Department / Account Officer specified in this field will receive an amount from the entry to be allocated based on a percentage (set in the related field PERCENT) of the allocation amount (refer to the fields BAND.AMOUNT and BAND.PERCENT for details). </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION to FROM.DAO form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>Fields TO.DAO and PERCENT form a related subvalue set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 4 numeric characters. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to hold a description of the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 30 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the type of entry which is to be allocated. When the allocation process is run each multi value is tested in turn, from the top of the record to the bottom. Whenever a match is found the allocation from the entry is carried out according to the rest of the fields in the multi value group. </p>
            <p>Multiple selections for each multi value group are made possible by specifying MI.SELECTION records in the sub values. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION (field 2) to FROM.DAO (field 13) form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the MI.SELECTION table.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input except for the first sub value of the last multi value of the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.PL.ALLOC2.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The unique identifier for records on this key. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAND.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the allocation amount from the incoming record. </p>
            <p>This allocation amount is used to calculate the amounts from which the allocation to the Departments / Account Officers specified in the field TO.DAO is made. </p>
            <p>The specification of the allocation amount is set as a series of bands and a related percentage for each band. The final band (that is all of the P &amp; L entry not in the bands previously specified) may be specified using the keyword REST. </p>
            <p>The simplest method is to set the allocation amount to all of the amount on the incoming P &amp; L entry. This is set as ... </p>
            <p>     7.1.1 BAND.AMOUNT.  REST      8.1.1 BAND.PERCENT  100 </p>
            <p>... and is the default. </p>
            <p>Specifying bands. ================= </p>
            <p>If more complex banding is required then this is specified as a series of amounts, with a related percentage entered in the BAND.PERCENT field. </p>
            <p>In the followiung examples it is assumed that the local currency is US dollars. </p>
            <p>Example One. </p>
            <p>There may be a requirement that each Department / Account Officer keeps the first $100 dollars from any profit they earn, and after that keeps half this profit. This would be set as </p>
            <p>     7.1.1 BAND.AMOUNT. 100.00      8.1.1 BAND.PERCENT 0      7.1.2 BAND.AMOUNT. REST      8.1.2 BAND.PERCENT 50 </p>
            <p>Example Two </p>
            <p>The Department / Account Officer has to allocate all of the first $100, half of the next $1,000 but then keeps the remainder. </p>
            <p>     7.1.1 BAND.AMOUNT. 100.00      8.1.1 BAND.PERCENT 100      7.1.2 BAND.AMOUNT. 1,000.00      8.1.2 BAND.PERCENT 50 </p>
            <p>In this example, as there is no REST keyword, only the first $1100 of the incoming amount is re allocated. </p>
            <p>If the REST keyword is required it must be in the last sub value of the group, but it is not mandatory. </p>
            <p>This field defaults to a value of REST if it is the last sub value within a multi value group. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION (field 2) to FROM.DAO (field13) form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>Fields BAND.AMOUNT and BAND.PERCENT form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 19 numeric characters or 'REST' Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAND.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used in conjuction with the field BAND.AMOUNT to specify the allocation amount from the incoming P &amp; L entry. See the helptext for the field BAND.AMOUNT for further details. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION to FROM.DAO form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>Fields BAND.AMOUNT and BAND.PERCENT form a related sub value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 rate field, zero also allowed.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input, defaults to 100.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEG.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the category code which will be on the MI.AUTO.ENTRY record generated for the department / account officer specified in the key of this record as the balancing entry to one created for the department account officer specified in the TO.DAO field. </p>
            <p>If this field is left blank then the CATEGORY of the incoming entry will be used as a default at run time. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION (field 2) to FROM.DAO (field13) form a related multi value group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 Numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the CATEGORY file in the range 50000 - 69999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEG.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the category code which will be on the MI.AUTO.ENTRY record generated for the department / account officer specified in the related TO.DAO field. </p>
            <p>If this field is left blank then the CATEGORY of the incoming entry will be used as a default at run time. </p>
            <p>Fields SELECTION (field 2) to FROM.DAO (field13) form a related multi value group. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 Numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record on the CATEGORY file in the range 50000 to 69999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

