<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.SELECTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used to define categories of recrds for use whenever records are to be selected throughout the MI application. </p>
            <p>This table is referenced whenever records are being selected for inclusion in databases (MI.DB.DEFINITION), lines (MI.LINE), or columns (MI.COLUMN). </p>
            <p>An typical MI.SELECTION record might be 'LCYMORTGAGES' which would contain the definition of mortgages in local currency. Whenever local currency mortgages need to be specifically selected throughout the MI system then this record will be referenced. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The source field to be used in this selection. </p>
            <p>This field may contain the key of another MI.SELECTION record enabling selections to be grouped together. </p>
            <p>If it does not contain the key of another MI.SELECTION record then it contains the name of a field on the source file. If so then it is linked with operand and criteria into a multi-value group. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>OR or AND. </p>
            <p>Specifies how the various selections on this record are to processed as a group. </p>
            <p>If OR is specified then any source must satisfy at least one of the selections to be selected. </p>
            <p>If AND is specified then a source has to satisfy all the selections to be selected. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>OR or AND</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRITERIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>The values that the selection field is to be compared to. </p>
            <p>More than one value can be specified for example if a range is being specified. </p>
            <p>Multiple criteria can also be used to specify an OR relationship. For example EQ 1000 1050 1080 OR will select the record if the selection field equals one of the three values. </p>
            <p>No input to this field will be treated as null </p>
            <p>Forms part of a multi-value group with SELECTION and OPERAND. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Maximum 30 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.SEL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of the mi.selection record. </p>
            <p>Whilst this may be any short description, care should be taken to establish a method of constructing names that is meaningfull. </p>
            <p>Example:  MORTGAGESLCY indicating local currency mortgages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No spaces</p>
            <p>Maximum 30 characters.</p>
            <p>Must be uppercase.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>How the selection field is to be compared to the criteria. </p>
            <p>All the usual T24 operands such as EQ, LT, RG, etc. are valid. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid operand:  EQ  equal NE  not equal LT  less than LE  less than or equal GT  greater than GE  greater than or equal RG  range NR  not in range</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

