<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.STAT.DEFINITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to define a process to analyse any give T24 file. </p>
            <p>The file to be analysed and the records to be analysed are defined on this record, the selection may be defined using the MI.SELECTION mechanism, by specifying a UniVerse command or by specifying a routine. </p>
            <p>The main function of this file is to assign an MI.STAT.TYPE, which has costing information attached to it, to each record which is being processed on the file. Again, the MI.SELECTION mechanism is used to specify the MI.STAT.TYPES. </p>
            <p>The last date on which the MI.BUILD.STAT process for this MI.STAT.DEFINITION was run is also held on this field. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.STAT.DEF.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the MI.STAT.DEFINITION record is held here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to nine alphanumreic characters</p>
            <p>Input must not be "ALL"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.CMD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to reduce the number of records which will be presented for processing. There are two ways in which this field may be used; </p>
            <p>1)   A routine may be specified by setting the first character to "@".      At run time, when a MI.BUILD.STAT record containing this record key      is verified, the routine is called with one argument. This      argument is expected to contain a list of record keys upon return. </p>
            <p>2)   A UniVerse select command may be defined. No validation is made      upon this type input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p>If a routine is specified, the routine must be catalogued.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STAT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The MI.STAT.TYPE which will be assigned to the record being processed when the record matches the selections defined in the associated SELECTION field is defined here. </p>
            <p>This MI.STAT.TYPE will be used to populate the MI.STAT record with information such as the cost of the oustanding item, the profit centres to debit / credit the cost and the transaction and P &amp; L category to use. </p>
            <p>Fields STAT.TYPE to OPERAND form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid MI.STAT.TYPE record.</p>
            <p>Mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the relationship between the selection parameters if there is more than one, as defined in the associated SELECTION fields. </p>
            <p>AND - the record is selected if it fulfils ALL the selection criteria </p>
            <p>OR - the record is selected if it fulfils ANY of the selection criteria </p>
            <p>Fields STAT.TYPE to OPERAND form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be either AND or OR.</p>
            <p>Defaults to AND</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>MI.SELECTION records that contain the selection for the associted STAT.TYPE. </p>
            <p>Source records that match the selections will be assigned the associated STAT.TYPE. Only one STAT.TYPE will be assigned to each source record, being the first one matched. </p>
            <p>If no selection is defined, all source records match the selection. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the MI.SELECTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The description of the record is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The file on which the process will run is defined in this field. </p>
            <p>Input into this field should specify the name of the T24 file on which the analysis process will run, e.g. ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.SELECTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as another method of reducing the number of records presented to the record processing. Each record must match the MI.SELECTION specified here before it is processed. If no match is made, the record is not processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the MI.SELECTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.RUN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the analysis process was run using this process definition is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

