<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>MI.STAT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to hold the MI statistic entries generated by the MI.BUILD.STAT application, using the definitions set on the file MI.STAT.DEFINITION, and refer to an outstanding item which has had a cost associated to it. </p>
            <p>The records on this file are pulled into the MI databases via the MI.AUTO.ENTRY application. Records are produced on MI.AUTO.ENTRY via the MI.AUTO.MAPPING and associated processes. </p>
            <p>Records on this file are cross referenced on the file MI.STAT.XREF. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The profity and loss category, taken from the MI.STAT.TYPE record, is held in this field and should be mapped to the PL.CATEGORY field in the MI.AUTO.MAPPING application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the PRODUCT.CATEGORY of the record which produced this MI.STAT record, where applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Where present, must be the key to a valid record on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The credit transaction code assigned to the MI.STAT.TYPE is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.CNTR.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The profit centre which will be credited the UNIT.COST is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be they key to a valid record on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNIT.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>The evaluated cost assigned to the MI.STAT.TYPE via the MI.UNIT.COST mechanism is held in this field, in local currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 amount field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the record, on the file specified in FILE.NAME, which produced this MI.STAT record is held in this field. </p>
            <p>In conjunction with the FILE.NAME field it is possible to specify on the standard selection record for this application a series of field joins which may be referenced in the MI.AUTO.MAPPING application to provide additional information to the MI.AUTO.ENTRYs which will be generated. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.STAT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The MI.STAT.TYPE which has been assigned to this record is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the MI.STAT.TYPE file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.CNTR.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The profit centre which will be debited the UNIT.COST is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be they key to a valid record on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The debit transaction code assigned to the MI.STAT.TYPE is held in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid record on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the CUSTOMER.NO of the record which produced this MI.STAT record, where applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Where present, must be the key to a valid record on the CUSTOMER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.CREATED</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the record was created is held in this field. It is this field which is used as the date on which the rebuild and purging process es are based. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The file on which the process which produced this record was run is held in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.STAT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>A unique key by which the MI.STAT record may be identified. It is generated by the system, based on the date and time (in hundredths of a second) at which the transaction is input and a sequence number. </p>
            <p>The key is made up as follows: (a)        4 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st            December 1967. </p>
            <p>(b)        Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers            and (usually) 2 decimals.  If the time is an exact number            of seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted. </p>
            <p>(c)        Sequence number.            If a transaction generates several Entries, all the Entries            have parts (a) and (b) the same and are distinguished            from each other by their Sequence numbers. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>13 numeric characters or 16 characters consisting of 15 numeric characters with a decimal point after the 9th. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

