<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MI</product>
<table>REBUILD.BAL.MVMT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file is used to control the building of the BALANCE.MOVEMENT file. </p>
            <p>This file provides the facility for several types of build which may be run on line or during the batch. </p>
            <p>Population </p>
            <p>This job processes the movements across account or contracts and also populates the 'static' information such as customer number and currency of the account or contract. </p>
            <p>Calculation </p>
            <p>The calculation of the average balances are is carried out by this job, and relies on the information provided by the population job to create accurate average balances. Although this job will run without the population job being run first, the information will not be as accurate as the latest movements will not be included on the average balances. </p>
            <p>Refinancing </p>
            <p>The refinancing rates are extracted by this job and applies the settings on the MI.PARAMETER record to determine which rate is applicable and any margins applicable to that rate. </p>
            <p>Rebuilding </p>
            <p>It is possible to modify the dates used by the main jobs and hence perform rebuilds. The calculation date and population date will be set to the same date by the rebuild period, but the refinancing date may be set to a different date. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.ONLY.CONT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When this field is set to Y the RATE.CHANGE.DATE field on the BAL.MVMT.BVAL file will be updated for all contracts according to the first time the contract moved after the date specified in the fieLd RATE.ONLY.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must either be Y or N</p>
            <p>Optional Input. Null defaults to N.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.11</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.CONTRACTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as part of the rebuild processing. If this field is set to Y then upon verification the calculation, population and the refinancing dates for CONTRACTS only will be reset to the earliest movement, or if a rebuild date is present, the earliest movement after that rebuild.date. </p>
            <p>Performing this action will not run the calculation, population and refinancing rate extraction jobs, but those jobs may be included on the same REBUILD.BAL.MVMT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be either Y or N.</p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.12</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.ONLY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the refinancing is required to be set independently from the main processing date, this field should be used to contain the date from which the rebuild of the refinancing rate extraction date should be run from. </p>
            <p>This field should be used in conjumction with the fields RATE.ONLY.CONT and RATE.ONLY.ACCT to extract the refinancing rate date for contracts and accounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.ONLY.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When this field is set to Y the RATE.CHANGE.DATE field on the BAL.MVMT.BVAL file will be updated for all accounts according to the first time the account moved after the date specified in the field RATE.ONLY.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must either be Y or N</p>
            <p>Optional Input. Null defaults to N.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the BALANCE.MOVEMENT file is required to be rebuilt then this field should hold the date from which the rebuild is to take place. </p>
            <p>This field is used in conjunction with the REBUILD.ACCOUNTS and REBUILD.CONTRACTS fields which calls the rebuild job and modifies the records on the BA.MVMT.BVAL file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.ACCOUNTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as part of the rebuild processing. If this field is set to Y then upon verification the calculation, population and the refinancing dates for ACCOUNTS only will be reset to the earliest movement, or if a rebuild date is present, the earliest movement after that rebuild.date. </p>
            <p>Performing this action will not run the calculation, population and refinancing rate extraction jobs, but those jobs may be included on the same REBUILD.BAL.MVMT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be either Y or N.</p>
            <p>Optional Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used as the key to the REBUILD.BAL.MVMT file and as such to uniquely identify the records on the file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATE.AVG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to trigger the calculation of average balances on the BALANCE.MOVMENT file. </p>
            <p>Once this job is completed for each account or contract the CALC.AVG.FROM field on the corresponding BAL.MVMT.BVAL record will be set to  yesterdays date - indicating that the account or contract has had the average calculated on it up to and including that date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be Y or N.</p>
            <p>Optional Input. Null defualts to N.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A language related description of the rebuild record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 15 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXTRACT.REFIN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to indicate whether or not the extraction of refinancing rates is required. If this flag is set to Y then the refinancing rates will be extracted according to the table set up on the MI.PARAMETER record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be Y or N.</p>
            <p>If this field is left blank then the refinance rate extraction job will ot be run.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Inputter </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Record status </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POPULATE.BAL.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to trigger the population job. When a record is verified with this field containing a 'Y' any movements which have occurred since the last population will be reflected on the BALANCE.MOVEMENT file. </p>
            <p>When this job has been run the field BACK.VAL.DATE on the BAL.MVMT.BVAL file will be set to null, indicating that the account or contract is up to date and does not need to be processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be either Y or N.</p>
            <p>Optional Input. If left blank then this field defaults to N at run time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

