<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.AUTO.TRANSLATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PREFIX</field>
<desc>
            <p>The prefix is the initial part of the DE.TRANSLATION record key that this application will create. Used by delivery by identifying this part of the id means that the user can specify a short meaningful prefix.</p>
            <p>Example</p>
            <p>The user wants to have both a short and long description of the TRANSACTION records which have a numeric key.  The prefix can be set to TXNS/ and TXNL/ and will have the appropriate record id added resulting in records like TXNS/123 and TXNL/123.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Prefix should not include the / separator - i.e. enter just TXNL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This option is to specify if NEW records only are to be created, or whether ALL records should be done - both new and existing,</p>
            <p>If the number of records is very large and you only wish to add a few new ones then NEW should be chosen, this will leave the existing records unchanged.</p>
            <p>If several of the existing underlying record descriptions have changed you will need to select ALL, this will create new records where required and update ALL the existing records. It does this by overwriting them all regardless of whether they have changed or not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Permiited values of ALL or NEW</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FQY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future expansion</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the file that will be read when creating DE.TRANSLATION records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid application file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEPERATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The seperator used in building the key to the DE.TRANSLATION record that will be created or updated.</p>
            <p>If the user wants to create records such as TXNL/1000 then TXNL is the prefix chosen and entered in the PREFIX field, / as the seperator defined here and 1000 is the id of the TRANSACTION file. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>API</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future expansion</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIMITER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used in building the key to the DE.TRANSLATION record and is similar to the field SEPERATOR. System will not accept if both DELIMITER and SEPERATOR are assigned.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A standard detail field that can be used to specify what this particular record is set-up for and the fields used to create the resultant DE.TRANSLATION records.</p>
            <p>Example</p>
            <p>This record creates id's such as CATSHRT/1000 using the CATEGORY file and the short description.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional text field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the field from where this utility will extract the description for the DE.TRANSLATION record. It can be a short or long description but care should be taken when using other field types as the internal values will be used. By this it is possible to use a date field by mistake and the data extracted would be in the form YYYYMMDD not 21 JULY 2002.</p>
            <p>Allowing the user to select the field is for maximum flexibility but the system will not prevent the user from entering data which is nonsensical.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Field must exist on STANDARD.SELECTION of file detailed in FILE.NAME       field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.RUN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This date field is provided for future expansion but can be entered for information purposes at present.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.AUTO.TRANS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the Id of the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

