<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.ADDRESS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>DE.ADDRESS File contains the names and address of a bank's customers and also of each company within the banking organisation.</p>
            <p>   The basic postal address of each Customer (Delivery Address ID = Company.C-Customer.PRINT.1) is automatically updated when the address is changed through Customer Maintenance.  This record on the Address file cannot be amended (except for the HOLD.OUPUT field), and its CURR.NO will always be 1.</p>
            <p>   DE.ADDRESS is used for inputting all addresses except 'PRINT.1', i.e. SWIFT addresses, Telex addresses and special postal addresses.</p>
            <p>   In a printed message all Customer names are from the PRINT.1 address except when the field specified is TO.ADDRESS from the Message Header. The Delivery Address record used for TO.ADDRESS is dependent upon the DE.PRODUCT file.</p>
            <p>   To input or update Customer addresses (other than PRINT.1) the user must sign on to the Company holding that Customer record.  For example, if Companies 'A' and 'B' share a Customer file located in Company 'A', then Customers Delivery Addresses can only be amended by signing on to Company 'A', even though Company 'B' uses the same Customer file.</p>
            <p>   In order to hold printed output for an account/customer the HOLD.OUTPUT field must be set.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INSTITUTION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of institution.</p>
            <p>   Not used at present.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-8 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOWN.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Customer's or Company's town and country.</p>
            <p>   Multilanguage field. Where SWIFT is used the first language must only allow standard SWIFT character validation. If SWIFT is not used the languages can be configured via ASCII.VALUES and ASCII.VAL.TABLES to allow the required range of characters.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-35 type S (SWIFT) characters. (Mandatory input for print addresses. Not allowed for TELEX or SWIFT addresses.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLACKOUT.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the start time of blackout period represented in terms of Server time.</p>
            <p>As an example, </p>
            <p>Let us say, Customer in Central America is not interested in receiving SMS messages during lunch time between 1:00 p.m and 2:00 p.m.</p>
            <p>So, in DE.CUSTOMER.PREFERENCES, following details will be provided.</p>
            <p>BLACKOUT.START  13:00</p>
            <p>BLACKOUT.END  14:00</p>
            <p>OFFSET        -06:00</p>
            <p />
            <p>Let us say, he is a customer of a bank in Paris and T24 delivery services are run here.</p>
            <p>So, in DE.PARM, OFFSET detail will be provided as  +01:00 </p>
            <p>Now, in DE.ADDRESS, when representing the blackout start time with respect to the Server time, </p>
            <p>Start time will be  20:00 and</p>
            <p>End time will be 21:00, a total of 7 hrs gap between server time and customer time.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1)Time should be entered in HH:MM format (24 hour format).</p>
            <p>    HH – denoting hours and MM -  denoting minutes</p>
            <p>   2) Applicable to SMS carrier only.Valid only for SMS carrier</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTRUCTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not yet implemented.  The ID of a special instructions record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-6 numeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POST.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Customer's or Company's postal address code.</p>
            <p>   Multilanguage field. Where SWIFT is used the first language must only allow standard SWIFT character validation. If SWIFT is not used the first language can be configured via ASCII.VALUES and ASCII.VAL.TABLES to allow the required range of characters, and multiple language definitions will not be required.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input for print addresses. Not allowed for TELEX or SWIFT addresses.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EMAIL.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>    This field can contain the first email id of the customer. This client contact data is </p>
            <p>      required by CRM. This field has been added in correspondence to the customer </p>
            <p>      template.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>      Maximum of 50 characters allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the second line of a Customer's or Company's name.</p>
            <p>   Multilanguage field. Where SWIFT is used the first language must only allow standard SWIFT character validation. If SWIFT is not used the languages can be configured via ASCII.VALUES and ASCII.VAL.TABLES to allow the required range of characters.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-35 type S (SWIFT) characters. (Optional input for print addresses. Not allowed for TELEX or SWIFT addresses.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SMS.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>          This field can contain the first SMS(text) number of the customer. This client contact data is </p>
            <p>            required by CRM. This field has been added in correspondence to the customer </p>
            <p>            template.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>            Maximum of 16 characters allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the country of a Customer's or Company's address.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-35 type S (SWIFT) characters.  Optional input for print addresses.  Not allowed for TELEX or SWIFT addresses.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HOLD.OUTPUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not the printed ouput is to be held.</p>
            <p>   This field only allows input for PRINT addresses. If this field is set to 'Y' then all output sent to the address will be held. If the output is classed as customer output then it will be held on the F.CUSTOMER.HOLD file as opposed to the &amp;HOLD&amp; file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Y or NO.  Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the code of a country where the delivery address is.  This field is not used at present.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-2 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input) If the INSTALL PARAMETER on the DE.PARM file is 'R' (resident), then the COUNTRY CODE must be an ID on the COUNTRY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the name of a Customer or Company abbreviated to 35 characters.</p>
            <p>   Multilanguage field. Where SWIFT is used the first language must only allow standard SWIFT character validation. If SWIFT is not used the languages can be configured via ASCII.VALUES and ASCII.VAL.TABLES to allow the required range of characters.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   3-35 type S (SWIFT) characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Company or Customer, carrier and address version number whose address is held in this record.</p>
            <p>   When the ID contains a Customer number the appropriate Customer company code is placed before it when building the key of this file.</p>
            <p>   Example:</p>
            <p>   If the input ID is C-405000.PRINT.3 (The 3rd delivery print address for Customer 405000.) and the Customer company is GB-003-2500, then it will go on file as GB0032500.C-405000.PRINT.3</p>
            <p>   If the INSTALL PARAMETER field on DE.PARM is 'R' (Resident) then:</p>
            <p>   a) Customer files will be checked to validate Customer numbers. b) Mnemonics can be entered in place of Customer numbers. c) The Company mnemonic can be used in place of the Company Code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   a)   Code or Mnemonic of the sign-on Company, which defaults for a      Customer address. b)   '.' c)   'C-' then a Customer number. (Required for a Customer address.) d)   '.' e)   The carrier, e.g. PRINT, SWIFT, TELEX (Mandatory input.) f)   '.' g)   2 numeric digits. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>   The carrier must be an address carrier, i.e. the carrier must reference a carrier on the DE.CARRIER file in which the carrier address is the same as the id.  e.g. You may want to send two types of Telex messages, one using SWIFT format and one using free format messages.  However, you would not want to set up two sets of telex addresses.  Therefore, one type of Telex message would be defined on the carrier file as Telex, with a carrier address of Telex, formatting module of SWIFT and carrier module of Telex.  The free format messages would be defined on the carrier file as a carrier of Telexp, carrier address of Telex (so that they use Telex addresses on DE.ADDRESS), formatting module of Telexp and carrier module of Telex.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the first line of a Customer's or Company's full name.</p>
            <p>   Multilanguage field. Where SWIFT is used the first language must only allow standard SWIFT character validation. If SWIFT is not used the languages can be configured via ASCII.VALUES and ASCII.VAL.TABLES to allow the required range of characters.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-35 type S (SWIFT) characters. (Mandatory input for print addresses. Not allowed for TELEX or SWIFT addresses.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDR.LOCATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ANSWERBACK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Customer's (or Company's) acknowledgment when called up to receive a TELEX message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-20 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>   Mandatory input for TELEX addresses.</p>
            <p>   Not allowed for SWIFT, PRINT or SIC addresses</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHENTICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLACKOUT.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the End time of blackout period represented in terms of Server time.</p>
            <p>As an example, </p>
            <p>Let us say, Customer in Central America is not interested in receiving SMS messages during lunch time between 1:00 p.m and 2:00 p.m.</p>
            <p>So, in DE.CUSTOMER.PREFERENCES, following details will be provided.</p>
            <p>BLACKOUT.START  13:00</p>
            <p>BLACKOUT.END  14:00</p>
            <p>OFFSET        -06:00</p>
            <p />
            <p>Let us say, he is a customer of a bank in Paris and T24 delivery services are run here.</p>
            <p>So, in DE.PARM, OFFSET detail will be provided as  +01:00 </p>
            <p>Now, in DE.ADDRESS, when representing the blackout start time with respect to the Server time, </p>
            <p>Start time will be  20:00 and</p>
            <p>End time will be 21:00, a total of 7 hrs gap between server time and customer time.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1)Time should be entered in HH:MM format (24 hour format).</p>
            <p>    HH – denoting hours and MM -  denoting minutes</p>
            <p>   2) Applicable to SMS carrier only.Valid only for SMS carrier</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPLY.TO.ADR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the mail address which the customer can use to communicate to the bank incase there is a problem.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Maximum of 50 characters allowed</p>
            <p>   Should contain a valid email address format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PHONE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>    This field can contain the first phone number of the customer. This client contact data is </p>
            <p>      required by CRM. This field has been added in correspondence to the customer </p>
            <p>      template.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>      Maximum of 16 characters allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STREET.ADDR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Customer's or Company's street address.</p>
            <p>   Multilanguage field. Where SWIFT is used the first language must only allow standard SWIFT character validation. If SWIFT is not used the languages can be configured via ASCII.VALUES and ASCII.VAL.TABLES to allow the required range of characters.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   1-35 type S (SWIFT) characters. (Not allowed for TELEX or SWIFT addresses.)</p>
            <p>   For PRINT addresses: Non Mandatory, if the field STREET.NON.MANDAT = 'Y' in   the CUSTOMER.DEFAULT record whose ID is equal to the value of the Customer's   SECTOR field; otherwise Mandatory.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Customer number to whom Secure Message is to be sent.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Valid Customer number</p>
            <p>   Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies either a Customer's SWIFT address, or TELEX number, as appropriate to the record ID.</p>
            <p>   The format for a SWIFT address is as follows:            bbbbcclltrrr where:</p>
            <p>   bbbb is the bank code (must be alpha).            cc   is the country code.  If the INSTALL PARAMETER                 field on DE.PARM is 'R' (resident), the country                 code must exist on the country file; otherwise it                 must be alpha.            ll   is the location code and must be in the range A-Z                 or 2-9.            t    is the terminal code (only allowed on "to                 addresses", therefore if the address is for a                 company code).  Must be in the range A-Z or 2-9.            rrr  is the branch code and is optional.  If entered it                 must be alphanumeric. If VALIDATE.BIC in DE.BIC.PRAMETER is Yes then, DELIVERY ADDRESS must be a valid entry on DE.BIC file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1-18 type numeric characters, for TELEX. (Embedded spaces allowed.) 8 or 11 type S (SWIFT) characters, for SWIFT if the address is for a customer number or 9 or 12 type S (SWIFT) characters for SWIFT if the address is for a company code (Embedded spaces not allowed.) (Mandatory input for SWIFT or TELEX addresses, not allowed for print addresses.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERFACE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Bank identifier in the front end software.</p>
            <p>   This field is used with STACHEM front-end software.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   0 - 35 alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>HOLD.MAIL.START</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>HOLD.MAIL.END</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>HOLD.MAIL.OPT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
