<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.BIC.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ORIGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the record. (There is only one record on Parameter.) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>ID must be System </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAPPING.API</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of T24 subroutine to call as an alternative means of mapping each BIC+ directory record into DE.BIC.</p>
            <p>This routine gets triggered when verifying DE.BIC.LOAD.Each data record from the BIC file and the field separator used will be passed in common variables LOCAL1 and LOCAL2 to this mapping routine</p>
            <p>The routine should handle the mapping and form the actual DE.BIC record. The Mapped DE.BIC record and the ID should be passed back in the same common variables LOCAL1 and LOCAL2</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALIDATE.BIC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This Optional field determines whether the BIC code is to be validated against the BIC codes (Swift Address) available in DE.BIC Application.</p>
            <p>BIC code can be entered in some T24 application either as BIC code (like in NETTING.AGREEMENT) or prefixed with SW- (like in FUNDS.TRANSFER.).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>To raise error message as per above on input of BIC code in Applications, records in DE.BIC application is checked as follows</p>
            <p>When BIC is entered as 11 characters (Bank, Country, Location &amp; Branch), then exact match record checked.</p>
            <p>When BIC is entered as 8 Characters</p>
            <p />
            <p>This functionality is available in following applications: FUNDS.TRANSFER, STANDING.ORDER, AGENCY, DRAWINGS, NETTING.AGREEMENT, DE.ADDRESS,AC.EXPECTED.RECS, EB.QUERIES.ANSWERS, EB.FREE.MESSAGE,DE.MT101.REQUEST</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input  Yes or No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALIDATE.SAK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>When this field is set to YES,  if Swift codes are used in the fields Receiver Bank &amp; Collrem Bank in FUNDS.TRANSFER  application and</p>
            <p />
            <p>R</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input field</p>
            <p>Allowed values YES &amp; Null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

