<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.CARRIER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file contains details of all the carriers available in Delivery.  To enable a carrier, it must be specified on the Delivery Parameter file, DE.PARM. </p>
            <p>The id of this file is the name of the carrier, as used in DE.PRODUCT. each record contains the address type to be used for the carrier (i.e when accessing DE.ADDRESS), the formatting rules (DE.FORMAT.carrier) and the carrier module (e.g. DE.O.CC.SWIFT).  If the carrier module is GENERIC, i.e. the messages are handled by the generic program DE.CC.GENERIC, interface must be specified.  The interface must reference a record on DE.INTERFACE, which contains details of the protocol for all generic interfaces (non-generic interface details are stored on the parameter file, DE.PARM). </p>
            <p>When the record is authorised, formatting and carrier files are created if they do not already exist. These files are F.DE.O.MSG.format-module and F.DE.O.PRI.format-module for the formatting files and F.DE.O.MSG.interface and F.DE.I.MSG.interface for the interface files. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>IN.FORMAT.MODULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the inward formatting module to be used.  The rules describing the formatting of the messages should therefore exist on the file, DE.FORMAT.format-module, e.g. DE.FORMAT.SWIFT.  The formatting of these messages is done by the program DE.I.FORMAT.format-module.MESSAGE, e.g. DE.I.FORMAT.SWIFT.MESSAGE.  Therefore, this program should exist. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-8 type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>The formatting program, DE.I.FORMAT.format-module.MESSAGE, must exist, e.g. DE.I.FORMAT.SWIFT.MESSAGE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORMAT.MODULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the formatting module to be used.  The rules describing the formatting of the messages should therefore exist on the file, DE.FORMAT.format-module, e.g. DE.FORMAT.SWIFT.  The formatting of these messages is done by the program DE.O.FORMAT.format-module.MESSAGE, e.g. DE.O.FORMAT.SWIFT.MESSAGE.  Therefore, this program should exist. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-8 type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>The program, DE.FORMAT.format-module, must exist (e.g. DE.FORMAT.SWIFT)</p>
            <p>The formatting program, DE.O.FORMAT.format-module.MESSAGE, must exist, e.g. DE.O.FORMAT.SWIFT.MESSAGE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.BYTE.LEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>It can hold a maximum of 7 numeric digits.</p>
            <p>Used to specify the maximum number of bytes that an incoming message can possess.</p>
            <p>If this field is left null, then the incoming message will be treated as a SWIFT message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERFACE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the interface to be used.  This is only used when messages are processed using the generic interface (i.e. when carrier-module is "GENERIC"). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-20 type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>This field cannot be input if the field CARRIER.MODULE is not "GENERIC"</p>
            <p>This field must be entered if CARRIER.MODULE is "GENERIC"</p>
            <p>If entered, it must reference a record on DE.INTERFACE</p>
            <p>If entered, cannot be the same of FORMAT.MODULE (except for the existing interfaces of "PRINT" and "SIC")</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of address to be used for this carrier. </p>
            <p>e.g. A record may be specified on DE.CARRIER with an id of TELEXF. Messages may be formatted using a format module of TLXF (DE.FORMAT.TLXF) but may use TELEX addresses.  Therefore, when the address file is accessed for addresses, it will done using a key of C-customer.TELEX.address-no (e.g. C-100001.TELEX.1) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-8 type "A" characters</p>
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>If entered, must either be the same as carrier (i.e. the id of the current record) or must reference another record on this file.</p>
            <p>If null, defaults to the id of the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The name of the carrier.  This is the carrier as used in DE.PRODUCT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-8 alphanumeric (type "A") characters</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARRIER.MODULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the carrier module.  For most of the existing modules this will be the same as the formatting module; for new interfaces it will be GENERIC.  If GENERIC is specified, messages will processed by DE.CC.GENERIC.  This program handles all the updates of the delivery files and outputs the message to F.DE.O.MSG.interface (where interface is the interface field on DE.CARRIER), where it will be processed by DE.O.CC.interface. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-8 type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>Default "GENERIC"</p>
            <p>If the carrier module is not "GENERIC", a program must exist, DE.O.CC.carrier-module, e.g. DE.O.CC.SWIFT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Description of the carrier </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-35 Type "A" (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p>Multivalue field</p>
            <p>Multi-language field</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

