<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.HOLD.INTERFACE.MSG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                 DE.HOLD.INTERFACE.MSG                  ===================== </p>
            <p>This application is designed to maintain necessary information for delivery messages holding purpose.  The ID of each record describes the conditions which make the messages to be retained inside the destination front-end software. </p>
            <p>It is compound as follows : </p>
            <p>application name.message type.application format.message format </p>
            <p>The application name may be replaced by 'ALL' when the condition applies to all applications. The second, third, and fourth parts of the identifier are optional (when absent, it means all).  A priority order is followed to determine what condition must be applied to a message : the complete ID is searched first, then an ID with only the 3 first parts, then the 2, then the first (application). </p>
            <p>If nothing is found, a second search is done in the same way after having replaced the application name by 'ALL'. The first record found is taken and the search stops. The department code of this record will be transmitted in the external header of the message before it is sent to the front-end. If the department code is non-null, the front-end software will print the message in the required department and hold it until an action is performed. </p>
            <p>If no record is found, no holding is to be performed, so a null department code will be given. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the origin application, the message type, the application format, and the message format to which this record applies. </p>
            <p>See former sheet for the filling rules. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-20 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  The four possible parts of this field are separated with dots. Ending dots may be forgotten.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERFACE.DEPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Code of the department that is to verify that kind of messages, and for which a print will be done by the front-end software. </p>
            <p>The department codification may be completely specific to the front-end users, so no validation will be done on this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>0-4 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input. Default value is 0000).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

