<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.INPUT.TESTKEY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The program allows the entry of a testkey to a telex message or a batch of telex messages. </p>
            <p>On entering this application the messages currently awaiting testkeys are displayed.  A message can be selected by entering the line number.  The following functions are available: </p>
            <p>a) 'I' - Input testkey </p>
            <p>   This function will display the telex message on the screen and allow    the input of a testkey.  The message can be paged forward or backwards    in the normal way.  For a batch message, however, a single page summary    of the messages in the batch is displayed.  When a testkey is input the    screen display returns to the list of messages with the message marked    as input.  The input function will not be allowed for a message which    has already had a testkey input and authorised.  If a testkey has    already been input, but not yet authorised, a warning message will be    displayed.  The previous testkey will be overwritten with a new entry    if the user proceeds. </p>
            <p>b) 'A' - Authorise testkey </p>
            <p>   This function will display the message on the screen (which may be    paged through in the normal way).  For a batch, however, a single    page summary of the message in the batch is displayed.  The testkey    must be re-entered and if it matches the previously input testkey the    screen display will return to the list of messages with the message    marked as authorised. </p>
            <p>   The authorised function will not be allowed for a message without a    testkey already input, nor will it permit the same user to authorise    a testkey.  A maximum number of attempts are allowed to authorise a    testkey as defined in the parameter table (DE.PARM).  If this is    exceeded the testkey is erased and must be re-input for this message. </p>
            <p>Note : Authorisation is dependent on the 'AUTHORISE TEXT KEY' setting on        the parameter table. </p>
            <p>After a function has been executed and the screen display returned to the list of messages (or when the list is first displayed) the user may refresh the list by typing 'R'.  This will remove from the display any messages which have been marked as authorised during the current session. </p>
            <p>Messages which have been authorised have the testkey inserted as a line in the formatted message and are then placed on the appropriate outward carrier queue to be sent out. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

