<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.MM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW OF BAR CHARTS ====================== </p>
            <p>Message Management is used to access a range of bar charts which give concise information about the flow of messages within the Delivery System. </p>
            <p>There are bar charts showing message volumes for each queue of messages. For each queue are displays broken down by priority and by carrier. Additionally there are the following displays, broken down by message type: </p>
            <p>          Messages being held.           Messages awaiting batching.           Formatted messages that are ready for output.           Messages on the outward repair queue.           Messages on the outward testkey queue.           Messages on the inward repair queue.           Messages on the inward testkey queue. </p>
            <p>Keys 1, 2, 3 and 4 allow the scale of these bar charts to be set to the following ranges: </p>
            <p>          1     0 - 20           2     0 - 200           3     0 - 2000           4     0 - 20000 </p>
            <p>This will permit the user to 'tailor'  the bar chart to suit the information being displayed.  For example, the user could choose a detailed chart of the short queues, then switch to small scale to put the longer queues into perspective. </p>
            <p>When a bar chart has too much information  to fit across the screen, the chart can be scrolled right by using F8, then scrolled back by using F7. </p>
            <p>It is possible to leave a bar chart by pressing either F1 or 'Q'. </p>
            <p>Example: Bar Chart of Unmapped Messages. </p>
            <p>             MESSAGES WAITING TO BE MAPPED </p>
            <p>   20 |    19 |    18 |    17 |    16 |    15 | M  14 | E  13 | S  12 | S  11 | A  10 | G   9 | E   8 | S   7 |     6 |     5 |     4 |////////     3 |////////     2 |/// 4 //     1 |////////     0 |--------------------------------------------        UNMAPPED </p>
            <p />
            <p>Count of Unmapped Messages: DE.MM.BC.UNMAPPED --------------------------------------------- This bar chart shows the number of messages waiting to be Mapped. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Unformatted Message Counts by Priority: DE.MM.BC.UNFORMATTED ------------------------------------------------------------ Provides a bar chart showing the number of messages on the Unformatted Message Queue, split out by Priority.  Counts are labelled 'U' 'P' 'N' 'T' and are for priorities 'Urgent', 'Priority', 'Normal' and the total. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Counts of Messages on Hold by Carrier and Priority: DE.MM.BC.HELD ----------------------------------------------------------------- This provides counts, for each carrier, of the messages being held. The different Form Types are grouped together as 'PRINT'. Each count is split out by Priority.  Counts are labelled 'U' 'P' 'N' 'T' and are for priorities 'Urgent', 'Priority', 'Normal' and the total. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Counts of messages awaiting testkeys by priority: DE.MM.BC.O.TESTKEY -------------------------------------------------------------------- This provides counts for each priority of messages on the outward awaiting testkey queue and a total of all messages on the queue. Batches of telex messages are shown as a single entry in the 'N' (Normal) priority column and included as a single message in the 'T'(Total) column. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Counts of messages awaiting batching by batch number: DE.MM.BC.O.BATCHING ------------------------------------------------------------------------- This provides a count of messages contained in all batches being built and a total of all messages in the batching queue.  Each batch is shown as a batch number with the number of messages it currently contains.  The total column is labelled 'TOT'. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Messages Ready for Transmission (by Carrier and Priority): DE.MM.BC.READY ------------------------------------------------------------------------- Provides counts, for each carrier, of the messages that are ready for transmission.  The different Form Types are shown separately. Each count is split out by Priority.  Counts are labelled 'U' 'P' 'N' 'T' and are for priorities 'Urgent', 'Priority', 'Normal' and the total. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Messages Queued for Repair: DE.MM.BC.REPAIR ------------------------------------------- This bar chart provides the number of messages queued for Repair. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Summary of Message Counts, by Priority: DE.MM.BC.O.SUMMARY ---------------------------------------------------------- Provides a single bar chart showing the number of messages on each queue and the total of all the message queues. </p>
            <p>Each queue has counts labelled 'U' 'P' 'N' 'T' and are for priorities 'Urgent', 'Priority', 'Normal' and the total, but messages that are Unmapped or in the batching or Repair Queue are only shown in the 'total' column as these queues do not have a separate index by priority. </p>
            <p />
            <p>DE.MM.BC.O.RECONCILIATION ------------------------- This is a bar chart showing counts of: </p>
            <p>          The messages received from the banking applications           Unformatted messages           Deleted messages           Messages on the repair queues           Messages being held           Messages being batched           Messages awaiting testkeys           Messages that are ready to transmit           Messages that are underway to Swift or Telex, but have           not been acknowledged or rejected           Messages that have been delivered (and, if appropriate,           acknowledged). </p>
            <p>The totals displayed should always add up because if a message from a banking application requires multiple copies then the number of extra copies will be added to the number of messages received, thus balancing the number of messages sent. </p>
            <p>The only exceptions are when a momentary imbalance occurs while extra copies are generated, or while a message is moved from one queue to another and a permanent imbalance resulting from a system failure. A warning is displayed if the totals are not correct. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Inward Messages Awaiting Routing: DE.MM.BC.INWARD ------------------------------------------------- Provides a bar chart showing the number of messages on the Inward Message Queue, split out by Priority. Counts are labelled 'U' 'P' 'N' 'T' and are for priorities 'Urgent', 'Priority', 'Normal' and the total. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Inward messages awaiting testkey verification: DE.MM.BC.I.TESTKEY ----------------------------------------------------------------- This provides a bar chart showing the number of messages on the inward testkey verification queue split out by priority.  Counts are labelled 'U', 'P', 'N' and 'T' representing priorities of 'Urgent', 'Priority', 'Normal', and the Total. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Inward Messages Queued for Repair: DE.MM.BC.I.REPAIR ---------------------------------------------------- This bar chart shows the number of inward messages queued for repair. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Message Counts by Message Type ------------------------------           1) DE.MM.BC.HELD.BY.MT           2) DE.MM.BC.O.TESTKEY.BY.MT           3) DE.MM.BC.READY.BY.MT           4) DE.MM.BC.REPAIR.BY.MT           5) DE.MM.BC.I.TESTKEY.BY.MT           6) DE.MM.BC.I.RP.BY.MT (inward repair) Provides bar charts showing the number of messages on the Held, Ready, Repair and inward repair Queues, Testkey and inward testkey queues, split out by Message Type and a total of all Message Types. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>