<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.MM.DISPLAY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW OF MESSAGE DISPLAYS ============================ </p>
            <p>Message Management Display presents the user with a menu from which he can choose to look at any of the Message Queues.  An example of the menu is as follows: </p>
            <p>1 OUTWARD -      WAITING TO BE MAPPED 2                UNFORMATTED 3                HOLD 4                REPAIR 5                BATCHING 6                TESTKEY 7                AWAITING ACKNOWLEDGEMENT 8                FORMATTED - PRINT (DEFAULT) 9                FORMATTED - PRINT (CHEQUE) 10               FORMATTED - PRINT (..etc..) 11               FORMATTED - SWIFT - MERVA 12               FORMATTED - EUCLID 13               FORMATTED - TELEX 14               FORMATTED - TANDEM 15 INWARD -      AWAITING TESTKEY VERIFICATION 16               UNFORMATTED 17               REPAIR </p>
            <p>The batching queue is only displayed if the Batching Req field on the parameter field is set to 'Y'. </p>
            <p>The number and order of 'carrier' queues (e.g. SWIFT, TELEX) depends on the outward carriers on the parameter file and the order they are specified in.  If the "GENERIC" carrier is specified in outward carriers, the carrier file, DE.CARRIER, is examined and each generic interface is then displayed, showing the name of the carrier (the id on DE.CARRIER) and the interface. </p>
            <p>e.g. 11               FORMATTED - SWIFT - MERVA </p>
            <p />
            <p>The number and order of the print queues depends on the number of forms defined on Form Type - each Form Type has its messages on a separate Message Queue. </p>
            <p>e.g. 9                FORMATTED - PRINT (CHEQUE) </p>
            <p>From each option a list is displayed of the Messages on the appropriate Message Queue.  The user can choose one message listed on the screen by entering its line number, or go to the next page of the list by pressing F3, or go to a particular page of the list by entering a page number (such as P3). </p>
            <p>For unmapped messages just a list of ID's will be displayed.  No action can be taken. </p>
            <p>When a line number has been selected the Message Header can be 'Seen' by entering 'S', amended ('Input') by entering 'I' authorised by entering 'A' or printed by entering 'P'. When a Message has been formatted (on all Message Queues except Unmapped and Unformatted) the additional facility to view the contents of the Message (as opposed to the Header) by entering 'V' is available. After 'V' the System gives the following options: </p>
            <p>D        Display the Message on the screen. P        Print the Message. Return to the list of Messages. </p>
            <p>If the message is not found on the current file it is automatically retrieved from history. </p>
            <p>Several options are also available on batched messages in the testkey or outward carrier queues.  When a line number corresponding to a batch message is entered the contents of the batch may be displayed by entering 'X'. </p>
            <p>The delivery reference of messages in the batch are listed and an individual message may be selected for input ('I'), seeing ('S'), authorisation ('A') or printing ('P').  When the batched message is viewed ('V') the complete batch message will be displayed or printed.  The batch cannot be viewed from the screen of the expanded batch, only from the list of queued messages. </p>
            <p>When a list of messages in the batching file is displayed a batch may be completed by entering 'C' adjacent to any message in the batch.  The batch then passes from the batching file to the testkey file or to the outward telex carrier queue depending on whether a testkey is required for it. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

