<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.MM.PRINT.MSG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is used to print the contents of a Formatted message, or display them on the screen. It is similar to the 'V' function in DE.MM.HISTORY.DISPLAY and DE.MM.DISPLAY. </p>
            <p>On entering this Application the following question is displayed on the screen: </p>
            <p>Do you wish to display or print the messages? Enter D (Display), or P (Print) or [RETURN] to end. </p>
            <p>When 'D' or 'P' is chosen it requests the message key.  This may either be the Header ID, the full ID including the copy number of the message or a batch number. If a specific copy is requested then only that copy will be displayed, otherwise F1 will display each copy before returning to enter another message key.  If a batch number was entered the complete batch message will be displayed. </p>
            <p>Whether a message is on 'Hold', ready for Carrier Control, awaiting a testkey or batching, or in History, if it has been formatted it can be displayed. </p>
            <p>If the Message Details are printed, the bottom of the page will have '** COPY  **  COPY  **  COPY  **' printed across it.  The message details are printed on the printer assigned to the terminal requesting the reports. This is not necessarily the same printer that the original message was printed on.  The message details are always printed on default stationery. </p>
            <p>When a message is displayed on the screen the following facilities are available: </p>
            <p>i)   F2 and F3 go backwards and forwards through the display in the normal      way. </p>
            <p>ii)  If the Message is more than 79 characters wide the display can be      paged left and right by using F7 and F8 respectively. </p>
            <p>iii) It is possible to go directly to a particular formatted page of a      printed (or TELEXP) message. For example, P5 displays what would be      page 5 when printed and not screen 5. </p>
            <p>Example. </p>
            <p>Message D198703065775461 has four copies. Copies 1, 3 and 4 are formatted, but copy number 2 has a Disposition of REPAIR. </p>
            <p>If D198703065775461.3 is entered only copy 3 of the message will be displayed before returning to request another message key. </p>
            <p>If D198703065775461 is entered copy 1 will be displayed, then F1 will cause copy 3 to be displayed, then copy 4. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

