<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.MM.HISTORY.DISPLAY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>When the End Of Period Processing is run all messages processed since the previous End Of Period Processing are moved onto the History File. They can then be examined using the History Display. </p>
            <p>When DE.MM.HISTORY.DISPLAY is entered, the user is asked to choose either inward or outward messages and this is followed by two options: </p>
            <p>i)  Enter a date (in the format year, month, day - 8 digits YYYYMMDD) to     obtain a list of all the messages received by the Delivery System on     that day.  For example, to obtain a list of all messages received by     the Delivery System on 31st March 1986 the user would enter 19860331. </p>
            <p>ii) Press enter for a complete list of messages. (This may be quite slow     due to the number of messages involved.) </p>
            <p>When a list of messages has been obtained the option to go directly to a particular page is available (e.g. P5 goes to page 5, or the last page if there are less than 5).  The user may also enter a line number to select a message on the current page. </p>
            <p>Having selected a message the Functions available are: P   Print the Message Header (not allowed on batches) </p>
            <p>S   See the Message Header on the screen (not allowed on batches) </p>
            <p>V   Presents the user with a further choice:     P     Print the Message details     D     Display the Message details on the screen. </p>
            <p>X   Expand a batch message to list the messages it contains.     When expanded the P and S functions above are available for each     message in the batch. </p>
            <p>When Message Details are being displayed it is different from (S) Seeing the Header, in two ways: </p>
            <p>i)  If the Message is more than 79 characters wide the display can be     paged left and right by using F7 and F8 respectively. </p>
            <p>ii) It is possible to go directly to a particular formatted page of a     printed (or TELEXP) message. P5, for example, displays what would be     page 5 when printed and not screen 5. </p>
            <p>If the Message Details are printed, the bottom of the page will have '** COPY  **  COPY  **  COPY  **' printed across it. </p>
            <p>No input can be made to any of the fields of a Message Header on the History file. </p>
            <p>If a batch message is selected the 'View' option will display or print the completed batch message. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

