<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.MM.SYSLOG.DISPLAY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>An error occurring within the 'phantom' message processing modules can be handled in two ways: </p>
            <p>o  Errors associated with a particular message are reported in the ERROR    CODE or MSG ERROR CODE fields on the relevant Message Header. </p>
            <p>o  Errors not associated with a particular message cannot be reported    immediately to a screen because phantom jobs are not attached to a    screen, instead, they are written to a Delivery System Log.  A report    of these errors can then be seen from any screen by using the    Application DE.MM.SYSLOG.DISPLAY. </p>
            <p>On entering this Application a screen is displayed giving options to select a particular part of the Log and either display it on the screen or print it.  However, defaults are set up so that pressing F5 causes all today's messages to be displayed on the screen.  F2 and F3 can be used in the standard way to page backwards and forwards through the part of the log selected. </p>
            <p>On entering DE.MM.SYSLOG.DISPLAY the following screen is presented for the user to select the required display: </p>
            <p>       CARRIER CONTROL - SYSTEM LOG PRINT REQUEST </p>
            <p>------------------------------------------------------ 1 Date............... from: DD MMM YY to: 31 DEC 99 2 Time............... from: 00:00:00  to: 00:00:00 3 Carrier............ PRINT,SWIFT,TELEX,EUCLID,TANDEM 4 Line number........ from: 00        to: 99 5 Event ID number.... from: 000       to: 999 6 Display or print... DISPLAY </p>
            <p>(DD MMM YY in 'Date.. from' represents today's date.) </p>
            <p>The above defaults will list all the errors logged today.  The values may be amended in the normal way - enter the line number, then go backwards and forwards using F2 and F3. </p>
            <p>1 Date     Dates must be entered in the format day month year, as in the            defaults.  The intervening spaces are optional.            Validation ensures that the 'to' date is not before the 'From'            date. </p>
            <p>2 Time     Times are entered in hours, minutes and seconds.  The seconds,            or the seconds and the minutes may be allowed to default to            zero. </p>
            <p>3 Carrier  When more than one Carrier is entered they must be separated by            commas with no extra spaces. </p>
            <p>4 Line number </p>
            <p>           The Line number identifies the physical line that the messages            are being sent down. </p>
            <p>5 Event ID number </p>
            <p>           A code identifying the type of event that is to be searched for            in the log. </p>
            <p>6 Display or print </p>
            <p>           'DISPLAY' will show the log on the screen.            'PRINT' sends it to the system printer. </p>
            <p>If the cursor is on one of the above fields then F1 and F4 both go back to the 'Action' line.  From the 'Action' line F1 exits, or F5 executes the display. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

