<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.MM.SETUP.TRANSLATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This facility is provided mainly to setup the delivery translation file initially, but can also be used to update the translation file from time to time.  There are various records that are delivered with the translation file initially, but additionally, there are codes which are file dependent which are required, e.g. category codes are passed to delivery for translation in printed messages.  This application enables the user to copy the description from all records on a particular file to the translation file, prefixing the codes with the prefix required in formatting. </p>
            <p>Firstly, the user will be prompted whether he wishes records on the Delivery Translation file to be overwritten.  If 'Y', overwrite, is entered existing records will be updated (but never deleted); if 'N' is entered, only records which do not already exist will be created.  The user will then be required to enter the file name (without company mnemonic) records are to be copied from, and the prefix to be used when updating the translation file.  The prefix is that used on the delivery format record. </p>
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>If a category code requires translation, the conversion on the delivery format record might be CATG/.  Therefore, the prefix required when copying records from the category file would be 'CATG/'. </p>
            <p>Once the records have been copied, the number of records created and updated will be displayed.  The user can then enter another file name or F1 to end. </p>
            <p>NOTE : The description is always copied from the first field in the file        being copied from.  Therefore, for records copied from the        transaction file where a short description is required (TXNS/), the        description must be amended on the translation file to the required        length. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

