<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.O.SELECT.NEXT.MESSAGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW OF OUTWARD FORMATTING ============================== </p>
            <p>Outward Formatting selects messages for formatting by using separate indexes of Urgent, Priority and Normal messages.  All Urgent messages are processed first, followed by a set number of Priority messages, as specified in 'Read Priority' on the System Status record and then a set number of Normal messages are processed, as specified in 'Read Normal'. If more Urgent messages have arrived they are processed next before returning to process more Priority or Normal messages. </p>
            <p>If a header contains an Override Carrier, it will determine the formatting required and this carrier will be the only one used.  There will only be one copy of a message, the Format will be Version 1 and the Status, Priority and Language used will be those picked up during Mapping. </p>
            <p>Normally a header will not contain an Override Carrier so the DE.PRODUCT file will be read.  If the relevant Product record specifies a message is to be sent by SWIFT, but the required Format Swift record does not exist, then the message will be Formatted for Telex instead.  If it cannot be Formatted for Telex it will default to print.  If the print format does not exist and a special language was requested, the print format in base language will be used.  If a print format does not exist, the message will go to the repair queue. </p>
            <p>If a message is routed by a company level Product record, the language of the customer will be used in formatting, rather than the language on the Product record, as the language of the customer is more relevant. </p>
            <p>Although a record may exist on the Product table to send all messages to a particular customer by TELEX and PRINT for example, if copies are not allowed for a particular message type (copies on the message table is 'NO'), only the first carrier will be used when the message is formatted. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

