<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.PHANTOM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Whereas input and maintenance of the tables controlling the Delivery System is performed on-line from a terminal, the processing of messages is done by 'phantom' jobs that run all day without being attached to a particular terminal.  These jobs are initiated by using the Phantom application.  This asks for the name of the program to be run, checks that it is not already active (by performing the Unix command "ps"), then starts the program. The operator can then either initiate another program or press [RETURN] to exit. </p>
            <p>Function Required            Program Name -----------------            ------------ Mapping                      DE.O.MAP.MESSAGES Outward Formatting           DE.O.SELECT.NEXT.MESSAGE </p>
            <p>Outward Carrier Control for: SWIFT via ST200              DE.O.CC.SWIFT SWIFT via DMNL               DE.O.CC.DMNL Print                        DE.O.CC.PRINT Tandem                       DE.O.CC.TANDEM Tandem to tape               DE.CC.TANDEM.TAPE </p>
            <p />
            <p>Outward and Inward Carrier Control for: Generic interfaces           DE.CC.GENERIC Telex                        DE.CC.TELEX Inward Formatting            DE.I.SELECT.NEXT.MESSAGE </p>
            <p>Inward Carrier Control for: SWIFT via ST200              DE.I.CC.SWIFT SWIFT via DMNL               DE.I.CC.DMNL EUCLID                       DE.I.CC.EUCLID Time Check (Release 'Holds') DE.MM.TIMECHECK </p>
            <p>These phantom jobs can be stopped by updating the Shutdown fields in the System Status record on the Parameter file to: </p>
            <p>'N' (giving a 'normal' shutdown after processing all messages on the relevant message queue), </p>
            <p>or </p>
            <p>'U' (giving an immediate shutdown after the message currently being processed). </p>
            <p>However, DE.CC.TANDEM.TAPE cannot be stopped by updating the shutdown flag and will only terminate once all records have been processed. </p>
            <p>The SWIFT and DMNL carrier control programs are alternatives and cannot be run at the same time.  For example, if DE.O.CC.SWIFT is running then DE.I.CC.SWIFT can be started but not DE.O.CC.DMNL or DE.I.CC.DMNL. </p>
            <p>Some of the programs listed above can also be run as normal applications attached to the terminal that initiates them.  This is potentially useful only for DE.O.CC.PRINT where run 'interactively' a specific Form Type, Priority and Department can be selected, but run as a phantom all Form Types, Priorities and Departments are printed. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>

