<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.RESET.ACTIVE.FLAG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This facility is provided solely for the purpose of recovering from a system failure.  It must not be used for the everyday shutdown of message processing as this is done by amending the System Status record in the DE.PARM file at the end of a days processing.  If due to (for example) a system failure, the message processing modules have not been shutdown, the Shutdown fields in the System Status record may contain 'A' (Active).  In this event, a check must be made to ensure that the modules are not in fact active and, if they are not, fields should be reset to 'C' (Closed) by using DE.RESET.ACTIVE.FLAG.  Similarly, if End of Period terminates abnormally, the Shutdown fields on the System Status record may contain 'E' (end of period).  After checking that End of Period is not active, these fields should be reset to 'C'. </p>
            <p>When this Application is entered it lists the Shutdown fields in the DE.PARM file and their values, which may be A, C, E, U, or N. (see Parameter). </p>
            <p>When the number of a particular field is entered then if that field contains 'A' 'U' or 'N' it will be set to 'C' (Closed). </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example: </p>
            <p>The screen may look like this: </p>
            <p>1   Inward Formatting                   A 2   Outward Formatting                  N 3   Mapping                             U 4   Time Check                          A 5   Outward Carrier Control - Print     A 6   Outward Carrier Control - SWIFT     A 7   Outward Carrier Control - Telex     A 8   Outward Carrier Control - Euclid    C 9   Outward Carrier Control - Tandem    A 10  Inward Carrier Control  - SWIFT     A 11  Inward Carrier Control  - Euclid    C </p>
            <p>The example screen above shows that the various message processing routines are active.  If the status of these routines do not become 'C' (Closed) after a 'Normal' or 'Urgent' shutdown, it is because they were terminated abnormally and are therefore not active. In order to reset each status flag to 'C' numbers 1-8 must be entered. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
</menu>
</t24help>