<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.RECEIVED.SWIFT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds a cross reference between incoming delivery messages received from Swift, and the resulting Funds Transfer, generated by the FT.IN.PROCESSING routine. </p>
            <p>The file is used for enquiry purposes, and to ensure that the same message does not generate 2 or more Funds Transfers in a recovery situation. </p>
            <p>The record is created by the incoming SWIFT phantom when a message is received, and the Funds Transfer reference is added by the application FT.IN.PROCESSING. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>COMP.TXN.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction reference and company mnemonic of the Funds Transfer generated by the incoming SWIFT message. </p>
            <p>The company mnemonic is that of the company in which the Funds Transfer was generated. </p>
            <p>The contents of this field will be checked before generating the Funds Transfer for the message, to ensure that it has not already been processed. If a reference is present then no new Funds Transfer will be generated. This situation is possible if the system has been recovered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>12 alphanumeric Funds Transfer referenec number in the the format:  a)     "FT"  b)     5 digit Julian date in the form YYDDD where YY is the last 2        digits of year ans DDD is the day number.  c)     5 digit serial number in the range 50000 - 59999  Followed by "/" and a 3 alphanumeric company mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The reference number of the incoming delivery message. </p>
            <p>The delivery key is generated by the incoming SWIFT phantom when the message is received. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>16 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

