<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.SWIFT.DIVERSION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>DE.SWIFT.DIVERSION provides the means, for both inward and outward messages, to divert SWIFT messages for a given SWIFT message type and SWIFT address from the SWIFT carrier to another file. </p>
            <p>The SWIFT message type must be specified along with the SWIFT delivery address as entered for SWIFT address via the DE.ADDRESS application. </p>
            <p>The process that the SWIFT messages are diverted to is also specified plus outward and inward files and records.  The file names are validated against the existing database and the record names are used to write the diverted messages to the file. </p>
            <p>In special cases, for inward messages, a condition may be set up to direct the SWIFT message to a special record rather than the standard one. </p>
            <p>The files containing the diverted messages may be purged via a batch process after a specified number of days. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>IN.SPECIAL.IF</field>
<desc>
            <p>For inward messages input to this field will be checked.  If the condition is located in the message special action is taken. </p>
            <p>If a condition entered here is found to be true during processing, the following field will be used to form the key of the diverted file. </p>
            <p>This is only true of inward messages. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters.  Multivalued field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTWARD.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the file to which SWIFT messages being sent will be diverted. </p>
            <p>The file names here will be used to store outward SWIFT messages.  The file named will for part of the diversion message on delivery header records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 25 characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid file on the system, and must be a valid file entry in the current user's VOC file.</p>
            <p>There must also be a corresponding entry on the FILE.CONTROL application with a file type of 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.RECORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the key to be used when diverting inward messages for the correct message type to the inward file. </p>
            <p>Input entered here will form the key of inward messages diverted to the inward file identified in the previous field. </p>
            <p>Input of the form 'L01' will generate a key of run date suffixed by '.L01' </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTWARD.RECORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the key to be used when diverting outward messages for the current message type to the outward file. </p>
            <p>Input entered here will form the key of outward messages diverted to the outward file identified in the previous field. </p>
            <p>Input of the form '.L01' will generate a key of run date suffixed by '.L01' </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the file to which SWIFT messages being received will be diverted. </p>
            <p>The file named here will be used to store inward SWIFT messages.  The file named will form part of the diversion message on delivery header records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 25 characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Must exist as a valid file on the system, and must be a valid file entry in the current user's VOC file.</p>
            <p>There must also be a corresponding entry on the FILE.CONTROL application with a file type of 1.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.CUST.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not the real customer Swift address is to be used for diverted messages, rather than the dummy address. </p>
            <p>The Swift address will be replaced by the real Customer address in diverted messages if this field is set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 alpha characters. 'Y' = 'Yes' 'N' = 'No'</p>
            <p>Only 'Y', 'NO' or null is allowed.</p>
            <p>Null input implies 'NO', and the dummy address field will only be replaced if this field is set to 'Y'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRAILER.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the format of a standard Swift trailer to be appended to diverted messages. </p>
            <p>The exact format entered here will be used to add a Swift trailer to any diverted messages. The user should take care that the data entered is an acceptable Swift format (if the trailer records are critical to the function of any diversion software in use).  No further validation is performed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 22 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.DAYS.ON.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of days that diverted data will be kept on file within the system. </p>
            <p>Data will remain on the diverted files until the number of days specified here have elapsed. </p>
            <p>The DE.PURGE.DIV.FILES will delete the data on a daily basis once the time for data to be held has been exceeded. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric plus 1 alpha characters.</p>
            <p>The number of days may be suffixed with 'C' for Calendar or 'W' for Working.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPECIAL.RECORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the key to be used when diverting inward messages for the current message type to the inward file, only if the previous fields condition is true. </p>
            <p>Input entered here will form the key of inward messages diverted to the inward file identified in the INWARD.FILE field. </p>
            <p>This field is only used if the condition in the previous field is found to be true. </p>
            <p>Input of the form '.L01' will generate a key of run date suffixed by '.L01' </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the SWIFT message type to be diverted to another file rather than the standard SWIFT carrier. </p>
            <p>In the delivery system messages will normally be sent via the SWIFT carrier. </p>
            <p>Messages set up in this application can be diverted from SWIFT into another file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Must exist on the DE.MESSAGE file.  The enrichment is taken from the DE.MESSAGE description.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.DELIMITERS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not standard Swift delimiters will be added to diverted messages prior to diversion. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to 'Y' then the standard Swift start message and end message codes will be added to the message prior to diversion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 alpha characters. 'Y' = 'Yes' 'N' = 'No'</p>
            <p>Only 'Y', 'NO' or null is allowed.</p>
            <p>Null input implies 'NO', and the delimiters will not be added to diverted messages.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOW.PASS.THRU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Will either be YES, NO or blank. If YES then an incoming message will be 'copied' to the diversion file and then processing will continue on the message, otherwise the message will be 'diverted' to the diversion file and no further processing performed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Either YES, NO or blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVERT.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The delivery address for the diverted message is entered in this field. </p>
            <p>Must be a valid SWIFT address for this diverted message. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>From 8 to 11 characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>First 4 characters must be alpha.</p>
            <p>Characters 5 to 6 must be a valid code in the COUNTRY application.</p>
            <p>Characters 7 to 8 must be in the range A-Z or 2 to 9.</p>
            <p>If present, characters 9 to 11 must be alphanumeric.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIVERT.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the process that SWIFT messages are being diverted to and that certain diversion checks will take place. </p>
            <p>Input to this field identifies that the contents of the following fields should be checked, and possibly amended within delivery programs before messages are diverted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 characters. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

