<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>DE.SEQUENCE.NUMBER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application allows the sequence numbers used by the delivery system for external interfaces to be reset. </p>
            <p>For a given carrier type, either the Incoming sequence number and/or the Outgoing sequence number can be reset. The existing sequence numbers are shown before the new number is entered. The sequence number will not be changed until authorisation of the record. </p>
            <p>The current sequence number is held on the file LOCKING with a key of "IN-carrier" or "OUT-carrier", where carrier is "SIC", "SWIFT", "TELEX" etc. </p>
            <p>It may sometimes be necessary to reset a sequence number if a carrier goes down while sending a message for example. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OUT.SEQ.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current value of the outward carrier sequence number at the time of input. </p>
            <p>The current value of the outgoing sequence number is held on the LOCKING file with the key "OUT-carrier" where carrier is the key to this record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name of the carrier for which the sequence numbers are to be changed. </p>
            <p>The carrier may be one of the following values: </p>
            <p>           SIC, SWIFT, TELEX, EUCLID. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p>The carrier must exist in the DE.PARM record in the OUTWARD.CARRIERS or INWARD.CARRIERS field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.SEQ.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value of the Incoming sequence number at the time of Input. </p>
            <p>The current sequence number is held on the LOCKING file with the key "IN-carrier" where carrier is the key to this record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 6 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.IN.SEQ.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the new value of the incoming sequence number. </p>
            <p>The new sequence number will not take effect until the record is authorised. The record cannot be authorised if the carrier phantom is still active. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.OUT.SEQ.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The new value to be used as the sequence number for the outward carrier. </p>
            <p>The new sequence number will not take effect until the record is authorised. The record cannot be authorised if the carrier phantom is still active. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric characters. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

