<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>EB.MESSAGE.111</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The EB.MESSAGE table allows the production of  SWIFT message  MT111  Request for stop payment of a cheque.  This is produced via the Delivery module.</p>
            <p>Only one stop instruction for one Account number is maintained on a record, and only one message can be raised at a time. Amendment to authorised record is not allowed, and a new message would have to be raised for a new stop on the same account.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>QUERIES</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field may contain either the reason for stopping the payment of the cheque or a  request for reimbursement authorisation.</p>
            <p>Contains an Enquiry called - List of DE.TRANSLATION Query Codes.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 6 multi-values allowed.</p>
            <p>Up to 35 type S (SWIFT) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.SENDER.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p> Identifies the Inward Sender's Reference specified on incoming SWIFT MT111 Request for Stop Payment  messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard GLOBUS alphanumeric field.A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.This is a NOINPUT field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Receiver of the SWIFT message. </p>
            <p>This field is a NOINPUT field if a NOSTRO or a VOSTRO Account has been entered in the ACCOUNT.NUMBER field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric character Customer Code or 3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') character Customer Mnemonic. </p>
            <p>The account in the ACCOUNT.NUMBER field does not have to belong to this customer except if a NOSTRO or a VOSTRO Account has been entered in the ACCOUNT.NUMBER field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used when the Sender has previously credited the receiver with the cheque amount. </p>
            <p>This field is valid if a VOSTRO Account has been entered in the ACCOUNT.NUMBER field.</p>
            <p>Note: </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field should not be less than DATE.OF.ISSUE. </p>
            <p>This field does not accept forward dates.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 9 type D dates characters (Date format in range 1950 to 2049)  Type D. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the incoming SWIFT message</p>
            <p />received direct from Delivery.<p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input - Internal field.       </p><p /><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.SWIFT.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Incoming Swift message detail, which created the EB.MSSAGe.111 record, is held here.</p>
            <p />
            <p>It contains full information along with tag, which is available in the Block 4 of Incoming Swift message.</p>
            <p />  The information stored here is as it is received.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input - Internal field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.PROCESS.ERR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any process errors that may have occurred during the Swift Inward message processing using OFS.GLOBUS.MANAGER.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The process error may be due to Non mapping of Incoming message tag details in payment .stop Application or Errors encountered in payment stop application during Inward Message processing.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When Inward processing encounter any error related to this application, the Payment.stop records will be built as normal, except they will have a Record Status of 'IHLD'. The actual Error details will be held in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>But when it encounter non mapping of Tags in payment stop, Payment stop will not be put on Hold but stores tag details for information</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input - Internal multivalued field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid input YES or NO</p>
            <p>Message output is suppressed when set to NO.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency of the Account to which this Payment Stop Messsage refers. </p>
            <p>The amounts input to the CHEQUE.AMOUNT (Field 7)  must be in the Currency indicated by this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 characters (uppercase alpha) - type SSS. or 1-3 numeric character Currency Code. (Mandatory Input).</p>
            <p>Must exist on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.DRAWER.BK.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Account Number of the Drawer Bank as extracted from the incoming SWIFT MT111 Request for Stop Payment  messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard GLOBUS alphanumeric field.A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.This is a NOINPUT field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the beneficiary of the cheque.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Account must not be used.</p>
            <p>Up to 35 type S (SWIFT) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWER.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>DRAWER.ACC</p>
            <p>This field identifies the Account Number of the Drawer Bank when other than the Sender.</p>
            <p>This field will be used when the drawer bank is a branch of the Sender or a bank other than the Sender of the message.</p>
            <p>The information in this field will be used as the Party Identifier in SWIFT Tag 52.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Standard numeric Account number or 3-10 character Account Mnemonic (uppercase alpha, numeric) </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Confirmation that MT111 - request for stop payment of a cheque have been sent to the T24 delivery system for onward transmission to ordering institution.21 type A (alphanumeric) characters in the form: AYYYYMMDDUUUUUCCCCCC where A = (D)ELIVERED (R)ECEIVED YYYY = YEAR MM = MONTH DD = SEQUENCE NO UUUUU = SYSTEM USER NUMBER CCCCC = TIME STAMP (System generated.) </p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Fields ACTIVITY.CODE to DELIVERY.REF form a related multi value set.Standard GLOBUS numeric field.A maximum of 16 characters may be entered.This is a NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATE.PAY.STOP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes whether a Payment.Stop record has to be created or not. If the value is set to yes, while authorizing the record a Payment stop record will be create with the details available in this record. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be set to Y only when the record is created by inward       processing. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWER.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the Drawer Bank when other than the Sender.</p>
            <p>This field will be used when the drawer bank is a branch of the Receiver or a bank other than the Receiver of the message.</p>
            <p>Specifies the name or name and address of the financial institution.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 type S (SWIFT) characters.</p>
            <p>No  Multi Values are permitted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAW.BANK.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the option (A, B or D) for field DRAWER.BANK (i.e. Tag 52 in SWIFT Message MT112).</p>
            <p>BIC: </p>
            <p>This option (Option A) specifies the ISO Bank Identifier Code (BIC), and optionally the account or clearing code of the financial institution, initiating the transaction on behalf of itself or the ordering customer.</p>
            <p>LOCATION:</p>
            <p>This option (Option B) specifies the branch and optionally the account or clearing code of the financial institution, initiating the transaction on behalf of itself or the ordering customer.</p>
            <p>ADDRESS: </p>
            <p>This option (Option D) specifies the name and address and optionally the account or clearing code of the financial institution, initiating the transaction on behalf of itself or the ordering customer.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>BIC, LOCATION or ADDRESS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SENDERS.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the reference assigned by the Sender to unambiguously identify the message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>This field must not start or end with a / and must not contain two consecutive slashes // (SWIFT Error Code T26)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWER.CUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>DRAWER.CUS:</p>
            <p>This field identifies the Customer Number of the Drawer Bank when other than the Sender.</p>
            <p>This field will be used when the drawer bank is a branch of the Sender or a bank other than the Sender of the message.</p>
            <p>The information in this field is will be used on the SWIFT Tag 52a.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric character Customer Code or 3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') character Customer Mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the number of the cheque, which is to be stopped. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field must not start or end with a / and must not contain two consecutive slashes // (SWIFT Error Code T26)</p>
            <p>Up to 16 type S (SWIFT) characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the reference number allocated by Delivery for incoming SWIFT message received direct from Delivery. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This will enable enquiries to be made on the original SWIFT message received. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input - Internal field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAPPING.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Populated by the T24 delivery mechenism with the Mapping reference that  request for stop payment of a cheque has generated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Fields ACTIVITY.CODE to DELIVERY.REF form a related multi value set.Standard GLOBUS numeric field.A maximum of 13 characters may be entered.This is a NOINPUT field.Must be the key to a valid entry on the DE.MAPPING file</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.OF.ISSUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the date on which the cheque was issued (drawn).</p>
            <p>Note: </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field does not accept forward dates.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 9 type D date characters (Date format in range 1950 to 2049). </p>
            <p>Mandatory Field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.DRAWER.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Drawer Bank as extracted from the incoming SWIFT MT111 Request for Stop Payment  messages.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard GLOBUS alphanumeric field.A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.This is a NOINPUT field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Account Number of the Customer to whom the Cheque belongs. </p>
            <p>If  NOSTRO or VOSTRO Accounts are entered, field CUSTOMER.NO defaults and becomes NOINPUT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard numeric Account Number or 3-10 character Account Mnemonic (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type MNE. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Populated by the T24 delivery mechenism with the Activity that this request for stop payment of a cheque has generated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Fields ACTIVITY.CODE to DELIVERY.REF form a related multi value set.Standard GLOBUS numeric field.A maximum of 7 characters may be entered.This is a NOINPUT field.Must be the key to a valid entry on the EB.ACTIVITY file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Populated by the T24 delivery mechenism with the date the ACTIVITY.CODE was generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Fields ACTIVITY.CODE to DELIVERY.REF form a related multi value set.Standard GLOBUS date field.A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Cheque Amount of the cheque which is to be stopped.. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory input) The amount must be greater than Zero. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

