<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>EB.TICKLER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Tickler  is a Diary event or a Delegation tool as one  might address it.</p>
            <p>The Sender, say Manager, may schedule a certain event/s, on certain date/s, to different Receivers, say Assistants, setting the appropriate status for the said  tasks. These tasks can be broken into different applications. </p>
            <p>Setting such Ticklers, enables the  Supervisor to monitor the progress of the tasks assigned. </p>
            <p>Suitable  Enquiries or reports  may be extracted by the User to suit local requirements.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RCV.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the current status of the Tickler from the Receiver's perspective. </p>
            <p>This holds the value as 'SCHD' when a task is assigned at the  first instance.</p>
            <p>If the task assigned to the Receiver has been completed or should the Sender decide to Stop the Tickler  for any reason, it may be done by setting this to 'STOP'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are 'SCHD' or 'STOP'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts only valid transaction id which are given in EB.TICKLER.TXN.ID record
</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.USER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Refers to the User that has been assigned this task, the Receiver of the Tickler.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid Id  in the USER  table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SENDER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Refers to the User that has scheduled the Tickler. The default is always  the User that has input this Tickler.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TICKLER.TXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts any free format text/message that the Sender intends conveying to the Receiver of the Tickler.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Any alphanumeric character.</p>
            <p>Maximum of 50 characters  per line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SENDER.STAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Refers to the Tickler's status from the Sender's  point of view. This defaults to 'SCHD', which means the Tickler is scheduled for User/s on a particular date. </p>
            <p>In those cases where more than on Receiver is set on a single  date to carry out a tasks and the Sender intends to 'STOP' the job set for all the Receivers, this may be set to 'STOP', as a Top level measure. </p>
            <p>So when this is set to 'STOP' all the RCV.STATUS shall be set to 'STOP'.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid  inputs are 'SCHD' and 'STOP'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TICKLER.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the date for which the Tickler is scheduled. </p>
            <p>Defaults to TODAY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Cannot be less than TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This refers to the Application for which this Tickler is to be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>All 'H' and 'U' type Applications.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.TICKLER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the reference  number to uniquely identify  a particular Tickler.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The Tickler number is a 10 digit number, prefixed with 'TK' based upon       the following format: TK YY DDD 99999.where: TK = Tickler, YY = Current       Year, DDD = Julian Day and 99999 = Sequence Number       </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>     Specifies an alternative means of referring to the TICKLER. </p>
            <p />
            <p>     For each TICKLER, the system will automatically update an internal file called EB.TICKLER.TXN.ID, which will hold the     mnemonic of the TICKLER with the TICKLER id. This allows the user to list the ticklers in mnemonic sequence instead of Tickler reference. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                </p>
                <p />
                <p>up to 16 alphanumeric characters or special  characters. </p>
                <p>Must hold a unique value (No two Ticklers can have the same Mnemonic).</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

