<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>NOSTRO.INTERFACE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to perform the Nostro reconciliation between SWIFT messages and the bank accounting, using the NOSTRO-PC program from STS (Swift Terminal Services). It uses the parameters defined on NOSTRO.PARM for it's processing. </p>
            <p>The application must be run with the 'V' function. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the end date up to which the Nostro reconciliation processing is to take place. </p>
            <p>If no input is made to this field then if the START.DATE is present it will be defaulted to the value in START.DATE else it will default to the last working day which is defined on the DATES file. </p>
            <p>If field 2 EXTR.HIS.RECORDS is set to 'NO' on the NOSTRO.PARM file then the date entered may not be less than the last working day, but if it is set to 'Y' then it may be any previous date. </p>
            <p>The contents of this field must be greater than or equal to the contents of field START.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 standard date (type D) characters. (Optional input. See Details).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERFACE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the key to the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 20 alphanumeric (type A) characters. (Mandatory Input).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the start date from which the Nostro reconciliation processing is to take place. </p>
            <p>If no input is made to this field then it will default to the last working day which is defined on the DATES file. </p>
            <p>If field 2 EXTR.HIS.RECORDS is set to 'NO' on the NOSTRO.PARM file then the date entered may not be less than the last working day, but if it is set to 'Y' then it may be any previous date. </p>
            <p>The contents of this field must be less than or equal to the contents of field END.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 10 standard date (type D) characters. (Optional input. See Details).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

