<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>SWIFT.CODE.WORDS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The SWIFT Code Words application will maintain information for code words as defined in SWIFT standards, general definitions for SWIFT field 72. </p>
            <p>The SWIFT Code Word identifier must be a code word as defined for field 72 and the application accepts code word descriptions, and product codes. </p>
            <p>Code words defined in this application may be used as part of bank to bank information within other applications, corresponding to SWIFT field 72.  Providing that bank to bank information is available within another application entry of a code word and additional information will result in sender to receiver information appearing on delivery advices via the set-up within DE.MAPPING and DE.MESSAGE applications. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SUPPLEMENT.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in connection with the Queries and Answer message types (n95 and n96). These message types use code numbers which have a special meaning. Where the message needs additional information such as dates or text, the code number is appended with the details. This field shows how many detail items are needed. The explanation of the item is in the </p>
            <p><em>SUPP.PROMPT</em>
            </p> field.  <p>See the helptext on<strong></strong></p><p>the<em> SUPP.PROMPT</em></p> field for more details and examples.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Free format text</p><p>Input suggested as (1).. (2) with explantion in </p><p><em>SUPP.PROMPT</em></p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the SWIFT Code Word as used by the SWIFT Delivery system in sender to receiver information, SWIFT field 72. </p>
            <p>Code words entered here may be used by other applications for bank to bank information in the SWIFT system. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 to 10 Alphabetic characters (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>Input to this field must be equal to a SWIFT code word as defined in the SWIFT standards, general field definitions for SWIFT field 72.</p>
            <p>The code word must be a minimum of 3 and a maximum of 8 Alphabetic characters</p>
            <p>Input to this field must start and end with a slash character '/'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUPP.PROMPT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in connection with the Queries and Answer message types (n95 and n96). These message types use code numbers which have a special meaning. Where the message needs additional information such as dates or text, the code number is appended with the details. This field shows the explanation of the item, and where required the type of detail needed for the values in the </p>
            <p><em>SUPPLEMENT.INFO</em>
            </p> field.  <p>In order to identify these special codes, the id is entered as SWN95/16/ or SWN96/16/ to allow the values to be readily used with context work based Enquiries for each message series. Note that the data used in EB.QUERIES.ANSWERS application expects only the /16/ format.</p><p><strong>Example</strong></p><p>Codes 23 and 30 are used. </p><table border="0"><tr><td>/23/</td><td>Please send us a copy of the truncated cheque with         transaction reference (1)</td></tr><tr><td>/30/ </td><td>Amount protested by the Issuer</td></tr></table><p>Code 23 needs some extra information, indicated by the (1), so the user enters /23/abc1003. This would appear in the message as:</p><table border="0"><tr><td>:75:/23/abc1003</td></tr><tr><td>/30/</td></tr></table><p>These would be entered in the fields as:</p><table border="1" bgcolor="#FFFFFF"><tr><td><p><strong>Record id</strong></p></td><td><p><strong>SUPPLEMENT.INFO</strong></p></td><td><p><strong>SUPP.PROMPT</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td>SWN95/23/</td><td><p>(1)</p></td><td>Please send us a copy of the truncated cheque with         transaction reference (1)</td></tr><tr><td>SWN95/30/</td><td /><td>Amount protested by the Issuer</td></tr></table><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Free format text</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the meaning or use of the SWIFT code word. The description from SWIFT standards, general field definitions may be used. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the SWIFT.CODE record in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 Alphanumeric characters Multi language field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the type of SWIFT messages that will be generated for the defined product in SWIFT.CODE.WORD record </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the applications that will be allowed to make use of the SWIFT code in the SWIFT delivery system. </p>
            <p>The products entered here will be able to use the SWIFT code in the bank to bank information field when the specified application is run and provided that SWIFT field 72 is available to the application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 to 4 Alphanumeric characters Multi-valued field</p>
            <p>Must be a valid T24 application as entered at the Enter Application action line.</p>
            <p>The absence of any input in this field implies that any product using SWIFT field 72 may use this code word.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

