<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>DE</product>
<table>SWIFT.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
            <p>============================ SWIFT PARAMETER OVERVIEW ============================= </p>
	    <p> This is used to set the parameter for the SWIFT. </p>
	    <p> This parameter table will be used to define generic rules for SWIFT that may be used across many messages.  </p>
	    <p> The Current SWIFT Release and the Previous SWIFT release fields are used to enable the activation of the new SWIFT functionality.  </p>
	    <p> The fields Restricted Currency and Message type are used to restrict currencies for specific message types </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CURR.SWIFT.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will be used to hold the current SWIFT release. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Should hold a value within range 1950 - 2049. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.SWIFT.REL</field>
<desc>
            <p> This is a multi-value field to hold the previous SWIFT release History. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> No Input Field.   </p>
            <p> When future SWIFT changes are released the field PREV.SWIFT.REL will be updated with the value from CURR.SWIFT.REL.  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTRICTED.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p> Multi-value field used to define the Currency where SWIFT has restricted the use of it in certain message types.</p>
            <p> </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Should be a valid record in CURRENCY table. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p> Associated sub-value field to the RESTRICTED.CCY field, to hold the Message Type. </p>
            <p> This field is used to define the message types that the currency defined in field Restricted CCY is not allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Should be a valid message type in DE.FORMAT.SWIFT </p>
            <p> </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>SWIFT.PARAMETER.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
