<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>USRETL</product>
        <title>POSPAY.CHECK.DETAILS</title>
        <table>POSPAY.CHECK.DETAILS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table will store the check details sent by the customer, who has opted for the positive pay service & issued a check to any payee.</p>
			<p>The ID format of the record in this table is “Account number – Check number”</p>
     </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>	CUSTOMER.ID </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field will get updated with the customer number who holds the debit account number.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length - 15.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	ISSUE.DATE </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the issue date of the check.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length - 15, Field type – Date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	AMOUNT </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the amount mentioned on the check details sent by the customer.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length - 20, Field type - Amount.</p>	
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	CURRENCY </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the currency details of the check.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length - 3, Field type – Alpha-numeric.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field> STATUS </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field will initially update as “New” once it is received from the customer. The transaction status can be changed to “Matched”, when the check details received from the customer & from the clearing house are same (or) it can be changed to “Exception” if there is any mismatch between the check details provided by the customer & the clearing house. After paying or returning the check, the status will be changed to “Authorized” or “Deleted” from the “Exception status.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length - 10, Field type – Alpha-numeric.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	PROCESS.DATE </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the date on which the check presented for clearing.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length – 15, Field type – Date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	TRANSACTION.REF </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the FT number.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length -20. Field type – Alpha-numeric.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	ERROR.MESSAGE </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the error message that is to be sent to the customer, if there is any discrepancy in the check.</p>
				<p>This field is no-input field. It will be updated by error message once the clearing transaction fails.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length - 65, Field type – Alpha-numeric</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	COMMENTS </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field will get mandatory when any record in this table is edited for doing any amends & the user must input the reason for amending in the field, which is a free text message.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length - 35, Field type – Alpha-numeric.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	CUSTOMER.DECISION </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the decision received from the customer, whether to pay or return the check item.</p>
		    </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>	CUSTOMER.REASON </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds an appropriate reason if any given by the customer.</p>
		    </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
