<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>USRETL</product>
        <title>USRETL.PARAMETER</title>
        <table>USRETL.PARAMETER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
			<p>This table holds the handling method configuration and T24 Application and Version names to amend , authorise and delete the exception records.</p>
            <p>@ID - The ID must be a valid Lead Company Id</p>
     </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>HANDLING.METHOD </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field is used to define the positive pay handling ways whether it is a Direct handling or Third party handling.</p>
				<p>Positive Pay handling method can have values DIRECT or INDIRECT</p>
				<p>Rule: Field length - 8 Character type AAA.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>APPLICATION </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field should hold the valid T24 Application name.</p>
			</desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>VERSION.NAME </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the Version name for above application to amend/authorise/delete Positive Pay related transactions.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>STATEMENT.PATH </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field holds the path where combined statements are generated.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ACC.INT.PROP </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field is used to store the interest property records from AA.PROPERTY related to Accounts.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.INTTAX.PROP</field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field is used to store the interest tax property records from AA.PROPERTY related to Accounts</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>DEP.INT.PROP </field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field is used to store the interest property records from AA.PROPERTY related to deposits.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEP.INTTAX.PROP</field>
            <desc>
				<p>This field is used to store the interest tax property records from AA.PROPERTY related to deposits.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.PERDIEM.PROP</field>
            <desc>
				<p>This is the field used to store the property to be considered for calculation of Perdiem for Accounts product condition.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEP.PERDIEM.PROP</field>
            <desc>
				<p>This is the field used to store the property to be considered for calculation of Perdiem for Deposit product condition.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>DEP.CHECK.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
				<p>To parametrize suspense account used for pay by check option provided in deposit settlement instructions. This suspense account will be used as a PAY.OUT account if user chooses PAY.BY.CHECK option.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
