<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IF</product>
<table>IF.EXIT.POINTS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXIT.POINT.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the name of the Exit Point to which the associated Integration Flow is attached to. The Exit Points are the places in T24 Applications/Versions and Component Services from which the Integration Flow is executed to emit any notification out of corresponding T24 Application / Version or Component Service or TSA Service.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXIT.POINT.SOURCE</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This is the KEY field in this table to store the source of the exit point. For Version exit points, this key would be the name of the Version and for Application type exit points (configured at VERSION.CONTROL), the key would be the name of the application. For Component Service type event outs, key would be the name of the Component Service Operation (E.g., CustomerService.setPhysicalAddress). For TSA Service key would be the name of the Service.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEGRATION.FLOW.1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the unique name of the Integration Flow which is attached to the associated exit point. This is a sub-value field since a single exit point may emit more than one notification (e.g., two INPUT.ROUTINEs in a Version).</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE.CODE.1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the override codes associated with this exit point. Integration Framework will raise these overrides using the standard T24 override mechanism while delivering events.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>