<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IF</product>
<table>IF.INTEGRATION.FLOW.CATALOG</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXIT.POINT.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field links the IF.INTEGRATION.FLOW.CATALOG table with the IF.EXIT.POINTS table.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.DEFINITION.1</field>
<desc>
            <p><b>Overview</b>
            </p>
            <p>This field holds the definition of how flow data could be retrieved at run time for the field given in the associated FIELD.NAME. This is used only for CONTRACT type flow sources. The value stored in this field could be one of the following:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Name of a field in the flow source application<p>Example: DEBT.ACCT.NO field in FUNDS.TRANSFER Application</p></p>
                <p value="2">A link consists of Applications and fields which are linked together to form a path<p>Example: To retrieve account officer name of the debit account from FUNDS.TRANSFER Application</p><p>FUNDS.TRANSFER&gt;DEBIT.ACCT.NO&gt;CUSTOMER&gt;CUSTOMER&gt;ACCOUNT.OFFICER&gt;DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER&gt;NAME</p></p>
                <p value="3">
                    <p>A custom value which is provided in the Integration tooling which is expected to be part of all the events generated out of this flow, as it is.</p>
                    <p>Example: “PRIORITY-2”</p>
                </p>
            </p>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">&#160;</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the user defined name of the field being used in this flow. When a flow is created, each data (or enrichment) of the flow is expected to give a unique name which is used to identify the data and its position.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the data type for the field given in the associated FIELD.NAME.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOW.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the unique name which identifies this Integration Flow. This name has two components where the first part represents the name of the Integration Studio project and the second part which is used as the name of the flow when created from Integration Studio.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOW.SCHEMA</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the schema  which defines the event XML  which is constructed at runtime.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOW.SOURCE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the source where the flow is attached to. The source could be a Versions, Applications,TSA Service or Component Service.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOW.SOURCE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field is used to record the type of the flow source. The flow could be originated from difference sources  of types Versions, Applications, TSA Service or Component Services.</p>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Validations Rule</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
            <p>&#160;</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.INPUT.DEFINITION.1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This associated sub-value field is used to store the definition of how to supply data to the Component Service operation at run time. This data would be of the type given in its associated SERVICE.INPUT.TYPE field.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.INPUT.NAME.1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This associated sub-value field holds the name of the input argument to its associated service operation recorded in SERVICE.OPERATION.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.INPUT.TYPE.1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This associated sub-value field holds the type of the input defined for its associated input field recorded in SERVICE.INPUT.NAME. The types of inputs are as follows:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">COMPUTED – This type is either a direct input argument to the Component Service operation or a link consists of applications and fields.</p>
                <p value="2">DEFAULT – This type is to use the default value used from the environment (from I_COMMON etc.)</p>
                <p value="3">CONST – This type is used to capture a constant value from the user at design time and use it.</p>
            </p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.NAME.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the name of the job that triggers the event when the Exit Point type is TSA.SERVICE</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.OPERATION.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This is an associate multiple value field which holds the name of the Component Service operation and its output which is used supply data for the flow at run time. This field and its associated input fields are used only if the FLOW.SOURCE.TYPE is COMPONENT.SERVICE. The Component Service operation and its output argument is separated with ‘&gt;’ character.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.OUTPUT.NAME.1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field holds the name of the job that triggers the event when the Exit Point type is TSA.SERVICE</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.OUTPUT.TYPE.1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This associated sub-value field holds the type of the output argument to its associated service operation recorded in SERVICE.OPERATION.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>This is a no-input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>XSLT.MAPPING</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field allows the entry of a valid XSLT transformation string that will be used prior to calling the event dispatcher.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>