<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IF</product>
<table>IF.INTEGRATION.SERVICE.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESTINATION.PROP</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field defines a property name for which should a value is found in the event record to be used as the destination identifier (activation string in the case of CALLJEE/Event Delivery Service) when delivering the events as JMS messages. If no value could be found in the event record for the field name which is equivalent to what is defined in this field then the default destination identifier from the field “Destination Static” is used.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>Any alphanumeric value with not more than 25 characters length.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESTINATION.STATIC</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field defines a static destination identifier (activation string in the case of CALLJEE/Event Delivery Service) to be used when delivering the events as JMS messages. Usage of this field value is subject to value in related field “Destination Prop”.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p> Any alphanumeric value with not more than 35 characters length.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENTS.BATCH.SIZE</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field defines the number of events to be batched together for delivery within a single transaction. This field is not effective if field “Msg Delivery Mode” is set to “No Batch”.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>Any numeric value within the range of 1 to 9999 (both inclusive).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.BATCH.XML</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field defines whether or not the batched events to be delivered as individual JMS messages (i.e., 1 event = 1 JMS message) or as a single JMS message with a batched XML of events.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>Yes or No</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.DELIVERY.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This field defines the deliver mode which is to be used by the integration service when delivering the events as JMS messages within a single transaction. This field value is used along with values in related fields “Events Batch Size” and “Msg Batch Xml”.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>Following are allowed values with its description:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1"><i>No Batch</i> - The events are delivered individually</p>
                <p value="2"><i>Batch All</i> - All the events, irrespective of event types are batched for delivery</p>
                <p value="3"><i>Batch Event Type</i> - Events of similar type are batched together for delivery</p>
                <p value="4"><i>Batch Event Type Sorted</i> - Events of similar type are batched maintaining the order of the event creation</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.PROP.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p style="font-weight: bold;">Overview</p>
            <p>This multi value field defines the list of names to be used to create properties to set in the JMS message header. For each value in this field, a property would be added to the JMS message header with the value obtained from an equivalent field in the event record.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field.</p>
            <p>Any alphanumeric with not more than 35 characters length.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>