<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>BX</product>
        <title>Safe Deposit Box - Details table</title>
        <table>AA.SDB.BOX</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>AA.SDB.BOX will capture the safety deposit box inventory details i.e., status of the box, rental details, etc. Records will be created automatically by the system based on the configuration done in Safety Deposit Box Entry table. Input function is not allowed.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>AA.SDB.BOX.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the actual box number.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ALTERNATE.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the alternate ID of the box. Alphanumeric, linked to EB.ALTERNATE.KEY. This means user  can access the record by using the alternate id saved in this field. Bank can specify id of record in their legacy system.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the Arrangement ID to which the box is linked. Vetting ARRANGEMENT.ID.</p>
                <p>The field is a No Input, System maintained field. It is Linked to the EB.ALTERNATE.KEY. This means the user will be able to access the record by using the alternate id.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOX.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Box type of the box record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Multi-language T24 description field for each box.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>KEY.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a Multi-value field that holds the Key numbers pertaining to the box.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Alphanumeric characters may be entered in this field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LOCATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the physical location details of the box.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Multi-lingual free text may be entered in this field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the current status of the Box.</p>
                <p>The field contains drop down options from AA.SDB.STATUS virtual table (EB.LOOKUP) where the user can define their own status. However the following system defined status are released. Available, Rented, Reserved and Maintenance.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>If the status is changed manually by the user, then only the below status changes below are permitted.</p>
                <p>• Available -&gt; Maintenance / Reserved</p>
                <p>• Reserved -&gt; Available / Maintenance</p>
                <p>• Maintenance -&gt; Available / Reserved.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
