<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>BX</product>
        <title>Safe Deposit Box - Entry table</title>
        <table>AA.SDB.BOX.ENTRY</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table will define and maintain different box types for Safe Deposit Box. AA.SDB.BOX.ENTRY will capture the number of Safe Deposit Boxes to be made available in a branch/bank for each box type. A record will have to be created for each company in order for the system to make those boxes available for rent in the respective company. Reverse function is not available.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>AA.SDB.BOX.ENTRY.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It Specifies the Company in which boxes are to be made available.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Should be a valid company id.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOX.START.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the start sequence number of the Box id’s pertaining to a Box type. The Box start sequence cannot overlap with other box numbers i.e. every box at the branch will have a unique number. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>A maximum of 6 Alphanumeric characters may be entered in this field. The field is mandatory.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOX.TOTAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the Total number of boxes to be made available for the Box type. The Total number of boxes captured in BOX.TOTAL can be increased but cannot be decreased after the record has been authorized. When the Box total is increased new records in AA.SDB.BOX will be created for the incremental value.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>A maximum of 6 Alphanumeric characters can be entered. The field is mandatory.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOX.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It Specifies the Box type e.g. small, medium and large. The field is vetted via the EB.LOOKUP. This is a multi-value field associated with fields BOX.START.NO and BOX.TOTAL. Values in the  BOX.TYPE field cannot be deleted or modified after the record has been authorized.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory input when BOX.START.NO or BOX.TOTAL is defined.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Multi-language T24 description field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
