<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AB</product>
        <table>AA.ARR.PRODUCT.BUNDLE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>Defines the participants of the bundle and indicates the mandatory and optional participants. At the designer level, only defines the 'blueprint' of the composition of this bundle. The actual arrangement references would be allowed only at the arrangement level.The condition also links the participants with the INTEREST.COMPENSATION property condition.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MANDATORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the product is mandatory for the bundle to operate. If the product is marked mandatory, the customer who opts for this bundle SHOULD have atleast one arrangement belonging to this product. Otherwise, the customer is considered to be 'ineligible' for this bundle product. As many mandatory products can be stated as part of the definition. For example, the definition could insist on 'atleast' 2 savings accounts product for the bundle in which case, there would be 2 multi-values where this would be flagged as YES for the same product group.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. YES - indicates whether arrangement of this group should exist for this customer for the user to become eligible to take this bundle</p>
                <p>2. No - indicates it is not mandatory to state an arrangement for this product. But, may be stated if the customer has one.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MASTER.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the INTEREST.COMPENSATION property which is linked to this bundle. Only one master could be defined(if more than one Arrangement exists) and the arrangement against which the master is stated is assumed to be the Recipient or beneficiary arrangement in this bundle setup. All other participants are assumed to be donors.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Should be a valid property of INTEREST.COMPENSATION class</p>
                <p>2. Property should belong to the current bundle product</p>
                <p>3. Only one master type definition allowed</p>
                <p>4. One master definition should exist in this condition</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: - </p>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together </p>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Negotiation rules may be defined as a standard types in EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON. And those types may be used in this field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type". For example, if the rule is not to allow a value to go below 10, then the Value of 10 has to be stated in this field and together with NR.TYPE would evaluate the rule.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will hold two values either DUE, CAPITALISE or DEFER. This Field denote which application method(DUE or CAPITALISE)should be taken while applying periodic rule charges. DEFER would not make anything DUE immediately. An option may be stated to define how long to defer.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will have to accept a valid T24 period.The field indicates the period which is used for Evaluation of a rule. For example: If a field should not be allowed to increase more than 10000 with in a period of 1M, the field would actually hold the "1M" value.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken.</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is defined the product designer and validated during publishing.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p>Error - Blocks further processing </p>
                <p>Override - Gives an override </p>
                <p>Information - Records details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken(basically for Interest processing during COB)</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>(basically for Interest processing during COB)</p>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Bundle Definition is enhanced to allow specification of participating arrangements at their Product level.</p>
                <p>Ex, if a Notional Pooling allows only a certain type of “Checking Account” to be participants, then an existing Normal Current Account might need to be changed to “Checking Account” product before it can be added to a Bundle</p>
                <p>In the example above, both “Checking Account” and “Normal Current Account” will be part of the ‘Current Accounts’ Product Group.</p>
                <p>However, in the Bundle condition, instead of specifying this product group, we would instead, specify ‘Checking Account’ in a new field that can accept a valid AA Product.</p>
                <p>This new field will be mutually exlcusive to the existing Product Group field. Either the Product Group or a Product should be required</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the list of product groups that form part of this bundle product. If a customer needs to  have certain products mandatorily, then they may be flagged as MANDATORY and a customer cannot participate in a bundle if the pre-requisite is not met.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory field</p>
                <p>2. Should be a valid entry in AA.PRODUCT.GROUP</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Relevant only at the ""Arrangement"" level and cannot be defined during the 'designer' stage. When a bundle arrangement is drawn for a customer, this field would indicate the related arrangement references for the product group mentioned above. System would not allow a duplicate on this field. The field would link the various arrangement references and form a bundle under this arrangement. System would automatically update the AA.ARRANGEMENT record of stated arrangements with bundle references. The field arrangement which has the MASTER.TYPE defined against it is considered as the ""Recipient"" and all other arrangements are considered to be ""Donors"". The property to pool the balances to are defined in the INTEREST.COMPENSATION property defined as part of MASTER.TYPE field.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory input when the associated field is flagged as MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Duplicates not allowed</p>
                <p>Arrangement should belong to the group defined in the associated set</p>
                <p>Input allowed only at the Arrangement level.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. This is system maintained and is crucial for Reverse and Replay functionality. This field indicates which attributes have undergone a change in this instance. The difference between this field in NEGOTIATED.FLDS is that the latter would hold ALL the negotiations that have happened till this moment and CHANGED.FIELDS would only hold the negotiated fields for that activity.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p>RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for ex : CHANGE.PRODUCT) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p>NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p>The overall definition may be stated as RESETTING and certain individual attributes may be set to NON-RESETTING as well. This could be done using the NR.ATTRIBUTE fields.</p>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not. The overall definition may be stated as NON-NEGOTIABLE and certain individual attributes may be set to NEGOTIABLE as well. This could be done using the NR.ATTRIBUTE fields.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
                <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
