<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MD</product>
<table>MD.ADVICES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>                      MD ADVICES </p>
            <p>This file controls which activities will produce delivery output and the format of that output for different categories of contract. </p>
            <p>This control is made at category code level.  Therefore, separate records defining the output required, and, the format of that output may be entered for each category used within the Miscellaneous Deals module. </p>
            <p>However, the output format required for some categories will be the same as for others.  Therefore this file allows a given category to use the format definitions of a secondary category.  This eliminates the need to duplicate format details for similar categories of contract. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SPARE.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USED.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the category codes that are using this categories details. </p>
            <p>Rather than set up the same data on a number of different records one MD.ADVICES record can be pointed to another using the USE.RECORD field.  This field contains a list of records pointing to the current one. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated Multi valued field. No input allowed.</p>
            <p>Record cannot be reversed unless this field is null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.RECORD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the MD.ADVICES record that this category will use instead of setting up the data here. </p>
            <p>Rather than set up the same data on a number of different records this field allows the user to point a MD.ADVICES record to another MD.ADVICES record and use the MESSAGE/ACTIVITY.CODE, MESSAGE.TYPE and FORMAT for that record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 5 numeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be present on MD.ADVICES.</p>
            <p>No input allowed unless ACTIVITY.CODE, MESSAGE.TYPE and USED.BY are all null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Miscellaneous Deals activity code. </p>
            <p>This field is used by miscellaneous Deals to link a particular Activity to a particular DE.MESSAGE record and a particular format. </p>
            <p>For example if the MD.ADVICES record is set up as follows: </p>
            <p>2.1       ACTIVITY.CODE    100 3.1       MESSAGE.TYPE    2900 4.1       FORMAT             1 2.2       ACTIVITY.CODE    101 3.2       MESSAGE.TYPE    2320 4.2       FORMAT             1 Then when a MD.DEAL is input (activity code 101) an advice based on the DE.MESSAGE record 2320 will be sent to delivery with the format ID of 2320.1.1.GB (assuming it is an English language customer). </p>
            <p>On the other hand when charges are raised against the deal (activity code 100) an advice based on the DE.MESSAGE record 2900 (charge confirmations) will be sent to delivery with the format ID of 2900.100.1.GB. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 4 alphanumeric characters. Multi values field associated with fields 3.1 MESSAGE.TYPEand 4.1 FORMAT. Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be present on the MD.ACTIVITY file.</p>
            <p>No input allowed if the USE.RECORD field is not null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the category code to which the record applies. </p>
            <p>This field identifies the category code whose delivery output is controlled by this record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>Must be a calid category code on the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid miscellaneous deal category code as defined on the MD.PARAMETER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the applications format that will be used for printing of the Advice. </p>
            <p>This field is used by Miscellaneous Deals to link a particular Activity to a particular format print within a DE MESSAGE TYPE. </p>
            <p>For example if the MD.ADVICES record is set up as follows: </p>
            <p>2.1       ACTIVITY.CODE    100 3.1       MESSAGE.TYPE    2900 4.1       FORMAT             1 2.2       ACTIVITY.CODE    101 3.2       MESSAGE.TYPE    2320 4.2       FORMAT             1 Then when a MD.DEAL is input (activity code 101) an advice based on the DE.MESSAGE record 2320 will be sent to delivery with the format ID of 2320.1.1.GB (assuming it is an English language customer). On the other hand when charges are raised against the deal (activity code 100) an advice based on the DE.MESSAGE record 2900 (charge confirmations) will be sent to delivery with the format ID of 2900.1.1.GB. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 4 alphanumeric characters. Multi values field associated with fields 2.1 ACTIVITY.CODE and 3.1 MESSAGE.TYPE (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the DE.MESSAGE record. </p>
            <p>This field is used by miscellaneous Deals to link a particular Activity to a particular DE.MESSAGE record. </p>
            <p>For example if the MD.ADVICES record is set up as follows: </p>
            <p>2.1       ACTIVITY.CODE    100 3.1       MESSAGE.TYPE    2900 4.1       FORMAT             1 2.2       ACTIVITY.CODE    101 3.2       MESSAGE.TYPE    2320 4.2       FORMAT             1 </p>
            <p>Then when a MD.DEAL is input (activity code 101) an advice based on the DE.MESSAGE record 2320 will be sent to delivery with the format ID of 2320.1.1.GB (assuming it is an English language customer). On the other hand when charges are raised against the deal (activity code 100) an advice based on the DE.MESSAGE record 2900 (charge confirmations) will be sent to delivery with the format ID of 2900.1.1.GB. </p>
            <p>When details are to be input for Category this dada must be entered for all four activities: </p>
            <p>100       Charge Confirmation 101       Confirmation of a New Deal 102       Amendment of a Deal 103       Cancellation of a Deal </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 4 alphanumeric characters. Multi valued field associated with fields 2.1 ACTIVITY.CODE and 4.1 FORMAT. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be present on the DE.MESSAGE file.</p>
            <p>No input allowed if the USE.RECORD is not null.</p>
            <p>There must be a multi value set for all four activities.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPARE.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

