<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MD</product>
<table>MD.CSN.RATE.CHANGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>MD.CSN.RATE.CHANGE</p>
            <p>The commission rate input for various Deals under the relevant DEAL.SUB.TYPE and CATEGORY, may be changed using MD.CSN.RATE.CHANGE. The Id is the REVISION.DATE. This date signifies the date on which the change of commission rate will be processed. This is an End of Day activity and applies the new rate only on live contracts and those that are yet to mature, in other words the status is CUR and Maturity date is a future date, as on the date of processing.</p>
            <p>An EFFECTIVE.DATE is mandatory signifying the date from which this change has to take effect. This, at point of time can not be greater than the REVISION.DATE. This date may however be back dated. If so, an option is available to define as to whether the rate change has to take a retrospective effect or not.</p>
            <p>Other valid inputs are DEAL.SUB.TYPE, CATEGORY and COMM.RATE. Importantly these should have been defined in the MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION. Thus the pre-condition for MD.CSN.RATE.CHANGE is its definition in MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DEAL.SUB.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>DEAL.SUB.TYPE</p>
            <p>A valid Deal sub type as specified in the MD.PARAMTER (E.g.. GTISS, PBOND...) that will be selected as filter for rate change.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid entry in MD.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETRO.EFFECT</field>
<desc>
            <p>RETRO.EFFECT</p>
            <p>Decision field for retrospective application of revised commission rate for deals entered on or after the date specified in EFFECTIVE.FROM field and whose status is 'CUR'.</p>
            <p>If set to YES, all deals on the date of revision, which have the maturity date since then, are selected based on the other conditions set and are applied with the new rate. </p>
            <p>The customer account is debited or credited depending on the new rate. However, if Tax has already been debited and the resultant effect is credit to customer' account, then no portion relating to the Tax would be adjusted.</p>
            <p>In case it is a Deal with Participation, then retrospective effect will not be made available. However, the change would take effect from the date of commencement of next schedule.</p>
            <p>If set to NO, retrospective effect will be take place.</p>
            <p>Either way, all Deals along with MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION will be updated with the new commission rate.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input YES or NO</p>
            <p>No retrospective effect will be made available for Participated Deal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will accept the valid MD id for this new commission rate can be set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFFECTIVE.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>EFFECTIVE.FROM</p>
            <p>This represents the date from which the revised rate is effective. All deals entered on or after this date and having its maturity date greater than the revision date (Id date) will be selected for processing.</p>
            <p>The Id of this table which is the REVISION.DATE represents the date on which this rate change will be processed as an End of Day job.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Cannot be greater than the Revision date (Id date).</p>
            <p>Must be a valid date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVISION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which record will be processed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.COMM.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will accept the commission rate for the MD id given in the DEAL.ID field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>CATEGORY</p>
            <p>A valid category code and with in the range as specified in the MD.PARAMETER for the corresponding DEAL.SUB.TYPE.</p>
            <p>This field along with COMM.RATE are associated multi-values.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid code in the CATEGORY Table.</p>
            <p>Must be defined in the MD.PARAMETER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>COMM.RATE</p>
            <p>The revised commission rate to be applied for the deals falling under the specified CATEGORY.</p>
            <p>This field and CATEGORY are associated multi-values.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must hold a rate in MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION under this CATEGORY and       DEAL.SUB.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

