<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MD</product>
<table>MD.DEAL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW OF MISCELLANEOUS DEALS - MAIN FILE </p>
            <p>The Miscellaneous Deals module provides the facility to record deals which are off balance sheet. The principal amounts involved are booked as contingent entries. Facilities are provided for making charges and printing advices and confirmations. Limit checking is supported. </p>
            <p>In the event of participation entered in the Deal, the same may be recorded to the extent of participation. Although when a Deal is participated, movement of principal is not permitted, yet when ASSET.LIAB.NETTING is set to YES, such a movement of principal would be permitted. Such a flag also decides the amount for which contingent entry would be raised either for the Deal amount or to the extent of T24 Bank's participation. </p>
            <p>Charges maybe taken online or scheduled for a future date. Whenever, an event is scheduled for a future date in MD, the system updates the same in a file MD.SCHEDULES.</p>
            <p>Concurrently, where the User chooses to collect commission the same is permitted. The option on collection of these, however remains with the user. Charge and Commission collection are mutually exclusive. Tax may also be attached to such a Charge or Commission.</p>
            <p>In relation to commission, it can either be taken upfront or at the end of the Contract. The system either amortizes or accrues the same in the frequency as defined in the parameter. This scheduling of Commission can either be in terms of manual schedule or defined as a  frequency. It is but imperative that Commission debit account is always in the Deal currency.</p>
            <p>This commission may either be taken as a percentage of a fixed amount. When set as a percentage, the option to input a spread is available. By defining the appropriate MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION, it is possible to define a minimum commission amount for a Deal. This definition can also be done currency-wise.</p>
            <p>As MD, can be used for issuance of Guarantee, the system permits the user to collect Cash Margin for the same. Such a Cash Margin may be collected at the time of positive principal movement or any time online. </p>
            <p>In the event of a Principal decrease, the system permits release of cash margin on the event date. Release of provision (Cash Margin) could be carried out online or any future date as well.</p>
            <p>Such a cash margin, maybe taken in a currency different from that of the Deal currency and maybe parked in an account of different currency. An option to define a default MD Margin account is available in the parameter. In the event of such a margin taken, the user may choose to decide as the whether such margin should have an impact on the limit line or not.</p>
            <p>The commission input in the Deal is not changeable, however by defining the Deal Sub Type and the Category, the rate change may be effected through the application MD.CSN.RATE.CHANGE. It also enables a retrospective rate change. </p>
            <p>The support to MT760, MT767, MT768 and MT769 is available. </p>
            <p>In the event of a Guarantee being requested to be issued by a correspondent Bank, an option is available to impact the limit of Correspondent Bank, besides the applicant customer.</p>
            <p>Invocation of guarantee is supported along with the requisite messaging, appropriating the Provision and the share of participation if any. Where the invocation results in overdraft of a customer account, the PD link has been provided.</p>
            <p>Although the contingent entries are generated at End of Day, there is an option to trigger the same online. This when set, generates the movement entries at Start of Day. The maturity however is done only at End of Day.</p>
            <p>If MD, were to be used to issue a shipping guarantee, the system supports appropriation of Cash margin taken in LC into that of MD. The requisite LC reference and the appropriation amount has to be decided by the user. Thus when a Drawing is done under the Letter of Credit, quoting the reference of the MD.DEAL, the system understands the link and generates the accounting accordingly.</p>
            <p>Link to Syndicated Loans:</p>
            <p>When a Guarantee Deal is linked to Syndicated Loans, input of SL ref in the Deal triggers the requisite validations. This link to SL module is enabled only for issue of Guarantee (CA) type. Firstly, Facility should have been marked as available and its status is set as CUR. The customer of the MD.DEAL should have been defined as that of Facility or one of its allowed Customers. The currency defined in the Deal, should either be a permitted currency of the Facility or should not have been defined as a restricted currency. On input of amount, the system validates, the permitted or available amount in the referred Tranche of the Facility and this validation also caters to the exposure of each of the participants if exist in the Facility. Likewise the Date of the Deal cannot be prior to start of the Tranche Date under which it is drawn. Currently no Principal movement is permitted for such linked Deals.</p>
            <p>If charges were to be taken, the same is permissible only in cases where a linked deal is devoid of Participants. In cases, where participation exists in these Deals, the charges are to be collected from SL charges.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>When linked the Commission shall always be that of End type and the rate for the Deal currency would either be picked up Facility if found to be of the same currency, if not as defined in SL.FACI.RATES. The user has the option to amend the system defaulted rate. The commission shall always be collected as a frequency as defined in the Facility for Interest (</p>
            <p>INT.DUE.DATE</p>). In the event of tax being defined in the Facility, the same is defaulted in Tax key. The limit line shall also be impacted as defined in the relevant Facility. The accrual of commission shall continue to happen as it does for a normal deal with participation. In cases where a participant needs to be added to the Deal, it is imperative that such details are already incorporated in the Facility. In the event of Deal, being participated, the <p>ASSET.LIAB.NETTING</p> field shall always be defaulted to YES. The <p>NET.PRIN.AMOUNT</p> shall always denote the own Bank component of the Facility. <p /><p /><p>Although, in the event of Facility having its share of Participants, the MD.DEAL, may be amended to hold the share in a proportion different from that of the Facility. The default however, would be the distribution of Deal amount in the same ratio as in Facility. But at all times the exposure shall validate against the relevant files in the SL module, viz., SL.EXPOSURE.LEVEL, SL.FACI.BALANCES and SL.FACI.PART.BALANCES.</p><p /><p /><p>It is important to note that the field </p><p>SL.FUNCTION</p> in the PRE.SYNDICATION.FILE determines the permit of Own Banks share in the Deal. The Deal currency and Deal amounts of Guarantee shall comply with the <p>TR.MAX.LOANS, TR.MAX.CURRENCY, DD.MULT.AMOUNT, DD.MIN.AMOUNT</p> and <p>DD.MAX.AMOUNT</p> as defined under the said Tranche of the Facility. <p /></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies each separate delivery produced by T24 in connection with the miscellaneous deal. </p>
            <p>This field will hold all the identies of any advices produced by the delivery system in connection with the deal. </p>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with the ADVICE.TYPE field which holds the key to the MD.ADVICES record for each delivery advice the identity of which is recorded here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Internally generated multi valued field Multi value field associated with field 30.1 Advice Type. (No input allowed)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.BENEFICIARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The beneficiary of the current invocation claim . If left blank, will be defaulted with the customer ID of the INV.SETTLE.ACCOUNTwhen invocation pay method is 'Internal'. </p>
            <P>To generate 59F tag in MT103 and MT202C, address must be defined in following format.</P>
            <P>/1235674              - Account Number</P>
            <p>1/DAVID WARNER        - Beneficiary Name</p>
            <p>2/1000 QUARRY LAKE DR - Beneficiary Address</p>
            <p>3/US/SEATTLE          - Beneficiary Country and Town</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid Customer ID or SWIFT&#160;BIC or any free text.</p> <![CDATA[  ]]></desc>
            <p>Account number should start with '/' for 59F format</p>
            <p>First line should start with '1/' (ie) name of beneficiary for 59F format</p>
            <p>Address is not mandatory. It may or maynot have occurrence with '2/' for 59F format.</p>
            <p>If address is inputted then country code is mandatory (ie)'3/' for 59F format</p>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.REL.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROV.REL.ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>The account into which Cash Margin will be credited when released. The input account may be of any Currency. This is defaulted with PROV.DR.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid account in the ACCOUNT Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MOVEMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the date value for the principal movement entered in PRIN.MOVEMENT occurs. </p>
            <p>The contract principal amount is changeable throughout the life of the contract.  Once the value date has been passed the actual PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT field becomes a no-change field. </p>
            <p>All principal movements are then entered in the PRIN.MOVEMENT field and update the PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT during the end of day for the MOVEMENT.DATE. </p>
            <p>Any number of principal movements can be entered but with the following constraint:  If more than one movement is entered they must be entered in value date order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date format. Multi-valued field associated with field 15.1 PRIN.MOVEMENT recording the value dates of the movements entered. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>The MOVEMENT.DATE cannot be before the VALUE.DATE.</p>
            <p>The MOVEMENT.DATE cannot be after the MATURITY.DATE.</p>
            <p>An override is required if the MOVEMENT.DATE is a non-working day.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIN.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to allow the user to change the deal PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT during the lifetime of the deal. </p>
            <p>The deal PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT is changeable throughout the life of the deal. </p>
            <p>However, once the Value Date has been passed then the actual PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT field becomes a "no change" field. </p>
            <p>All principal movements to be entered after the WE.DATE use this field.  Any number of principal movements may be entered but with the constraint that the outstanding principal can never fall below zero, i.e. an asset can never become a liability and vice versa. </p>
            <p>Each PRIN.MOVEMENT is linked to a MOVEMENT.DATE.  The PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT being changed according to the PRIN.MOVEMENT during the day end of the MOVEMENT.DATE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point, minus sign and comma's. Multi valued field of principal movements associated with field 14.1 MOVEMENT.DATE. Decreases will be prefixed with a minus sign. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CURR</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency in which the charges detailed in the fields CHARGE.DATE, CHARGE.ACCOUNT, CHARGE.CODE and CHARGE.AMT are taken. </p>
            <p>Charges can be defined on any date provided it is not before the deal VALUE.DATE or after the MATURITY.DATE. All charges for a given date must be taken in the same currency and debited to the same account. Charges can be taken in any currency provided that the account to be debited is in the CHARGE.CURR. Any taxes on the charges will be debited to the CHARGE.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>The charges will be debited during the end of day of the CHARGE.DATE except when the CHARGE.DATE is before the next working day in which case they will be taken on line. Once this has happened the charge details will be removed from the 'live' record but can be seen by looking into the balances file. </p>
            <p>NB, If a deal is reversed, relevant charges taken will be reversed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-value field containing the currencies in which         charges are to be processed and debited to the customer.         3 alphabetic currency mnemonic or 1 - 3 numeric character         currency code. (Optional input but must be input in         conjunction with the fields CHARGE.DATE, CHARGE.ACCOUNT,         CHARGE.CODE and CHARGE.AMT).</p>
            <p>The currency code or mnemonic must exist on the CURRENCY         table.</p>
            <p>The CHARGE.ACCOUNT must be in the same currency as the         CHARGE.CURR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPLIT.COMMISSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>SPLIT.COMMISSION</p>
            <p>If this field is set to YES, the calculated commission will be split into two parts, one proportionate to the leader's share in the Deal that is reflected in the P&amp;L and the other will be credited to the Internal account as specified in the MD.PARAMETER (Field PART.CSN.ACC). </p>
            <p>If set to NO, the entire commission, including that relating to the Participants will move into the P&amp;L. </p>
            <p>If set to NULL, the flow would be that of NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.UPD.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether limits are to be updated or not. </p>
            <p>The interface to limits can be controlled both at the contract and parameter level. At the module parameter level fields are provided to control the use of limits with contingent and memorandum contract types. Via these fields the user can specify if the interface to limits is mandatory, optional or not allowed for these products. The fields used on MD.PARAMETER that do this are: </p>
            <p>CONT.LIMIT.LINK Can be Mandatory, Optional or Noinput. MEMO.LIMIT.LINK Can be Mandatory, Optional or Noinput. CL.LIMIT.LINK Can be Mandatory, Optional or Noinput. ML.LIMIT.LINK Can be Mandatory, Optional or Noinput. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to YES then limit processing will be perfomed and the limit type define in LIMIT.PARAMETER will be used. </p>
            <p>If set to No then no processing is done. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must either be 'YES' or 'NO' Default of No is used         when limits are set to Noinput in MD.PARAMETER</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.EXPIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>AUTO.EXPIRY</p>
            <p>Deal level decision field for controlling the expiry of the Deal past its Maturity date. Effectively the reversal of Contingent entries are controlled by this field.</p>
            <p>If set to YES, the Deal will expire on the date specified in the MATURITY.DATE. If set to NO, the STATUS of the Deal will be held as 'CUR' even past the Maturity Date.</p>
            <p>Defaults from EXPIRY.MODE in the MD.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCLUDE.PROVISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>INCLUDE.PROVISION</p>
            <p>Deal level decision to control the impact of Cash Margin on the corresponding limit.</p>
            <p>If set to YES, the impact on the limit will be reduced to the extent of Cash Margin taken in the Deal, proportionate to the Leader's portion.</p>
            <p>If set to NO, irrespective of any Cash Margin taken in the Deal, the limit line would reflect the entire amount of the Leader's portion.</p>
            <p>Will default the value from INCLUDE.PROVISION set in the MD.PARAMETER. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SENDER.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>SENDER.INFO</p>
            <p>Sender to Receiver Information.</p>
            <p>This field relates to Tag 72 of MT760 and MT767.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CB.LIMIT.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This switch will determine whether correspondent bank limit also should be updated or not for this contract.</p>
            <p />YES, would update and NO would not. User can override.<p /><p>This field will open up only when EXT.LIMIT details are defined in LIMIT.PARAMETER for MD application.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALTERNATE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ALTERNATE.ID</p>
            <p>An Alternate Identification for the Deal. This can be used to retrieve the Deal for amendment.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Cannot be duplicated across Deals.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.REQD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows user to decide whether they wish to produce any advices associated with this deal. </p>
            <p>This field allows the user to suppress any advices that would otherwise be produced over the lifetime of the deal. </p>
            <p>If this field is set to 'NO' then no advices will be produced. </p>
            <p>If it is set to 'YES' then a subset of the following advices will be produced in association with the deal during its lifetime. </p>
            <p>1         Confirmation of Deal 2         Amendment of Deal 3         Cancellation of Deal 4         Charge confirmations </p>
            <p>Contract confirmation will be produced only on initial input of the contract and cancellation confirmations only when a contract is reversed. Contract amendment confirmations will be produced whenever the contract principal is amended, i.e. when a principal increase or decrease is entered on the deal.  It is important to note that this advice is produced when the amendment is made and not on the value date of the actual movement.  Therefore, if a second principal movement is entered before the first has reached its value date both movements will appear on the confirmation.  Similarly, whenever the maturity date is amended an amendment confirmation will be produced. </p>
            <p>Charge advices will be produced whenever charges are debited, i.e. on the charge value date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input of 'YES' or 'NO' only. (Defaults to 'YES')</p>
            <p>Only input 'YES' or 'NO' allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.RECV.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field is used to specify the bank where the funds are to be remitted.  Free text field. Accepts </p>
            <p> customer number or SW-XXXXXXXX (for SWIFT message) or any free text (for PRINT message) .</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory if INV.INTER.BANK is input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.FORWARD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>BACK.FORWARD.KEY</p>
            <p>Opens up only if CSN.FREQUENCY is used. The date of application of commission will be based on the value of this field. If the date of application of commission as per the CSN.FREQUENCY is a holiday, this field controls the option to determine the date on which commission is to be collected.</p>
            <p>When set to 1, Calendar day will be used.</p>
            <p>When set to 2, Next working day will be used.</p>
            <p>When set to 3, Previous working day will be used.</p>
            <p>The default will however be Calendar day.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input 1, 2 or 3.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount invoked by the Beneficiary. Expressed in terms of the deal </p>
            <p />currency.<p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Standard Amount field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>REL.AMT</p>
            <p>The Cash Margin to be released for the Negative Principal movement at LD.PRN.MVMT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input only when there is a negative PRIN.MOVEMENT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.MARGIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to input the amount of Cash Margin collected from Letter of Credit, into the Guarantee and is represented in terms of the MD.DEAL currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Cannot be more than the Cash Margin outstanding in the referred LC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.OF.CHGS</field>
<desc>
            <p>AMT.OF.CHARGES</p>
            <p>This field specifies the currency code and the total amount of charges claimed by the Sender of the message.</p>
            <p>This relates to Tag 32a of MT769.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the LIMIT REFERENCE number to be checked for Limit control. </p>
            <p>If LIMIT.UPD.REQD is 'NO' then this field will be a no- input field and limits will not be called.  See help text for field LIMIT UPD REQD as to how that field can be set up. </p>
            <p>If input is allowed and no input is made in this field the Limits System will provide a default according to the LIMIT.PARAMETER.FILE.  It will look for the PRODUCT.NO  defined under the MD.DEAL.application. </p>
            <p>The credit line number generated will be NNNN-01 where NNNN is the ID of the Limit Reference record described above. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 10 characters for a LIMIT REFERENCE code. Input only allowed if LIMIT.UPD.REQD field is equal to 'YES' otherwise no input. (Optional Input, Default value seel details below)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid reference on the LIMIT Reference table.</p>
            <p>If no Limit exists for the counterparty a corresponding error message will be displayed by the system with an override facility.</p>
            <p>If the transaction amount exceeds the availability amount of the Limit, a corresponding error message will be displayed with an override facility.</p>
            <p>An override is required if the deal VALUE.DATE is before the limit start date.</p>
            <p>An override is required if the line expires prior to the deal final maturity date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.PAYMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>At contract level the commission amount payable or receivable can be set to be levied at the beginning (BEGIN) of the commission period or the end (END) of the commission period.</p>
            <p>The commission period is defined by the start of the contract and the end of the contract with optional interim dates specified by the user. If commission is defined then there must be either a schedule for the start date (for BEGIN contracts) or at maturity (for END contracts).</p>
            <p>Where it is set to END:</p>
            <p>Accruals are passed to a P/L category according to the cycling frequency and the customer is debited (or credited according to deal type) at the end of the period. For the bank the effect of the P/L is built up over the life of the contract rather than one lump payment at the end.</p>
            <p>Where it is set to BEGIN:</p>
            <p>Accruals are passed to a P/L category according to the cycling frequency and the customer is debited (or credited according to deal type) at the start of the period. This amount is then left in an advance P/L account and then dripped through to the real P/L. This gives the same effect of the P/L build up over the life of the contract as the END method.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>BEGIN - payment in advance</p>
            <p>END - payment in arrears</p>
            <p>Default is END</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICABLE.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field have been used to define the rule under which the guarantee is subjected to. only four types viz URDG, URCG, NONE, and OTHR can be inputted in this field.                          If OTHR is inputted in this field and the rule under which the gurantee inputted is issued, should be inputted in the Narrative field and it should not exceed 35 characters.                                             If URDG, URCG, and NONE are inputted in this field, then Narrative field should be left as blank.   APPLICABLE.RULE and NARRATIVE are being mapped for Swift tag 40C of MT760</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REINSTATE.CONTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the liquidated Guarantee has to be re-instated to live status.</p>
            <p>Field will allow user input when the status of the contract is 'LIQ'.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Valid option is 'YES'.</p>
            <p>Allowed only for automatically liquidated Guarantees with outstanding principal amount.</p>
            <p>Not allowed for Syndicated Guarantees.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.CR.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROV.CR.ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>The account into which Cash Margin will be credited. This account could be a NOSTRO as well and can be of any currency. If the account is not specified, the default will be an Internal account in the Deal currency (the account category as specified in the MD.PARAMETER ).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid account in the ACCOUNT Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.RECALC.ST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Specifies the date from which the periodic commission is to be recalculated on reinstatement.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Standard date format.</p>
                <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Allowed only for Guarantees with commission defined.</p>
                <p value="3" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Value cannot be less than old maturity date of Guarantee or greater than Today.</p>
                <p value="4" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Must be a valid date between previous commission end date and reinstatement date.</p>
                <p value="5" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Default value will be previous commission end date.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.AMT.ACY</field>
<desc>
            <p><strong>Commission Schedule</strong>
            </p>
            <p><strong>PARTICIPANT</strong>
            </p>
            <p>Participant of the guarantee issued</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid customer</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.CHANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>A number generated automatically by the system which identifies either a statement entry or a category entry in respect of a contract. </p>
            <p>Whenever charges are debited to the customer accounts Miscellaneous Deals will raise accounting entries,.  The IDs of these entries both STMT.ENTRY and CATEG.ENTRY, consist of a date- time stamp and a sequence number.  All entries raised by a particular transaction will have the same date-time stamp but different sequence numbers. </p>
            <p>This field has multi values that are linked in groups of three.  The first contains the base date-time stamp which is common to all entries, the second the sequence numbers of the STMT.ENTRY raised and the third the sequence numbers of any CATEG.ENTRYs. </p>
            <p>An example will illustrate the field more clearly: </p>
            <p>A miscellaneous deal is debited charges from a customer account which are credited to P/L.  The system will generate a statement entry and record the ID of this entry as follows: </p>
            <p>37.1      STMT.NO             673732684.48 37.2      STMT.NO             1 37.3      STMT.NO             1 </p>
            <p>The number automatically generated in field 37.1 is unique to the deal in question and is build in the following way: </p>
            <p>1         The first four digits '6737' indicate the number of days           since 1st of January 1968. </p>
            <p>          In our example it corresponds to the 11th of June 1986. </p>
            <p>2         The next five digits '32684' indicate the number of           seconds since midnight. </p>
            <p>          In our example it corresponds to an entry generated on           line at 09:04:44 </p>
            <p>3         The last two digits '48' indicate the number of           hundredths of seconds. </p>
            <p>The value assigned (again automatically) to field 37.2 identifies the number of in fielf 37.1 as a statement entry number.  This entry can be seen via the STMT.ENTRY application using the ID: </p>
            <p>          673732684.480001 </p>
            <p>The suffix '0001' identifies it as the first statement entry. </p>
            <p>Similarly there will be an entry on the CATEG.ENTRY as there is a value in field 37.3.  The ID will be: </p>
            <p>          673732684.48001 </p>
            <p>To view these entries the STMT.ENTRY and the CATEG.ENTRY applications should be used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated multi-valued field. No input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Customer the deal is to be recorded against. </p>
            <p>This is the identification number or mnemonic assigned to the customer, the system will use this number to: </p>
            <p>a)        Identify the customer the miscellaneous deal is to be           recorded against. </p>
            <p>b)        Obtain the Customer's name and address for inclusion           on all contract and advices produced by this module. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 to 10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic or        1 to 6 numeric character customer number (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid CUSTOMER number or mnemonic.</p>
            <p>One the deal has been authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the advice type used by the delivery record identified in the DELIVERY.REF field. </p>
            <p>Miscellaneous Deals produces on of four types of advice: </p>
            <p>100       Charge Confirmation 101       Confirmation of Deal 102       Amendment of Deal 103       Cancellation of Deal </p>
            <p>This field identifies which type of advice was produced by the call to delivery the identity of which is shown in the DELIVERY.REF field associated with this one. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated Multi-valued associated with field 29.1 Delivery.Ref (No input allowed)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains any additional information which has been defined locally to meet a specific local requirement. </p>
            <p>Up to 999 local elements can be defined in addition to Standard Fields previously specified.  Name(s) of the new element(s), as well as format and validation rules must be defined in local tables prior to any input. </p>
            <p>There is currently provision for the first ten local reference fields to be passed to the delivery module. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters as shown in local table definition for this field. (Optional or Mandatory Input as defined in local table for this reference element).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERDUE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the contract is overdue, then this field identifies the status of the  underlying PAYMENT.DUE contract. This is noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SG.ISSUED</field>
<desc>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Specifies whether Shipping Guarantee is issued against LETTER.OF.CREDIT or Import Collection Documents.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Valid options are LC and COLLECTION.</p>
                <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Following options are not allowed to process when the issued guarantee is a Shipping Guarantee:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p style="list-style-type: circle;">
                    <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Principal movements</p>
                    <p value="2" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Forward value date</p>
                    <p value="3" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">EVENTS.PROCESSING as End of Day</p>
                    <p value="4" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Under syndication</p>
                </p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">NO CHANGE field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SL.PROD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This is a system defaulted field when the Deal is linked to SL. The default happens from the Facility referred in the field SL.REF.TRANCHE. </p>
            <p>If a Guarantee were to be linked to SL, this is a mandatory input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should have been defined in the Facility.</p>
            <p>Valid inputs are SC or GT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.PAY.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The payment value date. Defaulted with INV.DR.VALUE.DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be equal to or greater than INV.DR.VALUE.DATE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.BANK.OP.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>SWIFT codes for bank operation (MT103)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid codes are </p>
            <p>CRED,       CRTS, SPAY, SPRI, SSTD</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>CHG.DETAILS</p>
            <p>This field contains the specific details of commission and charges claimed by the Sender. </p>
            <p>This relates to the Tag 71B of MT768</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.NETTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines whether provision collected is to be netted with invocation amount at the time of settlement of invocation claim.</p>
            <p>Entries will be netted only when Guarantee currency and Credit provision account currency are the same.</p>
            <p>Override message will be generated when currencies differ and PROV.NETTING field value will be changed to NO when override is accepted. For example </p>
            <p>Principal Amount USD	100,000; Provision Percentage      20%; Provision Amount	USD 20,000</p>
            <p>Invocation Amount	USD 50,000; Provision Netting	Yes</p>
            <table class="TableStyle-Basic" style="mc-table-style: url('../../../Resources/TableStyles/TemenosTables.css');" cellspacing="0">
                <col style="width: 66px;" class="Column-Column1" />
                <col style="width: 240px;" class="Column-Column1" />
                <col style="width: 113px;" class="Column-Column1" />
                <tbody>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Dr</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Credit Provision Account</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">USD 10,000</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Dr</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Invocation Debit Account</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">USD 40,000</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1">
                        <td class="BodyB-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: right;">Cr</td>
                        <td class="BodyB-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: right;">Invocation Credit Account</td>
                        <td class="BodyA-Column1-Body1" style="text-align: right;">USD 50,000</td>
                    </tr>
                </tbody>
            </table>
            <p>Validations  Rules : </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Acceptable values are Yes or No.</p>
                <p value="2">Value defaulted from PROV.NETTING field in MD.PARAMETER.  User can amend the defaulted value.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUE.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>MD.DEAL allows the participation by other parties in deals, usually on the Issuance of Guarantees for larger amounts. There would typically be a main deal which details the Guarantee issued, the parties who are participating and the commission rates and  dates. Secondary deals relating to the Participation taken by the other parties will be recorded in their name with a share of the commission payable to them. In accounting terms this deal is same as a Guarantee Received with the exception that there are commissions to be paid.</p>
            <p>The Customer entered here is used to identify the client of the main deal. It is not permitted to enter data in this field and the PARTICIPANT or AMT.PARTICIPATE fields at the same time.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid CUSTOMER record</p>
            <p>Cannot be used together with PARTICIPANT or AMT.PARTICIPATE</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROVISION</p>
            <p>Deal level decision field to check if Provision is to be taken for the Deal. When set to YES, the Provision related fields open up, else they are no input fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid inputs are YES or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MD.SCH.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>TAX.AMOUNT</p>
            <p>The tax on commission for the current commission schedule.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PARTICIPANT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The multi-value field contains the T24 Customer(s) who participate in a deal and is used together with the AMT.PARTICIPATE field. Where used the participant amounts will reduce the amount required for Limit purposes.</p>
            <p>This field is only valid for Asset type contracts and is not allowed for Liability contracts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid CUSTOMER record</p>
            <p>Mandatory if AMT.PARTICIPATE field is used</p>
            <p>Not allowed if ISSUE.CUSTOMER has been entered</p>
            <p>Contract must be an Asset type</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.SETTLE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The settlement account into which the invocation amount will be credited. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be a valid account in the ACCOUNT table.</p>
            <p>Cannot belong to the Applicant Customer.</p>
            <p>Cannot be the same as INV.DR.ACCOUNT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENTS.PROCESSING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults from the field in MD.PARAMETER. The user can select either ONLINE or END OF DAY. Based on this selection, the processing of the principal movements and raising contingent entries will proceed. </p>
            <p>If set to ONLINE, </p>
            <p />Limit update, contingent entries etc will happen on line. <p />END OF DAY will continue with the existing functionality of raising contingent , limit update etc during end of day process.<p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any non T24 references which identify the deal for the customer. </p>
            <p>Free format field to allow input of any customer reference of the deal.  Used for information purposes only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 35 free format alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FURTHER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>FURTHER.ID</p>
            <p>This field contains a code word that further identifies the purpose of the message. It can either be:</p>
            <p>ISSUE - When the message is an Issue of Guarantee.</p>
            <p>REQUEST - When the message is requesting an issuance of a Guarantee.</p>
            <p>This field is populated in the Tag 23 of MT760 of SWIFT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field for SWIFT message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate to be used between </p>
            <p />invocation debit <p />account and <p />invocation credit account. <p /><p>Defaults to mid rate of</p><p />Currency Market 1.<p /><p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.INTER.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify an intermediary bank through which funds are to be routed. If this field is entered, input to RE.AC.WITH.BNK is mandatory. Free text field. </p>
            <p />Accepts <p />customer number or SW-XXXXXXXX (for SWIFT message) or any free text (for PRINT message) . <p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Currency the deal is to be recorded in. </p>
            <p>This field indicated the currency of the deal. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alphabetic currency mnemonic or        1 - 3 numeric character currency code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>The currency code or mnemonic must exist on the CURRENCY table.</p>
            <p>Once the deal has been authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIAB.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>LIAB.AMT</p>
            <p>The amount for which the Contingent entries are raised for the Deal. In case the Deal has Participation, this field will hold only the portion relating to the Leader's contribution on the Principal amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.EXPIRY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the actual expiry date of Guarantee.</p>
            <p>Validations Rules:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Standard date format or 1-3 numeric for call/notice contracts.</p>
                <p value="2">Must be greater than value date.</p>
                <p value="3">Must be less than or equal to Maturity date.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accepts any of PROCESS, EXECUTE or CANCEL.</p>
            <p />
            <p />Input allowed only for authorized MD records.<p /><p /><p>The invocation is done two stages. First is the PROCESS stage, where the user can input the invocation details but no accounting entries/limit are raised. When the invocation is in PROCESS stage, the user can either EXECUTE the invocation or CANCEL it. When option EXECUTE is chosen, accounting entries/limit are raised. If CANCEL option is chosen, the invocation fields are cleared. Again no accounting entries/limit are passed.</p><p /><p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Invocation related fields open up only if this holds either PROCESS or       EXECUTE. </p><p>The status can only be PROCESS if the previous value is NULL.</p><p>The status can only be EXECUTE or CANCEL only if the previous value is       PROCESS.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAPITALIZE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>CAPITALIZE.DATE</p>
            <p>In the case of frequency based scheduling (End type), if the maturity date falls within the running commission schedule, the Deal will be kept "LIVE" past the maturity date till the end of the commission schedule. The commission will be booked at the end of the schedule.</p>
            <p>This field opens up to enable booking of commission on a day prior to the end date of the running commission schedule, but after the maturity date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Can be any date past the Maturity date but less than the date in       CSN.FREQUENCY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field enables the user to divert a particular message type to another Address.</p>
            <p>The user has a number of options:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Simple insertion of a name or address. This will re-route the message in     PRINT format to the named party.   </p>
            <p>The code 'TX-' followed by a telex number. This will re-route the message     by TELEX to the number detailed.   </p>
            <p>The code 'SW-' followed by a S.W.I.F.T. code. This will re-route the     message by SWIFT to the respective bank.   </p>
            <p>The code 'C-' followed by a valid customer number or mnemonic. This will     re-route the message in PRINT format to the customer indicated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>50 Alphanumeric character field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The contract identifier. </p>
            <p>The serial number will be assigned automatically if the appropriate option in the company record is set. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>"MD" followed by 10 digits :- YY - Year DDD -         Julian Day 99999 - Sequence No.</p>
            <p>Must be unique.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value date of the deal. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard date format. (Mandatory Input - defaults to current date)</p>
            <p>An override will be required if the date as defined on the HOLIDAY table is a non working day.</p>
            <p>Must be prior to the MATURITY.DATE defined below.</p>
            <p>Once the deal has been authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the actual date the transaction was agreed to by the parties to the deal. </p>
            <p>This field is used to record the date on which the terms of the contract were agreed by the parties concerned.  This date does not affect the processing of the deal and is held for information purposes only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard date format. (Mandatory Input - defaults to current date).</p>
            <p>If a non working day is input an override message will be generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ONLINE.MAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input of YES in this field shall ensure that the maturity of the Guarantee Deal is done Online. This is an input field only if the EVENTS.PROCESSING is set as ONLINE. The Maturity would be treated as TODAY.</p>
            <p>When set Online maturity, the commission accounting entries, Limit reinstatement, Release of Cash Margin are all done online along with liquidation of the Contract.</p>
            <p>Where the commission is Begin type and Manual and if the Deal were not in its last schedule, the User needs to delete all the future schedules. The accounting entries would however be passed for the entire schedule amount.</p>
            <p>Where the commission is End type and Manual and if the Deal were not in its last schedule, the User needs to delete all the future schedules and the CSN.DATE has to be input with Current date. The accounting  entries would however be passed only for the amount accrued till date.</p>
            <p>Thus commission accounting entries passed for the Begin type would always be for the entire current schedule and that of the End type would always be for the Accrued amount.</p>
            <p>When the Commission is set as a frequency, the system would set the CAPITALIZE.DATE as TODAY and the entries would be passed accordingly.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>When set to Online maturity the Deal shall not have any Principal       movements scheduled.</p>
            <p>When set to Online maturity the Deal shall not have any Charges       scheduled for a future date.</p>
            <p>When set to Online maturity the Deal shall not have Invocation set to       Process, Execute or Cancel.</p>
            <p>When set to Online maturity the Deal shall not have its Overdue status       relating to PD.</p>
            <p>Online Maturity shall not take place when the contract is linked to       Syndicated Loans.</p>
            <p>Online Maturity shall not take place where the contract is linked to LC,       but Drawings under the same are yet to be done.</p>
            <p>Online Maturity shall not be permitted for any Forward Deals.</p>
            <p>This field  shall accept either YES or NULL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.EXPOSURE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The country code representing the country where the exposure is deemed to reside. </p>
            <p>The values in this field will be used for country of exposure information purposes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input.  Defaults to COUNTRY.RISK).</p>
            <p>Must be a valid code in the COUNTRY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECV.CORRS.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Free text field to accept the receivers correspondent bank information. Defaulted from AGENCY table corresponding to the Receivers bank or the Beneficiary (if the Beneficiary is a bank). </p>
            <p />Accepts customer number or SW-XXXXXXXX (BIC code for SWIFT message) or any free text (for PRINT message) .  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency Market related to this transaction. </p>
            <p>This field will be applicable where the exchange control authorities have defined different markets for foreign currency dealing. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character Currency Market code (Optional input.  Defaults to default currency market for Miscellaneous Deals module on MU.TXN.GRP.CCY.MKT)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the CURRENCY.MARKET table.</p>
            <p>Once the deal has been authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.SPEC</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field must be used in those instances where the amount of the guarantee and, consequently, the amount released, cannot be expressed in terms of a specific amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>It should contain a description of the amount for which the bank which has issued or</p>
            <p>requested the issuance of the Guarantee is released of all its liability under the</p>
            <p>specified Guarantee.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field cannot co-exist with principal movements.</p>
            <p>Accepts  up to a maximum of 4 lines of  35 A (Alphanumeric)       characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.CSN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.PROV.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>OUTS.PROV.AMT</p>
            <p>Displays the Current Provision amount outstanding for the Deal. This is maintained in the Deal Currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.SECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The tax code applicable for  the charge as defined in FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RE.AC.WITH.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the bank where the funds are to be remitted. Mandatory field if INV.INTER.BANK is input. Free text field. </p>
            <p />Accepts customer number or SW-XXXXXXXX (for SWIFT message) or any free text (for PRINT message) . <p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory if INV.INTER.BANK is input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.PAYMENT.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The valid entries are EXTERNAL, INTERNAL or NOSTRO.</p>
            <p> NOSTRO</p>
            <p><![CDATA[ ]]></p>NOSTRO account .<p /><p /><p>INTERNAL</p><p />Any valid Customer a/c. This customer will be defaulted in field <p /><p /><p>INV.BENEFICIARY</p><p /><p /><p>EXTERNAL</p><p />Any valid <p /><p /><p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Can only be EXTERNAL or INTERNAL or NOSTRO.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELEASE.PROV</field>
<desc>
            <p>RELEASE.PROV</p>
            <p>Decision field for online release of Cash Margin.</p>
            <p>If set to YES, the field RELEASE.AMT opens up.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input YES.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEXT.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any useful extra information about the deal. </p>
            <p>Free format field to allow input of any extra information about the deal that the user feels will be useful.  Used for information purposes only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters for free format text - Type A. Multi value field (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CENTRAL.BANK.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format field. </p>
            <p>The contents of this field to be defined locally. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 10 alphanumeric characters (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When commission has been entered there must be a date or series of dates when the commission will be levied. The validation depends on whether the CSN.PAYMENT.TYPE is entered as BEGIN or END.</p>
            <p>The commission period is defined by the start of the contract and the end of the contract with optional interim dates specified by the user. If commission is defined then there must be either a schedule for the start date (for BEGIN contracts) or at maturity (for END contracts). </p>
            <p>Where it is set to END:</p>
            <p>Accruals are passed to a P/L category according to the cycling frequency and the customer is debited (or credited according to deal type) at the end of the period. For the bank the effect of the P/L is built up over the life of the contract rather than one lump payment at the end.</p>
            <p>Where it is set to BEGIN:</p>
            <p>Accruals are passed to a P/L category according to the cycling frequency and the customer is debited (or credited according to deal type) at the start of the period. This amount is then left in an advance P/L account and then dripped through to the real P/L. This gives the same effect of the P/L build up over the life of the contract as the END method.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>If the CSN.PAYMENT.TYPE is 'BEGIN' then the first         schedule's CSN.DATE must be deal value date</p>
            <p>If the CSN.PAYMENT.TYPE is 'END' then the LAST schedule's         CSN.DATE must be deal maturity date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEXT.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to allow input of any useful extra information about the deal. </p>
            <p>Free format field to allow input of any extra information about the deal that the user feels will be useful.  Used for information purposes only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters for free format text - Type A. Multi value field (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>TAX.TYPE</p>
            <p>Using this field together with the CONTRACT.GRP, it is possible to determine a particular tax code from the conditions based on:</p>
            <p>General tax type as defined in TAX.TYPE.CONDITION. </p>
            <p>Type of customer as defined in CUSTOMER.CHARGE.</p>
            <p>Type of contract as defined in CONTRACT.GRP field.</p>
            <p>The value in this field must equate to a record in the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION which contains tax codes related to the customer tax group and contract group.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input, must be present as a record in TAX.TYPE.CONDITION. The       actual TAX.TYPE.CONDITION key will be prefixed with '*' character.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.REL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROV.REL.DATE</p>
            <p>The date on which the Outstanding Provision amount is to be released. A schedule entry will be created in MD.SCHEDULES for this date. The release however happens as an End of Day activity.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Date format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p><strong>Commission Schedule</strong>
            </p>
            <p><strong>CSN.AMOUNT</strong>
            </p>
            <p>CSN.AMOUNT is the fixed amount for the commission period</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>If FIXED.AMOUNT is 'YES' then the input should be in the         amount format</p>
            <p>If FIXED.AMOUNT is 'NO' then no input is allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SL.LINK.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.DR.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value date for debiting the account. Defaulted with TODAY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>should be Equal to or Greater than TODAY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEF.CUST.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any customer beneficiary of the deal. </p>
            <p>Used to identify any customer beneficiary of the deal. The customer number of the beneficiary then provides the id for the file MD.BENEFICIARY. This file then holds the MD.DEAL number(s) for that customer, until the contract reaches maturity. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 10 alphanumeric mnemonic or 1 - 6 numeric character customer number. Multi value field (Optional Input) Must be a valid CUSTOMER number or mnemonic. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of charges the customer is to be debited with. </p>
            <p>If this field is left blank and a value has been entered in field CHARGE.CODE, then the value for this field is calculated according to the rules on FT.CHARGE TYPE or FT.COMMISSION&gt;TYPE for the Charge Code. </p>
            <p>Charges can be defined on any date provided it is not before the deal VALUE.DATE or after the MATURITY.DATE. All charges for a given date must be taken in the same currency and debited to the same account. Charges can be taken in any currency provided that the account to be debited is in the CHARGE.CURR. Any taxes on the charges will be debited to the CHARGE.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>The charges will be debited during the end of day of the CHARGE.DATE except when the CHARGE.DATE is before the next working day in which case they will be taken on-line. Once this has happened, the charge details will be removed from the 'live' record but can be seen by looking into the balances file. </p>
            <p>If a deal is reversed, relevant charges taken will be reversed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point and commas         (Optional input) Multi value field associated with fields         CHARGE.DATE. Sub value field associated with field CHARGE.CODE.</p>
            <p>An override will be required if an amount is input which         is not equal to the default amount for the CHARGE.CODE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This defines the base commission rate that will be used to calculate the commission payable/receivable based on the Amount (inclusive of any forward increases/decreases) and the INTEREST.BASIS field used. This rate may be adjusted by use of the CSN.SPREAD, which can be a positive or negative value, and the real rate to be apllied is then stored in CURRENT.RATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Rate format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.PARTICIPATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The multi-value field contains the amount(s) of the Customers who participate in a deal and is used together with the associated PARTICIPANT field. Where used, the participant amounts will reduce the amount required for Limit purposes.</p>
            <p><strong>Example:</strong>
            </p>
            <p>A guarantee of USD 100 million is required to be issued for a client and it has been decided that the risk will be offset by allowing participation from other banks.</p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>Field</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Value</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Enrichment</strong>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>100,000,000.00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td />
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PARTICIPANT</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>100123</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Friendly Bank PLC</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>AMT.PARTICIPATE</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>30,000,000.00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td />
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>PARTICIPANT</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>102178</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Worldly Bank USA Inc</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>AMT.PARTICIPATE</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>20,000,000.00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td />
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>NET.PRIN.AMOUNT</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p />
                        <p>50,000,000.00</p>
                    </td>
                    <td />
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>So in this instance the update to Limits would be for the USD 50,000,000.00 which represents the remaining risk.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount field</p>
            <p>Mandatory if PARTICIPANT field is used</p>
            <p>Not allowed if ISSUE.CUSTOMER entered</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a Drawing is done under the Shipping Guarantee, the Drawing reference is stored in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELEASE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>RELEASE.AMT</p>
            <p>The amount of Cash Margin to be released into PROV.REL.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>The amount will be released online upon Authorization.  If the Guarantee were linked to LC then the entire Cash Margin would be released. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input amount cannot exceed OUTS.PROV.AMOUNT.</p>
            <p>Standard Amount field.</p>
            <p>System defaulted, if linked to LC as Shipping Guarantee.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the exchange rate to be applied when debit and credit provision account currencies are different. </p>
            <p>Will default to mid-rate if not defined by the user.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>Input is not allowed when debit and credit provision account currencies are same.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIXED.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This flag allows the input of a user defined commission amount. Two values are permitted, either Yes indicating that a commission amont is to be entered; or No which informs the system that the rate is to be entered.</p>
            <p>If commission is entered on the MD.DEAL, signified by the use of the CSN.PAYMENT.TYPE then this field requires a value.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory where CSN.PAYMENT.TYPE is entered</p>
            <p>Only Yes or No permitted</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents either the final maturity date of the deal or the number of days notice before maturity.</p>
            <p data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13"> If not defined, maturity date will be calculated   from ADVICE.EXPIRY.DATE + EXPIRY.DAYS defined in MD.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Standard date format or        1 - 3 numeric characters.</p>
                <p value="2">An override will be required if the date as defined on the HOLIDAY table is a non working day.</p>
                <p value="3">The date must be greater than the VALUE.DATE defined above.</p>
                <p value="4">An override will be required if the field is changed from a notice to a fixed maturity date and the appropriate number of days' notice has not been given.</p>
                <p value="5">If the MATURITY.DATE has been entered in a Date format then any MOVEMENT.DATEs entered below cannot be after the Maturity Date.</p>
                <p value="6">If the MATURITY.DATE has been entered in a DATE format then any CHARGE.DATEs entered below cannot be after the MATURITY.DATE.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p><strong>Commission Schedule</strong>
            </p>
            <p>This is the account for paying the commission at the Schedule date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p value="1"> Account can be Suspense, Nostro or Customer Account</p>
                <p value="2">Account Currency must be same as the Deal Currency</p>
                <p value="3">If the Account Customer is different from the Deal         Customer then an override is generated.</p>
                <p value="4" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Must be an internal account in the currency of the contract for claimed commission.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.RISK</field>
<desc>
            <p>The country code representing the country where the credit risk is deemed to reside. </p>
            <p>This field can be used for the generation of country risk information. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 alpha numeric characters (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the COUNTRY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to store the Contract ID of any Contract that is LINKED to this MD.DEAL Contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Validation is currently done on this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.PRIN.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the amount that will be used to update LIMITs when there are values present in AMT.PARTICIPATE. </p>
            <p>The value is the PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT less the total of the values in AMT.PARTICIPATE and represents the banks exposure for the contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System generated, no user input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAR.PRN.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PAR.PRN.MVMT</p>
            <p>The amount of Participation for a given Principal movement by the Participating Customer in field PART.CUS.</p>
            <p>Associated sub value of PART.CUS</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Cannot exceed the Total movement in case of positive movement.</p>
            <p>Cannot be reduced to less than the existing Participation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>MSG.CLASS</p>
            <p>An integral part of the 'DELIVERY' multi-value set, this field contains a message class Id (defined in EB.ADVICES). There may be many classes specified, but only classes relating to the operation will be triggered.</p>
            <p>For example, the EB.ADVICES number MD-1101 (MD New Deal - CA Type) may have the following classes and messages.</p>
            <p>Message No:               2320</p>
            <p>EB.MESSAGE.CLASS:    OPERATIONS</p>
            <p>Message No:               760</p>
            <p>EB.MESSAGE.CLASS:    BANKADVICE</p>
            <p>Message No:                900</p>
            <p>EB.MESSAGE.CLASS:    DEBITPROVISION.</p>
            <p>Now assuming that the EB.MESSAGE.CLASS.ID has been mapped to MD internal class specified in MD.PARAMETER as follows:</p>
            <p>BASIC.MESSAGE = OPERATIONS</p>
            <p>BANK.ADVICE=BANKADVICE</p>
            <p>PROVISION.DEBIT=DEBITPROVISION</p>
            <p>In the MD Transaction, the system will always populate the OPERATIONS and NOTIFICATION class when MD is issued. The PROVISION.DEBIT class will only be triggered, when action on Provision debit account has been completed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.AT.SOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field decides whether the commission and charge is to be processed at SOD or EOD of the scheduled date.</p>
            <p>The value gets defaulted from the parameter table.  However, the user can amend the defaulted value.</p>
            <p>Acceptable values are YES, NO and None. If yes, then the processing will take place during SOD and if no or none, then</p>
            <p>the processing will take place during EOD of the scheduled date. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Acceptable values are Yes, No and None</p>
            <p>The value in this field is changeable during the life of the contract.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETURN.COMM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not allowed for claimed commission.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.INV.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Indicates the number of Invocation done under the Deal. This is incremented by 1 on each Invocation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROV.PERCENT</p>
            <p>The percentage of Cash Margin to be provided in the Deal for the Leader's portion. This percent converts into amount and populates in PROV.AMOUNT.</p>
            <p>Defaults the value from MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION if set for the DEAL.SUB.TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the ID of the Consolidation record on the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file into which this contract is to be consolidated for financial reporting. </p>
            <p>Financial balance details, outstanding balance for each contract are recorded on the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file so that they can be included in the financial reports produced via the reporting module.  This field identifies the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB record into which the balance details for the contract are consolidated. </p>
            <p>The criteria for the consolidation of miscellaneous deals are defined on the CONSOLIDATE.CONDS table. </p>
            <p>This field is maintained by the system during the end of day batch processing.  Whenever this field is updated by the system a history record will be written to maintain a full audit trail. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Alphanumeric as specified on the CONSOLIDATE.CONDS file. Internally generated field.  No input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The code of the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE or FT.CHARGE.TYPE record used to identify and calculate the charges to be debited to the customer. </p>
            <p>Charges can be defined on any date provided it is not before the deal VALUE.DATE or after the MATURITY.DATE. All charges for a given date must be taken in the same currency and debited to the same account. Charges can be taken in any currency provided that the account to be debited is in the CHARGE.CURR. Any taxes on the charges will be debited to the CHARGE.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>The charges will be debited during the end of day of the CHARGE.DATE except when the CHARGE.DATE is before the next working day in which case they will be taken on-line. Once this has happened, the charge details will be removed from the 'live' record but can be seen by looking into the balances file. </p>
            <p>If a deal is reversed, relevant charges taken will be reversed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 11 alphanumeric characters. Sub-valued field         associated with Fields CHARGE.DATE to CHARGE.ACCOUNT and         field CHARGE.AMT. </p>
            <p>1 - 11 alphanumeric characters. (Optional input but must         be input in conjunction with the fields CHARGE.DATE,         CHARGE,CURR, CHARGE.ACCOUNT and CHARGE.AMT)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid charge code on either FT.CHARGE.TYPE or         FT.COMMISSION.TYPE tables.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field identifies the manner in which overdue payments are handled. The default for all contracts is AUTOMATIC. </p>
            <p>There are three options available: AUTOMATIC SEMI-AUTOMATIC MANUAL </p>
            <p>AUTOMATIC will liquidate across the settlement accounts on the contract. </p>
            <p>MANUAL will create a PD contract instead. </p>
            <p>SEMI-AUTOMATIC will only raise a PD contract if insufficient funds exist on the settlement account. </p>
            <p>For further details see the helptext in PD.PARAMETER where these settings are controlled from. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the PD product is not installed for the current company then the only allowed setting is AUTOMATIC. Only AUTOMATIC allowed for liability contract types and where no charges apply.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>BANK.ADDRESS</p>
            <p>When the counter party is not a customer of the Bank, this text field will be used. Normally will hold the name and address of the RECEIVING.BANK.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.LIAB.NETTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>In the case of Participation Deals, this field decides on the impact on the contingent entry. </p>
            <p>When set to NO, the contingent entry is raised for the PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT. </p>
            <p>When set to YES, the contingent is netted on the amount of participation and is raised only for the NET.PRIN.AMOUNT.</p>
            <p>The input cannot  be changed once Authorized.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory when Participation deal is input.</p>
            <p>Default value is Null, which is "NO".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date upon which the charges will be debited to the Charge Account. </p>
            <p>Charges can be defined on any date provided it is not before the deal VALUE.DATE or after the MATURITY.DATE. All charges for a given date must be taken in the same currency and debited to the same account. Charges can be taken in any currency, provided that the account to be debited is in the CHARGE.CURR. </p>
            <p>Any taxes on charges will be debited to the CHARGE.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>The charges will be debited during the end of day of the CHARGE.DATE except when the CHARGE.DATE is before the next working day in which case they will be taken on line. Once this has happened they will be removed from the 'live' record but can be seen by looking into the balances file. </p>
            <p>If a deal is reversed, relevant charges taken will be reversed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 date format. </p>
            <p>Multi-valued field associated with field CHARGE.CURR to         field CHARGE.AMT.</p>
            <p>CHARGE.DATE cannot be before deal VALUE.DATE</p>
            <p>CHARGE.DATE cannot be after the deal MATURITY.DATE.</p>
            <p>If the CHARGE.DATE is a non working day then an override         will be required.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This defines the spread to add/subtract to the base commission rate that will be used to calculate the commission payable/receivable based on the Amount (inclusive of any forward increases/decreases) and the INTEREST.BASIS field used. The real rate to be apllied is then stored in CURRENT.RATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Rate format</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SL.REF.TRANCHE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>In the event of Guarantee being issued under Syndicated Loans, it is imperative that this field is input first. </p>
            <p>It accepts a valid Facility reference, appended with the Tranche number under utilization.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The Facility should be a valid reference. </p>
            <p>The appended Tranche should have been defined it the Facility.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.CUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>PART.CUS</p>
            <p>The Participant Customer of the deal for whom movement is set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must have been previously defined in the field PARTICIPANT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEF.CUST.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any customer beneficiary of the deal. </p>
            <p>Used to identify any customer beneficiary of the deal. Currently used for information purposes only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 10 alphanumeric mnemonic or        1 - 6 numeric character customer number. Multi value field (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid CUSTOMER number or mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the customer portfolio to which the deal is to be linked. </p>
            <p>This field is used to link a customer's Miscellaneous Deal to his securities portfolio.  The presence of a portfolio number in this field will cause the deal to be included in the customer's portfolio valuation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 3 numeric characters (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid portfolio number for the customer on the SEC.ACC.MASTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>OVR.CARRIER</p>
            <p>An integral part of 'DELIVERY' multi-value set, this field enables the user to override the defaulted carrier for particular message type and select a new carrier.</p>
            <p>For example, If a specific message is generated by SWIFT, the user is permitted to override this by choosing another carrier such as TELEX, PRINT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid input in CARRIER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The full commission rate that will be used to calculate the commission payable/receivable based on the Amount (inclusive of any forward increases/decreases) and the INTEREST.BASIS field used. This field is the sum of the fields CSN.RATE and CSN.SPREAD.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Rate format</p>
            <p>Populated by the System only</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>SEND.ADVICE</p>
            <p>Part of the 'DELIVERY' multi-value set, providing the option to decide whether to send the generated message or withhold it.</p>
            <p>Input of YES, sends the message and NO, does not.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid input YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUR.CORRS.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaulted with the Customer of the Nostro account when INV.PAYMENT.METHOD is 'Nostro'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The account that is to be debited with the charges. </p>
            <p>Charges can be defined on any date provided it is not before the deal VALUE.DATE or after the MATURITY.DATE. All charges for a given date must be taken in the same currency and debited to the same account. Charges can be taken in any currency provided that the account to be debited is in the CHARGE.CURR. Any taxes on the charges will be debited to the CHARGE.ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>The charges will be debited during the end of day of the CHARGE.DATE except when the CHARGE.DATE is before the ext working day in which case they will be taken on-line. Once this has happened, the charge details will be removed from the 'live' record but can be seen by looking into the balances file. </p>
            <p>If a deal is reversed, relevant charges taken will be reversed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 14 numeric characters relating to a customer account         or a Nostro account. or 3 - 10 type A (alphanumeric)         account mnemonic. </p>
            <p>Multi-value field associated with fields CHARGE.DATE to         CHARGE.CURR and fields CHARGE.CODE to CHARGE.AMT.</p>
            <p>The CHARGE.ACCOUNT must be in the same currency as the         CHARGE.CURR.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid ACCOUNT number or mnemonic.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The principal amount of the deal. </p>
            <p>This field contains the principal amount of the deal in the currency defined in the CURRENCY field.  In order to facilitate the entry of the amount an input feature has been provided which allows for the suppression of trailing zeros.  In English language text this is accomplished by using a 'T' to indicate the thousands and an 'M' to indicate the millions.  Other languages will require the provision of translation values. </p>
            <p>e.g.      Input          Value </p>
            <p>          1T              1000           2M          2000 000 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 14 numeric characters plus a decimal point and commas. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>This field cannot be negative.  The decision as to whether the deal represents an asset or liability depends on the value of the CONTRACT.TYPE field entered below.</p>
            <p>Once the deal has been authorised this field cannot be changed.  Any changes to the Principal should be entered using the PRIN.MOVEMENT and MOVEMENT.DATE fields below.  This field will then be updated during the end of day of the MOVEMENT.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>SETTLE.ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>This field identifies, where necessary, the account which is used for settlement of charges. The absence of this field and ACCT.WITH.BANK means that the account relationship between the Sender and the Receiver in the currency of the charges is to be used for settlement. </p>
            <p>This field relates to Tag 25 of MT768 and MT769 of SWIFT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>CONTRACT.GRP</p>
            <p>Allows particular groups of contracts to be identified. For example, all Deals over a certain equivalent value in a Particular Currency. The pre-condition for defining a particular group are defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION.</p>
            <p>This code can be defined in TAX.TYPE.CONDITION to define a group with a specific tax code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The tax amount applicable for the charge</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field have been used to define the rule under which the guarantee is subjected to.  This field is inputtable and mandatory, if OTHR value is inputted in APPLICABLE.RULE field.         If URDG, URCG, NONE are inputted in this field, then NARRATIVE field should be left as blank.    APPLICABLE.RULE and NARRATIVE are being mapped for Swift tag 40C of MT760.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROV.AMOUNT</p>
            <p>The actual Margin amount calculated as a percentage of NET.PRIN.AMOUNT is held here. PROV.PERCENT and PROV.AMOUNT are mutually exclusive. Input of one recalculates the other.</p>
            <p>When the default amount is changed, the PROV.PERCENT is recalculated and an override message is displayed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.ACCT.RND.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>In this field the user can define either up, down or natural for rounding the commission to be debited to the customer's account. If not value is input in this field, then the rounding will take place as per T24 default standard(natural). <p>Validation Rules:</p><p>Should be a valid EB.ROUNDING.RULE                                                                                 NO change permitted after first authorization.</p><p>                                                                       Default value is taken from the field ROUNDING.RULE in MD.PARAMETER.                                </p><p>For detailed options on different rounding types help text on EB.ROUNDING.RULE file can be referred.</p> <![CDATA[                                                                                                              ]]></p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.BNK.TO.BNK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Bank to Bank information.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Free text field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Cannot exceed 6 lines.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the type of Miscellaneous Deal. It defines whether the deal is a Commitment or a Memorandum type deal and whether the deal represents an asset or liability. </p>
            <p>This field identifies the type of Deal input. It defines whether it is a Commitment or Memorandum deal and whether the figure in the PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT field is an asset or liability. </p>
            <p>Contract principals will be recorded in the CRF with different asset types according to the CONTRACT.TYPE and contract status as follows: </p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>Type</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Forward Deals</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Live Deals</strong>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CA</td>
                    <td>FWDCONTDB</td>
                    <td>CONTDB</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CL</td>
                    <td>FWDCONTCR</td>
                    <td>CONTCR</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>MA</td>
                    <td>FWDMEMODB</td>
                    <td>MEMODB</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>ML</td>
                    <td>FWDMEMOCR</td>
                    <td>MEMOCR</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Once the deal has been authorised the CONTRACT.TYPE         cannot be changed.</p>
            <p>Can only be CA, CL, MA or ML.</p>
            <p>The CONTRACT.TYPE must be defined on the MD.PARAMETER         record for the company concerned.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a no input, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The address of the Beneficiary if the customer number of the Beneficiary is not known.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input is optional.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.MARGIN.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the Credit Provision account of the LC, representing the account from which the the Cash Margin has been apportioned from towards issue of Shipping Guarantee.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMENDMENT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>AMENDMENT.NO</p>
            <p>Number of amendment relates to the field 26E of MT767. Input of a number will reset the next two field GTEE.DETAILS and SENDER.INFO, so that fresh input relating to the amendment may be input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LD.PRN.MVMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>LD.PRN.MVMT</p>
            <p>The amount of Participation for a given Principal movement relating to the Leader. It is a system maintained field, holding the difference between the sum of PRIN.MOVEMENT and PAR.PRN.MVMT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field opens up only if the commission account is different from the deal currency and allows the user to input any absolute value that will be used by the system for calculating the commission amount that is to be debited to the customers account. <p><p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>                                                                                                               Should have numerical value                                                                                                 This field can be amended throughout the life of the contract                                                              if no value input in this field, then conversion rate will be picked up from the currency table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.AC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p><strong>Commission Schedule</strong>
            </p>
            <p><strong>ISSUE.CUSTOMER</strong>
            </p>
            <p>Issuing bank</p>
            <p>or </p>
            <p>Customer of the guarantee issued to</p>
            <p>If the contract type is CL and issue customer is entered on the deal then the deal is sub-participation of a CA deal for the issuing customer. The follwing table illustrates the Participation Issued and Sub-partcipation deals on the system. The participation issued and subparticipation details are as held on one system. The same deal on the participant's system will have the information as detailed in the last column.</p>
            <p />
            <table border="0" cellpadding="8" cellspacing="8">
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>DEAL</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>PARTICIPATION</strong>
                        <p><strong>ISSUED</strong>
                        </p>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>SUB-PARTICIPATION</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>SUB-PARTICIPATION </strong>
                        <p><strong>ON         OTHER SYSTEM</strong>
                        </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CONTRACT.TYPE</td>
                    <td>CA</td>
                    <td>CL</td>
                    <td>CA</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>CUSTOMER</td>
                    <td>DBL</td>
                    <td>LLOYDS</td>
                    <td>DBL</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT</td>
                    <td>USD 1,000,000</td>
                    <td>USD 250,000</td>
                    <td>USD 250,000</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>BENEFICIARY</td>
                    <td>DIXONS</td>
                    <td />
                    <td>DIXONS</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>ISSUE.CUSTOMER</td>
                    <td />
                    <td>DBL</td>
                    <td>T24<p>(receivable from DBL through</p><p>T24)</p></td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>PARTICIPANT</td>
                    <td>LLOYDS</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AMT.PARTICIPATE</td>
                    <td>USD 250,000</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>LIMIT.AMOUNT</td>
                    <td>USD 750,000</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be valid customer on the system</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROV.AMT</p>
            <p>The Cash Margin amount to be provided against the LD.PRN.MVMT, for the corresponding positive principal movement.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>User input Amount field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.CCY.CONV</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This is a User input field, representing the rate at which Facility is to be impacted when the Guarantee currency is different from that of the Facility. Static update of the Facility tables happens at the rate input in this field. The facility limit line is also impacted at this rate. Although the consol entry liquidating the facility happens at this rate, but that of Guarantee happens at Mid Reval Rate.</p>
            <p>It is important to note that, this rate will be used in the case of reinstatement of limit and facility in case the Facility is of revolving in nature.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p>Default would always be MRR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.INPUT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>MD.DEAL can accept the following types:</p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>Key</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Days/Denominator</strong>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>A</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>B</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>C</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>D</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>E</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>F</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>For illustrations of all supported </p>
            <p>INTEREST.BASIS</p> types see: <a href="INTEREST.BASIS_data.htm">INTEREST.BASIS</a><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>1 type A (alphanumeric) character. </p><p>Valid input is A, B, C, D, E, F, or blank. </p><p>Can only be used if CSN.PAYMENT type and associated         fields are set.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the status of the contract. It is an internal field and input here is automatically generated by the system. </p>
            <p>Having a status defined for each contract will facilitate the production of end of Day reports. </p>
            <p>The following values have been defined:-    1)    FWD = forward value    2)   CUR = current   3)  REV = reversed    4)   LIQ = deal has reached maturity date <conditionalText data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13"> 5)  EXP status of the contract from Advice Expiry date to</conditionalText> <![CDATA[ ]]><conditionalText data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">Maturity Date.</conditionalText></p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>
                    <p value="1" data-mc-conditions="FROMRELEASE.R13">System maintained field.</p>
                </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the profit centre to which the deal belongs. </p>
            <p>This field identifies the profit centre under which this deal is to be reported. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 4 Numeric characters (Optional Input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid account officer on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.PARAM</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field will hold a valid ID of EB.ACCRUAL.PARAM for the commission and accrual calculations. </p>
            <p> Based on the definition of this field a contract can be configured to do the following, </p>
            <p> Include first day of the interest period and exclude the last of the interest period </p>
            <p> Exclude the first day of the interest period and include the last of the interest period. </p>
            <p> Include both first (only value date) and last day of accrual period.</p>
            <p> Adjust the principal increase and decrease effective dates for interest calculation and accrual calculation purposes. </p>
            <p> By default the field shall hold null in which case the system shall include first day of the interest period and exclude the last of the interest period. </p>
            <p> This would be a NOCHANGE field after authorization. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.WITH.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>ACCT.WITH.BANK</p>
            <p>This field specifies the bank at which the Sender wishes to receive credit for charges claimed.</p>
            <p>This field relates to Tag 57a of MT768 and MT769.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>ACTIVITY.CODE</p>
            <p>This contains the activity code that is triggered by the latest activity, such as Input, Amendment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.RATE.EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.DR.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Draw down account from where the invocation amount will be debited. </p>
            <p />
            <p>If provision is held, then </p>
            <p />this field <p />will be defaulted with PROV.REL.ACCOUNT.<p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Should be a valid account in the ACCOUNT table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.DR.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROV.DR.ACCOUNT</p>
            <p>The Customer account from which the Cash Margin will be debited. It can be of a currency other than the Deal currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid account in the ACCOUNT Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the Override messages to which the user agreed during input. </p>
            <p>During the validation of a deal, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate anomalies, for instance the VALUE.DATE being a non working day. </p>
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the Override, the full text of the actual Override Message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multi-valued field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated multi valued field. No input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Category Code to which this transaction will be assigned. </p>
            <p>The CATEGORY must be within the range defined by the DEAL.SUB.TYPE on the MD.PARAMETER record for the company of the user. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 5 numeric characters (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>The CATEGORY must exist on the Category Table.</p>
            <p>Must be within the range defined by the DEAL.SUB.TYPE on MD.PARAMETER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Any non T24 references which identify the deal for the customer. </p>
            <p>Free format field to allow input of any customer reference of the deal.  Used for information purposes only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 35 free format alphanumeric characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BILL.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input to this field will ensure that the amount field is updated with the value of the bill. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 12 characters as defined for the BILL.NUMBER id for the BILL.REGISTER.  (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid bill number on the BILL.REGISTER file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.CLAIM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Decides whether the commission is to be claimed or collected.</p>
            <p>Options:</p>
            <p>
                <p value="1">Yes To be claimed</p>
                <p value="2">Null  To be collected from customers account</p>
            </p>
            <p>Validation:</p>
            <p>Allowed only for the 'BEGIN' type of commission.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVING.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>RECEIVING.BANK</p>
            <p>The counter party Bank to whom the Guarantee message is to be sent when it is an issue.</p>
            <p>Alternatively, it could be the Bank to whom an acknowledgement MT768 needs to be sent when it is a Guarantee received.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should a valid CUSTOMER.</p>
            <p>Should be classified as Bank.</p>
            <p>Mandatory field for SWIFT message.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.AMT.XRATE</field>
<desc>
            <p><strong>Commission Schedule</strong>
            </p>
            <p><strong>AMT.PARTICIPATE</strong>
            </p>
            <p>The participate amount taken</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid amount</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the amount used in the call to limits. </p>
            <p>The principal amount used for the purposes of limits will be the highest value of the contract either today or in the future taking into account all principal movements.  For example consider the following contingent asset contract: </p>
            <p>2         CURRENCY            USD 4         PRINCIPAL           1,000,000 6         VALUE.DATE          01/01/93 7         MATURITY.DATE       01/04/93 13.1      PRIN.MOVEMENT       - 200,000 14.1      MOVEMENT DATE       15/01.93 13.2      PRIN.MOVEMENT         500,000 14.2      MOVEMENT.DATE       01/02/93 13.3      PRIN.MOVEMENT       - 100,000 14.3      MOVEMENT.DATE       01/03/93 </p>
            <p>In this case the principal amount passed to limits would be 1,300,000 as this is the highest value of the principal throughout the contract life.  Hence the LIMIT.AMOUNT field would contain 1,300,000. </p>
            <p>This field will only be updated if LIMIT.UPD.REQD is 'YES'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internally generated field. No input allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.SUB.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to sub divide the CONTRACT.TYPE. </p>
            <p>This field is used to sub-divide each CONTRACT.TYPE into smaller groups.  A Deal Sub Type entered here must have been entered on the MD.PARAMETER record for the company in a position corresponding to the CONTRACT.TYPE entered above. </p>
            <p>It has no direct bearing on the processing of the deal other than defining the range of allowable categories for the CATEGORY field. It does this through the MD.PARAMETER record.  Each Deal Sub Type entered on the MD.PARAMETER is entered with a corresponding range of category codes.  This range is used in defining the upper and lower limits for the category code field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 5 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>Once the deal has been authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
            <p>Must be present on MD.PARAMETER for the company concerned and must correspond to the CONTRACT.TYPE entered above.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>TAX.KEY</p>
            <p>The tax key to be used on the commission amount.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid key in the TAX table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQUIDATION.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field identifies the manner in which overdue payments are handled. The default for all contracts is AUTOMATIC.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>There are three options available:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>AUTOMATIC - will liquidate across the charge/commission account on the contract</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>SEMI AUTOMATIC - will liquidate the charge/commission to the account only if sufficient balance is available. Else, PD will be written</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>MANUAL - will create a PD contract irrespective of availability of funds</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Only the charges and commissions taken in the deal are reckoned for this purpose. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If PD product is not defined for the current company, the only allowed value is AUTOMATIC. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Prior to inputting MANUAL or SEMI AUTOMATIC, a Parameter for MD has to be defined in PD.PARAMETER</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>MSG.NO</p>
            <p>An integral part of the 'DELIVERY' multi-value set, this field is used to determine the message to which the user wishes to amend the delivery and is used exclusively with the fields MSG.CLASS, OVR.CARRIER, OVR.ADDRESS and SEND.DATE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 numeric characters (Optional input).</p>
            <p>This must be defined in the DE.MESSAGE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LC.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the ID of the Letter of Credit, to be linked to this Guarantee for the purpose of apportioning the Margin.</p>
            <p>Such a link is permitted only for Import Letter of Credit with outstanding Cash Margin.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Letter of Credit ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSN.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>CSN.FREQUENCY</p>
            <p>This denotes the frequency in which the commission is cycled for capitalization.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input cannot be prior to value date.</p>
            <p>Standard Date/Frequency format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.CHRG.DETLS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT codes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Accepts     either OUR, SHA or BEN only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GTEE.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>GTEE.DETAILS</p>
            <p>Details of Guarantee. The content of this field may also be defaulted from MD.CLAUSES, by entering its ID and committing.</p>
            <p>This is linked to Tag 77C of MT760 and MT767.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SWIFT related field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUND.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The user can define either up, down or natural for rounding the commission calculated in a MD.Deal in the field ROUND.RULE, at the product level. The value in this field can be changed any time. If no value is input in this field, then the rounding will take place as per T24 default standard(natural). <p>Validation Rules:</p>                                                                                                                                                                    Should be a valid EB.ROUNDING.RULE                                                                                 NO change permitted after first authorization                                                                      Default value is taken from the field ROUNDING.RULE in MD.PARAMETER                               For detailed options on different rounding types help text on EB.ROUNDING.FULE file can be referred   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
           <p>Holds the message type of inward message associated with INWARD.MSG.REF. </p>
           <p>For example, if MT760 is received, then value MT760 will be updated in this field.</p>
           <p>
               <p>Validation Rules:</p>
          </p>     
          <p />
          <p>System maintained Field.</p>
      </desc>    
</t>
<t>
<field>INWARD.MSG.REF</field>
<desc>
         <p>Holds the reference of the inward message automatically processed by the system. Represents the ID of DE.I.HEADER record of the corresponding message type. </p>
         <p>For example, if the id of  DE.I.HEADER is  R20130421476697717707 R identifies an inward message, then this field is updated with the value R20130421476697717707.</p>
         <p>
             <p>Validation Rules:</p>
         </p>
         <p />
         <p>System maintained Field.</p>    
     </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FRONTED.BY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the participant who is fronting the issuance of Guarantee under Syndication.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed only with Syndicated Guarantee.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid participant defined at facility level in AVL.FRONTING field.</p>
            <p>Events Processing field must be set as 'Online'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MT799.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format text field for sending MT799 messages to participants under syndicated Guarantees.</p>
            <p>This field will be mapped to tag 79 of MT799 message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Maximum of 35 lines with 50 characters each line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.SENDER.INFO</field>
<desc>
			<p>Sender to Receiver Information.</p>
			<p>This field relates to Tag 72 of MT768 and MT769.</p>
			<p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
			<p></p>
			<p>SWIFT related field.</p>
		</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.REQUEST.ID</field>
<desc>
			<p>Stores the ID of the corresponding MD.IB.REQUEST record, when the request for issuance of MD.DEAL is received through Internet Banking.</p>
			<p>System updated field.</p>			
		</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INV.REGISTER.DATE</field>
<desc>
			<p>Date on which an invocation claim is registered in the system.</p>
			<p>System defaults to the current system date.</p>
			<p>Standard T24 Date field.</p>				
		</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GTEE.RETURN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the original guarantee is returned by the customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>User Input field.</p>
            <p>Cannot be less than Value Date.</p>
            <p>Forward date not allowed.</p>
            <p>Nochange.</p>
       </desc>
</t>
<t><field>IB.CLM.NARRATIVE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
