<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>MD</product>
        <title>MD.IB.REQUEST</title>
        <table>MD.IB.REQUEST</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This application is used for Corporate customer to initiate requests for issuance of guarantees through Internet Banking. When the request for issuance is approved by the Bank, the values from the fields of this application will be mapped to the corresponding fields in MD.DEAL and the system will create the MD.DEAL record and place it in IHLD, for the bank user to complete the process of issuance of guarantee.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defaults to the customer ID of the Corporate customer who is initiating the request for issuance of guarantee.</p>
                <p>System defaulted field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to CUSTOMER field of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DOCUMENT.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the file name of the attached/uploaded documents.</p>
                <p>System updated field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GTEE.DETAILS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the terms and conditions of the guarantee.</p>
                <p>User Input field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to GTEE.DETAILS of MD.DEAL.</p>
                <p>This field will list all the MD.CLAUSES records defined for the corporate customer, in CIB and enable the user to select from the list. The contents defined under the selected records will be defaulted in this field, and the user will be able to modify the same.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IB.ADDL.INFO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IB.AMEND.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the status of the amendment request.</p>
                <p>Dropdown - Allowed values are - With Bank_With Customer_Approved_Rejected.</p>
                <p>Allowed for bank user to input, mandatory for Interent banking enabled customers.</p>
                <p>System default to “With Bank”;, when corporate authoriser submits the request to bank.</p>
                <p>Override generated when the current status selected by the bank user is the same as the previous status.</p>
                <p>User updated mandatory field at bank side for CIB enabled customers and system updated at CIB side</p>
                <p>Following are the allowed values: </p>
                <p>“With Customer”, if request pending with customer for clarifications – To be updated by Bank user.</p>
                <p>“Approved” – if request is approved by Bank user – to be updated by bank user.</p>
                <p>“Rejected” – if request is rejected by Bank user – To be updated  by Bank user.</p>
                <p>“With Bank” – System updated value at CIB side.</p>
                <p>If value selected is “Approved”, then MD.DEAL (amendment) record is created in INAU status after MD.IB.REQUEST record is authorised. The online service, OFS.MESSAGE.SERVICE must be running for the system to create the MD.DEAL record.</p>
                <p>If value selected is “Rejected”, then IB.BK.TO.CUST field is mandatory.</p>
                <p>If value selected is “With Customer”, then IB.BK.TO.CUST field is mandatory.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IB.BK.TO.CUST</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field to input queries/clarifications by bank to be sought from Corporate customer on the request.</p>
                <p>Input allowed only for Bank user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IB.CUST.TO.BK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field to input any additional information/clarifications to be provided to the bank, by Corporate customer.</p>
                <p>Input allowed only for Corporate customers.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IB.EVENT.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the status of the request.</p>
                <p>Dropdown - Allowed values are - With Bank_With Customer_Approved_Rejected.</p>
                <p>Allowed for bank user to input, mandatory for Interent banking enabled customers.</p>
                <p>System default to “With Bank”;, when corporate authoriser submits the request to bank.</p>
                <p>Override generated when the current status selected by the bank user is the same as the previous status.</p>
                <p>User updated mandatory field at bank side for CIB enabled customers and system updated at CIB side.</p>
                <p>Following are the allowed values: </p>
                <p> “With Customer”, if request pending with customer for clarifications – To be updated by Bank user.</p>
                <p> “Approved” – if request is approved by Bank user – to be updated by bank user.</p>
                <p> “Rejected” – if request is rejected by Bank user – To be updated  by Bank user.</p>
                <p> “With Bank” – System updated value at CIB side.</p>
                <p>If value selected is “Approved”, then MD.DEAL record is created in IHLD status after MD.IB.REQUEST record is authorised. The online service, OFS.MESSAGE.SERVICE must   be running for the system to create the MD.DEAL record.</p>
                <p>If value selected is “Rejected”, then IB.BK.TO.CUST field is mandatory.</p>
                <p>If value selected is “With Customer”, then IB.BK.TO.CUST field is mandatory.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IB.INV.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the status of the invocation claim.</p>
                <p>System updated field based on INV.STATUS of MD.DEAL record.</p>
                <p>IF INV.STATUS = PROCESS, the system will update this field to “With Customer”.</p>
                <p>IF INV.STATUS = PROCESS, the system will update this field to “With Bank” , if CIB submits the response to the claim.</p>
                <p>Value in this field is cleared, when the claim is executed (INV.STATUS= EXECUTE) or cancelled(INV.STATUS = CANCEL).</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>“GR” followed by 10 digits :- YY - Year DDD - Julian Day 99999 - Sequence No.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMD.REQUEST.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Hold number of amendment request.</p>
                <p>System Maintained field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INV.DR.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the account from which the invocation amount is to be debited at the time of settlement of the claim.</p>
                <p>The field will list all the accounts related to the Corporate customer, with the account in the currency of the guarantee request listed on the top.</p>
                <p>User Input field. If no input, the system will default the account specified in the CHARGE.DR.ACCOUNT field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to INV.DR.ACCOUNT of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LC.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the LC reference under which the shipping guarantee has been requested.</p>
                <p>User input field. Mandatory if LETTER OF CREDIT is selected for SG.ISSUED field.</p>
                <p>System validates if the reference input by the user is a valid LC reference.</p>
                <p>Mapped to LC.REFERENCE of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LIMIT.EX.REASON</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the reason for request of the guarantee when the system prompts that the limit is exceeded.</p>
                <p>User input mandatory field, when the user wishes to submit the request in spite of limit being exceeded.</p>
                <p>Input allowed only in CIB for corporate customers.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LIMIT.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the LIMIT.REFERENCE id.</p>
                <p>System Maintained field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Date on which the guarantee expires. Denotes the end date of the guarantee.</p>
                <p>Mapped to ADVICE.EXPIRY.DATE of MD.DEAL.</p>
                <p>Standard T24 date field, user input field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MD.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the corresponding MD.DEAL record ID, when the request for issuance is approved.</p>
                <p>System updated field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MOVEMENT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>To specify the date from which the increase/decrease of the guarantee amount is effective.</p>
                <p>User input field. Mandatory when PRIN.MOVEMENT has a value.</p>
                <p>Mapped to MOVEMENT.DATE of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.EXPIRY.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>To specify the new end date of the guarantee during amendment.</p>
                <p>User input field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to ADVICE.EXPIRY.DATE of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OTHER.INFORMATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field to input any information that needs to be provided with regard to the issuance of guarantee.</p>
                <p>Input allowed only for Corporate customers.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds Override messages.</p>
                <p>System Maintained Field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMENDMENT.DETAILS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Corporate user to input the amendment details of the guarantee in this field.</p>
                <p>Input allowed only for Corporate user while initiating a guarantee amendment request.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRIN.MOVEMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>To specify the increase or decrease of the guarantee amount during amendment.</p>
                <p>User input field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to PRIN.MOVEMENT of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the amount for which the guarantee request is placed. User input field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to PRINCIPAL.AMOUNT field of MD.DEAL.</p>
                <p>The value in this field is expressed in the currency defined in the currency field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROV.DR.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the account from which the cash margin/provision is to be taken.</p>
                <p>The field will list all the accounts related to the Corporate customer with the account in the currency of the guarantee request listed on the top.</p>
                <p>User Input field. If no input, the system will default the account specified in the CHARGE.DR.ACCOUNT field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to PROV.DR.ACCOUNT of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SG.ISSUED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether the request is for issuance of shipping guarantee under Letter of Credit or Documentary collections.</p>
                <p>User Input field. Allowed values LETTER OF CREDIT, COLLECTIONS</p>
                <p>Mapped to SG.ISSUED of MD.DEAL.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>START.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Date on which the guarantee must be effective. Denotes the value date of the guarantee.</p>
                <p>Mapped to VALUE.DATE of MD.DEAL.</p>
                <p>Standard T24 date field, User input field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUPPORT.DOCS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the issuance is requested for the shipping guarantee, then Corporate customer can upload supporting documents using the Upload function in CIB.</p>
                <p>Mandatory if shipping guarantee is requested for Collections.</p>
                <p>Applicable only for Shipping guarantee request.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BENEFICIARY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the name and address of the beneficiary of the guarantee request.</p>
                <p>User Input Field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to BEN.ADDRESS field of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>To specify the date on which MD.IB.REQUEST is inputted.</p>
                <p>System Maintained field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the type of guarantee requested to be issued. User input field.</p>
                <p>Field will list all the categories defined for deal sub types in MD.PARAMETER.</p>
                <p>Mapped to CATEGORY of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHARGE.DR.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the account from which charges is to be collected. </p>
                <p>User Input mandatory field. The field will list all the accounts related to the Corporate customer with the account in the currency of the guarantee request listed on the top.</p>
                <p>Mapped to CHARGE.ACCOUNT of MD.DEAL</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CLIENT.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>To specify the Corporate customer&apos;s reference.</p>
                <p>User input field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to REFERENCE.2 field of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMM.DR.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the account from which the commission is to be collected.</p>
                <p>The field will list all the accounts related to the Corporate customer with the account in the currency of the guarantee request listed on the top.</p>
                <p>User Input field. If no input, the system will default the account specified in the CHARGE.DR.ACCOUNT field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to CSN.ACCOUNT of MD.DEAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifes the currency in which the guarantee has to be issued. User Input field.</p>
                <p>Mapped to CURRENCY field of MD.DEAL.</p>
                <p>Standard T24 currency field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
