<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MD</product>
<table>MD.PROV.BALANCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>MD.PROV.BALANCES</p>
            <p>As Cash Margin (Provision) can be taken for a MD.DEAL, the details regarding the same are stored in this file. When Cash Margin is taken the transactions are online. The release or additional provision may be taken either as an online activity or as an End of Day activity.</p>
            <p>When Provision is taken, it may be parked into an account of a different currency and the although the release of Provision will default to the Debit Provision account, yet it can be changed.</p>
            <p>The Provision taken is stored along with the details of the Provision debit account, Provision credit account, Provision account currency, Outstanding Provision amount, Provision release account and Provision release amount.</p>
            <p>On every release of Provision the release details are displayed as multi-value sets.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RELEASE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a part of the Release multi-value set, representing the Date on which the Cash Margin was released.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.REL.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents the account into which the Provision (Cash Margin) is released.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.DR.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the account from which Provision was taken.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROV.CR.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the account into which the Provision is credited.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELEASE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This represents  the amount of Provision released on the RELEASE.DATE into PROV.REL.ACCT forming a part of the Release Multi-value set.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This file has the details relating to Provision taken in the Deal, such as Debit Provision account, Credit Provision account, Currency in which Provision is held, Outstanding Provision amount and that in Local currency. In case of release of Provision, the release date, account and amount.</p>
            <p>The ID is a valid authorized MD.DEAL reference.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
            <p>Built only if Provision is taken for the Deal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.PROV.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents outstanding Provision in terms of Credit Provision account currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.PROV.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field mention the outstanding provision amount interms of LCCY</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTS.PROV.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the currency in which Provision is stored.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

