<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>MD</product>
<table>MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION</p>
            <p>This table facilitates defaulting Provision percentage, Commission percentage and ensuring collection of Minimum Commission amount for Guarantees issued.</p>
            <p>The Id of this table is DEAL.SUB.TYPE. Input of PROVISION.PERCENT ensures default of this percentage in the Deal when PROVISION is set to YES. </p>
            <p>To ensure that a minimum amount of commission is recovered for any Deal, MIN.COMM.AMT.LCCY and MIN.COMM.TENURE are used. </p>
            <p />
            <p>When the resultant commission of a Deal is greater than the default value,     the computed value stays.</p>
            <p>When the resultant commission of a Deal is greater than the default value,     but the tenor is less than the default value, the computed value stays.</p>
            <p>When the resultant commission of a Deal is less than the default value,     but the tenor is greater than the default value, the default commission is     taken.</p>
            <p>When the resultant commission of a Deal is less than the default value and     the tenor is less than the minimum period, the commission is recalculated     for the default period. If this commission is greater than the default     commission, it is applied else the default commission is applied.</p>
            <p>This default commission may be defined currency-wise. In the absence of any default value for a given currency, the equivalent of the local currency is computed and applied.</p>
            <p>In the same manner the percentage of commission for any CATEGORY under a DEAL.SUB.TYPE can be defined and that will be defaulted in the Deal.</p>
            <p>This definition of commission percentage becomes mandatory if MD.CSN.RATE.CHANGE is to be invoked.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MIN.COMM.TENURE</field>
<desc>
            <p>MIN.COMM.TENURE</p>
            <p>The minimum tenure represented in days for which the commission is to be calculated. This field is used along with MIN.COMM.AMT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When the resultant commission of a Deal is greater than the default value,     the computed value stays.</p>
            <p>When the resultant commission of a Deal is greater than the default value,     but the tenor is less than the default value, the computed value stays.</p>
            <p>When the resultant commission of a Deal is less than the default value,     but the tenor is greater than the default value, the default value is taken.</p>
            <p>When the resultant commission of a Deal is less than the default value and     the tenor is less than the minimum period, the commission is calculated for     the default period. If this commission is greater than the default     commission, it is applied else the default commission is applied.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.COMM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>MIN.COMM.AMT</p>
            <p>The minimum amount of commission to be applied in the Deals for the corresponding Currency.</p>
            <p>This is an associated multi-value of CURRENCY. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROVISION.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>PROVISION.PERCENT</p>
            <p>The input here is used to default the percentage of Cash Margin to be used for a given DEAL.SUB.TYPE in the record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.COMM.AMT.LCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>MIN.COMM.AMT.LCCY</p>
            <p>The minimum amount of commission in local currency equivalent.</p>
            <p>If the minimum commission amount is not defined or specified through the fields CURRENCY and MIN.COMM.AMT,then the local equivalent of the calculated commission is compared against this amount and greater of the two is applied</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard Amount field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>CATEGORY</p>
            <p>The category for which the default commission percentage is specified. This field along with COMMISSION.RATE are an associated multi-value.</p>
            <p>The definition of this category and rate however becomes mandatory if a rate change is to be defined.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A valid category in the CATEGORY Table. Should be within the range as       specified in the MD.PARAMETER for the corresponding DEAL.SUB.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>COMMISSION.RATE</p>
            <p>The default percentage of commission to be applied for a given category in the Deal.</p>
            <p>This field along with CATEGORY are associated multi-values.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory if MD.CSN.RATE.CHANGE is to be invoked.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>CURRENCY</p>
            <p>The currency for which a minimum amount of commission is to applied. If the Deal currency is not specified here, the local equivalent of the calculated amount is compared against the MIN.COMM.AMT.LCCY.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid currency in the CURRENCY Table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.SUB.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>It accepts only valid deal sub type. This file holds the default commission and provision percentage for the deal sub types and categories within them.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DUPLICATE.CHECK</field>
<desc>
          <p>DUPLICATE.CHECK</p>
          <p>Input to this field must be a valid record id from the EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE file.</p>
          <P>The EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE file allows for the definition of a criterion to check against for the occurrence of any duplicate contracts that then match this.</P>
          <P>When more than one Id is input for validation, for a given MD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION, override is generated even if the condition is satisfied for one of them.</P>
          <p>
              <p>Validation Rules:</p>
          </p>
          <p />
          <p>Optional input</p>
          <p>Multi-value field.</p>
          <p>Must be a valid Id in the EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE file, whose application is set as MD.</p>
          <p>Accepts up to 35 alpha-numeric characters.</p>
       </desc>   
</t>  
<t>
<field>CSN.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Period for calculation of commission when commission rate is given.</p>
            <p>Values are – Monthly, Quarterly, Semester, Null</p>
            <p>Default value is null. Null indicates that the commission is to be calculated for the actual number of days considering the rate as ‘per annum’ basis.</p>
            <p>When the csn period is defined, collection of commission must be upfront always. Event processing should be online and process at sod should be Yes and frequency not allowed.</p>
            <p>Rate change is not allowed if commission period is defined</p>
            <p>The below table illustrates the calculation of commission based on different csn periods.</p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                    <tr class="Body-Body1">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Commission Rate</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Csn Period</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">Guarantee Amount</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Date of Issue</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Expiry Date</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">Commission per csn period</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Number of months (csn periods)</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Total commission</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">0.1%</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Monthly</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">100,000</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1st Jan. 2015</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">15th Mar 2016</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">100</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">15</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1500</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">0.25%</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Quarterly</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">100,000</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1st Jan. 2015</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">15th Mar 2016</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">250</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">5</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1250</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">0.5%</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Semester</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">100,000</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1st Jan. 2015</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">15th Mar 2016</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">500</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">3</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1500</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr class="Body-Body1">
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1%</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">Null</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">100,000</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1st Jan. 2015</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">15th Mar 2016</td>
                        <td class="BodyD-Column1-Body1">--</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">429 days</td>
                        <td class="BodyE-Column1-Body1">1191.62</td>
                    </tr>
            </table>
        </desc>
</t>             
</menu>
</t24help>

