<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EU</product>
<table>AC.CCY.CONVERSION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CONVERT.STO</field>
<desc>
            <p>A Y/NO flag to determine if STANDING.ORDERS are to be converted to the above ccy or to be renumbered to the new account number for external customer accounts only. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The new currency to convert to. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-3 numeric character Currency code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>It must be an existing code on the CURRENCY Table.</p>
            <p>It must be the same as the currency on the accounts 'current' currency FIXED.CCY.</p>
            <p>Interest and charge conditions must be defined from the start of the current capitalisation period for this new ccy.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.COMPENSATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.CONVERTED</field>
<desc>
            <p>System date the conversion took place </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Noinput</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEEP.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>A Y/NO flag to specify if the system is to use the mnemonic for the new created account in the above ccy. </p>
            <p>This will also transfer any ALT.ACCT.IDS from the original account to the new created account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.LIQU.IND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CLOSE.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>A Y/NO flag to denote that the system should attempt to automatically close the renumbered account by calculating the AUTO.CLOSURE.DATE as the next capitalisation date (either CR or DR). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Y or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CLOSURE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the account in national currency is to be closed. A date can be entered or if AUTO.CLOSE.ACCT is set to Y then the system will calculate the next capitalisation date (either DR or CR) for the account and will default. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Type DD (standard date format in range 1000 - 2049) (Optional input)</p>
            <p>If AUTO.CLOSE.ACCT is set to 'Y' and the next capitalisation date can not be determined then todays date is defaulted.</p>
            <p>For internal accounts the date is set to todays date if AUTO.CLOSE.ACCT is set tp 'Y'.</p>
            <p>Date must be after the CONVERSION.DATE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING.RESTRICT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any restictions for posting entries that are to be imposed on the account. </p>
            <p>Restrictions in the range 90-99 indicate Accounts which will be closed automatically as soon as all balances are zero. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Posting restriction code upto 4 characters, based on EB.OBJECT. Posting restriction code in the range 90 - 99. (Mandatory input if account set for closure)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.TRANSFER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION to be used to transfer the balance to the new ccy account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input only if module FT exists for this company.  Noinput if FT module does not exist for this company.</p>
            <p>Must be of TYPE 'AC'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RENUMBER.ACCT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The new number the account is to be renumbered to. </p>
            <p>For internal accounts this will represent the ACCOUNT number of the new account to be created in the above ccy. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard numeric Account Number (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Number can not already exist on ACCOUNT file.</p>
            <p>For internal accounts must have an internal account format, with the first 3 characters being the ccy defined above.</p>
            <p>For external accounts must have an external account format.</p>
            <p>For a multi-company environment, the account number must adhear to the INTERCO.PARAMETER SYSTEM settings.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Error Log of any exception message's raised </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Noinput</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the conversion is to take place. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Type DD (standard date format in range 1000 - 2049). (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>Date must be GE to system date.</p>
            <p>Date must be GE the FIXED.START.DATE on the account's 'current' ccy record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

