<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EU</product>
<table>EU.CONTRACT.CONVERSION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWDOWN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.CONTRACT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the contract ID for the new contract created by the conversion process.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when the new contract is created)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain any errors encountered when trying to either early mature the original contract or create the new contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system whenever errors are encountered)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.FT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the ID of the FUNDS.TRANSFER transaction created for contracts where a principal repayment is scheduled for the conversion date. The FUNDS.TRANSFER will debit the original principal liquidation account and credit the suspense account used for early maturity (for loans). This will be vice versa for deposits.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when the original contract is matured early)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the new limit reference which will be used as the limit reference for the contract that is matured (early) on the conversion date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 format for Limit Reference</p>
            <p>3 to 7 numeric characters LIMIT.REFERENCE code. (Optional Input; Default value:  see details below).</p>
            <p>Input in this field must be a valid LIMIT.REFERENCE number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will normally contain an interest payment date.</p>
            <p>When conversion takes place, this is the date on which the original contract will be matured (early) and the new contract will begin.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when the record is created)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains details of any overrides applicable to this item.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when overrides occur)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the reference number to uniquely identify a contract. The contract must already exist.</p>
            <p>The format of the key is as follows:</p>
            <p>AA YYDDD NNNNN A</p>
            <p>where:     AA       -     Application identifier.               YYDDD    -     Year and date of input in julian date format.               NNNNN    -     Sequence number which is unique for the date                              of input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>10 numeric characters prefixed by 2 characters identifying the application module.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.INT.CONV</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this field is set to 'Y', then it will allow non-interest-payment date conversions, otherwise not.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the interest amount charged, once the conversion has taken place.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OT.TRANSFER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERTED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the principal for the new contract after conversion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when the new contract is created)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.FT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the FT id for the interest accrued, once the conversion has taken place.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.TRANSFER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMIT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement.</p>
            <p>As in the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to define in the Item file up to 999 Local Elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified. These Local Elements should be defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice.</p>
            <p>The name(s) of the new element(s), as well as the Format and <p>Validation Rules:</p>, must be defined in the LOCAL.TABLE, prior to the creation of any conversion records.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters as defined in the Local Table definition for this Local Reference field.  Multivalue field.  (Optional or Mandatory Input according to definition in LOCAL.TABLE for this Local Reference element)</p>
            <p>As defined by the User within the LOCAL.TABLE and LOCAL.REF.TABLE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the amount of the FUNDS.TRANSFER transaction created for contracts where a principal repayment is scheduled for the conversion date. The FUNDS.TRANSFER will debit the original principal liquidation account and credit the suspense account used for early maturity (for loans). This will be vice versa for deposits.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when the original contract is matured early)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.TRANSFER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.CONV.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the actual business date on which the conversion took place.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field. (Populated by the system when the new contract is created)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the application to which this contract relates and will normally only contain:</p>
            <p>LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS             MG.MORTGAGE             MM.MONEY.MARKET             SWAP</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field. (Populated by the system when the record is created)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the category code to which this deal will be accounted for the transfer of the balance between contracts, i.e. the liquidation account for the old contract and the drawdown for the new contract. An account must exist for this category.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 format for Category.</p>
            <p>5 numeric characters Category code        or 2 numeric characters i.e. last 2 digits of valid category code.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input.  No Default Value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGINAL.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the principal for the original contract prior to conversion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when the new contract is created)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 currency field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OLD.LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the limit reference on the original contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when the record is created)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the currency to which the contract will be converted and is defaulted from the FIXED.CCY field on the currency record of the original currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.  (Populated by the system when the record is created)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

