<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EU</product>
<table>EU.CCY.CONVERSION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The application EU.CCY.CONVERSION is a utility to perform multiple contract and account conversions to EUR. The options specified will be used to create AC.CCY.CONVERSION records for each account to be converted and similarly to create EU.CONTRACT.CONVERSION records for contracts.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NCU.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEEP.MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       Y      NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency to which the Account or Contracts selected should be converted.</p>
            <p>The currency specified should be the currency that the contract or account currency is fixed to, e.g if DEM and FRF accounts are to be converted the NEW.CCY should be EUR since DEM and FRF are fixed to EUR.</p>
            <p>This field will populate:</p>
            <p>- NEW.CCY in the AC.CCY.CONVERSION record created for the ACCOUNT   APPLICATION</p>
            <p>- NEW.CCY in the EU.CONTRACT.CONVERSION record created for non ACCOUNT   APPLICATIONs</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry in the CURRENCY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RENUMBER.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the subroutine used to generate the new account number when an ACCOUNT is to be converted.</p>
            <p>When accounts are converted the account to be converted is renumbered. The number used must either be entered in the AC.CCY.CONVERSION record for the account, or allocated automatically using a subroutine. Since each site may decide on a different numbering convention, a subroutine can be written to return the renumbered account number.</p>
            <p>For example account numbers may be 10 digits, the leading digit is zero. A convention for the renumbered accounts could be to replace the leading '0' with a '9'. In order to do this a routine must be written to return the modified account number, the name of the routine must be specified here.</p>
            <p>For each ACCOUNT record selected an AC.CCY.CONVERSION record will be created and the specified subroutine will be executed. The account number returned will be stored in the RENUMBER.ACCT.NO field of the created record.</p>
            <p>Subroutine Details ------------------ The subroutine must have no arguments, the account number to be renumbered should be passed in the common variable COMI, the new value should also be returned in this variable. Any error should be returned in ETEXT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be defined in PGM.FILE as type S.</p>
            <p>Only allowed if APPLICATION is ACCOUNT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CLOSE.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether accounts are to be authomatically flagged for closure on conversion.</p>
            <p>When the NCU account is renumbered as part of the conversion process, there is an option to allow the renumbered account to be closed. This option will be taken if the field AUTO.CLOSE.ACCT is set to YES in the AC.CCY.CONVERSION record.</p>
            <p>Entry in this field will populate the AUTO.CLOSE.ACCT field in the AC.CCY.CONVERSION record which is created.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input when APPLICATION is ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>Input not allowed when APPLICATION is not ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>Must be YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 50 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.TRANSFER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HOLD.RECORDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NCU.LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 7 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:             2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is any unique key idetifying the bulk conditions and the conversion actions to be taken.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be 3-35 alpha characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECT.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the name of the field defined in the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the associated APPLICATION to be used to perform the selection specified in the associated fields OPERAND and VALUE.</p>
            <p>The field used may be of type 'D', 'I', 'J'. Multiple field selections can be specified by adding additional values to this field. Where multiple selection fields are used the combination is treated as 'AND' when performing the selection, so that records are only selected where each selection conidtion is true.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>At least one selection is required.</p>
            <p>Must be a field of type 'I', 'D' or 'J' defined in the STANDARD.SELECTION record for the APPLICATION.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.SUSP.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the value (or values) for the associated SELECTION.FIELD and OPERAND which must be true in order to request a contract or account conversion.</p>
            <p>A list of values may be specified by either entry of each value separated by a space, or by expanding the sub values. Multiple values for a field are treated as an 'OR'.</p>
            <p>When using operands LK or UL the value can be prefixed and or suffixed by '...' to signify the wildcard element of the value, for example to select accounts with MNEMONIC like GB would be specified as:</p>
            <p>SELECTION      MNEMONIC OPERAND        LK VALUE          ...GB...</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Any value may be specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.TRANSFER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IGNORED.RECORDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on which selected accounts are to be converted.</p>
            <p>This is the date on which the system will actually perform the account conversion, and will populate the field CONVERSION.DATE in the AC.CCY.CONVERSION record created.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory input for APPLICATION of ACCOUNT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERT.STO</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       Y      NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the OPERAND to be used with the SELECTION.FIELD and the specified VALUE.</p>
            <p>Valid OPERANDS are:</p>
            <p>EQ  -  Equals                    NE  -  Not Equal to                    RG  -  Within the range                    NR  -  Not in the range                    GE  -  Greater than or Equal to                    GT  -  Greater than                    LE  -  Less than or equal to                    LT  -  Less Than                    LK  -  Like                    UL  -  Unlike</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be defined for each SELECTION.FIELD.</p>
            <p>Must be EQ, NE, GE, GT, LE, LT, RG, NR, LK, UL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.POST.RESTRICT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the posting restriction to be used if accounts are to be automatically closed as part of the conversion process.</p>
            <p>The content of this field will populate the field POSTING.RESTRICT in the AC.CCY.CONVERSION records created for the selected accounts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed if APPLICATION is not ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 90 - 99.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry in the POSTING.RESTRICT application.</p>
            <p>Only allowed if AUTO.CLOSE.AC is set to YES.</p>
            <p>Not allowed if AUTO.CLOSE.AC is set to NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.TRANSFER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies which application the specified selection criteria apply to and therefore which application records are to be converted.</p>
            <p>The EU.CCY.CONVERSION application allow selections to be built for:</p>
            <p>ACCOUNT          LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS          MM.MONEY.MARKET          MG.MORTGAGE          SWAP</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
            <p>Must be ACCOUNT, MM.MONEY.MARKET, SWAP, MG.MORTGAGE or LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTH.RECORDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OT.TRANSFER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.INT.CONV</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this field is set to 'Y', then it will allow non-interest-payment date conversions, otherwise not.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

