<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>EU</product>
<table>SC.ACC.MASTER.CONV</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application may be used to define a new reference currency for a group of portfolio ids linked by a logical relationship. There are fields in the file that can be used to specify the logical relationship. The application will work out a list of portfolios that have been selected as a result of the relationship. These portfolios will be converted in the end of day processing by the program EOD.SC.CONV.REF.CCY that runs in the batch suite SC.BATCH.APP </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>UNSUCCESS.TEXT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will get populated in the end of day process that attempts to convert the portfolios listed in the SELECTED.IDS field if any error occured in this process. This field will contain the error text. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No INput Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTED.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be multi-valued and contains the list of all the SEC.ACC.MASTER records that will be processed. The list is selected as a result of the selection criteria specified in the fields above. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.CONTENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the value to be matched according to the OPERAND and FIELD.NO fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to specify the field number or name on the SEC.ACC.MASTER for which the selection criteria is being specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be an existing field no or name on the SEC.ACC.MASTER record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.REFERENCE.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the new reference currency to be used by the SEC.ACC.MASTER records listed in the SELECTED.IDS field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the condition to be used when selecting the field in FIELD.NO </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be any of 'EQ', 'NE', 'LT', 'GT', 'LE', 'GE', 'RG', 'NR', 'LK', 'UL'</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if FIELD.NO is entered</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNSUCCESS.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will get populated in the end of day process that attempts to convert the portfolios listed in the SELECTED.IDS field if any error occured in this process. This field will contain a list of PORTFOLIO IDS that were unsuccessful in the conversion attempt. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No INput Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a free formatted id field that may be used to identify the selection criteria. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Free Formatted</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

