<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.AUTO.BATCH</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application defines the upload reference for which auto batching needs to be triggered.</p>
            <p>ID will be in the format BA+Julian Date+5 digit sequence number</p>
            <p>E.g BA0101000001</p>
            </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free text field to record the description of auto batch definition.</p>
         </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the upload reference for which auto batching of registers needs to be done based on rules defined in BL.BATCH.CONDITIONS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid Upload reference updated in BL.REGISTER.</p>
            <p />
         </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date when auto batching process was executed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System maintained field.</p>
            <p />       
         </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ACTION to be performed on the registers on whether to batch registers based on upload reference (or) rebatch the registers when product is changed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values are “BATCH” and “REBATCH”</p>
            <p>Upload reference is mandatory for "BATCH"</p>
            <p>If upload reference is defined  then default value must be BATCH</p>
            <p>Seller ID is mandatory when REBATCH option is selected.</p>
            <p />       
         </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELLER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the customer for whom CHANGE PRODUCT (or) REBATCHING action needs to be triggered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory when CHANGE.PRODUCT or REBATCH is selected</p>
            <p>Not allowed with upload reference</p>
            <p>Must be valid customer record.</p>
            <p />       
         </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGE.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether product change action needs to be triggered for seller based on CHANGE PRODUCT preset conditions defined in BL.BATCH.CONDITIONS</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>SELLER ID mandatory when CHANGE PRODUCT is defined</p>
            <p>Not allowed with upload reference</p>
            <p />       
         </desc>
</t>

<t><field>BL.AUTO.BATCH.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>PROCESSED.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
