<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.BUYER.SELLER.LIMIT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to record the Buyer-Seller limit for information purpose.This application will hold Buyer's maximum exposure for which the record is setup</p>
            <p>The ID of the application could be the Buyer's customer reference suffixed with 'BS'</p>
            <p>The Buyer-Seller limit will be update when any BL.REGISTER which has the BL.TYPE attached has its INFO.PARTY defined as 'BUYER-SELLER'</p> 
            <p />        
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field defines the currency in which the BUYER-SELLER limit is defined</p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                </p>
            <p />
            <p> Id of the Currency</p>
        
        </desc>
        
        </t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to define the overall exposure of the buyer,Amount expressed in the currency defined in the CURRENCY field</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Field is Mandatory</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTSTANDING.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to update the current outstanding amount under the utilization of the limit expressed in the limit currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Updated field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAILABLE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to update the available amount under the limit expressed in the limit currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Updated field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELLER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to define the valid customer ID of the seller associated with the limit amount in LIMIT.AMT field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be a Valid customer ID in T24</p>
            <p>Cannot be same as Buyer's customer reference</p>
            <p>Associated Multi value that defines the limit amount, outstanding amount and currency specific amounts</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to define the buyer's maximum exposure towards the seller for whom this record is set up.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field will define the seller's exposure towards Buyer </p>
            <p>The Sum of the LIMIT.AMT cannot exceed the total Buyer's exposure.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.OS.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to update the current outstanding amount under the utilisation of the sub-limit expressed in the limit currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Updated field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to update the available amount under the limit expressed in the limit currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Updated field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to update the currency in which the current outstanding amount under the utilisation of the sub-limit is expressed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Updated field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OS.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to update the current outstanding amount under the utilization of the limit expressed in the currency of utilization.</p> 
            <p>The total of these amounts for all currencies to be updated in the field TOT.OS.AMT expressed in the limit currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>System Updated field.</p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETENTION.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field to define percentage of margin to be applied when a financial transaction is input involving the buyer and the seller.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Value defined will get defaulted in BL.REGISTER when BL.TYPE is assigned and retention margin is set to 'Allowed'.</p>
            <p>Acceptable values to be any numeric between 1 and 99.</p>  
            <p>Decimals not to be allowed.</p>  
            <p>Optional field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>BL.BS.LIMIT.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>OUTSTANDING.AMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>AVAILABLE.AMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>AVAIL.AMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
