<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.BALANCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file contains a record for each </p>
            <p>BILL.REGISTER </p>and store basic accounting information such as <p>VALUE-DATE, MATURITY-DATE, PRINCIPAL, TOTAL INTEREST, ACCRUED INTEREST, GRACE DAYS INTEREST, ETC.</p><p /><p>BL.REGISTER id is the key for this file.</p><p /><p>After the no of days as mentioned in BL.PARAMETER to move it to history from the date of maturity of the BL contract, these details will be moved to history file- BL.BALANCES.HIST.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Drawer of the Bill (in case of a customer) or the Liability Customer (in case of a customer) will default in this field for that BR.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.GRACE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the total Interest collected upfront for the Grace days. However the Grace days interest received in advance will be accrued on the last working day before the maturity of the contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The present status of the Bill will appear in this field.</p>
            <p>The following are the details of status, maintained by the system :</p>
            <p>CURR: The bill is in live status</p>
            <p>REVE: The bill is reversed status</p>
            <p>LIQ: The bill is in liquidated status</p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p>This is an internal file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of  the Bill as defined in BTTC  will appear in this field. eg. Collateral, Discount, Collection</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The BL id to which the BR is attached is shown here. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQ.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Liquidation Mode (Automatic, Semi-Automatic or Manual) as defined in the BR/BL will appear in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency market defined while BL application will appear in this field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>HCurrently not used</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Interest spread as defined in the BL.BILL contract defaulted here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Consol key ( key of the consolidation record in the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file) will appear in this column</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>
                <p>Internal field </p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the effective interest rate as specified in the respective BL.BILL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Position type as defined for the BL contract will appear here.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.ACCR.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The last date up to which the Accrual done for Interest Received in Advance for BL contract of  Discount operation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently not used</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently not used </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAILY.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the amount that has to be accrued daily.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.ACCRUED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently not used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Interest Basis as defined in the BL.BILL will be defaulted here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of the Bill as defined in BR will appear in this field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINCIPAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Principal amount of the BL.Register will appear in this field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the Interest key applicable for the BL.BILL Contract.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account officer as defined in the BL gets defaulted here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUED.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the amount accrued up to date as specified in the last accrual date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BILL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id for BL.BALANCES is the BL.REGISTER Id.Based on the Id of BR all accounting information related to the BR will appear in the screen</p>
            <p>No input file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The BL.Bill category will appear in this field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the Bill Register will appear in this field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROJ.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the total Discount amount collected upfront from the customer for the actual no of days of the contract (Not including the Grace days)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Maturity date of the Bill as defined in the BR will appear in this field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAILY.GRACE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the daily accrual to be done for the Grace days.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currently not used</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EFF.PRINCIPAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Records the principal balance on the Contract at each stage during settlements throughout the life of the deal</p>
            <p>Records each principal balance of the deal over it's lifetime. The field consists of a number of multi-values each recording the principal balance of the deal at various stages. The date on which the amount became effective is recorded on the associated multi-vale of the field EFF.DATE</p>
            <p>This field denotes maximum amount that can be disbursed out of a BL.BATCH record. It is the sum of all MAX.AVAIL.AMOUNT of all BL.REGISTER records attached in the batch</p>

               <p>Validation Rules:</p>
           
                <p>System maintained field </p>
                <p>Standard T24 Amount Field</p>
                <p>Multi-Valued field associated with EFF.DATE</p>
           
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the principal balance amounts in the EFF.PRINCIPAL field became effective</p>
            <p>Records each date that the principal balance field changes during settlements</p>
            
               <p>Validation Rules:</p>
           
                <p>Standard date format Multi-valued field associated with EFF.PRINCIPAL</p>
                <p>System maintained  Field</p>
           
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>SUSP.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the unamortised discount interest portion is suspended, then this field holds the total suspended interest amount until it is recognized.</p>
            <p>This shall be reversed during any of below events happened in an invoice.</p>
            <p>1)  Maturity or settlement with liquidation mode as AUTOMATIC.</p>
            <p>2)  When the SUSPEND.INT is marked from YES to NO.</p>
            <p>3)  Underlying PD is settled or written off.</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

