<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.BILL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The individual Bill Registers and Bill Batches are attached and made as a contract through this application.</p>
            <p>The id for this application is auto generated once it is defined in AUTO.ID.START and COMPANY files. The id format is BLYYDDDNNNNN.</p>
            <p>It is possible to include both individual Bills and Bill Batches in a Bill Contract. When a </p>
            <p>BL.BATCH is included in a Bill Contract, the system would expand and display all the BL.REGISTERS attached to the Batch. Only authorized BL.REGISTERS and BL.BATCHES could be included in a Bill Contract.</p>
            <p>A BL.REGISTER or BL.BATCH already included in a Bill Contract could not be included again in another Bill Contract. The system would ensure that all the BL.REGISTERS attached to a Bill Contract (either directly or through Batches) are of the same currency and with same LIABILITY.CUSTOMER as specified in the Contract. Bills of  different Liability Customers cannot be attached in a Bill Contract.</p>
            <p>While it is possible to attach BL.REGISTERS of different BL.TYPE in the same batch, it is not possible to have a contract by attaching different BL.TYPES. However, if the BL.TYPE is of the same product, it can be batched and the Contract can be made. </p>
            <p>The system would ensure that all the BL.REGISTERS attached to a Bill Contract (either directly or through Batches) have their START.DATE not later than the VALUE.DATE of the Bill Contract. It is possible to include BL.REGISTERS maturing on different dates in a Bill contract. It is possible to Add/Remove BL.REGISTERS/BL.BATCHES to an already authorised Bill Contract. Copy Option is not allowed in this Application. After the no of days as mentioned in BL.PARAMETER to move it to history from the date of maturity of the BL contract, these details will be moved to history file- BL.BILL.HIST.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REM.BR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>When we have to remove a BR from an existing authorised BL, the BR id to be entered in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid BR id attached to the existing BL.</p>
            <p>BR id for which the collection status not changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the flat amount of charges to be debited to the Customer on the value date for a new contract, or on-line for an existing contract.</p>
            <p>The charges amounts will always be defined in contract currency.</p>
            <p>When a charge code defined in BTTC contains a CHARGE.CODE linking it to FT.CHARGE.TYPE/FT.COMMISSION.TYPE, the charge amount will be defaulted when no input is made to this field. The charge amount will be based on the outstanding principal of the contract at input time, according to the rates defined in the FT charges table.</p>
            <p>Charge/Commission  receivable will be debited from the CHRG.LIQ.ACCT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CALC.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the Interest Method is "Yield Added", Interest calculation frequency will defined here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Interest frequency format.</p>
            <p>Daily/Monthly</p>
            <p>Mandatory for "YIELD ADDED" Interest Method.</p>
            <p>For other Interest method -No input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOLIDATE.ENTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an YES or NO field. </p>
            <p>When more than one Statement Entry appear in an Application, it results in multiple entries in the statement of the customer. To make the sum of all the multiple entries to appear as one entry in the Statement, we define "YES" in this field. If "NO" is keyed in, the multiple entries will appear as it is in the statements.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Yes or No </p>
            <p>Defaults from the Consolidate.entry field as defined in BL.PARAEMTER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.TAX.CHG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. The total  tax on charges amount collected for this particular contract will reflect in this field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the value date (or start) of the contract.</p>
            <p>When value is not entered defaults to Today.</p>
            <p>If entered by the User, it should be greater than or equal to Deal Date.</p>
            <p>This date should be greater than or equal to the Start Date of all attached Bill Registers.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-9 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input. Default equals     system date.)   </p>
            <p>An override will be required if the date as defined on the HOLIDAY table     is a non working day.   </p>
            <p>Must be prior to FIN.MAT.DATE.   </p>
            <p>Once the contract has been authorised, this field cannot be changed.</p>
            <p>An override will be required if the date is not defined on the HOLIDAY     table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.INTEREST.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents a reference on the TAX table which will indicate the rate to be used for the computation of Interest taxation.</p>
            <p>This field can be defaulted if the TAX.INTEREST.TYPE field is used. See the help text for CONTRACT.GRP and TAX.INTEREST.TYPE for further information.</p>
            <p>Interest taxation in all instances is charged on the relevant interest payment dates. No accrual will be performed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2 numeric characters. (Optional input. Default = no tax.)   </p>
            <p>Must be a valid reference on the TAX table.   </p>
            <p>Once authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field updated automatically once committed.</p>
            <p>Tax on charges/commission amount is updated by the system if defined in FT.CHARGE/COMMISSION.TYPE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-set, this field is used to determine the message type to which the user wishes to amend the delivery and is used exclusively with the fields &lt;MSG.CLASS.NO&gt;, &lt;OVR.CARRIER&gt; and &lt;SEND.MESSAGE&gt;.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 4 numeric characters. (Optional input).   </p>
            <p>The record must be defined on the DE.MESSAGE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REM.BB.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>When we have to remove a BB from an existing authorised BL, the BB id is populated into this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid BB id which is attached to the existing BL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Bill reference no will be generated by the system and maintained here.</p>
            <p>Contains the delivery keys used for the generation of BL advices / documents / payments from the Electronic Delivery System.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current date being the defaulted date of the Bill Contract, is populated automatically </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Deal date should be less than or equal to Today.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLL.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Overall Collection Status of the BL is defined here from either of Cleared or Returned. Appropriate transaction gets generated based on the collection status.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will identify the LIMIT.REFERENCE number to be checked for limit control on BL transactions.</p>
            <p>Each BL transaction will be checked against the LIMIT file to verify the availability of a limit facility for the customer specified in BL Contract. If no input is made at this field, the LIMIT system will provide a default according to the values defined in the LIMIT.PARAMETER file. If required, more details can be found in the LIMIT user guide.</p>
            <p>For Collection Bills limit reference will be updated based on the Default.Info as defined in LIMIT.PARAMETER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3-7 numeric characters.   </p>
            <p>Input to this field must be a valid LIMIT.REFERENCE number.   </p>
            <p>If no limit exists for the customer, a corresponding error message will be     displayed by the system with an override facility.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.BB.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The BB id of the new BB which is to be added to the existing BL Contract specified here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a authorised BB which is not linked to any BL</p>
            <p>Added BB currency should be equal to BL contract currency  </p>
            <p>Liability customer should be equal to BL Customer.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.COLL.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>BL.BILL</p>
            <p>BR.COLL.STATUS</p>
            <p>The Collection Status of the BR is defined here from either of  Cleared or Returned. Appropriate transaction entries are created based on the collection status.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Either Cleared or Returned. </p>
            <p>Available after authorisation. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local Currency equivalent of the tax amount appearing in the previous field Tax Amount.</p>
            <p>No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMD.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. If there is an amendment made to this contract like adding one more BR or deleting a BR from the BL Contract, the value date of the amendment will get populated here automatically.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Defaults to system date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local currency value of the Charge amount is updated by the system when the charge amount is non Local currency.</p>
            <p>No input Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REM.BB.BR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. When a BB is removed from an existing BL through rem bb no. field, when the contract is committed, the BR numbers attached of  the removed  BB will populate this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p> Number to identify either a Statement Entry or a Category Entry in respect    of the contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults to the Interest rate basis as defined for the Contract currency in CURRENCY Application.</p>
            <p>Following Interest Keys are supported in Bill module expect "S" Special for Interest method Discount and Yield added. </p>
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>Key</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Days/Denominator</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>A</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>A1</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/360*</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>A2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/360*</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>B</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/360</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>C</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>D</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/366</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>E</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>366/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>F</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/365</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>F1</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/365*</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>F2</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>360/365*</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>S</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Special</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>For Discount to Yield Interest method C &amp; D Interest Basis not Allowed.</p>
            <p>For illustrations of all supported </p>
            <p>INTEREST.BASIS types and for types marked * see: INTEREST.BASIS</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-2 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input. Default = CURRENCY     table value)   </p>
            <p>Once authorised this field cannot be changed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMD.BR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIN.LIQ.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the account number where entries are made for the reimbursement of the principal at liquidation.</p>
            <p>Based on ACCOUNT.PARAMETER definition, system defaults the accounts.</p>
            <p>In case the underlying Contract Customer (eg. Customer.id in MONEYMARKET,Counterparty in FOREX, etc.) has a record in CUSTOMER.SSI application, then the account number in this field gets defaulted as per the definition for that Customer from CUSTOMER.SSI. For more information on the usage of this feature please refer to CUSTOMER.SSI application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-14 numeric characters-relating to a Customer Account, a Nostro Account.     or 3-10 alphanumeric account mnemonic. (Optional input. Default value =     Drawdown account.)   </p>
            <p>Must be a valid ACCOUNT number or mnemonic.   </p>
            <p>The system will check for posting restrictions and require an override if     necessary.   </p>
            <p>The principal liquidation account must be denominated in the contract     currency</p>
            <p>Once authorised, this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field denotes the date on which the message as defined in this multivalue set will get generated.  Incase the message has to be produced for a future date, then that future date has to be mentioned here. </p>
            <p>If the message date is for a future date, then the messages are scheduled and generated as on that date through BL batch processing. Scheduled message detail is available in BL.BILL.DELIVERY.SCHEDULE for the corresponding BL no and scheduled date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Default value null </p>
            <p>If null message will be generated as of activity date.</p>
            <p>Should be a valid Date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional  input field. The default mechanism (see below) will happen as per below automatically along with other fields ( INT.SPREAD, INT.KEY).</p>
            <p>Default Mechanism</p>
            <p>1.</p>
            <p>The system would first look for an appropriate BTTC record and take the values defined therein. Then it would use the values defined in appropriate BGC record for modification/override purposes. Finally it could use the values from BL.PARAMETER. It is possible that some of the fields<p />in BTTC or BGC records are not defined (null values). As a general rule, the system would skip these fields and<p />use the values defined at the next level of parameter records. <p>2.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract are same then the system would first look for a BTTC record with key "DISCOUNT*NNNN" where "NNNN" is the value of the common Bill-Type. If there is no such record<p />then the system would look for a record with key "DISCOUNT". <p>3.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract is<p />not the same, then the system would only look for a BTTC record with key DISCOUNT. <p>4.</p><p />The system would first update the Contract Group field in Bills Contract; it would determine which is the first<p />Contract Group defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION file (Record Key: BL)which satisfy the Bill Contract conditions.<p />If no contract group defined therein satisfies the Bill Contract conditions, the system would not update<p />the Contract Group field in<p />the Bills Contract. <p>5.</p><p />The BGC file could have records<p />with key values of either "C-Customer No." or a valid Bill Contract Group. In BGC, the system would first look for a record with key "C-Customer No.". If<p />the record<p />does not exist, then the system would look for a record with key equal to the Contract Group field in the Bills Contract. <p>6.</p><p />The values in BGC record fields could in some cases override the BTTC values are in some cases could modify the BTTC values. It is possible that both BTTC and BGC records are not available or that the values for some fields are not defined in these records. In such cases, the values from the BL.PARAMETER file <p />would be used by the system to default the values.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Interest rate is allowed if the Interest key and Interest spread is NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMEND.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. If there is an amendment made to this contract like adding one more BR or deleting a BR from the BL Contract, the date on which the amendment will get populated here automatically.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Defaults to system date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.PRINCIPAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>If there is a change in the Principal due to any amendment in the Bill, while the Principal field will show the latest Principal, this field will default the original principal, when  first time contract is committed and authorised.</p>
            <p>This is a no input field.  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMD.EXP.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. If there is an amendment made to this contract like adding one more BR or deleting a BR from the BL Contract, and if there is any change in the expiry date of the contract, this amended date amendment will get populated here automatically. </p>
            <p>In an existing  contract, if the newly added BR or BB has a new expiry date which is greater than the existing expiry date reflecting in the contract, the new expiry date will reflect here.</p>
            <p>On the contrary, if the newly added BR or BB has a an expiry date which lesser than or equal to the existing expiry date reflecting in the contract, there will not be be any change in the expiry date populated here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated by the system - Tax Code for the Charges. Tax code defined for the charge in FT.CHARGE.TYPE / FT.COMMISSION.TYPE will be defaulted here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.DISC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field which is filled automatically when a bill is discounted. The amount defaulted in this column is the total discount on the Bill Contract. The discounted amount is equivalent to the interest charged on the principal of the Bill at the specified rate of interest for the period of maturity of the Bill at the defined Interest Basis.</p>
            <p>Eg. Bill Amount US $ 100000; Tenor of the Bill 60 days; Grace Days 3C;Int Basis  B(366/360)</p>
            <p>Rate of Interest is 10%</p>
            <p>The Total Disc Amount is calculated as follows:</p>
            <p>US$ 100000 x 10/100 x63/360 = US$ 1750.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWDOWN.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the account number to which the principal Amount of BL.BILL contract would be credited.</p>
            <p>This is an optional field. If not entered, default would be the first account in the Currency of Contract for the Contract Customer as per ACCOUNT.PARAMETER definition. System would issue override message if an account belonging to another customer is entered.</p>
            <p>In case the underlying Contract Customer (eg. Customer.id in MONEYMARKET,Counterparty in FOREX, etc.) has a record in CUSTOMER.SSI application, then the account number in this field gets defaulted as per the definition for that Customer from CUSTOMER.SSI. For more information on the usage of this feature please refer to CUSTOMER.SSI application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input. Defaults to account in contract currency for the BL.BILL       customer..</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid ACCOUNT number or mnemonic.</p>
            <p>The system will check for account posting restrictions and require an     override if necessary.</p>
            <p>The drawdown account must be denominated in the contract Currency.</p>
            <p>Once authorised , accounts cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.BR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The BR id which has to be added with the existing BL has to be given here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid BR id which is not linked to any BL/BB</p>
            <p>Liability customer equal to the BL customer for Discount Operation.</p>
            <p>BR currency should be of existing BL  currency</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional with values "Discount" or "Discount to Yield" or "Yield Added". </p>
            <p> Default value is "Discount".</p>
            <p> See user guide to know the calculation details.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>If Interest Method is Yield added - Interest basis C &amp; D not       Allowed.</p>
            <p>No input field once authorised.</p>
            <p>For "Yield added" method Interest Calculation Frequency is       mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.LIQ.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the account to which the fees/charges will be debited.</p>
            <p>This field indicates the account which will be debited with any charges applicable to a Bills contract.</p>
            <p>Fees and Charges are always expressed in the contract currency.</p>
            <p>In case the underlying Contract Customer (eg. Customer.id in MONEYMARKET,Counterparty in FOREX, etc.) has a record in CUSTOMER.SSI application, then the account number in this field gets defaulted as per the definition for that Customer from CUSTOMER.SSI. For more information on the usage of this feature please refer to CUSTOMER.SSI application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-14 numeric characters-relating to a Customer Account or         a Nostro or a Internal Account. or 3-10 alphanumeric         account mnemonic. (Optional input. Default = Principal         liquidation account.) </p>
            <p>The system will check for account posting restrictions         and require an override if necessary. </p>
            <p>Must be an account denominated in the contract currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.BL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Holds the BL.REGISTER of BL.BILL reference for which the delivery message is produced</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>NOINPUT field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field enables the user to override the defaulted carrier for a particular message type and select a new carrier.</p>
            <p>For example : If a specific message is generated by SWIFT, the user is able to override this by choosing other available options from the CARRIER table, eg TELEX or PRINT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid record in the CARRIER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This specifies the operation of the Bill and based on this operation appropriate entries are generated.</p>
            <p>Valid operations are COLLATERAL / COLLECTION / DISCOUNT.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.INTEREST.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Using this field together with the CONTRACT.GRP field it is possible to determine a particular tax code from conditions based on:</p>
            <p>General tax type as defined in the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION application Type of customer as defined in the CUSTOMER.CHARGES application Type of contract as defined in the CONTRACT.GRP field.</p>
            <p>The CONTRACT.GRP code is determined every time the contract is changed by evaluating the conditions defined in the BILLS record of the APPL.GEN.CONDITION application. (see  APPL.GEN.CONDTION for more information).</p>
            <p>The value in this field must equate to a record in the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION application which contains tax codes related to customer tax group and contract group.</p>
            <p>Whenever interest tax is recalculated the correct tax code will be determined and the TAX.INTEREST.KEY and TOT.INT.TAX fields updated accordingly.</p>
            <p>If the calculated tax amount changes between sending a payment and the end of the relevant tax period then an exception will be raised during the end of day indicating the different amounts.</p>
            <p>It will be stored in EXCEPTION.LOG.HIST.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input, must be present as a record on TAX.TYPE.CONDITION. The     actual TAX.TYPE.CONDITION key value will be prefixed by the "*"     character (asterisk).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BILL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The id for this application is auto generated. The id format is BLyydddnnnnn. If you press F3 or any other key mapped for auto-default. The id will get autogenerated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional  input field. The default mechanism (see below) will happen as per below automatically along with other fields ( INT.SPREAD,INT.RATE).</p>
            <p>Default Mechanism</p>
            <p>1.</p>
            <p>The system would first look for an appropriate BTTC record and take the values defined therein. Then it would use the values defined in appropriate BGC record for modification/override purposes. Finally it could use the values from BL.PARAMETER. It is possible that some of the fields<p />in BTTC or BGC records are not defined (null values). As a general rule, the system would skip these fields and<p />use the values defined at the next level of parameter records. <p>2.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract are same then the system would first look for a BTTC record with key "DISCOUNT*NNNN" where "NNNN" is the value of the common Bill-Type. If there is no such record<p />then the system would look for a record with key "DISCOUNT". <p>3.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract is<p />not the same, then the system would only look for a BTTC record with key DISCOUNT. <p>4.</p><p />The system would first update the Contract Group field in Bills Contract; it would determine which is the first<p />Contract Group defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION file (Record Key: BL)which satisfy the Bill Contract conditions.<p />If no contract group defined therein satisfies the Bill Contract conditions, the system would not update<p />the Contract Group field in<p />the Bills Contract. <p>5.</p><p />The BGC file could have records<p />with key values of either "C-Customer No." or a valid Bill Contract Group. In BGC, the system would first look for a record with key "C-Customer No.". If<p />the record<p />does not exist, then the system would look for a record with key equal to the Contract Group field in the Bills Contract. <p>6.</p><p />The values in BGC record fields could in some cases override the BTTC values are in some cases could modify the BTTC values. It is possible that both BTTC and BGC records are not available or that the values for some fields are not defined in these records. In such cases, the values from the BL.PARAMETER file <p />would be used by the system to default the values.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid BASIC.INTEREST or PERIODIC.INTEREST key is allowed</p>
            <p>To specify PERIODIC.INTEREST key, prefix the "P" with the interest key. (Example: For periodic interest key "01" ,specify it as "P01")</p>
            <p>Interest Key is allowed only when the Interest Rate is NULL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.BB.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is a non-input field. This is updated by the system when committed, with the ID of the Bill Contract or Bill Batch or Bill Register for which the following charges are applied. This field is associated  with  Charge Code and Charge Amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Category Code to which this transaction will be assigned. This will default once it is defined in BL.TYPE.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 numeric characters.   </p>
            <p>No input field   </p>
            <p>Must exist on the CATEGORY table.   </p>
            <p>Once authorised the contract Category code can not be changed through this     Application</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional  input field. The default mechanism (see below) will happen as per below automatically along with other fields ( INT.KEY,INT.RATE).</p>
            <p>Default Mechanism</p>
            <p>1.</p>
            <p>The system would first look for an appropriate BTTC record and take the values defined therein. Then it would use the values defined in appropriate BGC record for modification/override purposes. Finally it could use the values from BL.PARAMETER. It is possible that some of the fields<p />in BTTC or BGC records are not defined (null values). As a general rule, the system would skip these fields and<p />use the values defined at the next level of parameter records. <p>2.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract are same then the system would first look for a BTTC record with key "DISCOUNT*NNNN" where "NNNN" is the value of the common Bill-Type. If there is no such record<p />then the system would look for a record with key "DISCOUNT". <p>3.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract is<p />not the same, then the system would only look for a BTTC record with key DISCOUNT. <p>4.</p><p />The system would first update the Contract Group field in Bills Contract; it would determine which is the first<p />Contract Group defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION file (Record Key: BL)which satisfy the Bill Contract conditions.<p />If no contract group defined therein satisfies the Bill Contract conditions, the system would not update<p />the Contract Group field in<p />the Bills Contract. <p>5.</p><p />The BGC file could have records<p />with key values of either "C-Customer No." or a valid Bill Contract Group. In BGC, the system would first look for a record with key "C-Customer No.". If<p />the record<p />does not exist, then the system would look for a record with key equal to the Contract Group field in the Bills Contract. <p>6.</p><p />The values in BGC record fields could in some cases override the BTTC values are in some cases could modify the BTTC values. It is possible that both BTTC and BGC records are not available or that the values for some fields are not defined in these records. In such cases, the values from the BL.PARAMETER file <p />would be used by the system to default the values.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Interest Spread is allowed if the Interest Rate is NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows particular groups of contracts to be identified.</p>
            <p>The conditions which define a particular group are defined using the APPL.GEN.CONDITION for BL Application.</p>
            <p>Each time the contract is changed the conditions are re-evaluated which can result in a new CONTRACT.GRP code.</p>
            <p>This code can be defined in the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION application to refer to a particular tax code, in conjunction with the relevant customer group condition.</p>
            <p>If the CONTRACT.GRP changes then this may well result in new codes being allocated to the relevant TAX.PRINCIPAL.KEY, TAX.INTEREST.KEY and TAX.COMMISSION.KEY fields being updated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>5 character alphanumeric.</p>
            <p>No input field and updated by the system.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Insert text here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Rule 1</p>
            <p>Rule 2</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.CHG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. The total charges charged for this particular contract will reflect in this column.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field. Currency is defaulted once the Contract is committed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The currency will be same as that of Bill.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field updated automatically once committed.</p>
            <p>Tax on Interest (discount) amount is updated by the system by picking the Key from the Tax table for calculating Interest Tax.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BB.COLL.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>BL.BILL</p>
            <p>BB.COLL.STATUS</p>
            <p>The Collection Status of the BB is defined here from either Cleared or Returned. Appropriate transaction entries gets generated based on Collection Status.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the identification number or mnemonic assigned to the Customer. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3-10 alphanumeric customer mnemonic or 1-10 numeric character customer   number. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid CUSTOMER number or mnemonic.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Once the contract has been authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the dealer desk position which needs to be updated by the deal being created. The dealer desk code is held on the position record so that the exchange position can be displayed at dealer desk level.</p>
            <p>Each deal on the system will be allocated a two-digit dealer desk code. This code will be used to maintain position at the dealer desk level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2 alphanumeric character dealer code in the range A-Z, a-z, plus 0-9.     Optional input; Default = dealer desk defined on the user profile.   </p>
            <p>The code entered must appear on the DEALER.DESK table.   </p>
            <p>When entering an internal deal, the dealer must be different from the one     entered in the counter party field.   </p>
            <p>The field cannot be changed once the deal has been authorised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BB.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the ID of the Authorised Bill Batch(s) attached to this Bill Contract.</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field that facilitates inclusion of  more than one  Bill Batch under this Contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be a valid Bill Batch ID   </p>
            <p>Batch should not be attached to any BILL. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINCIPAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the total amount of the BL.Registers attached to the Bill Contract. This is an optional field. If the user enters amount, it would be validated against the total amount of all Bill Registers attached to the contract. If not entered by the user, this field would be updated by the system, when the contract is committed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.LIQ.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the account number where entries are made for the reimbursement of the Interest (together with any taxes applicable to that interest) at liquidation.</p>
            <p>The defaulting process looks firstly at the SEC.ACC.MASTER record using the portfolio no. If no default found uses the CUSTOMER.CCY.ACCT record and finally if still no default found takes details from the AGENCY record and NOSTRO.ACCOUNT table. These settings can be overriden by using ACCOUNT.PARAMETER to set the account default method.</p>
            <p>In a case where interest is subject to taxes, such taxes will always remain associated with their interest amount and will always be liquidated through the same account.</p>
            <p>Thus it is not possible to liquidate interest and ocrresponding taxes through two different accounts or in two different currencies.</p>
            <p>Input in this field will be necessary only when the idsposal of the interest is different from the disposal of the principal.</p>
            <p>This field cannot be changes once BL contract is authorised.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-14 numeric characters-relating to a Customer Account or         a Nostro Account or Internal Account. </p>
            <p>3-10 type A alphanumeric account mnemonic. (Optional         input. Default value = PRIN.LIQ.ACCT).</p>
            <p>The system will check for account posting restrictions         and will require an override if necessary. </p>
            <p>Must be a valid ACCOUNT number or mnemonic. </p>
            <p>The Interest liquidation account must be denominated in         the contract currency. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The date when the Bill contract is due to mature. Optional field.</p>
            <p>When the user enters a date system check that the date is equal to latest maturity date. Otherwise System Defaults the latest maturity date of the Bill Register or Bill Batch when more than one Bill is attached in the same contract.</p>
            <p>Example</p>
            <p>Bill no.            Maturity Date</p>
            <p>BR0102200005        20010120 </p>
            <p>BR0102200004        20010210</p>
            <p>BR0102200002        20010205</p>
            <p>If all the above BR's are entered in the same contract, the maturity date which is defaulting will be 20010210.</p>
            <p>The system raises override when the maturity date is a non working day in the country(ies) defined in BUS.DAY.DEFN.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No Input Field.</p>
            <p>For Discounted Bills, the Discounted Amount which is currently the Interest amount which is calculated based on the tenor of the Bill  and debited to the Interest Liquidation Account a pre defined by the User. This is calculated automatically and populated in this field. </p>
            <p>This shows the Discount interest collected upfront for the BR mentioned in the Multivalue set.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.TAX.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total of all the taxes pertaining to the Interest will get populated in this field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMD.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Acting as part of the delivery multivale set, this field provides the user with the ability to decide whether to send or withhold delivery of any message produced under the contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options available are (Y)es - Send Message or (N)o - Do Not Send Message   </p>
            <p>Default is (Y)es</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the account officer responsible for the relationship with the CPARTY. This information will be used by the Management Information System (MIS) for the determination of the Customer Profitability Analysis.</p>
            <p>This field has been provided to enable the user to override at transaction level the CPARTY default account officer defined in the CUSTOMER file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-4 digit numeric field.   </p>
            <p>(Optional input; Default value = Account Officer specified on the CPARTY's customer file.)   </p>
            <p>The Account Officer Code must appear on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>No Input field. System updates this field based on the user operation in BL module.</p>
            <p>This field holds the activity number, which is triggered by the latest activity in the life-cycle of the transaction.. The activity is 4 digit number composed of three main parts:</p>
            <p>First indicates the operation </p>
            <p>1. Collection, 2- Discount, 3- Collateral</p>
            <p>Second indicates the function </p>
            <p>1 -New  2-Amend   3 - Maturity  4- Reversal &amp; 5     -Tracer </p>
            <p>Third indicates the type of Bills.</p>
            <p />
            <p>1. Outward &amp; 2 . Inward</p>
            <p>Forth &amp; Last digit indicates the storing information details</p>
            <p />
            <p>1. BR level (BL.REGISTER)  2. BL level (BL.BILL)</p>
            <p>For example. : For the outward collection input activity,  the activity code is</p>
            <p>for operation  is "1", function "1", type "1" and for BR level information ="1"</p>
            <p>Hence the activity code is "BL-1111".</p>
            <p>The complete list of activity codes can be found in Users Manual.</p>
            <p>Should be a valid record in EB.ACTIVITY.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field has the date for the activity code as specified in the previous field.  The system generates appropriate Activity code &amp; activity date based on the user input.</p>
            <p>No Input field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.BB.BR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. When a BB/BR is attached to an existing BL through Add BR/BB no. field and contract is committed, the new BR/BB numbers attached to BL will be populated in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQ.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Optional with values AUTOMATIC, SEMI-AUTOMATIC or MANUAL. Default would be No value. If a value is entered in this field, Liquidation Mode field in all the Bill Registers attached to the Bill, would be updated to that value.</p>
            <p>(See PD user guide for more information)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory if the consolidate entry is set to "YES"</p>
            <p>Once authorised cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a mandatory field which will determine whether the commission/charge to be charged or  to be waived.</p>
            <p>If entered as "Y" then the BR/BB/BL id, charge related fields in BL will not be defaulted and  commission/charges will not be collected.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid values "Yes" or "No"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUS.DAY.DEFN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates those countries whose calendars must be checked with regard to holiday validation.</p>
            <p>The default value will be the Country of the currency of the Contract but the User can input any number of extra codes if required. For example, the country of the participants.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>4 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input. Multivalue field.)   </p>
            <p>The code must have a valid entry on the REGION/HOLIDAY table.   </p>
            <p>Once authorised a change in this field will require redefinition of the     schedules.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.TYPE.COND</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No Input field. Once the contract is committed, this field would be updated with the value id of BL.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION which satisfies the Bill operation and BL.TYPE .</p>
            <p>If these records exist in BTTC file for the Operation and BL.TYPE or Operation alone then that Id will get updated (Refer to Defaulting Mechanism). Otherwise value will be NULL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BB.BR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. This field is automatically populated with the BRs pertaining to the BB ids entered in the previous field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.MKT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency Market related to this transaction.</p>
            <p>This field will be applicable to those users in different countries, where the exchange control authorities have defined different markets for foreign currency dealing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 numeric digit Currency Market code. (Optional input. Default = 1)   </p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the CURRENCY.MARKET table.   </p>
            <p>Once the contract has been authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSURE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a No Input field. Defaults to value date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the ID of the Authorised Bill Register(s) attached to this Bill Contract..</p>
            <p>This is a multi-value field that facilitates inclusion of  more than one  Bill Register under this batch.</p>
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be a valid Bill Register ID   </p>
            <p>Should not be a un-authorised / matured Bill/ Bill already attached to other batches/contracts</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERPOLATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the interest key is specified as PERIODIC.INTEREST key , then Interpolation will be done to arrive the interest rate for a period (Like interpolation done for Money Market Application)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Defaulted to "YES"</p>
            <p>No Input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional field with the Format nnC or nnW where nn is a number from 1 to 99. An input of 0 is also allowed. "C" stands for Calendar days and "W" for Working Days.</p>
            <p>If no value is entered, then the value would default as explained below which is a defaulting mechanism.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If BGC value is defined (not null) then BGC value would be defaulted.</p>
            <p>If BTTC value is defined (not null) and BGC value is not defined (null), then BTTC value would be defaulted. If both BGC and BTTC values were not defined (null), then the Grace Days defined in the BL.PARAMETER file would be defaulted.  </p>
            <p>Discount Interest will be calculated  and charged upfront based on actual no of day Plus Grace days as specified here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Value of 1-99 allowed prefixed by "C" or "W" </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defaults from position type of BL.PARAMETER </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Defaults value "TR"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COL.STA.DAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. This field is updated with the current business date automatically when the collection status is changed to "Cleared OR Returned"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>An integral part of the 'Delivery' multi-value set, this field contains a message class ID, (defined in EB.ADVICES). There may be many classes specified, but only classes, which are related to the operation, will be triggered. </p>
            <p> For example, the EB.ADVICES number BL-1312 (BL Collection Maturity Realisation) may have the following classes and messages:</p>
            <p>Message No. : 405</p>
            <p>EB.MESSAG.CLASS : DRAWER BILL REALISATION ADVICE</p>
            <p>Message No. : 910</p>
            <p>EB.MESSAG.CLASS : CREDIT ADVICE</p>
            <p>And let us assume that the EB.MESSAGE.CLASS ID has been mapped to BL  internal class specified in BL.PARAMETER as follows:</p>
            <p>MATURITY.CLEAR= DRAWER BILL COLLECTION ADVICE</p>
            <p>CREDIT.CUST=CREDIT.ADVICE  </p>
            <p>User can choose whether to produce the messages or Not by changing the YES/NO flag - </p>
            <p>SEND.NOTICE.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Bill Contract currency.</p>
            <p>This field indicates the currency of the contract. The currency should be the same as the Currency of all attached Bill Registers</p>
            <p>.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 alphabetic currency mnemonic or 1-3 numeric character currency code.     (Mandatory Input.)   </p>
            <p>The currency code or mnemonic must exist on the CURRENCY table.   </p>
            <p>Once the contract has been authorised this field cannot be changed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents a reference on the FT.CHARGE/COMMISSION.TYPE.CONDITIONS table which holds the Profit and Loss Category code where the charge amount will be credited.</p>
            <p>Charges have not been restricted to any product but can be defined for all the products covered by the Bills Module; such charges can be applied on the date of the Contract only.</p>
            <p>Charges or Commission will be handled by the system on a cash basis.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-3 numeric characters. (Optional input. Multivalue field. Default value     on FT.CHARGE/COMMISSION.TYPE.CONDITIONS).   </p>
            <p>Must be a valid code on the FT.CHARGE/COMMISSION.TYPE.CONDITIONS table.   </p>
            <p>Charge code invalid if WAIVER filed is set to 'YES' .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.STATUS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field. This field is updated with the current business date automatically when the collection status is changed to "Cleared or Returned"</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Updated by the system to the processing date. No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the BL.BILL contract status. This field is updated by the system based on the activity of the BL contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input field</p>
            <p>Valid values "CUR" or "LIQ"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERALL.COLL.STAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>BL.BILL-BL.BILL</p>
            <p>OVERALL.COLL.STAT</p>
            <p>This field used to define the overall Collection Status of the Bill.  This is user friendly option through which all BR/BB collection status can be changed instead of changing one by one.</p>
            <p>For example :</p>
            <p>If 10 BR's attached to a BL cleared and instead of changing the status of each BR, overall collection status can be changed to "Cleared". Similarly if 2 BR's returned out of 10 BR's, mark the individual BR's collection status as "Returned" and change the overall status to "Cleared"</p>
            <p>Once authorise the collection status it cannot be changed again.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the final Interest Rate arrived by the system to calculated the Discount Amount.</p>
            <p>The system arrives Effective Interest Rate by adding the Interest rate as per Interest Key or Interest Rate plus spread and Interest Differential, if any defined in the appropriate BGC record for the Customer / Group.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input field.</p>
            <p>Cannot be Less than or Equal to ZERO.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field specifies the action to be performed on an invoice or BL.REGISTER or BL.BATCH record</p>

            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options available are DISBURSE , SETTLE</p>
            <p>User Input Field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DISB.ALLOT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This  Field specifies how the disbursement amount to be  allotted between registers when disbursement is done against batch</p>

            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options available are PRORATA , FIFO </p>
            <p>Default Value is PRORATA</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field specifies the exchange rate when cross currencies are involved</p>
            <p>It is the rate between the drawdown account currency and BL.BILL currency during disbursement</p>
            <p>It is the rate between the Principal Liquidation account currency and BL.BILL currency during settlement</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Rate Field</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when cross currencies are involved</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field specifies the customer spread to be  applied on the exchange rate if exists</p>

            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Rate Field</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when cross currencies are involved</p>
            <p>Defaulted from BL.GROUP.CONDITION if not inputted by the user</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field specifies the effective rate after applying EXCHANGE.RATE and EXCHANGE.SPREAD</p>

            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Rate Field</p>
            <p>Updated only when cross currencies are involved</p>
            <p>System maintained field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>OTHER.BANK.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field specifies the charges deducted by the other bank out of the settlement amount towards their charges</p>

            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Amount Field</p>
            <p>Specified in the currency of BL.BILL</p>
            <p>User Input Field</p>
            <p>Applicable only during settlements</p>
            <p>It can not exceed the settlement amount</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>MKT.EXCH.PRFT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
