<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.BILL.DELIVERY.SCHEDULE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application has the details of messages which are scheduled for a future date. The id for this application BL No "."Date</p>
            <p> When the messages are scheduled for a future date in BL application using message date, those BL reference no with the Message type and activity code are captured here automatically by the System..</p>
            <p> As on the scheduled date, BL batch process generates the messages using this details..</p>
            <p> If a message is scheduled for a future date for a BR, then that BR cannot be removed from BL using remove BR/BB option.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MSG.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Message class that will be used to generated the messages</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>BL message Type for which the message is scheduled.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>BL Activity code for which the message is scheduled.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BL.BILL.DELIVERY.SCHEDULE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id for this application is BL Ref no "." Message date. </p>
            <p> Contains the list of BL's which are scheduled for a future date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BL.SCH.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the key to this live file. </p>
            <p> The key is the scheduled date followed by BL.REGISTER ID (for BR level msg) or BL.BILL ID (for BL level msg) separated by a 'dot'.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.BL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid BR/BL reference no for which the message has to be generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVR.CARRIER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the type of delivery carriers used for delivery of messages, transfers etc.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

