<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.BATCH.CONDITIONS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application defines the soft conditions for determining product types, batching and change product conditions for the bulk upload of invoices done thru' EB.FILE.UPLOAD.</p>
            <p>ID should be in the format:</p>
            <p>COMPANY CODE - PRODUCT</p>
            <p>COMPANY CODE - BATCH</p>
			<p />
		    <p>(or)</p>
            <p>CUSTOMER - PRODUCT</p>
            <p>CUSTOMER - BATCH</p>
            <p>CUSTOMER - CHANGE.PRODUCT</p>
	        <p>for defining product update and auto batch conditions.</p>
	        <p>For defining change product rules when product change needs to be triggered for bulk registers based on preset conditions.</p>
	        <p>Change product condition will be applicable for registers created manually and uploaded records.</p>
            </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free text field to record the description of the rule defined.</p>
         </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.BL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the default product type to be used when conditions defined to determine product type is not satisfied.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be valid product from BL.TYPE.</p>
            <p>Not allowed when ID ACTION = "BATCH".</p>
            <p>Mandatory when ID ACTION = "PRODUCT".</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAND.COND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the mandatory conditions for batching of invoices.</p>
            <p>System would default following mandatory conditions and in addition user can define additional mandatory conditions.</p>
            <p>CURRENCY</p>
            <p>LIABILITY CUSTOMER</p>
            <p>PRODUCT TYPE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be valid field in BL.REGISTER.</p>
            <p>Not allowed when ID ACTION = "PRODUCT".</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies product type to be updated based on the conditions defined in the DECIS.FIELD to DECISION.TO fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be valid product from BL.TYPE application.</p>
            <p>Not allowed when ID ACTION = "BATCH".</p>
            <p>Mandatory when conditions is defined in DECIS.FIELD to DECISION.TO fields.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECIS.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the valid name defined in standard selection of BL.REGISTER application.Local subroutine can be attached to define conditions.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECISION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the condition to be evaluated for the field defined in DECIS.FIELD.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>EQ,NE,GT,LT,GE,LE,LK,UL,RG,NR</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input if local subroutine is not attached in DECIS.FIELD.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECISION.FR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the constant which the value derived from DECIS.FIELD is compared to.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input if DECISION.FIELD is defined.</p>
            <p>Not allowed if if local subroutine is attached in DECIS.FIELD.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DECISION.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the upper value used for field value comparisons based on ranges where the DECISION field is defined as NR or RG.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Not allowed if DECISION is not RG or NR.</p>
            <p>Not allowed if if local subroutine is attached in DECIS.FIELD.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>


<t><field>BL.BATCH.CON.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
