<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.CHARGES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>This file contains a detail of charges and tax collected from each BL.REGISTER, BL.BATCH and BL.BILL.</p>
            <p />
            <p>It shows the charge code, charge currency, charge amount, charge date and tax collected for a particular BR/BB/BL level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>After the no of days as mentioned in BL.PARAMETER to move it to history from the date of maturity of the BL contract, these details will be moved to history file- BL.CHARGES.HIST.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TAX.INT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>For Bills of  Discount operation type,  tax collected on Interest is defaulted here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field has the TAX code pertaining to the charge code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This shows the Tax amount in local currency if the BL Contract is non-local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field has the Tax amount collected for the charge code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the charge amount collected for the BR/BB/BL for the currency as specified in the previous field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.AMT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the charge amount in Local currency when the charges collected from a non-local currency at BR/BB/BL level</p>
            <p>The exchange rate for conversion to local currency is arrived based on the exchange rate applicable on the charge date for the currency market as specified in BL.BILL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the charge collected currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the charge code which is used to collect charges for the BR/BB/BL.</p>
            <p>It is a valid record in FT.CHARGE.TYPE / FT.COMMISSION.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multivalue set for the charge code with charge amount ,charge amount in lcy, charge date, tax code &amp; tax amount , tax amount in lcy.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field shows the date on which the charge is collected. In BL module the charge is collected on CASH basis</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to this file is the BR/BB/BL id's for which the charges are collected.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

