<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.GROUP.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CHG.PREMIUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount to be added to the charge amount calculated.</p>
            <p> Either CHG.DISCOUNT.AMT or  CHG.PERCENT (or CHG.AMT) should be input</p>
            <p> Either PREMIUM AMOUNT or DISCOUNT AMOUNT should be input</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.DIFFERENTIAL</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> Interest Spread (difference) applied to the Interest Rate is input in this field by the user, which is defaulted by the system, to arrive at the Effective Interest Rate. The value could be either positive or negative. </p>
            <p />
            <p> System would however</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETENTION.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to specifiy the default value for Retention margin for an invoice at customer level. It can be set both at customer level or by group level</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard T24 Rate field  to specify retention margin percentage</p>
            <p>Accepts values in range 0 – 99</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.MAXIMUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Maximum Amount to be charged on transfers to which this Charge range applies. CHG.MAXIMUM.AMT is a NOINPUT field when corresponding CHG.AMT  is input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for internal reference</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A charge Code  or "ALL" is defined in this field. This is an associated field of Chg Percent , Chg Ccy  &amp; Chg Amt.</p>
            <p> Only alpha characters are acceptable.</p>
            <p> If Charge code is entered as "ALL" only Chg Percent is allowed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> This is a multi-value field</p>
            <p> Must be a valid record in FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE or     "ALL"</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional field with the Format nnC or nnW where nn is a number from 1 to 99. An input of 0 is also allowed. "C" stands for Calendar days and "W" for Working days.</p>
            <p> If no value is entered, then the value would default as explained below in a defaulting mechanism.</p>
            <p> The values input in this field</p>
            <p>  would be defaulted to the Bill Contracts.In the Bill Contract, if BTTC value is defined (not null)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Value of 1-99 allowed suffixed by "C" or "W".</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.MINIMUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Minimum Amount to be charged on transfers which attract this Charge range. CHG.MINIMUM.AMT is a NOINPUT field when corresponding CHG.AMT  is input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.PERCENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the charge has is a percentage of the value of the Bill Amount, it can be specified in this field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input</p>
            <p> Allowed only when Chg Amount is not specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BL.GROUP.CONDITION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains either the ID of a group of BL customers (as defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION) or the ID of an individual customer preceded by 'C-' (e.g. C-100018).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> A maximum of 12 characters may be entered.   </p>
            <p> Must be either the ID of a APPL.GEN.CONDITION with module as "BL.BILL"     or a valid CUSTOMER number preceded by 'C-'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the amount to be charge is a flat amount per Bill Register or Bill Batch or Bill Contract, it should be defined here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Flat amount in the defined currency</p>
            <p> Allowed only when the Chg Percent is Null</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency of the Charge should be specified here which should have already been defined in the Currency Table.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid record in CURRENCY file.</p>
            <p> Allowed only when the Chg Percent is not specified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.DISCOUNT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount to be deducted from the Charge amount calculated .</p>
            <p> Either CHG.PREMIUM.AMT or  CHG.PERCENT (or CHG.AMT) should be input</p>
            <p> Either PREMIUM AMOUNT or DISCOUNT AMOUNT should be input</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>EXCH.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field refers the spread for currency exchange</p>
             <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Rate field to specify preferential spread.</p>
            <p>It can accept 0 from 100 %</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

