<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file contains Basic data and Parameter fields required for Bill contract processing. There is only one record as "SYSTEM" is maintained and which has all basic details </p>
            <p>which includes Transaction code for various activity, Accrual frequency, P&amp;L category code for Interest Received Advance, grace days etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>These fields will be used to default the values in BL module when the values are not defined in BGC or BTTC.</p>
            <p>Record in this file is essential before inputting Bill contract or any other BL module static file.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ERLY.PAY.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.IRA.ADJ.PRV.MT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Profit &amp; Loss category code to which the interest pertaining to the past month received  is to be posted.</p>
            <p>In a Discounted Contract, when a back value dated contract is made, discounted Interest received  pertaining to the previous months will be credited to the Profit &amp; Loss category code specified in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 numeric characters.    </p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-59999.   </p>
            <p>Must be a valid P&amp;L category code on the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional input field. The values specified are used are used to check if the calculated Effective Rate of Interest is within permissible limits. The method of using these values for generating override messages is explained under "Defaulting Mechanism".</p>
            <p>If an interest rate is defined here, it implies that the Minimum Interest Rate should not go below the rate specified in this field for this product. When the effective rate comes below this interest rate, an override message will be generated.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date and time that the record was last committed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.PAY.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The <a href="DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER_DEPT.ACCT.OFF.CODE.HTM">DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER</a> code of the <a href="USER_USER.ID.HTM">USER</a> that last modified the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.IRA.ADJ.PRV.YR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Profit &amp; Loss category code to which the interest pertaining to the previous year received  is to be posted.</p>
            <p>In a Discounted Contract, when a back value dated contract is made, discounted Interest received  pertaining to the previous year will be credited to the Profit &amp; Loss category code specified in this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 numeric characters.   </p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-59999.   </p>
            <p>Must be a valid P&amp;L category code on the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.IRA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Profit &amp; Loss category code to which the interest received in advance is to be posted.</p>
            <p>The discount Interest received in advance in a discounted contract in a Bill transaction pertaining to the current month will be credited to the Profit &amp; Loss category code as specified in this field.</p>
            <p>Once authorised this field cannot be changed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 numeric characters. (Mandatory input).   </p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-59999.   </p>
            <p>Must be a valid P&amp;L category code on the CATEGORY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAY.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Transaction code as defined here will be used in transactions when the repayment takes place in BL contract processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in TRANSACTION file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.PROD.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Default product category for the Bill transaction defined here. Once authorised this can not be changed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-6 numeric characters. (Mandatory input) </p>
            <p>The code entered must be present on the CATEGORY file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERPOLATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INPUTTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The users that have modified the contract are held in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>The input to this field is " " or "NO". If " ", there will be an automatic override for all the Holidays defined in the Holiday Table. If "NO" there will be an override message appearing whenever an holiday date is defined for maturity of the Bill</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CO.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The company code that the record belongs to.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLATERAL.ENTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The current number of the record</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.TXN.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>BL.PARAMETER</p>
            <p>ID</p>
            <p>The id of the this parameter file was SYSTEM.  From 13.1.01 this has been changed to company file.  Effective from 13.1.01 each company must have a BL.PARAMETER file individually.</p>
            <p />
            <p>VALIDATION RULES:-</p>
            <p>1. The ID of the parameter file can be only company </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.TXN.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.POST.MAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the number of days post maturity of the contract after which the records are to go to the history file.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>3 digit Numeric</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is linked to FT.COMMISSION.TYPE. By specifying a valid charge code and calendar based field , we can collect charges based on calendar or Non-calendar.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in FT.COMMISSION.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Shows the current status of the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISB.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>The transaction code as defined here will be used in transactions when there is Disbursement in BL contract processing.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be a Valid record in  TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALENDAR.BASED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional field. If it is decided that the Commission charged should be a on periodic basis and if we define that the value as NULL, the commission will be charged on a non calendar basis and if it is YES, the commission will be on a Calendar based.</p>
            <p>Calendar comprises of 4 quarters viz. Jan to Mar, Apr to June, July to Sept, Oct to Dec.</p>
            <p>For example</p>
            <p>In April, when a BL Contract is back value dated to March, and it was decided to charge on a periodic basis.</p>
            <p>If we define that the Commission should be charged on a non calendar Basis, (leaving the Calendar Based field as NULL), the commission will be charged from March to May as a block and June to August as another block. </p>
            <p>However, if we define the Commission to be charged as Calendar Based, (filling the Calendar Based field as YES), the starting block will be taken as Jan to March, since the value date falls in that block and it will charge for two Blocks, one for Jan to Mar and another for Apr to Jun.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BL.MSG.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>BL.MESSAGE.CLASS and EB.MESSAGE.CLASS are used to formulate the class mapping between Bill Internal Class and EB.MESSAGE.CLASS. </p>
            <p> The main driving concept of ACTIVITY and CLASS has lend itself to facilitate the user by automatically trigger only the message related to the operation, which user are currently do. In a sense, the system will try to default a sensible CLASS tiding to corresponding activity, and populate the information on the Bill transaction. Consequently, the user can take control of the class to choose whether he/she wants to produce as per suggestion by the system.</p>
            <p>The following types are valid types:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>+AMEND.ADD</p>
            <p>+AMEND.REMOVE</p>
            <p>+ USER.DEFINE1</p>
            <p>+ USER.DEFINE2</p>
            <p>..... + USERDEFINE10</p>
            <p>For more detail, please refer T24 Users Guide.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Multi value set </p>
            <p />
            <p>Duplicate values not allowed (Only 1-to-1 mapping) </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only the following values are allowed : </p>
            <p>
                <p>DISC.ADVICE,COLLATERAL.ADVICE,</p>
                <p>REVERSAL.ADVICE, AMEND.ADD, AMEND.REMOVE,MATURITY.CLEAR,</p>
                <p>MATURITY.RETURN,DEBIT.CUST,DEBIT.BANK,CREDIT.CUST,</p>
                <p>CREDIT.BANK,USER.DEFINE1....USER.DEFINE10</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLECTION.ENTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Future Use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the number of days a client has to settle a Bill repayment before penalty interest is charged.</p>
            <p>This field defines the number of days, after a repayment date, that a client has in which to settle the balance on his Bill account. At the end of this period a penalty will be charged based on the outstanding debit balance on the Bill account.</p>
            <p>Penalty charges are calculated by applying a percentage rate to any debit balance on the Bill account. The calculation and application of the penalty is made on a monthly basis on the day determined by this field. </p>
            <p>This is an Optional Field with the Format nnC or nnW where nn is a number from 1 to 99."C" for calendar days and "W"  working days.  An input of 0 is also allowed. If no value is entered, then the value would default as per the defaulting mechanism.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 2 numeric characters. (Optional input)   </p>
            <p>Must be numeric suffixed with "C" or "W"</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.OF.DAY.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Future Use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency Market relative to the Bill transaction.</p>
            <p>Indicates the market that exchange rates apply, e.g. Money Market, Notes etc. This field is the default if CURRENCY.MARKET is not entered on the BL.Bill application.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2 numeric characters. Market 1 must always be input.    </p>
            <p>For all the countries where more than one market exists for the     determination of the exchange rates, input of the various markets in this     field will be essential to ensure a correct definition of the exchange rates     applicable to the various markets.   </p>
            <p>The Currency Market 1 will always be mandatory.   </p>
            <p>If a market &gt;= 10, the market indicated in the first digit must be     already present on the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOLIDATE.ENTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an YES or NO field. </p>
            <p>When more than one Statement Entry appear in an Application, it results in multiple entries in the statement of the customer. To make the sum of all the multiple entries to appear as one entry in the Statement, we define "YES" in this field. If "NO" is keyed in, the multiple entries will appear as it is in the statements.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Yes or No or Null   </p>
            <p>Value defined here defaults in BL.Bill application. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional input field. The values specified are used are used to check if the calculated Effective Rate of Interest is within permissible limits. The method of using these values for generating override messages is explained under "Defaulting Mechanism".</p>
            <p>If an interest rate is defined here, it implies that the Maximum Interest Rate should not exceed the rate specified in this field for this product. When the effective rate comes below this interest rate, an override message will be generated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.CAT.IRA</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the existing Profit &amp; Loss category code defined for Interest received in Advance (IRA) to be changed, new category code can be given here. </p>
            <p>After End of day, the category as specified here will become IRA category and all transactions will be posted to this category.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-5 numeric characters.   </p>
            <p>Must be in the range 50000-59999.   </p>
            <p>Must be a valid P&amp;L category code on the CATEGORY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REV.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a BL contract is reversed the reversal transaction goes through this transaction code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory </p>
            <p>Must be a valid code in TRANSACTION file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.MSG.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used in conjunction with the previous field to populate the class on the Bill transaction. Without this field set, the user will not be able to control the delivery message. This message class should be used in EB.ADVICES, which are associated to Bill activity.</p>
            <p>For example- To generate message.class  COLLECTIONADVICE, during Collection Bill input activity, EB.ADVICES should have a record with message.class as COLLECTION.ADVICE for the activity code - Collection Bill Input.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Should be a valid record in EB.MESSAGE.CLASS</p>
            <p>Cannot use the same EB.MESSAGE.CLASS for several BL.MESSAGE.CLASS (only 1     to 1 mapping is allowed).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HOLIDAY.OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an Optional field. If the value is "Null", it generates in BL.BILL application an override message if the maturity date is an holiday for each BR's. And if it is made "No", such messages will not get generated when the maturity date is an holiday.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Null or No. </p>
            <p> Defaults to Null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.DTE.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the default Position Type for Bill transactions </p>
            <p>Indicates the position the transaction will be recorded under, e.g. Trading, Investment, Reserve, etc.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>No Input field.</p>
            <p>Defaulted value "TR".</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BL.PARAMETER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the parameter file was SYSTEM.  From release 13.1.01 this has been changed to accept only COMPANY as the id.</p>
            <p>Effective from 13.1.01- each company must have a BL. PARAMETER file individually.</p>
            <p />
            <p>validation rules</p>
            <p />
            <p>1.ID of the parameter file can be only company</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.AMORT.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>In a discounted contract, the Discounted interest amortisation frequency is defined in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The user has the choice of either Daily or Monthly or Week accruals and the following examples define the various options:-</p>
            <p />
            <p>(i) 12 DEC 2001 D - this input specifies that the first interest accrual shall be on 12th Dec 2001 and thereafter interest accruals shall be at daily (D) intervals.</p>
            <p />
            <p>(ii) 31 JAN 2001 M0131 - this input specifies that the first interest accrual shall be on 31st Jan 2001 and thereafter interest accruals shall be at monthly (M01) intervals on the last day (31) of each month.</p>
            <p />
            <p>(iii) 31 JAN 2001 M0115 - this input specifies that the first interest accrual shall be on 31st Jan 2001 and thereafter at monthly (01) intervals on the fifteenth day (15) of each month.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is updated automatically whenever the accrual process has taken place and so unless the accrual cycle is to be changed, the only time attention needs to be paid to this field is at installation. Prior to the first 'off-line' of the system, the date entered here must be equal or greater than the 'NEXT RUN DATE' field in the appropriate BL BATCH job. If it is greater than the date specified on the batch record then the update of the batch job NEXT RUN DATE must coincide with the date entered here at some point in the future.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Daily     or Monthly or Week</p>
            <p />
            <p>1 - 14 alphanumeric characters in the form:- Standard     frequency format. (Mandatory input) </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Must     be a valid date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.REV.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>For future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORT.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This transaction code is used for transaction relating to amortisation of the Discount amount , which is collected up front in Discount operation.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDIT.DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is populate by using the auditor review function (<a href="file://FUNCTION.Q.HTM">Q</a>), and holds the date and time at which the function was used</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUDITOR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is populate by using the auditor review function (<a href="file://FUNCTION.Q.HTM">Q</a>), and holds the date and time at which the function was used.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTHORISER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The user that authorised the record.</p>
            <p>Where a record has been modified multiple times (i.e the <a href="STANDARD.HELP_CURR.NO.HTM">CURR.NO</a> is greater than 1) only the last authoriser is shown</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DUPLICATE.CHECK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the check to be made for any duplicate contracts as per conditions defined in EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE.</p>
            <p>Override message will be triggered if there are duplicate contracts as per conditions defined in EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE for new contracts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be valid id in EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE defined for BL.REGISTER application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DOC.BACK.VAL.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the  maximum back value days allowed for document captured in BL.REGISTER with DOCUMENT.DATE field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 to 999 days allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RETURN.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies whether the excess interest on account of early settlement is to be returned to the customer or not</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Options are YES or NO</p>
            <p>Default value is NO</p>
            <p>Nochange after first input</p>
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EXCH.PRFT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field refers the category to which the profit or loss is posted when cross currencies are involved during disbursement or settlement</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>User Input Field</p>
            <p>Should be a valid code in CATEGORY table</p>
            <p>It accepts CATEGORY in range 50000 - 59999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

