<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.REG.ERROR.DTLS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application holds details of errors encountered during the update of product or creating batch for the uploaded invoices.</p>
            <p>ID of this application will be either BL.REGISTER or BL.BATCH id.</p>
            </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ERROR.STAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the stage on when error is encountered.Errors can be encountered during following process.</p>
            <p>UPDATE PRODUCT - Error encountered during updation of product.</p>
            <p>BATCH - Error encountered during creation of batch.</p>
         </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPLOAD.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the upload reference from uploaded file thru' EB.FILE.UPLOAD application.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ERROR.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the details of error encountered during updation of product or creation of batch.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t><t>
<field>PROCESS.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the  date on when errors are encountered during processing.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the status of error encountered during attaching product or batching.</p>
            <p>Pending - When any errors are encountered when product type is attached to BL.REGISTER thru' BL.UPDATE.PRODUCT service.</p>
            <p>Manual_Resolved - When product type is attached manually thru' BL.REGISTER.</p>
            <p>Auto_Resolved - When product type is successfully updated thru' online service BL.UPDATE.PRODUCT.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.RESOLVED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on when update product or batching errors are rectified either thru' manually or thru' online service.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>BL.REG.ERROR.DTLS.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
