<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>BL</product>
<table>BL.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>K.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>used for internal reference</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value specified is used to check if the calculated Effective Rate of Interest is within permissible limits. The method of using these values for generating override messages is explained under "Defaulting Mechanism".</p>
            <p>If an interest rate is defined here, it implies that the Effective Interest Rate should not exceed the rate specified in this field during BL.BILL contract processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional  input field. The default mechanism (see below) will happen automatically along with other fields ( INT.SPREAD,INT.RATE)</p>
            <p>Default Mechanism</p>
            <p>1.</p>
            <p />The system would first look for an appropriate BTTC record and take the values defined therein. Then it would use the values defined in appropriate BGC record for modification/override purposes. Finally it could use the values from BL.PARAMETER. It is possible that some of the fields<p />in BTTC or BGC records are not defined (null values). As a general rule, the system would skip these fields and<p />use the values defined at the next level of parameter records. <p>2.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract are same then the system would first look for a BTTC record with key "DISCOUNT*NNNN" where "NNNN" is the value of the common Bill-Type. If there is no such record<p />then the system would look for a record with key "DISCOUNT". <p>3.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract is<p />not the same, then the system would only look for a BTTC record with key DISCOUNT. <p>4.</p><p />The system would first update the Contract Group field in Bills Contract; it would determine which is the first<p />Contract Group defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION file (Record Key: BL)which satisfy the Bill Contract conditions.<p />If no contract group defined therein satisfies the Bill Contract conditions, the system would not update<p />the Contract Group field in<p />the Bills Contract. <p>5.</p><p />The BGC file could have records<p />with key values of either "C-Customer No." or a valid Bill Contract Group. In BGC, the system would first look for a record with key "C-Customer No.". If<p />the record<p />does not exist, then the system would look for a record with key equal to the Contract Group field in the Bills Contract. <p>6.</p><p />The values in BGC record fields could in some cases override the BTTC values are in some cases could modify the BTTC values. It is possible that both BTTC and BGC records are not available or that the values for some fields are not defined in these records. In such cases, the values from the BL.PARAMETER file <p />would be used by the system to default the values.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Must be a valid record in BASIC.INTEREST or PERIODIC.INTEREST</p><p>Either Interest key or Interest rate is allowed.</p><p>To specify PERIODIC.INTEREST - specify interest key prefixed with "P"       (ie. To specify PERIODIC.INTEREST key "01" - it is "P01")</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETENTION.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is to specify the default value for Retention margin for an invoice at transaction level</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 Rate field  to specify retention margin percentage</p> 
            <p>Accepts values in range 0 – 99</p>           
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the file is BL-Operation (Collateral or Collection or Discount ) or BL-Operation followed by BL.TYPE connected by "*" .</p>
            <p>When contract is inputted through BL module the charges and interest rate will be defaulted based on the key of operation and type of BL.</p>
            <p>If appropriate operation and key is not available and key is available only for operation then that record will be used for defaulting purpose.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid operations Collateral or Collection or Discount.   </p>
            <p>If BL.TYPE key is defined - Must be a record in BL.TYPE file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional  input field along with other associated fields. The Interest Rate has to be defined here.</p>
            <p> The default mechanism (see below) will happen automatically along with other fields ( INT.SPREAD, INT.KEY).</p>
            <p>These values are used as default values in a Bill Contract. The method of Defaulting is explained in the "Defaulting Mechanism"</p>
            <p>Default Mechanism</p>
            <p>1.</p>
            <p />The system would first look for an appropriate BTTC record and take the values defined therein. Then it would use the values defined in appropriate BGC record for modification/override purposes. Finally it could use the values from BL.PARAMETER. It is possible that some of the fields<p />in BTTC or BGC records are not defined (null values). As a general rule, the system would skip these fields and<p />use the values defined at the next level of parameter records. <p>2.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract are same then the system would first look for a BTTC record with key "DISCOUNT*NNNN" where "NNNN" is the value of the common Bill-Type. If there is no such record<p />then the system would look for a record with key "DISCOUNT". <p>3.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract is<p />not the same, then the system would only look for a BTTC record with key DISCOUNT. <p>4.</p><p />The system would first update the Contract Group field in Bills Contract; it would determine which is the first<p />Contract Group defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION file (Record Key: BL)which satisfy the Bill Contract conditions.<p />If no contract group defined therein satisfies the Bill Contract conditions, the system would not update<p />the Contract Group field in<p />the Bills Contract. <p>5.</p><p />The BGC file could have records<p />with key values of either "C-Customer No." or a valid Bill Contract Group. In BGC, the system would first look for a record with key "C-Customer No.". If<p />the record<p />does not exist, then the system would look for a record with key equal to the Contract Group field in the Bills Contract. <p>6.</p><p />The values in BGC record fields could in some cases override the BTTC values are in some cases could modify the BTTC values. It is possible that both BTTC and BGC records are not available or that the values for some fields are not defined in these records. In such cases, the values from the BL.PARAMETER file <p />would be used by the system to default the values. <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Either Interest Rate or Interest key is allowed.</p><p>Spread is not allowed when the Interest Rate is specified.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional field with the Format nnC or nnW where nn is a number from 1 to 99. "C" stands for Calendar days and "W" for working days. An input of 0 is also allowed.</p>
            <p> If no value is entered, then the value would default as explained below which is a defaulting mechanism.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If BGC value is defined (not null) then BGC value would be defaulted.</p>
            <p />If BTTC value is defined (not null)<p />and BGC value is not defined (null), then BTTC value would be defaulted. If both BGC and BTTC values were not defined (null), then the Grace Days defined in the<p />BL.PARAMETER file would be defaulted. <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Value of 1-99 allowed suffixed with "C" or "W" </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p> The value specified is used to check if the calculated Effective Rate of Interest is within permissible limits. The method of using these values for generating override messages is explained under "Defaulting Mechanism".</p>
            <p>If an interest rate is defined here, it implies that the Effective Interest Rate should not go below the rate specified in this field during BL.BILL Contract processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This is an optional input field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an optional  input field along with the associate fields. The spread percentage has to be defined in this field.  The default mechanism (see below) will happen automatically along with other fields   (INT.KEY,  INT.RATE).</p>
            <p>Default Mechanism</p>
            <p>1.</p>
            <p />The system would first look for an appropriate BTTC record and take the values defined therein. Then it would use the values defined in appropriate BGC record for modification/override purposes. Finally it could use the values from BL.PARAMETER. It is possible that some of the fields<p />in BTTC or BGC records are not defined (null values). As a general rule, the system would skip these fields and<p />use the values defined at the next level of parameter records. <p>2.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract are same then the system would first look for a BTTC record with key "DISCOUNT*NNNN" where "NNNN" is the value of the common Bill-Type. If there is no such record<p />then the system would look for a record with key "DISCOUNT". <p>3.</p><p />If Bill-Type of all Bill Registers attached to a Bill Contract is<p />not the same, then the system would only look for a BTTC record with key DISCOUNT. <p>4.</p><p />The system would first update the Contract Group field in Bills Contract; it would determine which is the first<p />Contract Group defined in APPL.GEN.CONDITION file (Record Key: BL)which satisfy the Bill Contract conditions.<p />If no contract group defined therein satisfies the Bill Contract conditions, the system would not update<p />the Contract Group field in<p />the Bills Contract. <p>5.</p><p />The BGC file could have records<p />with key values of either "C-Customer No." or a valid Bill Contract Group. In BGC, the system would first look for a record with key "C-Customer No.". If<p />the record<p />does not exist, then the system would look for a record with key equal to the Contract Group field in the Bills Contract. <p>6.</p><p />The values in BGC record fields could in some cases override the BTTC values are in some cases could modify the BTTC values. It is possible that both BTTC and BGC records are not available or that the values for some fields are not defined in these records. In such cases, the values from the BL.PARAMETER file <p />would be used by the system to default the values. <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Interest Spread is allowed only when Interest key is specified.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an associated multivalue field along with Charge.Code field.  </p>
            <p>A charge or commission can be defined at BL.REGISTER/BL.BATCH/BL.BILL level. The charge gets defaulted while processing respective application. User can give additional charge code or change the amount during BL processing. </p>
            <p>The charges defined in the CHARGE.CODE field could be applied at BL.REGISTER level in which case the Charge would be calculated and applied for each attached BL.REGISTER of a Bills Contract.</p>
            <p>If the Level were defined as BL.BILL, then the charge would be applied only once at the Bill Contract Level on the Principal amount of the contract.</p>
            <p>The financial transactions happens during the BL.BILL contract.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p>Valid values BL.REGISTER / BL.BATCH / BL.BILL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is a multi-value field. This field can be filled with any valid charge codes defined in the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE table. This is an associated multivalue field along with CHARGE.LEVEL field</p>
            <p>All details related to charge code will be populated during BL contract processing.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-11 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Must be a valid record in FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Currency for which the charges are defined. This along with Int.Key, Int.Spread, Int.Rate field are associated fields.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The currency code or mnemonic must exist on the CURRENCY table. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISB.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code defined here is used for transaction processing during BL Disbursement which uses this BTTC Key.</p>
            <p> If it is not defined here, the code defined at the BL.PARAMETER level would be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional field.</p>
            <p>Must be valid record in TRANSACTION file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

