<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>AC.APPLICATION.LINK</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p>AC AC.APPLICATION.LINK - Overview </p>
        <p>
        </p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SUSP.APPLN</field>
<desc>
            <p>The application ID where the entries are to be routed to an Internal Suspense Account during END.OF.DAY, when there are overrides.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid T24 Application</p>
            <p> Associated Multi-value field with fields with the fields DR.CATEGORY and       CR.CATEGORY.</p>
            <p> Mandatory field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Suspense category code to be used for Credit  entries generated during EOD.  If the amount to be suspended during EOD is in Credit,  then the amount will be posted in an internal account in the category mentioned in this field, in the respective currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid category code in the range 10000 -19999</p>
            <p> One account in the category mentioned in this field should be opened, for     the system to post entries during EOD.</p>
            <p> Associated Multivalue with fields SUSP.APPLN and Dr.CATEGORY</p>
            <p> Can be the same Category code as that of Dr.CATEGORY.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Suspense category code to be used for debit entries generated during EOD.  If the amount to be posted to suspense during EOD is a debit then the amount will be posted in an internal account in the category mentioned in this field for the appropriate currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid category code in the range 10000 -19999</p>
            <p> One account in the category mentioned in this field should be opened, for the system to       post entries during EOD. Once this is done accounts in other currencies       will be opened appropriately as needed. </p>
            <p> Associated Multivalue with fields SUSP.APPLN and CR.CATEGORY</p>
            <p> Can be the same Category code as that of CR.CATEGORY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This table is used to route entries generated during END.OF.DAY Batch run to an Internal Suspense Account, if there are Overrides.  The Applications where the Overrides are to be routed and the respective Internal account categories for Debit and Credit are mentioned in this table.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> ID is SYSTEM</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

