<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>AC.ACCOUNT.SWEEP.HIST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p> AC.ACCOUNT.SWEEP.HIST - Overview </p>
        <p>This file is used to record the details of the sweeps performed on the id Account for the year/month. Details such as the run date, sweep amounts, balance and references are stored both for processing and for use in reports or enquiries. 
</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SWEEP.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is the specific date of the year/month on which the sweep was run and for which the associated data refers.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.POOL.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the cash pool id of the processing cash pool</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.TFR.CR</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE.USED</field>
<desc><p>Which of the several balance fields on the ACCOUNT file was used when deciding how much to sweep between the accounts.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.ACCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UP.TO.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWEEP.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>The amount of the sweep run on the particular date.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STARTING.BAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Balance of the Account before the sweep was run.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWEEP.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The AC.SWEEP.TYPE which dictated the amount and direction of the sweep performed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.START.BAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Hold the balance of the Credit account before the sweep is done. Credit account means for surplus sweep type, this holds the balance of Link account and balance of ID account of AC.CASH.POOL in case of Maintenance sweep. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input- Internal Field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETTING</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMT.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
        <p>A user sub-routine which is invoked to calculate the amount to be transferred between the id account and the linked account. A PGM.FILE record will be required before the sub-routine name can be input. It should be noted that the sub-routine is triggered only when the rule conditions, as defined in AC.CASH.POOL, have been met.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.TFR.DR</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CP.SEQ.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicates the sequence within the sweep that this run was performed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>The frequency date and cycle the AC.CASH.POOL is set for.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BACK.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.ACCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.SWEEP.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BV.SW.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the back value date for which the adjustment is done. This is a multi-value set along with the Account balance details that will be used for sweep purpose on a back value date. Available only when the BACK.VAL.ADJ flag is set to YES and adjustment amount is there for the already swept amount. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input -Internal field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGREGATE.BAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>On CASHPOOL type sweeps the total amount of funds debited/credited from the lower to the higher account.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NXT.RUN.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>When the next run date is based upon the existing frequency cycle.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.ST.BAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>This has the revised starting balance of the Cash pool ID account after back value dated entries for a sweep date Revised start balance and the Debit or Credit account balance based on sweep type is compared and the adjustment amount, which is required, is arrived at. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input- Internal Field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCHEDULE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.START.BAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Hold the balance of the Debit account before the sweep is done. Debit account means for surplus sweep type, this holds the balance of ID account in AC.CASH.POOL and balance of Link account in case of Maintenance sweep. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input -Internal field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.SW.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.SWEEP</field>
<desc>
        <p>The id of this file is based on the Account number of the sweep and the year/month it was run. Format of the id is account.no-yearmonth for example a typical id would appear: 17205-200002 This records the sweeps performed on Account 17205 in February 2002. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> System generated</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.BAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the revised account balance after back value dated transaction based on which adjustment amount will be arrived. This balance reflects the revised starting balance plus/minus the already swept amount based on the sweep type. For this activity balance, once again the Cash pool conditions are applied to arrive the Adjustment amount which needs to be passed. Available only when the BACK.VAL.ADJ flag is set to YES and any adjustment is there for the already swept amount. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input- Internal Field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJUSTED.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds adjustment amount, which is passed because of the back value-dated transaction. Available only when the BACK.VAL.ADJ flag is set to YES and any adjustment amount is there for the already swept amount </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input- Internal Field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSAL.IND</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.SW.BAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the revised sweep amount based on the revised starting balance after back value dated entries for a sweep date. Original Sweep amount and revised sweep amount is compared and adjustment entries are passed. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input- Internal Field</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Record id of the work file AC.CASH.POOL.LINK which invoked the sweep and whose details are recorded here.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CP.GROUP.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>The rule used for the sweep (id of the AC.CP.GROUP.PARAM).</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RERUN.IND</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASHFLOW.AMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used in conjunction with CASHFLOW type rules. These are essentially the same as a Two Way sweep rule except that there is a controlling limit on how much can be taken from higher level account. This limit and the AGREGATE.BAL field control how much can be taken from the higher level account. There is no limit on how much can be transferred to the higher level account</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWEEP.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>The system reference which is comprised of the account pair and the processing date of the sweep performed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORRECTION.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is currently not in use.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.ACCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.PERCENTAGE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

