<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>AC.CONSOLIDATE.COND</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This Application allows to define the rules for the consolidation of entries for either an Account or Category record.</p>
            <p>  A valid record id to AC.CONSOLIDATE.COND should be set in the Account or Category record for which consolidated entries should be raised.</p>
            <p>  The following consolidation criteria applies:</p>
            <p>  Entry Type</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Account Number or P&amp;L category</p>
            <p>  Currency</p>
            <p>  System Id</p>
            <p>  Transaction Code</p>
            <p>  Value Date</p>
            <p>  Exposure Date</p>
            <p>  Reversal Marker</p>
            <p>  Currency Market</p>
            <p>  Suspense Category</p>
            <p>  Terminal Number</p>
            <p>  Account Officer (P&amp;L only)</p>
            <p>  Product Category (P&amp;L only)</p>
            <p>  Plus any additional elements defined in AC.CONSOLIDATE.COND</p>
            <p>  The combined key is structured as follows, the &amp;#8220;!&amp;#8221;  ! character is used as a delimeter, for example a consolidated entry from the FT application may look like:</p>
            <p>  S!12345678!GBP!FT!210!20021126!!!1!!89</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FILTER.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to suppress entries for the given TRANSACTION code on EB.CONTRACT.BALANCES</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Must be a valid TRANSACTION code </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID to the AC.CONSOLIDATE.COND record which defines the rules for the consolidation of entries. This ID should be defined in the CONSOLIDATE.ENT field in the ACCOUNT or CATEGORY record to allow the consolidation of entries for that Account or Category.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILTER.SYSID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to suppress entries on EB.CONTRACT.BALANCE for the given EB.SYSTEM.ID</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Must be a valid record on EB.SYSTEM.ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.SYS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The EXCLUDE.SYS.ID is a multi-valued field that defines the EB.SYSTEM.ID codes that should not be consolidated, the assumption is that the system consolidates all types unless specified here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.ENTRIES.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of entries that should be raised for the day before entries are consolidated for an account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the ID is other then DEFAULT, then if NO.OF.ENTRIES is zero or null then all entries are cosolidated.</p>
            <p>  If the ID is DEFAULT, then if NO.OF.ENTRIES is zero then all entries are consolidate for an account, but if NO.OF.ENTRIES is null then there is no consolidation of entries for an account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADD.CONSOL.FLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ADD.CONSOLD.FLD is a multi-valued field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field gives the description for the consolidation rules defined in that record</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ENTRY.TYPE field indicates types of entry to consolidate. An empty field implies all types will be consolidated.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  S, C, F or R</p>
            <p />
            <p>  S - Statement Entries (STMT.ENTRY)</p>
            <p>  C - Categ Entries (CATEG.ENTRY)</p>
            <p>  F - Forward Entries (STMT.ENTRY)</p>
            <p>  R - Consol Entries (RE.CONSOL.SPEC.ENTRY)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  -</p>
            <p />
            <p>  -</p>
            <p />
            <p>  -</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCL.PROD.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi-valued field that defines the product CATEGORY codes that should not be consolidated. The assumption is that all product CATEGORY are consolidated unless specified here</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi-valued field that defines the TRANSACTION codes that should not be consolidated. The assumption is that all transaction codes are consolidated unless specified here.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.DETAIL.APP</field>
<desc>
            <p>System ID’s defined here will NOT maintain entry detail</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Must be a valid record ON EB.SYSTEM.ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>User defined routine can be attached here to determine if entries should be consolidated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Input must exist on PGM.FILE as type S (subroutine) program</p>
            <p>  .</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

