<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>AC.PRINT.MASK</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p>AC.PRINT.MASK 
</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MASK</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicated whether the statement entries are to be masked or not. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Mandatory Input. </p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">YES Indicates that entries should be masked. </p>
            <p value="2">NO - Indicates that entries should be unmasked.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATCHED.TO</field>
<desc>
        <p>All statement entries ids that are to be matched. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> All entries must exist on the STMT.ENTRY file. If more than one entry is captured, then they must be all debits or all credits.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is updated by the system. Its the total of all the statement entries in the MATCHED.TO field. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>No input field </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is updated by the system. It is the total of all statement entries in the MATCHED.FROM field. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>No input field </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NET.TOTAL</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is updated by the system. The net total between the TO.TOTAL and the FROM.TOTAL fields must be zero otherwise and error will be generated. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>No input field </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MASK.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Descriptive field used to update statement entries. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MASK.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Todays date Updated by the system. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>No input field </p>
        <p>Standard T24 date </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATCHED.FROM</field>
<desc>
        <p>All statement entry ids that are to be matched. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Statement entry id must exist on the STMT.ENTRY file. If more than one entry is captured then they must be all debit or all credit entries.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
        <p>The account number of the customer who's entries are to be masked. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Mandatory Input</p>
        <p>Must be a valid Account </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.DATE.SEQU</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The end date for the selection of statement entries to be masked. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional Input Default is todays system date.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the start date for the selection of statement entries to be masked. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional input Default is todays system date.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

