<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>AC.STMT.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p>AC.STMT.PARAMETER</p>
        <p>The purpose of this table is to define defaults for account statement details when opening new accounts. When a new account is opened, an account statement record, specifying the date and frequency for printing account statements is generated automatically by the system. The default frequency is determined by the STMT.GEN.CONDITION table. This table determines whether the account statement record is set to produce statements when there has been no movement, descriptive statements, interest and charges statements and advices and tax advices and the minimum number of months for a statement to be produced if at all. If no record exists the default will be 'NO' and the minimum frequency will be 6 months. 
</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TAX.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the value for TAX.ADVICE in the default ACCOUNT.STATEMENT record for a newly opened account. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 'Y'(es) or 'N'(o). Mandatory Input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PB.CONS.CR.TRANS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies a valid Credit transaction code to which the consolidated Passbook Credit entries refer to. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Allows only a valid positive numeric integer value. Must be a valid Credit transaction code from the TRANSACTION table.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.STMT.AND.ADV</field>
<desc>
        <p>Indicates whether the interest statement and advice job should run. Possible values are “Y”, “N” or “”. If set to “Y”, the interest statement and advice job should select and process the relevant records.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.OFFICER</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the value for deciding whether the alternative ACCOUNT.OFFICER will be printed in PRINT.ACCOUNT.STMT, if this field exists on the ACCOUNT record. </p><p>Validation Rules</p><p> 'Y'(es) or 'NO' Mandatory input. Defaults to 'Y'es.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CLOSING.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the value for INT.CLOSING.ADVICE in the default ACCOUNT.STATEMENT record for a newly opened account. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 'Y'(es) or 'N'(o). Mandatory Input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.SCALE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the value for INTEREST.SCALE in the default ACCOUNT.STATEMENT record for a newly opened account. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 'Y'(es) or 'N'(o). Mandatory Input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.MONTHS.STMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the value for MIN.MONTHS.STMT that controls the minimum frequency for statements to be produced in PRINT.ACCOUNT.STMT. The default of null is 6 months although you can specify no minimum frequency or any number of months between 1 and 9999. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> NONE - No minimum frequency. 1-4 numeric characters.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PB.CONS.DR.TRANS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies a valid Debit transaction code to which the consolidated Passbook Debit entries refer to. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Allows only positive integer numeric values Must be a valid debit transaction code from the TRANSACTION table.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IF.NO.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the value for IF.NO.MOVEMENT in the default ACCOUNT.STATEMENT record for a newly opened account. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 'Y'(es) or 'N'(o). Mandatory Input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SP.PB.CONS.MAX</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of transactions after which Savings Bank Account entries are to be consolidated for Passbook printing. If the number of transactions during the day after last print in a Passbook Savings account exceeds the number specified in this field then the entries would be consolidated and printed as total of Debit and / or Credit entries. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Allows only a positive integer numeric value.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT.STATEMENT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the value for DESCRIPT.STATEMENT in the default ACCOUNT.STATEMENT record for a newly opened account. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 'Y'(es) or 'N'(o). Mandatory Input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIRST.STMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies whether a statement is required to be produced the first day if there has been no movements for the Account since being opened. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 1 alphabetic character. Y(es) or N(o).</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.MVMT.REQD</field>
<desc>
        <p>In a value dated accounting system (i.e. in ACCOUNT.PARAMETER, VALUE.DATED.ACCTING is YES) , if this field is Null or No, then real forward entries with a Value-Date equal to or less than the next statement date, booked during the statement period alone, will be reported in the statements. If it is desired that all the real forward entries irrespective of value date booked during the statement period, are to be printed in the next statement, then this field has to be made YES. Example: Last statement date-15.3.2002. Next Statement date-31.3.2002 Booking date- 16.3.2002-Value date-28.3.2002 Booking date- 20.3.2002-Value date-5.4.2002 If this field is NULL/NO then only the entry with value date 28.3.2002 will be reported in the next statement due on 31.3.2002. On the other hand if this field is YES then both the entries will be reported in the next statement due on 31.3.2002. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Allowed values NULL/NO/YES. </p>
        <p>Input allowed only when the field VALUE.DATED.ACCTING is YES in ACCOUNT.PARAMETER. </p>
        <p>NULL will not be allowed if this field already has the value NO/YES.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Defines the key to AC.STMT.PARAMETER. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 'SYSTEM'</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

