<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>ACCOUNTING.REFER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is an internal file containing details of transactions and account balances for printing in the referral report. </p>
            <p>Referral conditions are defined in the REFERRAL file. These may depend on transaction details such as transaction code, amount and sign, or the balance of the ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>The REFERRAL code in each ACCOUNT record specifies which referral conditions, if any, are applicable to that ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>Balances are only tested for referral conditions on days on which there have been entries over the ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>The T24 Report Generator is used to print a report containing information from this file. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The type of ACCOUNT as specified in the CATEGORY field of the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4-5 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the date and time when the entry was processed or the balance was checked. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>a.   Date displayed as DD MMM YYYY b.   '-1' (provided for possible future use, meaningless at      present.) c.   Time since midnight in seconds and hundredths of seconds.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The TRANSACTION CODE of an entry to be referred, identifying the type of transaction. </p>
            <p>This field is only present if a REFERRAL condition which checks entries has been specified in the ACCOUNT and there has been an entry over the ACCOUNT today which meets the specified conditions for referral. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The CUSTOMER to whom the ACCOUNT belongs as specified in CUSTOMER field of the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USER.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>OUR REFERENCE from an entry to be referred. This is the reference given to the transaction/deal by the Bank. </p>
            <p>This field is only present if a REFERRAL condition which checks entries has been specified in the ACCOUNT and there has been an entry over the ACCOUNT today which meets the specified conditions for referral. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard amount format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERAL.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the REFERRAL record specifying the conditions under which the entry or balance is to be referred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric characterS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of the ACCOUNT on which a transaction or balance is to be referred. </p>
            <p>The REFERAL.CODE in each ACCOUNT record specifies which, if any, referral conditions are applicable. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard account format.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Account Officer responsible for the ACCOUNT. </p>
            <p>This is the ACCOUNT.OFFICER from the ACCOUNT record, if present, otherwise it is the ACCOUNT.OFFICER from the CUSTOMER to whom the ACCOUNT belongs, as specified in the CUSTOMER field of the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Actual Balance on the ACCOUNT after all end of day processing. </p>
            <p>This balance includes all entries over the ACCOUNT, including uncleared items with forward exposure dates. </p>
            <p>This field is only present if a REFERRAL condition which checks the BALANCE has been specified in the ACCOUNT, and there have been entries over the ACCOUNT today, and the BALANCE meets the specified conditions for referral. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount, in the currency of the ACCOUNT, of an entry to be referred. </p>
            <p>This field is only present if a REFERRAL condition which checks entries has been specified in the ACCOUNT and there has been an entry over the ACCOUNT today which meets the specified conditions for referral. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the ACCOUNT as specified in the CURRENCY field of the ACCOUNT record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alphabetic characters Currency code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

