<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>ACCOUNT.LIQUIDATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is an internal file containing details of Accounts which are used for booking (liquidating) the interest and charges calculated on other Accounts.  It provides a cross reference of all Accounts whose interest and charges are booked to each Liquidation Account. </p>
            <p>If the interest and charges calculated on an Account are to be booked to another Account, the Account to which the amounts should be booked is entered in the INTEREST.LIQU.ACCT field in the Account record of the originating Account. </p>
            <p>The Liquidating Account must be in the same Currency as the originating Account. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies an Account whose interest and charges will be booked to the Liquidation Account specified in ACCOUNT.NUMBER. </p>
            <p>Any number of Accounts in the same Currency may have their interest and charges booked to the same Liquidation Account.  The Liquidation Account number is entered in the INTEREST.LIQU.ACCT field in each of the originating ACCOUNTS.  The Accounts are defined in ACCOUNT, one Account per field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Account Number format. Internal field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Account to which all interest and charges calculated on Accounts listed in the rest of the record will be booked. </p>
            <p>The Account Number in this field specifies the Liquidation Account for interest and charges calculated on all Accounts detailed in the other fields of this record.  All Accounts must have the same Currency as the Liquidation Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Account Number format. Internal field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

