<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>ACCR.REV.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Accrual Reversal Parameter table that holds the following.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Accrual reversal processing for FCY indicator.</p>
            <p>    Accrual reversal processing for LCY indicator.</p>
            <p>    Accrual PL category codes by Application.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.IND.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field. If REVERSE.FCY changes then this field is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.IND.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input field. If REVERSE.LCY changes then this field is updated by the system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must be a valid PL Catgeory code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPP.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field, if the CRF code is different to the Catgegory code, then the CRF code is entered in this field.</p>
            <p>   It must be either a valid PL Category code or a valid CRF.TYPE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSAL.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Mondatory field if REVERSE.FCY is YES. Valid options are TODAY or YDAY.</p>
            <p>   TODAY = Reversal entry using todays exchange rate.</p>
            <p>   YDAY = Reverse using the exchange rate that was used to posted the accrual.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSE.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reversal Accrual processing for foreign currency contracts. Valid options YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.CASH.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must be a valid lead company code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK.PL.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must be a valid PL Category Code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Several applications allow the input of back dated transactions, the interest accrued for these back dated transactions can be allocated to different PL Category codes, in order to catch all the accrued interest in the reversal process these Category codes must be linked to the main Category code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.IND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Must be a valid system indicator from EB.SYSTEM.ID table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSE.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reversal Accrual processing for Local currency contracts. Valid options YES or NO.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

