<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>ACCT.INACTIVE.RESET</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table allows Account records which have been flagged as 'Inactive' to be reset. </p>
            <p>The 'Inactive' flag is set on during the end of day processing, if there has been no Customer initiated activity over the Account for the period specified in the INACTIVITY.MONTHS field in the COMPANY record. </p>
            <p>When the 'Inactive' flag is on, an override is required in order to validate any transaction involving entries over the Account. </p>
            <p>The Inactive Marker in the corresponding Account record is reset when the Account Inactive Reset record is Authorised. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Account record in which the Inactive Marker is reset by this record. </p>
            <p>The Inactive Marker in the corresponding Account record is reset when this record is Authorised. </p>
            <p>Authorised ACCT.INACTIVE.RESET records remain on the file as an audit trail. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Account Number format.</p>
            <p>There must be a corresponding Account record on the ACCOUNT file.</p>
            <p>For a new ACCT.INACTIVE.RESET record, the Inactive Marker in the corresponding Account record must be set to Y.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESET.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the date on which the Inactive Marker in the corresponding Account record is reset by this record. </p>
            <p>In Authorised records this field contains the date of the last time the Inactive Marker in the corresponding Account record was reset. </p>
            <p>In Unauthorised records, this field contains the current date,  i.e. the date on which the Account will be reset by Authorising the record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

