<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>ADHOC.STATEMENTS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p>ADHOC.STATEMENTS Overview </p>
        <p>When a request for 940 or 950 is received through Inward 920 Message, a record is created in DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST. Also this application is updated with the the list of Accounts, requested message type (either 940 or 950) and the relevant DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST id relevant to this Account. During end of day statement processing, the records in the application are selected for the execution date and required statements are generated as a special statement. Once the statement is generated, this record is deleted from the system and delivery reference is updated in the relevant DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST/ACCOUNT.STATEMENT. </p>
        <p>&#160;</p>
        <p>&#160;</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STMT.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Id for this application is a date. This contains the list of accounts for which statement is requested through inward MT920 message for the ID date. This application and ADHOC.MESSAGES application is updated during MT920 inward processing which has a request for 940/950 statement. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input updated by the system.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.ACCT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This contains the Account for which statement is requested.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.STMT.REQ</field>
<desc>
        <p>Contains the DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST id which created this record. Once a required statement is generated during End of day processing, the delivery reference number is updated back in the relevant request. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input -Updated by System Valid DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST id.</p>
        <p>&#160;</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.REQ.ACC</field>
<desc>
        <p>Contains the Account for which statement requested. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input - Updated by System Should be a Valid T24 Account</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.REQ.MSG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Contains the message type (either 940 or 950) which is requested for the Account as appearing in the previous field. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No input-Update by System Allowed values either 940 or 950</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

