<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>ALT.ACCT.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The T24 application ALTERNATE.ACCOUNT is used to provide a link between the T24 account number and another identifier that the user may have for the account. This application forms part of the structure by which the alternative account can be maintainded. Records maintained here will define the user's alternative method of identifying accounts. Details form the various fields will be used to validate the entry of alternative account numbers. </p>
            <p><strong>ALT.ACCT.PARAMETER</strong>
            </p>
            <p>This file is used to setup the conditions for the checkdigit and account size. This must then be referenced on the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER record.</p>
            <p><strong>ACCOUNT.PARAMETER </strong>
            </p>
            <p>The multi-valued field ALTERNATE.ID will allow entry of alternative account access identifiers which must previously be defined in the ALT.ACCT.PARAMETER application.</p>
            <p><strong>NB</strong> To permit the use of the alternate id's as well as the T24 Account number &amp; mnemonics you <strong>must</strong> set the flag to </p>
            <p>ALTERNATE.ACCT.IDS</p> to YES.  <p><strong>ACCOUNT</strong></p><p>The ACCOUNT application displays the alternative access identifiers from the above application within the multi-valued ALT.ACCT.TYPE field and allows entry of the alternative account identifiers in the linked ALT.ACCT.ID field. Validation is performed in accordance with the definitions from the ALT.ACCT.PARAMETER application. </p><p><strong>ALTERNATE.ACCOUNT</strong></p><p>The cross-reference application is maintained by the ACCOUNT application. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maximum length of the account number. </p>
            <p>The account number entered as an alternative identifier in the ACCOUNT application must not exceed the length specified here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-2 numeric characters. Mandatory input.  The maximum length of an account number is 16 characters, and this is the maximum value that will be accepted here.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Abbreviated description of the ALT.ACCT.PARAMETER used for enrichments. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 alphanumeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field.</p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.LENGTH</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum length of the account number. </p>
            <p>The account number entered as an alternative identifier in the ACCOUNT application must be at least the length specified here. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 alphanumeric characters.  The value entered here must be no greater than the value entered in the previous field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.MASK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the mask the user wants to apply to alternative account identifiers. </p>
            <p>           1. No = 1234;      Mask = ##### - #####               Display =       1234 </p>
            <p>           2. No = 1234567;   Mask = ##### - #####               Display =       12 - 34567 </p>
            <p>           3. No = 1234;      Mask = R##### - #####               Display =       00000 - 01234 </p>
            <p>           4. No = 1234567;   Mask = R##### - #####               Display =       00012 - 34567 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4-20 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory Input.</p>
            <p>Input in this field must contain 4 '#' characters as a minimum. The number of '#' characters defines the maximum length of the account number.</p>
            <p>When CHECKDIGIT.TYPE = 1, input in this field must contain 12 '#' characters.</p>
            <p>When CHECKDIGIT.TYPE = 2, input in this field must contain 10 '#' characters.</p>
            <p>characters '0...9', 'A...Z', 'a...z' are not allowed.  The only exception being that the 1st character can be 'R' which means that the account number will be right adjusted and that it may contain leading zeros.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.NO.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of account number to be allowed. </p>
            <p>The account number entered as an alternative identifier in the ACCOUNT application will be validated against the value entered here. </p>
            <p>There are two possible values:</p>
            <p>A is for alphanumeric Account numbers such as GBPCUR12345, whilst blank is an implied numeric only record id. It should be noted that if alphanumeric ids are used then it is not appropriate to use a value in the </p>
            <p>CHECKDIGIT.TYPE</p> field.  <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Valid input is either 'A' implying alphanumeric id; or         blank implying numeric id.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.ACCT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique identifier which defines the name of the main record on the file. As many records can be present a meaningful id such as the name of the other Account system may be helpful.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 10 alphanumeric characters. (Mandatory Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHECKDIGIT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Use of a checkdigit will ensure that the user input conforms to the acceptable value of the records in the other system. The input here identifies the check digit calculation method to be used for the alternative account number to be entered in the ACCOUNT application. </p>
            <p>This field should be specifically used where the accounts have 2 check digits based on modulus '97'. </p>
            <p>The following values should be noted: </p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>Id </strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Effect</strong>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>3</td>
                    <td>For 10 digit account numbers with a modulus 11 check</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>5</td>
                    <td>For a standard checkdigit calculation with the         account numbers zero filled to the DISPLAY.MASK</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>99</td>
                    <td>No checkdigit calculation with the account number         zero filled to the DISPLAY.MASK.</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>blank</td>
                    <td>Standard modulus 11 checkdigit</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>NONE</td>
                    <td>No checkdigit at all, only checks minimum and maximum         id length</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>@<em>routine</em></td>
                    <td>The input of an executable <em>routine</em> will         further validate the alternative account identifier when         input in the ACCOUNT application. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>1,2 &amp; 6</td>
                    <td>Specialised. See COMPANY record for details</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. </p>
            <p>The following values will be accepted: '1', '2', '3', '5',         '6', '99', NONE, and 'blank'; or the name of an         executable routine.</p>
            <p>Input of a checkdigit type is only allowed if the         previous field is null, i.e. the account identifier will         be numeric.</p>
            <p>If an executable routine is used it must be prefixed by         '@', and be defined in the PGM.FILE application as type 'S'.         Enrichment is provided from the screen title.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the usage of this ALT.ACCT.PARAMETER record. </p>
            <p>This field may be expanded to allow the user to enter the description of the ALT.ACCT.PARAMETER in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the description is to be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. Multi-language field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

