<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>CASH.FLOW.EXCEPTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this file is to hold all cash flow exceptions raised as part of the start of day cash flow processing.  When forward valued entries are pulled into the cash flow window, defined on the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER file (field CASH.FLOW.DAYS), that where previously outside, then the same limit and overdraft checking is made.  If an entry causes a limit to be exceeded or overdraft situation, then a record in this file will be created. </p>
            <p>This file is used for display purposes only, no input is allowed. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the account number for which the exception has occurred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Account Number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which the entry has caused an exception. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date Format.  Multivalued field associated with field range DATE to LIMIT.OVERDRAFT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the excess caused by an entry. </p>
            <p>If LIMIT.OVERDRAFT contains the narrative 'LIMIT EXCEEDED' then the amount displayed here will be the amount of the excess. </p>
            <p>If LIMIT.OVERDRAFT contains the narrative 'UNAUTHORISED OVERDRAFT' then the amount displayed here will be the debit working balance of the account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Amount format.  Multivalued field associated with field range DATE to LIMIT.OVERDRAFT.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.OVERDRAFT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies whether a Limit has been exceeded or the account has gone into an unauthorised overdraft. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Can contain either the narratives 'LIMIT EXCEEDED' or 'UNAUTHORISED OVERDRAFT'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

