<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>CATEG.ENTRY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is the internal file which contains details of all Profit and Loss entries. </p>
            <p>Entries are generated in this file by every on-line and batch process which involves debiting or crediting Profit and Loss. </p>
            <p>This file is used by any process which needs details of Profit and Loss entries. </p>
            <p>Only the See, Print and List functions may be used in this Application. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRODCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The transaction code to be used for the CRF movement for the CRF.TYPE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alpha character code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the branch or office whose Profit and Loss is updated by this Entry. </p>
            <p>The Company Code is in the format CCGGGLLLL </p>
            <p>           where   CC is the Country Code                    GGG is the Company Group Code </p>
            <p>           and     LLLL is the local code to identify the different                    processing companies (e.g. branches) within one                    Country. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>9 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PC.APPLIED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of Profit and Loss updated by this Entry. </p>
            <p>If the Entry is for a Product type Profit and Loss Category (e.g. Commission), then the Product Category code is also stored in PRODUCT.CATEGORY. </p>
            <p>For Entries to base level Profit and Loss Categories (e.g. Purchase of Goods), then the Profit and Loss Category code needs no further breakdown by Product Category. </p>
            <p>Note : Profit and Loss Category codes are in the range 50000 - 69999. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>5 numeric characters.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CYCLE.FORWARD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes whether forward entries should be cycled to the next working day when the value date on the entry is reached. </p>
            <p>Some applications may raise forward entries with a value date, but no processing may occur on the value date. For example a Fiduciary order, a security order or a Past Due record. It is important for these application to leave the entry as the impact on the cash-flow is required for the account. In these cases the value of this field should be set to Y, which will cause the date to cyled every night instead of being removed. </p>
            <p>Other applications such as LD, Swaps and Bond Processing in securities, allow adjustment of the value date on non-working days, so that it is possible to get a back dated entry for an event to be processed in the future. For these situations thisi field can contain the date on which the event is to be processed, amd therefore the date the forward entry expires. The system will cycle such entries forward when the value date is less than the system date until the expiry date is reached. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>May contain a Y or a Standard format date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A multivalue field containing a variable number of lines of 34 characters which may be printed on descriptive statements in addition to the standard narrative and/or reference. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 34 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.  Multivalue field.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in Category Entry records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROD.MI.CATEG.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the Profit or Loss was earned on a  foreign Currency Account, or a foreign currency transaction, this field contains the Rate which was used to convert the Currency Amount to the local equivalent (AMOUNT.LCY) at the time of the originating transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric characters and decimal point, (standard Rate format, type R), or null.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.INT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.REF.NUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in Category Entry records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAL.MI.CATEG.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPL.DRILLDOWN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The SWIFT Currency Code of the Account or transaction on which the Profit or Loss was earned.  Not used if the originating Account or transaction was in local Currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters or null.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.INT.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUPPRESS.POSITION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the entry should be considered when calculating the effect on the Position file. </p>
            <p>The accounting system will maintain positions automatically where suppression is not indicated.  The statement and CRF entries passed to the accounting program will be totalled by currency, and a position against the local currency will be raised for the net amount in each currency. Category entries will only be considered when suppression is set to "C". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>"Y" or "C".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in Category Entry records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.PROD.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>CRF Product Category. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the reference number by which the originating transaction may be accessed in the front end Application system which generated the Entry. </p>
            <p>For most systems this is the same as OUR.REFERENCE, but not for systems like DATA.CAPTURE where OUR.REFERENCE is an input field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-25 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSPNSE.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value date of the entry if the entry has been suspensed in a value dated accounting system. </p>
            <p>If value dated accounting is in operation (field 2 VALUE.DATED.ACCTNG on the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER file is set to 'Y'), then any transactions entered from applications capable of value dated accounting (currently Funds Transfer, Data Capture, Teller, and Foreign Exchange), that generate split value dated entries will have this field updated.  The value date will indicate the latest value date of entry pairs. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PALCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the run date on which the Entry was generated. </p>
            <p>The run date is normally, but not necessarily the actual date at the time the Entry is generated, e.g. if the previous day's business is still being processed after midnight, the actual date changes, but the run date is still the previous day. </p>
            <p>The date used is from the TODAY field in the DATES record (ref: General Tables) for the Company being processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Standard Date format.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the system by which the Entry was generated and the file from which further details may be obtained. </p>
            <p>The following is a list of possible codes and the corresponding files containing further details: </p>
            <p />
            <p>SYSTEM ID       APPLICATION </p>
            <p>                Foreign Exchange FX              FOREX </p>
            <p>                Funds Transfer FT              FUNDS.TRANSFER </p>
            <p>                Loans and Money Market LD              LD.LOANS.AND.DEPOSITS MM              MM.MONEY.MARKET MMP             MM.PAYMENT.ENTRY MMR             MM.RECEIPT.ENTRY </p>
            <p>SYSTEM ID       APPLICATION </p>
            <p>                Data Capture DC              DATA.CAPTURE </p>
            <p>                Securities SC              SC.BUY.SELL SC              FORWARD.TRADE SC              POSITION.TRANSFER SC              SECURITY.TRANSFER SC              OPT.PURCHASE.SALES SC              OPT.OPTION.TAKEUP SCBD            REDEMPTION.BAL SCBL            BOND.LENT.MASTER SCCP            DIV.POST.CHECK SCCI            CAPTL.INCREASE.DET SCNI            NI.ADMIN.MASTER SCSF            SAFEKEEP.DET SCSD            STOCK.DIV.DET Others          STMT.ENTRY </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2-4 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPARTMENT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Department where the original transaction was input. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric characters Department Account Officer code.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the type of product the interest or commission has been earned on.  Not used in Entries updating base level types of Profit and Loss e.g. Purchase of Goods. </p>
            <p>For interest and charges earned on Customers' Accounts this field contains the Category code from the Account record.  For Profit and Loss earned on other products, the Product Category is entered in the originating transaction or generated by the originating Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 or 5 numeric characters Category code or null.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODCAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGINAL.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the original exchange rate on the entry before auto payments was applied to it. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the Entry. </p>
            <p>All Profit and Loss Entries are expressed in Local Currency, even when they are the result of a foreign currency transaction, or interest and charges calculated on a foreign currency Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus decimal point (standard amount format, type AMT), signed.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRILL.ENQUIRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIG.LOCAL.EQUIV</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEG.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>A unique key by which the Entry may be identified. It is generated by the system, based on the date, system user number and time (in hundredths of a second) at which the transaction is input and a sequence number. </p>
            <p>The key is made up as follows: </p>
            <p>(a)        5 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st            December 1967. </p>
            <p>(b)        5 digit user number, the system user number of the inputter            First introduced in G8.1.00 </p>
            <p>(c)        Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers            and (usually) 2 decimals.  If the time is an exact number            of seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted. </p>
            <p>(d)        Sequence number. </p>
            <p>If a transaction generates several Entries, all the Entries have parts (a), (b) and (c) the same and are distinguished from each other by their Sequence numbers. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>19 numeric or 22 characters consisting of numeric characters with a decimal point after the 15th.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PM.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIQUIDATION.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of transaction.  The code is used to determine M.I.S. details. </p>
            <p>The TRANSACTION table contains details such as Description, SWIFT Narrative and M.I.S. information. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>            
            <p>  Internal file.</p>
            <p>  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PC.PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency for which the CRF movement is to be raised, if different to the currency of the entry. </p>
            <p>When the 'other' side of the accounting entry is the CRF type, the system will raise a CONSOL.ENT.TODAY record in the same currency as the entry, unless the CRF.CURRENCY is specified.  In some circumstances the currency of the deal may be different to the entry raised, for example where a deal in BEF allow settlement in LUF accounts. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-character currency code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Customer on whose behalf the transaction generating the Profit or Loss was performed, or who owns the Account on which the Profit or Loss was earned. </p>
            <p>Not used for transactions where there is no Customer, e.g. cashing travellers' cheques for non customers of the Bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 numeric characters Customer code or null.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in Category Entry records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTERPARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.SELECT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVERSAL.MARKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates that the Entry is the reversal of a previous Entry with the same Transaction code.  Amounts and volumes of Entries accumulated for charging and MIS purposes will be reduced.  (There is no system checking between a reversal Entry and the original Entry.) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>R or null.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Reference given to the transaction/deal by the Bank.  In most cases this reference provides the link between the CATEG.ENTRY file and the master file of the originating application, but for Entries input via DATA.CAPTURE it is only present if input manually. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 16 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters, or null.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any additional element which has been defined locally to meet a particular requirement in one of the applications generating Category Entries. </p>
            <p>In the majority of T24 Applications, the User is allowed to define up to 999 Local Elements in addition to the standard fields previously specified.  These Local Elements are defined by the User where deemed necessary according to local practice. </p>
            <p>If any Local Element(s) defined in an originating Application (e.g. DATA.CAPTURE) are required to be stored in the CATEG.ENTRY record, the Element(s) required must be defined in the CATEG.ENTRY record in the LOCAL.REF.TABLE (ref: Utilities), using the same Local Table number(s) as are defined for the originating Application. </p>
            <p>The Format of these elements is as defined by the User in the LOCAL.TABLE. </p>
            <p>This option is only used by systems like DATA.CAPTURE which do not maintain files beyond the end of day. Any Local Elements entered in other front end systems can be accessed by referring back to their own files. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 characters as defined in the LOCAL.TABLE (ref: Utilities) for this Local Reference field in the originating application.  Multivalue field.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.MAT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The maturity date associated with the resultant CRF entry. </p>
            <p>This date may be present where maturity splitting of CRF date is required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>8-character standard date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSURE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in Category Entry records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OUTSTANDING.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGINAL.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the original account number to which this entry was posted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>A multivalue field linking together all the Statement Entry records and Category Entry records generated at the same time by the same transaction/ deal. </p>
            <p>The keys to the Statement Entry file and the Category Entry file are made up of 2 parts, Statement Number and Sequence Number. </p>
            <p>If a transaction generates several Entries, all the Entries have the same Statement Number, the Entries on the same file are distinguished from each other by their Sequence Numbers. </p>
            <p>The Statement Number consists of: </p>
            <p>1.         4 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st            December 1967. </p>
            <p>2.         Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers and            (usually) 2 decimals.  If the time is an exact number of            seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted. </p>
            <p>The Sequence number is a 4 digit number from 0001 to 9999. </p>
            <p>Every Entry generated by the same transaction/deal has the same values in fields 26.1 to 26.3. </p>
            <p>Field 26.1 contains the Statement Number which is the first part of the key for all the Statement Entries and Category Entries. </p>
            <p>Field 26.2 contains the range of Sequence Numbers used for the Statement Entries. If there are no Statement Entries, this field will contain null. </p>
            <p>Field 26.3 contains the range of Sequence Numbers used for the Category Entries. If there are no Category Entries, this field will contain null. </p>
            <p>Example : If a transaction processed on 3rd June 1986 at 30.5 seconds           after 11.15 a.m. generates 3 Statement Entries and 2 Category           Entries - </p>
            <p>The Statement Number is 672940530.50 made up as follows - </p>
            <p>           Date  6729            Time  40530.50 </p>
            <p>The Entries generated have the following Ids - </p>
            <p>Statement Entries        Category Entries </p>
            <p>672940530.500001         672940530.500001 672940530.500002         672940530.500002 672940530.500003 </p>
            <p>All the Entries have the following values in Fields 26.1 to 26.3 - </p>
            <p>Field 26.1  672940530.50 Field 26.2  1-3      (3 Statement Entries) Field 26.3  1-2      (2 Category Entries) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>a)   Field 26.1  STATEMENT NUMBER 9 integers and (usually) 2      decimals.  b)   Field 26.2  range of STATEMENT ENTRY SEQUENCE NUMBERS.  Up to      5 numeric characters with '-' after the first.  c)   Field 26.3  range of CATEGORY ENTRY SEQUENCE NUMBERS.  Up to 5      numeric characters with '-' after the first.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The CRF Asset Type which corresponds to the 'other' side of the accounting entry. </p>
            <p>The system will automatically generate the 'other' side of accounting entries if this field is specified.  The system will raise a record to the CONSOL.ENT.TODAY file if this type is specified for the opposite amount of the entry, or the CRF.AMOUNT and CRF.CURRENCY if specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-12 character consolidation asset type.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOKING.DATE.SEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THEIR.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reference given to the transaction/deal by the Customer/correspondent bank, e.g. their reference for SWIFT, cheque serial number. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 16 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount to be used for generating CRF Entries. </p>
            <p>The amount will normally be taken as the opposide of the AMOUNT.FCY for foreign currency entries, or the AMOUNT.LCY for local.  If the currency is different to eht entry and the amount does not correspond to that of the entry, the CRF.AMOUNT will be used.  This amount should be signed correctly, as the system makes no checks against this. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 standard amount characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RE.MVMT.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.FILE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUSPENSE.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The suspense category to be used for split value dated transactions. </p>
            <p>When a split value dated transaction is processed in a value dated accounting system then the first 'leg' will be balanced against a suspense account.  This will be washed out when the second leg reaches value date. The suspense account that is used is determined by the category of the second leg entry. </p>
            <p>This category code is derived from the SUS.CATEGORY in the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER file for the PRODUCT.CATEGORY of the entry being suspensed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Numeric characters in the range 10000 - 19999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGINAL.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the amount in the original currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency Market marker. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal file.  This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORIGINAL.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the original currency on the entry. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used in Category Entry records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account Officer responsible for the Customer on whose behalf the transaction generating the Profit or Loss was performed, or for the Account on which the Profit or Loss was earned. </p>
            <p>This field is present in all Category Entries. If there is no Customer/ Account relationship for the original transaction, then the appropriate code has to be entered in the originating application, in some cases it is a department code, e.g. for travel expenses. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-4 numeric characters Department Account Officer code.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNTING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the Profit or Loss was earned on a  foreign Currency Account, or a foreign currency transaction this field contains the Amount of the Entry in the Currency of the originating Account or transaction. Not used in Entries where the origniating Account or transaction was in local Currency. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point (standard amount format, type AMT) signed, or null.  Internal file.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUS.PL.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the customer account number related to the entry.</p>
            <p>When booking PL at customer account company is turned on at INTERCO.PARAMETER for the system id of the entry then the entry has to be booked in the company of this account.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Customer account number populated by the transaction application</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESSING.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the profit and loss entry will actually be realised in the general ledger. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Null. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

