<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>CHEQUE.BATCH</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p> CHEQUE.BATCH </p>
        <p>Cheque Batch is used to group cheques that are to be sent for Clearing or that have been returned or cleared. 
</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The forward or backward date on which the collection credit will be taken into customer account when the cheque/ collection instrument is Cleared. In the case of return of the cheque/ collection instrument, the debit to the specified internal account will be taken into account, on this date. Whenever the user wishes to change the original value date, for reasons like postponement of clearing etc., this field can be used. This field is available in CHEQUE.COLLECTION and in CHEQUE.BATCH also, under each cheque collection record included in the batch. User has the option to use this field or the OVERALL.VALUE.DATE available in the batch. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional field Standard Date format The date entered here will be validated against the range of minimum/ maximum backward and forward values specified in DATES file.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Enter the currency of the Cheque Collection Id in the Cheque Batch. If mulitple currencies in the Cheque Batch, then this field and the AMOUNT field is used to split the amount for cheques in the same currency within a multi currency batch of cheques. One currency must be entered for each Cheque Collection record currency in the Cheque Batch. The CURRENCY field is used in conjunction with the AMOUNT field to calculate the currency totals. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Mandatory (3 alphanumeric characters). Multivalued. No duplicate currencies allowed. Must be a valid currency from the currency file. Currency must exist on the Cheque Batch record.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Override text. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Alphanumeric characters. System updated field. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERALL.STATUS</field>
<desc>
        <p>The indicates the overall status of the cheques on the Cheque Batch record. The field can only be entered after the Cheque Batch record has been authorised. The status entered into the OVERRALL.STATUS field will automatically populate the CHQ.STATUS field of all Cheque Collection Id's that still have a status of CLEARING on the Cheque Batch record. Records with a CHQ.STATUS field not equal CLEARING will not be modified. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional. Only valid input is either RETURNED or CLEARED.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQ.STATUS</field>
<desc>
        <p>This contains the status of the cheque. The CHQ.STATUS field is used to determine what processing should take place to the cheque on the Cheque Collection record. The CHQ.STATUS field does not allow input until the Cheque Batch record has been authorised. Valid input to the CHQ.STATUS field is either CLEARING, CLEARED or RETURNED. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Mandatory. Multivalued. Only CLEARING, RETURNED or CLEARED allowed as input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERALL.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Contains the future or the back date on which the clearing credit of the cheques/ collection instruments will be taken into account. In the case of cheque returns, the date will be taken into account for debit to the internal account specified for this purpose. This field can be entered after the batch is authorised. In a cheque batch, this field indicates the overall value date of the cheque records grouped under that batch. The value date entered in this field is populated automatically to the value dates of the individual CHEQUE.COLLECTION records grouped under this batch, except for the ones with specific value dates. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional Standard Date input The date entered here will be validated against the range of minimum/ maximum backward and forward values specified in DATES file and suitable overrides/ errors will be produced</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.OF.CHQS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Enter the number of cheques that are in the physical batch of cheques. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Mandatory. Numeric The number of cheques entered must equal the number of Cheque Collection Ids entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>Overall description of Batch. The better the decription the easier is is to identify when updating at a later date. This description can be used in any specified language. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> 3-35 alphanumeric characters. Mulitlanguage field. Mandatory input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable. Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Insert text here </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Rule 1 Rule 2</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQ.COLL.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Enter the Cheque Collection Id of the Cheque Collection record to be included on the Cheque Batch record. The Cheque Collection record holds the information on the cheque that is to be included and will automatically populate the CHQ.CURRENCY, CHQ.AMOUNT fields and set the CHQ.STATUS field to CLEARING. After the Cheque Batch record has been authorised the Cheque Collection Id can not be removed from the batch. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Mandatory. Mulitvalued. Must be a valid Cheque Collection Id. No duplicate Cheque Collection Ids allowed. Cheque Collection Ids can only be used on one Cheque Batch record.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved For Future Use </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No Input Allowed</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQ.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Displays the currency of the cheque from the Cheque Collection record. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Display only. Mulitvalued.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>Local reference fields may be defined to contain additional information required about cheque issues. Fields may be setup according to the T24 structure of local reference data elements and </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> As defined in the appropriate local table definitions</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Enter the total amount of the cheques. This field contains either the total amount for the Cheque Batch record in a single currency batch or the total amount of the currency specified in the CURRENCY field for a multi currency batch. The CURRENCY and AMOUNT fields are validated against the internally calculated amounts for each currency. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Mandatory. Multivalued.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Enter the appropriate charge type to be applied to all cheques in the Cheque Batch record. The charge type can be either FT.COMMISION.TYPE or FT.CHARGE.TYPE. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Optional. Must be a valid FT.COMMISION.TYPE or FT.CHARGE.TYPE.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUE.BATCH.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the ID field on the CHEQUE.BATCH record. It contains the application id 'CCBA' concatenated with a julian date and a sequence number. Eg. {CCBA9533200001} </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> No reversal allowed.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQ.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Displays the amount of the cheque from the Cheque collection record. </p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p> Display only. Multivalued.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

