<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>CREATE.NETTING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application takes accounting entries for transaction that are covered by a NETTING.AGREEMENT and groups them together (see NETTING).</p>
            <p>Transactions elected for NETTING will be built into groups using the 'V' FUNCTION.</p>
            <p>The selection will be based on:</p>
            <p>CURRENCY, COUNTERPARTY AND VALUE.DATE (for FOREX transactions)</p>
            <p>CURRENCY,COUNTERPARTY, VALUE.DATE, SYSTEM.ID,SEND.CORR.BK,REC.CORR.Bk and OPERATION.CODE (For FT transaction )</p>
            <p />
            <p>Please note NETTING application is used by FT to generate MT102 and MT203. I.e., No Accounting entries at Netting Level for FT.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the System.Id for which Netting details to be created. Details entered here along with COUNTERPARTY, SYSTEM.ID, REC.CORR.BANK, SEND.CORR.BANK, VALUE.DATE,  CURRENCY and OPERATION.CODE is be used to select criteria for propagation to the NETTING file to generate MT102 / MT203 instead of MT103 / MT202 respectively.</p>
            <p>To create netting for FOREX application CURRENCY, COUNTER.PARTY, and VALUE.DATE is alone used to for selection Criteria and Input in this field not allowed.</p>
            <p>This field is made as multi value field for future use. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>FT or FX</p>
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.CORR.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Sender Correspondent Bank (tag 53) in Funds transfer application and details entered here along with COUNTERPARTY, SYSTEM.ID, REC.CORR.BANK,VALUE.DATE, CURRENCY and OPERATION.CODE  is be used to select transactions for propagation to the NETTING file to generate MT102 and MT203.</p>
            <p>To create netting for Forex application CURRENCY,COUNTERPARTY, and VALUE.DATE is alone used to for selection Criteria and Input in this field not allowed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input allowed only when SYSTEM.ID = FT </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>When CHQB is given in this field, the system will try to net payments, which have been instructed to be paid by CHEQUE to beneficiary. When CREDIT is given, the credit transfers should be processed according to the netting agreement between sender and receiver.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input </p>
            <p>Valid values are CREDIT and CHQB</p>
            <p>Mandatory for MSG.TYPE 102     </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the value date of transactions used in association with CURRENCY and COUNTERPARTY as selection criteria. The value date represents the start of a range of value dates that will be used to select transactions for propagation to the NETTING file. The parameter NETTING.PARAMETERS - DAYS.AHEAD will be summed with this date to provide the final value date in the range. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.CORR.BK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Receiver Correspondent Bank (tag 54) in Funds transfer application and details entered here along with COUNTERPARTY, SYSTEM.ID, SEND.CORR.BANK, VALUE.DATE, CURRENCY and OPERATION.CODE is be used to select transactions for propagation to the NETTING file to generate MT102 and MT203.</p>
            <p>To create netting for Forex application CURRENCY, COUNTERPARTY, and VALUE.DATE is alone used to for selection Criteria and Input in this field not allowed.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input allowed only when SYSTEM.ID = FT </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTERPARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Counterparty of transactions used is association with VALUE.DATE and CURRENCY as selection criteria. Will be used to select transactions for propagation to the NETTING file for agreement.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATE.NETTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is an identification code. </p>
            <p>It should be use to ease identification of the criteria contained in the associated CREATE.NETTING record. </p>
            <p>Use a convention that obeys the rules below. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-10 alphanumeric characters.  (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency of transactions used is association with VALUE.DATE and COUNTERPARTY as selection criteria. Will be used to select transactions for propagation to the NETTING file for agreement. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the message type for which netting to be done.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Swift Message Type as defined in DE.MESSAGE.</p>
            <p>This field if valid only if System.Id has value 'FT'</p>
            <p>Now the allowed message type are 102 and 203</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

