<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AC</product>
        <table>EB.ACCRUAL</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table will store details of individual charge or commissions which are being accrued or amortised. </p>
            <p>    It will normally be updated via a forward accounting entry which will store addtional data related to the accrual process in the multi valued ACCRUAL.DATA field.</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.ACT.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The unrounded local equivalent of the amount accrued to date in foregin currency. Updated for foregin currency amounts.</p>
                <p>    The local equivalent of each individual accrual amount will be calculated at the current mid rate and then added to the local amount accrued to date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.AMORT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the charge amount is being accrued or amortised. A indicates accrual M indicates amortisation.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The rounded amount accrued to date in Foregin currency. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The rounded amount accrued to date in foregin currency. Updated for foregin currency amounts.</p>
                <p>    The local equivalent of each individual accrual amount will be calculated that the current mid rate and then added to the local amount accrued to date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.DAYS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The number of days accrued to date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.FROM.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The date acruals commenced.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.OTS.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a set which is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the status of the accrual to date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the unrounded Foreign Currency Amount which has been accrued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.OTS.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a set which is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the status of the accrual to date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the unrounded Local Currency Amount which has been accrued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.TO.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The date that accruals have been calculated to.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Can be set by a calling application to indicate that the end.date, charge amount has changed or that accruals need to be reversed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.AMT.CHG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a multivalued set which also includes ACC.AMT.EFF.DATE, ACC.AMT.FCY and ACC.AMT.LCY. This field set is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the schedule to be used for future accruals, allowing for 'catch-up' adjustments for retrospective changes and schedule adjustments relating to Day Basis. The daily accrual processed by core accounting is driven from this field set.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the Charge Amount used as the basis for calculating ACC.AMT.LCY &amp; ACC.AMT.FCY in the schedule described above. It is an information-only field which is not referenced by core accounting when raising the accrual.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMORT.ADJUST</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a system updated field.</p>
                <p>Defaulted from ic.charge record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMORT.DIF.CTG.ACCT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMORT.DIFF.PL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a system updated field.         </p>
                <p>Defaulted to “” or END or SPECIAL based on ic.charge application</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMORT.RMN.CTG.ACCT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMORT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a system updated field</p>
                <p>Defaulted to “” or END or SPECIAL based on ic.charge application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APPLICATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The source application e.g. an account, contract or portfolio.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.START.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Date Type Field </p>
                <p>Contains Accrual Calculation Start date based on the Cancel Period</p>
                <p>CALC.START.DATE = Charge Make Due Date + Cancel Period</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field value gets updated with the date on which the change in either amount or end date or both happens. It is updated by the calling application.</p>
                <p>The new set of fields should be store in Descending order of change date, so, latest change would always be on top of this multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHARGE.AMT.FCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The amount to accrue or amortise in foregin currency.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHARGE.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The amount to accrue or amortise in local currency.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.AMT.FCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a multivalued set which also includes ACC.AMT.EFF.DATE, ACC.AMT.LCY and ACC.AMT.CHG. This field set is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the schedule to be used for future accruals, allowing for 'catch-up' adjustments for retrospective changes and schedule adjustments relating to Day Basis. The daily accrual processed by core accounting is driven from this field set.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the Foreign Currency Amount(s) in the schedule described above.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHARGE.CCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The currency of the amount being accrued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHARGE.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A charge identifier provided by the source application. For example from generic charges on accounts it would be the IC.CHARGE key followed by the IC.CHARGE.PRODUCT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CO.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The company code of the source account or contract. Derived from the accounting entry.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONTRACT.BAL.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The contract balance @id.  When amortise in local is set this will be the original contract balance @id suffixed with –LOCAL ; for applications that do not interface to EB.CONTRACT.BALANCES this will be the customer debit account _LOCAL</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The key of the source contract, account or portfolio.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRF.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Normally accruals are booked to CAL (CRF or CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB) and to P&amp;L using the P&amp;L category code, i.e the CAL asset type is the same as the P&amp;L category code.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>For Arrangement Architecture accruals the CAL entry can be booked using an asset type that differs from the P&amp;L category code.</p>
                <p>This field will hold the asset type for AA accruals and if it is not populated the CRF accruals will be booked using the P&amp;L code.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The customer of the source contract account or portfolio.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEALER.DESK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EB.ACCRUAL.PARAM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If non standard accruals methids are required this can be passed by the source applciation to indicate how accruals and rounding are to take place.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>END.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The end date of the accrual or amortisation process.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a multivalued set which also includes ACC.AMT.EFF.DATE, ACC.AMT.FCY and ACC.AMT.CHG. This field set is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the schedule to be used for future accruals, allowing for 'catch-up' adjustments for retrospective changes and schedule adjustments relating to Day Basis. The daily accrual processed by core accounting is driven from this field set.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the Local Currency Amount(s) in the schedule described above.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FREQUENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The accrual frequency, D = daily M = monthly </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FT.COMM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The key to the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record used to calculate the charge amount</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.AMOUNT.FCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a system updated field.</p>
                <p>When there is a change in charge amount which is in FCY.  When more than one change happens on a given date, this would be overwritten.</p>
                <p>Updated only with SPECIAL or END amort types.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.AMOUNT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a system updated field.</p>
                <p>When there is a change in charge amount which is in LCY or local equivalent of the FCY amount.  When more than one change happens on a given date, this would be overwritten</p>
                <p>Updated only with SPECIAL or END amort types</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.END.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a system updated field.</p>
                <p>Updated when there is a change in the end date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIGINAL.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When maortise in local is active for a foregin currency amount both the original foreign currency amount and local currency amounts are amortised, in other words the original exchange rate at teh time off booking the charge is retained. This original rate is used to populate the exhange rate field of the P&amp;L amortisation entries </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OTS.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The total amount accrued to date in foreign currency, Normally the accrued amounts are split by month.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OTS.AMOUNT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The total amount accrued to date in local currency.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is for information only and retains the period derived from FT.COMMISSION.TYPE for applications that use this to derive the end date of the accrual or maotisation process.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The P&amp;L category that the acruals are booked to. THis will normally correspond to the pl category on the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.EFF.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a multivalued set which also includes ACC.AMT.FCY, ACC.AMT.LCY and ACC.AMT.CHG. This field set is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the schedule to be used for future accruals, allowing for 'catch-up' adjustments for retrospective changes and schedule adjustments relating to Day Basis. The daily accrual processed by core accounting is driven from this field set.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the effective date(s) in the schedule described above.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PREV.AMT.FCY</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PREV.AMT.LCY</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PREV.END.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field value would be updated by eb accrual processing, when there is change in period end date.</p>
                <p>It is always updated only once by system, during the first change in date for a given date, that is, it would not be be overwritten during subsequent changes for the date</p>
                <p>This is a system updated field.</p>
                <p>Updated only with SPECIAL or END amort types</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The product category of the source contract account or portfolio. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>START.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The start date of the accrual period.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUSPENSE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates that for charges being accrued on accounts that the account is currently in suspense.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The system @id related to the source application and picked up from the accounting entry.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TXN.CR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The credit transaction code derived from FT.COMMISSION.TYPE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TXN.DR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The debit transaction code derived from FT.COMMISSION.TYPE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.OTS.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a set which is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the status of the accrual to date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the rounded Foreign Currency Amount which has been accrued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.OTS.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a set which is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the status of the accrual to date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the rounded Local Currency Amount which has been accrued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACC.OTS.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This no-input field is part of a set which is populated by applications with a daily, non-linear accrual method such as Securities Safekeeping, Management/Advisory and Trailer Fees. The set illustrates the status of the accrual to date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field shows the system date up to which T24 has accrued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The department account officer from the accounting entry.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCR.ACT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The unrounded amount accrued to date in foregin currency. Updated for foregin currency amounts.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
             <t>
            <field>CR.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
            <p>Value in this field is system updated. Internal account is updated in this field based on the category passed by applications to core eb accrual processing</p>
            <p>When this field value is not null, amortization credits this internal account instead of P&L.</p> 
            <p>TXN.DR and TXN.CR are mandatory when the profit is booked against an internal account instead of P&L account</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    <t><field>AMORT.DIFF.PL.CAT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
