<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>EB.AF.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application defines the parameters relating to the restriction of unauthorised movements to available funds. The parameters may be set at application level or at transaction level within the application. Input is not allowed here but through EB.AF.PARAM.CHANGE. Any new parameters effective today will be written to the EB.AF.PARAM after the end of day. </p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the date the parameter changes has been effective from.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines for which transaction code within that application should unauthorised updates to Available funds be blocked. If a parameter is set at transaction level it will take precedence over the parameter set at application level                         </p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p>A valid transaction code No duplication is allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the application at which restriction for update of Available funds movements and balance by unauthorised movements, may be made.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p>Valid Id to EB.SYSTEM.ID</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.BAL.NAU.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines unauthorised credits for that application do not update the available balance and do not raise a movement for available funds.                                                </p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p>NO Do not raise available funds movement with unauthorised credits                      </p>
            <p>Null Raise available funds movements with unauthorised debits</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.BAL.NAU.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines unauthorised debits for that application do not update the available balance and do not raise a movement for available funds.                                                </p>
            <p>Validation Rule</p>
            <p>NO Do not raise available funds movement with unauthorised debits                       </p>
            <p>Null Raise available funds movements with unauthorised debits</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.NAU.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines unauthorised credits for that transaction code within that application do not update the available balance and do not raise a movement for available funds. Whatever is input at transaction level will take precedence over the parameter set at application level.                      </p>
            <p>Validation Rule </p>
            <p>NO Do not raise available funds movement with unauthorised credits                                        </p>
            <p>Null Raise available funds movements with unauthorised credits</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.NAU.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>his field determines unauthorised debits for that application do not update the available balance and do not raise a movement for available funds                               </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NO Do not raise available funds movement with unauthorised debits          </p>
            <p>Null Raise available funds movements with unauthorised debits</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

