<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>EB.AF.PARAM.CHANGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>It allows to only change or add parameters relating to the restriction of unauthorised movements to available funds. The parameters may be set at application level or at transaction level within the application. Any new parameters effective today will be written to the EB.AF.PARAM after the end of day. Only the parameters existing in EB.AF.PARAM are used to restrict movements.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field determines the date the parameter changes will be effected. If it is todays date then the change will go to EB.AF.PARAM after end of day. </p>
            <p>If date input is less than todays date then it is defaulted todays date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Valid date</p>
            <p>Defaulted to todays date if      there is any input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field determines for which transaction code within that application should unauthorised updates be blocked. If a parameter is set at transaction level it will take precedence over the parameter set at application level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> A valid transaction      code </p>
            <p />
            <p />No duplication is allowed     </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.NAU.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>  This field determines unauthorised debits for that transaction code within that application do not update the available balance and do not raise a movement for available funds.  Whatever is input at transaction level will take precedence over the parameter set at application level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> NO  Do not raise      available funds movement with unauthorised debits </p>
            <p>Null  Raise available      funds movements with unauthorised debits</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID.........</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> The record id defines the application for which there will be an update restriction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> It should be a valid      record from EB.SYSTEM.ID</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field></field>
<desc>
        <p data-mc-conditions="DOCTYPES.Helptext">
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field determines if unauthorised credits do not update the available balance and do not raise </p>
            <p />movements<p />at application level.   <p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p> NO  Do not raise      available funds movement with unauthorised credits </p><p>Null  Raise available      funds movements with unauthorised credits</p></p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.BAL.NAU.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> This field determines if unauthorised credits for that application do not update the available balance and do not raise a movement for available funds. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> NO  Do not raise      available funds movement with unauthorised credits </p>
            <p>Null  Raise available      funds movements with unauthorised credits</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.BAL.NAU.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> This field determines unauthorised debits for that application do not update the available balance and do not raise a movement for available funds. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> NO  Do not raise      available funds movement with unauthorised debits </p>
            <p>Null  Raise available      funds movements with unauthorised debits</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.NAU.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   This field determines unauthorised credits for that transaction code within that application do not update the available balance and do not raise a movement for available funds.  Whatever is input at transaction level will take precedence over the parameter set at application level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> NO  Do not raise      available funds movement with unauthorised credits</p>
            <p>Null  Raise available funds      movements with unauthorised credits</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>It identifies the SYSTEM.ID to which there should be a restriction of unauthorised debits or credits or both to available funds movements.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid id from EB.SYSTEM.ID</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

