<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>EB.FINANCIAL.SYSTEM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This new table will allow the balancing options to defined for financial system.   A default record of T24 will be used for defining standard system behaviour.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Here we can choose the option to raise the self balancing entries by different SYSTEM.ID and POSITION.TYPE </p>
            <p />
            <p>   When balancing entries are raised during the Close of Business the system will write to the EB.EOD.ERROR file.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p> Description of the EB.FINANCIAL.SYSTEM</p>
            <p>       __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>          (1) Up to 35 characters free text.</p>
            <p />
            <p>              Multi-value field.</p>
            <p>              (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLNCING.TXN.CDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of Transaction for the self balancing entries.</p>
            <p>   __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>   The Transaction Code on an entry determines the references and narratives printed on statements and also default values which are added to the entry if not entered by the User, e.g. Value Date, Exposure Date, etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Category and transaction code must be input for default records and are to be used </p>
            <p>   when left blank on a system/postion type multi value set</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>     (1) 3 numeric character Transaction Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIN.SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID of the Financial System record </p>
            <p />
            <p>   3 Alapha Numeric character</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.ID.POS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define the SYSTEM.ID-POSITION.TYPE </p>
            <p> POSITION.TYPE should be a valid entry in FX.POS.TYPE</p>
            <p>   __________________________________________________</p>
            <p>   Based on this the self balacing entries will be raised for different applications and position type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Multi Value field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTRNL.BAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Balancing entry raised using this balance type.</p>
            <p>   __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>    (1) It must be an existing code on the AC.BALANCE.TYPE table</p>
            <p>    (2) Only with INTERNAL type AC.BALANCE.TYPE can be used.</p>
            <p>    (3) Mandatory input, if BALANCE.INTRNL is set to Y</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.BL.SYS.COB</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to raise the self balancing entries during COB</p>
            <p>   __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If the field is set to Y, the self balancing entries will be raised during COB.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If the field is set to NO, the accounting stops  processing and gives a fatal error during cob.  This will stop the transaction being processed at all.  It will be recommended that this setting should be selected for temenos test environements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    (1) Y or NO</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Multi Value Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.BL.SYS.ONL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to raise the self balancing entries during Online</p>
            <p>   _______________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Specifies Wether the self balancing entries has to be raised online or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If the field is set to Y, the self balancing entries will be raised online.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If the field is set to NO, the accounting stops  processing and gives a fatal error.  This will stop the transaction being processed at all.  It will be recommended that this setting should be selected for temenos test environements.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    (1) Y or NO</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Multi Value Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCED.INTRNL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Use to raise the self balancing entries for internal balance type entries</p>
            <p>   _______________________________________________</p>
            <p>   Specifies if the internal entries should be balanced or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    (1) Y or NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCING.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Category code for the Internal account</p>
            <p>   _______________________________________________</p>
            <p>   Identifies the Category code part of the account number that is to be raised.  Category and transaction code must be input for default records and are to be used when left blank on a system/postion type multi value set.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    (1) Code entered must be on the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

