<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS stores the details relating to the way the accounting entries will be generated in order to make the contracts compatible with the IFRS requirements. This is kept as a separate table so that the user can do the setup based on their requirements. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Upon validation the POSITION.TYPE will be defaulted to "IF".</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.ENT.TGRT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Speficies whether the entry needs to be raised to Internal Accounts or to the CRF base.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.THIS.MTH.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The category to be used while posting entries for backdated or future-dated amendment. The category in this field will be used to raise entry to adjust the current month's profit and loss.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory only if ENTRY.TARGET is set as PL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING.STYLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows the specifying of the posting style to be followed i.e.  IO or ADJUST method. </p>
            <p />
            <p>On an ADJUST basis, the system will post the difference between yesterday value (IFRS balance) and today’s value (IFRS balance) where as on I/O basis, the system will reverse yesterday’s value and re-post the new value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>CONTRA.TXN denotes the Transaction codes to be used for the generation of entries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1. For CRF entry target, only a valid RE.TXN.CODE is allowed.</p>
            <p>2. For Account entry target, only a valid entry in TRANSACTION table is allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REV.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Reversal transaction codes to be used for the generation of entries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1. For CRF entry target, only a valid RE.TXN.CODE is allowed.</p>
            <p>2. For Account and PL entry target, only a valid entry in TRANSACTION table is allowed. </p>
            <p>3. Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USE.AC.HD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is part of the associated multi-value set of fields for ACCT.HEAD.TYPE above.</p>
            <p>This field may be pointing to any existing ACCT.HEAD.TYPE defined already in the IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS.</p>
            <p>If there is any input in USE.ACCT.HEAD.TYPE, then the associated multi-value fields  are NOINPUT for that ACCT.HEAD.TYPE </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of IFRS.POSTING.DETAILS records will be a free text field to link to the contracts at IAS.CLASSIFICATION – IFRS.SUBTYPE level.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.YR.ENTRY.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The category to be used while posting entries for backdated amendment. The category in this field will be used to raise entry to adjust the previous year's profit and loss.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory only if ENTRY.TARGET is set as PL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IN.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the Reversal transaction codes to be used for the generation of entries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1. For CRF entry target, only a valid RE.TXN.CODE is allowed.</p>
            <p>2. For Account and PL entry target, only a valid entry in TRANSACTION table is allowed. </p>
            <p>3. Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTRY.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field ENTRY.TYPE will allow specifying the type of the entry. It can have different categories to post the profit amounts and loss amounts by specifying PROFIT or LOSS respectively. If it is specified as BOTH, the system will post profit or loss to the same category.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENTRY.TARGET</field>
<desc>
            <p>ENTRY.TARGET will allow specifying whether the entry needs to be raised to Internal Accounts, PL categories or to the CRF base.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.REV.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>CONTRA.REV.TXN denotes the Reversal transaction codes to be used for the generation of entries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1. For CRF entry target, only a valid RE.TXN.CODE is allowed.</p>
            <p>2. For Account entry target, only a valid entry in TRANSACTION table is allowed. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>A freeform field to record the description of the specific record. Can be used to highlight the unique settings in the individual records in a user friendly way.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.PREV.MTH.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The category to be used while posting entries for backdated amendment. The category in this field will be used to raise entry to adjust the previous month's profit and loss.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory only if ENTRY.TARGET is set as PL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.HEAD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>Holds the asset types defined in the IFRS.ACCT.METHODS i.e AMORTISED, FAIRVALUE, DISCLOSURE, IMPAIR.AMORTISED, UNWIND or IMPAIR.AMC.ADJUST.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Also holds the hedge asset types HEDGED.EFFECTIVE, HEDGING.EFFECTIVE, HEDGED.INEFFECTIVE, HEDGING.INEFFECTIVE, HEDGED.CLOSED.RELATION, HEDGING.CLOSED.RELATION</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Hedge related asset types are allowed only when 'IH' product is installed in the company.</p>
            <p>If HEDGED.EFFECTIVE is defined, then system validates for HEDGING.EFFECTIVE also to be defined</p>            
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the posting is to happen to the CONTINGENT or the NON-CONTINGENT base. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the internal account category for account type entries, PL category for PL type entries or CRF asset type. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory Input</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRA.CAT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the internal account category for account type entries or CRF asset type. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

