<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>NETTING.AGREEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>Payment NETTING - </p>
            <p>(Maintenance file) </p>
            <p>Used to define the NETTING agreement that exists between the bank and customer. </p>
            <p>Each agreement will be identified by its AGREEMENT.NO during the NETTING process. </p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>A single agreement for each Customer record.</p>
            <p>The first part of ID of the record can either be customer ID or 8 or 11 BIC code. BIC code accepted only for message type 101</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency for which the agreement is valid. If it is null, the agreement is for all currencies.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This     field is inputable if the Netting Agreement Id has message type 102.</p>
            <p />
            <p>3 characters     (uppercase alpha) - type SSS or 1 to 3 numeric characters Currency Code.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETTING.AGREEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This can be either a customer code or customer mnemonic, followed by a "." &amp; then the module or message type the Netting agreement is for (e.g. 100500.RP, 100500.102)</p>
            <p />
            <p>For each customer.module/Message type defined in the customer file an agreement can be established for the netting of transactions. </p>
            <p />
            <p>To define a Message netting for FT application (ie. to group MT103 / MT202's &amp; send a single MT102 / MT203 in lieu of it) , the Netting.Payment field in DE.PARM &amp; the Netting.Allowed field DE.MESSAGE should be set to "Yes"- Otherwise Not allowed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1 to     6 Numeric character Customer Number or 3 to 10 character customer mnemonic +     "." + Module or Message Type.</p>
            <p>Module     FT can not be given, instead message type(101,102,203) can be given</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the systems that will be included within the netting process.</p>
            <p>The following is a list of possible codes and the corresponding files containing further details:-</p>
            <p>SYSTEM ID APPLICATION</p>
            <p>Foreign Exchange FX FOREX </p>
            <p>Funds Transfer FT  (To send MT203 instead of MT202 from Funds transfer application)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>FX / FT ONLY at present (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCLUDED.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identify the currencies that will be included in the netting process. </p>
            <p>A combination of included and excluded currencies is not allowed (either one or the other) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 characters (uppercase alpha) - type SSS or 1 to 3         numeric characters Currency Code .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This field identifies the type of operation. If this field is null then the agreement is valid for both CREDIT and CHQB.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This field is inputable if the Netting Agreement Id has message type 102.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 12 type AMT (Standard Amount Format)       characters plus a decimal point.</p>
            <p />
            <p>It       is associated to SETTLEMENT.CCY field. This field is allowed only when       currency is given.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the start date applicable to this agreement. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Date to be entered in the standard date format. </p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Maximum total settlement amount for the associated currency. The total settlement amount in the netted entries should be less than or equal to the amount specified in this field. If not, the message MT102 will not be processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field will be allowed for input only if the Netting Agreement Id has message type 102.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Up to 12 type AMT (Standard       Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
            <p>It is associated to       SETTLEMENT.CCY field. This field is allowed only when currency is given.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGREED.CUSTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the Customer BIC code for which there is an agreement to debit the account as mentioned in Inward MT101 message.</p>
            <p>MT101 message requires Message User Group (MUG) registration and hence the registration is required between the Sender of the message and Ordering Customer with Receiver of MT101. To check this during Inward message processing, details can be specified here by creating a Agreement record for the Sender of MT101 (ID) and ordering Customer details (50G) in Agreed.Custs.</p>
            <p>When Check.Agreement  is set to "YES" in DE.MESSAGE for message MT101, then Incoming MT101 message will be moved to Repair incase the Agreement does not exist for the Sender or if Ordering Customer BIC code is not available in Agreed.Custs. This processing is applicable only when AGREED.ACCTS field is null and AGREED.CUSTS is not null for the MT101 message containing Ordering Customer BIC code processed through OFS.GLOBUS.MANAGER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />Input       allowed only when the ID has message type 101 otherwise Not allowed.<p /><p>Should be a Valid BIC code 8,9,12,11 Characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGREED.ACCTS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the Account number for which there is an agreement to process the Inward MT101 message.</p>
            <p>MT101 message requires Message User Group (MUG) registration and hence the registration is required between the Sender of the message and Ordering Customer with Receiver of MT101. To check this during Inward message processing, details can be specified here by creating a Agreement record for the Sender of MT101 (ID) and ordering Customer Account details in Agreed.Accts.</p>
            <p>When Check.Agreement  is set to "YES" in DE.MESSAGE for message MT101, then Incoming MT101 message with Account details will be moved to Repair incase the Agreement does not exist for the Sender or if Ordering Account is not available in Agreed.Accts. This processing is applicable only when AGREED.ACCTS field is not null for MT101 message containing Ordering Account details processed through OFS.GLOBUS.MANAGER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />Input       allowed only when the ID has message type 101 otherwise Not allowed.<p /><p>Should be a Valid Customer Account.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGREEMENT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The netting agreement number given by the customer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3-16 Alpha numeric characters.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the final date covered by this netting agreement. </p>
            <p>Any contracts value after this date will NOT be eligible for netting under this agreement. </p>
            <p>Any contracts from START.DATE to END.DATE will default to Y in the NETTING.STATUS field on the transaction. </p>
            <p>Leaving this field blank indicates that the agreement is open ended. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Enter date in standard date format. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDED.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identify the currencies that will be excluded from the netting process. </p>
            <p>A combination of included and excluded currencies is not allowed (either one or the other) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 characters (uppercase alpha) - type SSS or 1 to 3         numeric characters Currency Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

