<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>NOTICE.WITHDRAWAL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file records the withdrawal notice given by the holder of a savings account. </p>
            <p>It stores the amount that can be withdrawn and the dates when the funds are available. When a withdrawal is made on this account this information is checked and an override message displayed if the conditions are not met. </p>
            <p>Note: Muliple withdrawal notices for the same account can be stored. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.TAKEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date from which notice is given of withdrawal. Can be prior to today. </p>
            <p>This date (and the amount to be withdrawn - See NOTICE.AMOUNT) will be used to determine the date when the funds will be made available (DATE.AVAIL.FROM &amp; UPTO). </p>
            <p>This is calculated based on the period for this withdrawal amount setup up on the SAVINGS.COND file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>11 Date</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.AMT.TAKEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount the customer intends to withdraw. </p>
            <p>This amount will determine the notice period to be used from the SAVINGS.COND file. Eg. 3months notice may be required for amounts upto 500.00 whereas 6months notice is required for larger amounts. </p>
            <p>NOTE: Onc a notice amount is specifed the customer will be allowed to make ANY NUMBER of withdrawals upto this amount, without an override, until the notice is removed from this file or the UPTO date is reached. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>19 Numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Savings account number for which notice of withdrawal is being given. </p>
            <p>When the customer gives notice of a withdrawal it is recorded in this file using the account number as the key. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>16 Numeric characters (i Must be a valid savings account ie the account category must be defined on the SAVINGS record of ACCOUNT.CLASS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.AVAIL.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date when the funds will be made available. </p>
            <p>Calculated based on the date when notice was given (NOTICE.DATE) and the notice period defined on the SAVINGS.COND file. </p>
            <p>Eg. If the notice date given for a 500.00 withdrawal is 13/04/90 and the notice period is 3M (3 months) then the DATE.AVAIL.FROM will be set to 13/07/90. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>11 Date NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.AVAIL.UPTO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date upto which the funds will be made available. </p>
            <p>This is calculated based on the DATE.AVAIL.FROM and the availablity set in the SAVINGS.COND file. </p>
            <p>Eg. If the date available from is set to 13/07/90 and the AVAILABLITY field in the SAVINGS.COND file is 1M then the DATE.AVAIL.UPTO will be set to 13/08/90. </p>
            <p>If a withdrawal is attempted outside the FROM and UPTO date then a override: </p>
            <p>ACCOUNT &amp; - NOTICE CONDS FOR WITHDRAWAL NOT MET </p>
            <p>is displayed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>11 Date NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREE.AMT.TAKEN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

