<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>POS.ACCT.CORRECTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Allows correction entries to be passed to position accounts.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The exchange rate between the foreign and local currencies. This can be specified when a foreign currency position account is specified in either the CREDIT.POS.ACCT or DEBIT.POS.ACCT field. If the field is left blank in this circumstance, the system will complete the field by calculating the exchange rate from values in the AMOUNT.FCY and AMOUNT.LCY fields, unless the AMOUNT.LCY field is blank, in which case the value will be taken from the current midrate in the currency table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains overrides accepted by the user. NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contract id in the format “PAC/07123/67890” using the mask “L###/#####/##############”. The first three characters (“PAC”) are the application id. The next five characters (“07123”) are the year and julian date. The last five characters (“67890”) are the sequence number.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.POS.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The position account to be debited. This must be an existing position account and need not be specified, if CREDIT.POS.ACCT has been specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains statement numbers generated by the system. NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.FCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the transaction in foreign currency. This must be specified unless a single sided entry is being passed to a local currency position account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The amount of the transaction in local currency. This must be specified, if a single sided entry is being passed to a local currency position account. Otherwise, it may be left blank, in which case the system will complete the field by calculating the amount using the value in the EXCHANGE.RATE field, if one was specified, or using the current midrate from the currency table, if the EXCHANGE.RATE field is blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.POS.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The position account to be credited. This must be an existing position account and need not be specified, if a DEBIT.POS.ACCT has been specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The currency of the transaction. This must match the currency of the foreign position account specified in CREDIT.POS.ACCT or DEBIT.POS.ACCT. If a single sided entry is being passed to a local currency position account, this field should be blank.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

