<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>POSTING.RESTRICT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of this table is to define any type of restrictions which may be imposed on Accounts, e.g. 'POST NO DEBITS', 'WHEREABOUTS UNKNOWN', 'PENDING CLOSURE',  etc. </p>
            <p>Posting Restriction codes may be assigned to Accounts as required, which then means that any entries meeting the specified conditions will require an override. </p>
            <p>The system will automatically close any Account with a Posting Restriction in the range 90-99, as soon as all Balances are zero. </p>
            <p />
            <p>A basic restriction will work on all entries regardless of the accounting entry type (TRANSACTION code). It is also possible </p>
            <p>to make the restriction work only on specified TRANSACTION codes - or to work on all except a few which are </p>
            <p>to be bypassed - see fields ALLOW.TXN and TXN.CODE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESTRICTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of entries that are to be restricted, either only debits, only credits or both. </p>
            <p>This field is used to identify whether only debit, only credit or all entries are to be restricted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters: D(ebit) or C(redit) or A(ll) (Mandatory input) Must be ALL if Id is in the range 80-99.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to setup a list of TRANSACTION codes to be allowed or dis-allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING.RESTR.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the code by which the Posting Restriction details can be identified. </p>
            <p>Certain ranges of Posting Restriction Codes have a predefined purpose and should not be used for anything else. At present these are as follows: </p>
            <p>80-89      PENDING CLOSURE            Used to indicate Accounts which will be            closed soon, but are not to be closed            automatically yet. </p>
            <p>90-99      AUTOMATIC CLOSING            Used to indicate Accounts which should be            closed automatically as soon as all            Balances are zero. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 4 numeric characters based on EB.OBJECT. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOW.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>States whether the values in the field TXN.CODE are to be allowed (set to Yes) or dis-allowed (set to No). If left blank all </p>
            <p>transactions for the restriction type will be processed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Posting Restriction. This description is included in the override message. </p>
            <p>This field is a Description of the Posting Restriction, in the specified Language, which is used for reporting or enrichments.  The Description in Language 1 is stored in Override Messages in prime records. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of the DISPO.OFFICER to be assigned to this POSTING.RESTRICT ID if they are to have authorisation to approve dispo items.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid dispo officer as defined in the DISPO.OFFICER file.</p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the ID of the user defined OVERRIDE, assigned to this POSTING.RESTRICT ID. </p>
            <p>If user defined Override is specified in this field then it is raised instead of the core override. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

