<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>RE.POSITION.BALANCE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FORWARD.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Forward balance as at the end of the current day 'AMT' type field Forward balance is held in 'CURRENCY1'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.CURR.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Current balance held as at the end of the previous day. 'AMT' type field Amount is held in 'CURRENCY1'. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the second currency extracted from the key to the Position file record </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.BAL.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the key to the RE.POSITION.BALANCE file. </p>
            <p>Comprised of the following elements of the Position key :   Currency.Market - 1 character   Position.Type   - 2 characters   Dealer.Desk     - 2 characters   Currency1       - 3 characters   Currency2       - 3 characters </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.POS.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the POSITION record IDS that have been used to create the RE.POSITION.BALANCE record for forward positions. Multivalued field. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.LOCAL.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Forward balance as at the end of the current day in the local currency. 'AMT' type field Forward balance is held in the local currency of the bank. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard T24 customer field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.UPDATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the date at which the RE.POSITION.BALANCE record was last updated in the End Of Day. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the first currency extracted from the key to the Position file record </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORWARD.BAL.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.FWD.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Forward balance held as at the end of the previous day. 'AMT' type field Amount is held in 'CURRENCY1'. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Position Type extracted from the key to the Position file record </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREV.FWD.VAL.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       NOINPUT</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Current balance as at the end of the current day. 'AMT' type field Current balance is held in 'CURRENCY1'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPARTMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Dealer Desk Department which is specified in the RE.POSITION.BALANCE key. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the consol key ID which was created from the RE.POSITION.BALANCE record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.LOCAL.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Current balance as at the end of the current day in the local currency. 'AMT' type field Current balance is held in the local currency of the bank. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.POS.IDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the POSITION record IDS that have been used to create the RE.POSITION.BALANCE record for live positions. Multivalued field. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MKT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the currency market extracted from the key to the Position file record </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

