<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>REFERAL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used to establish conditions under which details of an Account or entries over an Account should be referred to the Account Officer. </p>
            <p>An end of day report is produced, containing details of transactions and balances to be referred. </p>
            <p>Fields 3-8 are used exclusively for establishing conditions for referring entries Fields 9-11 for referring Account balances. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the last Transaction Code in the range that is to be referred. </p>
            <p>The first Transaction Code in the range to be referred is specified in the corresponding Field 4. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field 4. (Input mandatory if corresponding TRANSACTION CODE FROM (field 4) is entered, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>Input must be an existing code on the TRANSACTION Table.</p>
            <p>Input is not allowed if TRANSACTION CODE FROM is not entered.</p>
            <p>Input must exceed TRANSACTION CODE FROM.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the referral conditions. Included in the referral report. </p>
            <p>This field is a description of the referral conditions which is used for reporting or enrichments. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the individual Transaction Code(s) that are to be referred. </p>
            <p>Any entry with this Referral condition and Transaction Code when passed to an Account will be referred (if no Movement Amounts are specified).  If Movement Amounts and Transaction Codes are specified then the entry must meet both conditions for it to be referred. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Example:   Field 3.1     1            Field 6       DEBIT            Field 7       100.00            Field 8       200.00 </p>
            <p>Entries: (i)Transaction Code 1, Amount DR 150.00 (will be referred)         (ii)Transaction Code 1, Amount DR 50 (will not be referred). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field (Optional input)</p>
            <p>It must be an existing code on the TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p>Duplicate Transaction Codes are not allowed within the same Referal record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERAL.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the code by which the referral condition details can be identified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 numeric characters (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the first Transaction Code in a range that is to be referred. </p>
            <p>The last Transaction Code in the range to be referred is specified in the corresponding field 5 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
            <p> Multivalue field associated with field 5. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Input must be on existing code on the TRANSACTION table.</p>
            <p>Input must be less than the corresponding TRANSACTION CODE TO (Field 5).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MOVEMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether debit, credit, or all entries are to be referred. </p>
            <p>This field indicates whether debit entries only, credit entries only, reversal entries only, or all entries are to be referred. Any entry with this Referral condition which meets the conditions defined in Fields 6-8 will be referred.  (If no Transaction Codes are specified). </p>
            <p>If Movement amounts and Transaction Codes, are specified then the entry must meet both conditions for it to be referred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-8 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters: D(ebit) or C(redit) or R(eversal) or A(ll) (Input mandatory if no Transaction Codes (Field 3) have been defined otherwise optional).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REMARKS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Free format text which may be used as required. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters Multivalue field (Optional input. No default value.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum amount for entries that are to be referred. </p>
            <p>If the Maximum Movement is not entered, then any amount greater than or equal to the Minimum Movement will be referred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input only allowed when MOVEMENT TYPE (Field 6) has been entered). It must be greater than the MINIMUM MOVEMENT (Field 7).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the minimum amount for entries that are to be referred. </p>
            <p>If the Minimum Movement is not entered, then any amount less than or equal to the Maximum Movement will be referred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point. (Input only allowed when MOVEMENT TYPE (Field 6) has been entered, then it is Mandatory if MAXIMUM MOVEMENT (Field 8) has not been defined, otherwise optional). It must be less than MAXIMUM MOVEMENT (Field 8).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE.COMPARISON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies how the Balance will be checked when deciding whether to refer. </p>
            <p>GE = Balances greater than or equal to the amount in                 Field 11 are to be referred. </p>
            <p>           GT = Balances greater than the amount in Field 11 are                 to be referred. </p>
            <p>           LE = Balances less than or equal to the Field 11 are to                 be referred. </p>
            <p>           LT = Balances less than the amount in Field 11 are to be                 referred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters: GE, GT, LE or LT (Mandatory input.  Only allowed if BALANCE SIGN (Field 9) has been entered.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Balance limit above, below, or equal to which Referral will occur. </p>
            <p>This field specifies the amount which will be checked against when deciding whether to refer the actual balance of the Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory input only allowed if BALANCE SIGN (Field 9) has been entered).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE.SIGN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether debit or credit account balances are to be referred. </p>
            <p>This field indicates whether to check for debit or credit actual account balances.  This check will only take place at the end of the day and only on Accounts which have had movement(s) that day. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-6 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters: D(ebit) or C(redit) (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency of the amounts that are held in Fields 7, 8 and 11. </p>
            <p>This field must be an existing code on the CURRENCY table (Ref: General Tables).  If this is different from the Currency of the Account, then the amount of the entries passed will be converted to the Referral Currency before checking whether they should be referred. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character or 1-3 numeric character Currency Code. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

