<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>REVAL.PARAM.ENT.TODAY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This will be a new installation level live file that will hold a snapshot of information about the revaluation rules to be used by the system as of the start of business. The file will be used in the end of day processing to detect any static field changes that may have occurred during the day such as SPOT.REVAL.BOOKING FWD.REVAL.BOOKING etc., so that appropriate action may be taken in the end of day processing. The layout of the file will be an exact copy of the REVALUATION.PARAMETER file layout. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LOSS.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the category code to which any loss resulting from revaluations were being posted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid category code if input.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 53001-53999 (Excepting for the value 53006 which is currently being used in the system)</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOSS.INT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the category code being used when constructing an internal account number to post the amount resulting from a loss calculated after the revaluation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be an existing category code set up the CATEGORY file</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 10000 - 19999</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRFT.DB.TXN.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the transaction code being used for raising a debit accounting entry on the profit side of the P&amp;L as a result of the revaluation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Will be a valid debit transaction code setup in the TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERPOLATION.MKR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies whether forward exchange rates were being interpolated or not.  Interpolation occurs when a rate can be established from two known rates.  For example, let us say that the one month forward rate for a particular currency is 1.50 and that the three month forward for the same currency is 1.60.  Using interpolation, the two-month forward rate will be calculated at 1.55. </p>
            <p>The value of this marker is important for the revaluation of Forward contracts using the REBATE revaluation method.  Details of the interpolation formula can be found in the Forex Main File documentation.  When '2' has been selected in this field, revaluation of forward contracts using the Rebate revaluation method will not interpolate an exchange rate but instead, pick from the FORWARD.RATES table the rate defined on the nearest date compared to the value date of the Foreign Exchange deal.  When '1' has been selected, the next available rate will instead be selected. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>'Blank' -  Rate will be interpolated '1'    -  Takes the next available rate '2'    -  Takes the closest rate</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.10</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRFT.CR.TXN.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the transaction code being used for raising a credit accounting entry on the profit side of the P&amp;L as a result of the revaluation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Will be a valid credit transction code setup on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPOT.REVAL.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not P/L and EXCHADS entries were being booked when contracts with a REVALUATION TYPE that is NOT 'RB', are revalued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid values are 'Y'ES or 'N'O</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.SYS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the revaluation system id that was being used by the revaluation process when raising revaluation P&amp;L accounting entries. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FASB.REVALUATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the revaluation was using the mid rate or the bid and offer rates. </p>
            <p>YES = Bid and Offer rates </p>
            <p>NO  = Mid rate (Default) </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid values are 'Y'ES or 'N'O</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRFT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the category code to which any profit resulting from revaluations were being posted. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid category code if entered.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range of 53001-53999 (Excepting for 53006 which is being used by the system)</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSTING.STYLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in this field reflectse how the revaluation acounting entries were being posted. There are two possible ways in which this can be performed as shown under : </p>
            <p>'I/O' - In this method the old amount is reversed out and the new amount is posted again. </p>
            <p>'ADJ' - In this method the difference between the old &amp; new amounts is posted as an adjustment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid values are 'I/O' or 'ADJ'</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRFT.INT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the category code being used when constructing an internal account number to post the amount resulting from a profit calculated after the revaluation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid category code set up on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p>Must be in the range 10000 - 19999</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOSS.CR.TXN.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the transaction code being used for raising a credit accounting entry on the loss side of the P&amp;L as a result of the revaluation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Will be a valid credit transaction code set up on the TRANSACTION file</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.DEAL.POST</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>The following values are permitted:       YES      NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the revaluation method was being used for revaluing deals arising out of the application in the APPLIC.ID field. The are only two ways in which revalution is performed, these being : </p>
            <p>'SP' - Spot revaluation that uses the spot rate. </p>
            <p>'RB' - Rebate revaluation that uses the forward rates table. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be either 'SP' or 'RB'</p>
            <p>If APPLIC.ID = FX.RB then must be 'RB'</p>
            <p>If APPLIC.ID # FX.RB then must be 'SP'</p>
            <p>If APPLIC.ID = REST then must be 'SP'</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local reference field </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As defined Locally</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRFT.PROD.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the product category that was used for the internal account number formed from the PRFT.INT.CATEG field </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Will be a valid CATEGORY code</p>
            <p>Will be between the range 20000 - 29999</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed has been set to 'ADJ'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOSS.DB.TXN.CD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the transaction code being used for raising a debit accounting entry on the loss side of the P&amp;L as a result of the revaluation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Will be a valid debit transaction code set up on the TRANSACTION file</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the revaluation was calculated against the local currency or the currency specified. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 Alpha-numeric currency code (type CCY).</p>
            <p>Input not Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.REVAL.BOOKING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether or not P/L and EXCHADS entries were being booked when contracts with a REVALUATION TYPE of 'RB' are revalued. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid values are 'Y'ES or 'N'O</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOSS.PROD.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the product category that was used for the internal account number formed from the LOSS.INT.CATEG field </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Will be a valid CATEGORY code</p>
            <p>Will be between the range 20000 - 29999</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLIC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to identify an application for which the fields associated to it have being set up. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
            <p>Must be a valid application set up for the company indicated in the ID or</p>
            <p>In the case of Forex it can be set to the following values :  FX.SP - Signifying all Forex contracts that have been set up with a revaluation type of 'SP'  FX.RB - Signifying all Forex contracts that have been set up with a revaluation type of 'RB'  FX.SL - Signifying all Forex contracts that have been set up with a revaluation type of 'SL'  FX.IN - Signifying all Forex contracts that have been set up with a revaluation type of 'IN'  FX.IH - Signifying all Forex contracts that have been set up with a revaluation type of 'IH'  FX    - Signifying all forex contract otherwise not defined specifically as above in other words a catch-all set.</p>
            <p>Special value of 'ALL' signifies a catch all for the entire system that will be revalued on an individual contract basis.</p>
            <p>Special value of 'REST' signifying a catch all which will not be revalued individually but rather in a consolidated manner.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.PROFITS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will be used to indicate whether or not profits resulting from revaluation were being booked out or not. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid values 'YES' or 'NO'</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the ID of the record. Each company in the system must have a separate set of revaluation parameters set for it. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL.REVAL.REP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the frequency being used for the production of the 'Detailed Revaluation Report' produced by the Forex End of Day process. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid frequency code</p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

