<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>REVAL.REPORT.SAVED</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This will be a new file that must be written to during the end of day revaluation process. The file may be used by an enquiry later for other purposes. The file must be an exact copy of the existing file REVAL.REPORT that gets cleared out during the and of day processing and gets used for other purposes as a consequence is not available for use later on.</p>
            <p>The IFRS related fields are NO INPUT fields and will be automatically updated only for CURRENCY.2  component of the POS.TRANSACTION record when the FOREX transaction is revalued.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>IFRS.REVALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the deal is revalued under IFRS or not.</p>
            <p>Updated with value 'YES' when transactions are revalued, if the field IFRS.REVALUE in POS.TRANSACTION has value  'YES'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.ADJ.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This amount indicates the difference between the last revalued amount and the new revalued amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.NPV.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in this field indicates the method of discounting used.</p>
            <p>A value S indicates SIMPLE method and C indicates COMPOUND method.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the revaluation type defined on the POS.TRANSACTION record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.DEAL.AMT.TODATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the Un-realised Profit or Loss at Deal Level  in local currency till todate. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This amount indicates the total loss or profit amount on this component of POSITION after the last revaluation process. In other words it is equal to the difference between the original local equivalent figure and the new local equivalent figure. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for Future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.NPV.AMT.TODATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the Net Present Value of the Unrealised Profit or loss in local currency till todate.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.NPV.AMT.TODAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will be the Id field. The field will comprise of several components as described under : </p>
            <p>1-2 Trading Type </p>
            <p>3-4 Currency Market </p>
            <p>5-6 Dealer Desk </p>
            <p>7-9 For Currency's Rank </p>
            <p>10-12 For Currency </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.DEAL.AMT.TODAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the Un-realised Profit or Loss at Deal Level  in local currency for today. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IFRS.NPV.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value in this field is the key used to obtain the discount rate from PERIODIC.INTEREST table, which is used for calculating the NPV of the deal. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVAL.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the last revaluation rate that was used. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for Future use </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the status of the component of the POSITION shown. The field may have the following possible values : </p>
            <p>'MAT' - Indicating Matured </p>
            <p>'REV' - Indicating a reversal </p>
            <p>'NEG' - Only in the case of FOREX deals indicating a negotiated deal </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FOR.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This amount is the original amount in the foreign currency on the contract. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNIQUE.TXN.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will identify a unique currency position component. The field will comprise of many elements as shown below : </p>
            <p>1 - A unique letter identifying a revaluation type bucket (A-F) </p>
            <p>2-9 Value Date </p>
            <p>10 onwards - The transaction id on the POSITION records's field TXN.REF.ID </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AFT.LCY.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This amount is the local equivalent amount after the last revaluation. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEF.LCY.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This amount is the local equivalent before the last revaluation took place </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.SINCE.SPOT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the number of days that have passed since spot period for the underlying contracts position component. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DDESK.REVLETTER.TXNID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used for sorting the deals for the IFRS reports. </p>
            <p>The field will comprise of many elements as shown below :</p>
            <p>1-2 Character - Dealer Desk</p>
            <p>3  A unique letter identifying revaluation type</p>
            <p>4 Onwards - The Transaction ID as specified in field TXN.REF.ID of POSITION table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

