<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>STANDING.ORDER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Encompassed within the Funds Transfer Module is a fully operational Standing Order Application.  This Application provides the following facilities: </p>
            <p>   1.        Funds Management Initiated By Balance Levels </p>
            <p>              The User can determine, on any account, Funds            Management conditions by specifying balance levels which            can operate in two ways:  As an indicator identifying a            balance level starting from which funds must be            transferred either into, or out of, the Account </p>
            <p>   2.        Fixed and Preset Payments </p>
            <p>              This will allow the User to load Standing Orders as Fixed            payments with known amount and frequency (e.g. the            monthly payment of the rent) or as preset payments            where the amount is unknown (e.g. payment of gas bill). </p>
            <p>   3.        Diary Instructions </p>
            <p>              Any account Diary instructions can be defined with their            related frequency.  An on-line retrieval facility            (Sto.Diary) will then allow the User to check at any time            the outstanding Diary instructions. </p>
            <p>   4.        Direct Debits </p>
            <p>              This facility will allow the User to load the Direct Debit            mandates which the bank has received from the Customer            and which authorises the bank to accept Direct Debits            received on the Account.  When the Direct Debits are            actually received by the bank, the User will then access            this file to check if the appropriate mandate has been            received from the Customer. </p>
            <p>   5.        Maturing Deposits </p>
            <p>              This facility will allow the User to pay away the balance            on an account to the beneficiary details set up on the            standing order on a particular date specified on the record.            The facility can be used to mature a fixed term deposit account. </p>
            <p>   6.        Periodic Payment of Interest </p>
            <p>              This facility will allow the User to pay away any interest            capitalised on an account periodically to the beneficiary            details specified on the record. </p>
            <p />
            <p>              If required, up to 999 different Standing Order            instructions can be created on any account. </p>
            <p>              During the End Of Day processing, the Application will            access the internal file (Standing.Order.Fqu) to process            all Standing Orders due for each day since the last run            date up to and including todays date.  Two separate end            of day processes are run, STO.BALANCES is run at end            of day to process Balance Maintenance Standing Orders,            STO.PAYMENTS is run at start of day to process all            other Standing Orders.  The following steps will then be            taken by the Application: </p>
            <p>   (i)        A Funds Transfer transaction will be generated for all            Standing Orders due since the last run date and these            transactions will be automatically Authorised provided no            error conditions or overrides exist. </p>
            <p>   (ii)       Where error conditions or overrides exist (e.g. there are            insufficient funds on the Standing Order account to            execute the instruction), the Funds Transfer Transaction            will be put on a Held status (code IHLD) and this            transaction will be listed on the Exception Display of the            Funds Transfer Application.  The next day, the User can            then access these transactions, make the necessary            corrections and/or determine the action to be taken on            overrides.  These transactions will then follow the normal            validation and authorisation process of the Funds            Transfer Application. </p>
            <p>   (iii)      When the Application is processing BI Balance            Maintenance Standing Orders and funds are not available            to pay into the Account, an unauthorised Funds Transfer            transaction will be generated with a status of IHLD.  The            override field will specify the Amount Required, the            Amount available and, if applicable, the Minimum balance            to be kept in the Account from which the funds have to be            taken.  With the help of this information, the User will            then decide on what action to take. </p>
            <p>   (iv)       Any transaction generated by the Standing Order            Application can be identified from the content of the            internal field Inward Payment Type which will contain the            value of STO and the Standing Order sequential number. </p>
            <p>   Relationship Between Files Within The Application The flow chart which follows shows the relationships between the various files existing in the Standing Order Application.  For details of Funds Transfer files (prefixed with FT) the User should refer to the Main Funds Transfer Application flow chart. </p>
            <p>   All of the files detailed within the chart have the standard 3 versions:            .'Live' file            .'Unauthorised' file            .'History' file. </p>
            <p>   STANDING ORDER FLOW DIAGRAM </p>
            <p>   STANDING ORDER  |             STO.BULK.CODE                 |                 |             STO.TYPE                 |                 |             FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION                 |                 |             FT.APPLICATION.DEFAULT                 |                 |             AGENCY                 |                 |             STO.DIARY </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FT.DEBIT.VAL.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a no input field, but is automatically populated by adding the number of working days entered in the DAYS.DELIVERY field, to todays date.  It is then used as the value date on the FUNDS.TRANSFER.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   You must be using a Value Dated Accounting system.</p>
            <p>   The VALUE.DATE.BAL field must be set to Y.</p>
            <p>   There must be a value in DAYS.DELIVERY. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECEIVER.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Customer code on the Agency file of the bank that is to receive the payment unless this is a BACS payment. </p>
            <p>   When the Application is generating a payment for the Pay Method codes OT and OD, the Receiver correspondent bank will be generated from the Agency file.  For payments in local currency with Pay Method codes OT and OD, if there is local currency Vostro account specified in the Agency record, this will be used for the Credit Account.  If proper autorouting instructions have not been defined on the Agency file, the Funds Transfer record generated will be placed on hold. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1 to 6 numeric characters Agency code or    3 to 10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') character Agency Mnemonic. (Optional input for the Pay Method codes OT, OD and OB.  Otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p>   The code input in this field must exist on the Agency file.</p>
            <p>   It must not be the same as the Customer of the appropriate Nostro Account for the currency and payment method of the transfer (see NOSTRO.ACCOUNT table).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PD.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define the rate used to pass to the PD module.</p>
            <p>   This is only relevant to RC type standing orders.</p>
            <p>   Currently the rate entered here will not be used by the PD system, as all RC type standing orders will generate contingent PD's with no penalty interest calculated when payments become overdue.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input</p>
            <p>   Standard rate field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.RUN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date on which the standing order was last run. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   For CVD type STO, Adjusted Date as per DAYS.PRIOR will be updated in this field.  </p>
			<p>   No Input Allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The asset ID held on the ASSET.REGISTER file which states which asset is being leased out. Once the standing order has been authorised then the Asset Register record is written away with a status of 'IN-USE</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Only entered if the bank is the lessor and then it must         be a valid ID on ASSET.REGISTER</p>
            <p>   Must have a status of OPEN</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   Identifies how commission is to be applied to the standing order.</p>
            <p>   Commission can be waived or altered using the following commission related   fields and same will be used  during the standing order end of day   process.</p>
            <p>   Debit Plus Charges       -  for debit plus   commission </p>
            <p>   Credit Less Charges     -  for credit less   commission </p>
            <p>   Waive                             - for waive commission</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Must       be either Debit Plus Charges or Credit Less Charges or Waive or Blank.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   If       the standing order pay method is set to OT and the system is set to       produce message type MT103, if field BEN.OUR.CHARGES is set to OUR       then this field must be set to debit plus commission, if BEN.OUR.CHARGES       is set to BEN then this field must be set to credit less commission.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.TO.BK.INFO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Bank to bank information. </p>
            <p>   This field will be transferred to the FT next generated transaction. </p>
            <p>   When SUPPRESS.FT is set to Y, this field will be used to map the details of the instruction code (Tag 23E) in the messages sent to TPS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 type SW (SWIFT allowed) characters.  Up to 6 subvalues are allowed, since it is the SWIFT rule.</p>
            <p>   When SUPPRESS.FT is set to Y, this field will validate according to the rules for tag 23E.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.VALUE.GAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the debit value date calculation rules. You can combine 1 or 2 date operations, always based on the frequency date, each operation being "+" or "-", followed by a number of days, and followed by "C" or "W", meaning calendar or working days. "+" and "C" are taken by default. If nothing is entered here, default calculation will be done thru the Funds Transfer calculation rules, depending on the payment method. Examples : "+01C-01W" which means "Last working day before the processing date" "-02C" means processing date less 2 calendar days, and so on ... </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 8 type ANY (alphanumeric) characters. "+" and "C" are optional, and zeros will be added if needed. Example : "1-1W" will be taken as "+01C-01W". Optional input, blank means default FT calculation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify Charge Frequency for this Standing Order and based on this frequency, charges will be collected during Funds.Transfer creation and this is valid till the end date if any specified in the next field.</p>
            <p>   Frequency can be specified as date (for one time execution) or date with valid frequency. If Charge frequency is specified, then it should be same as STO's Current.Frequency.</p>
            <p>   Ie. STO's Current. Frequency is specified as BSNSS, then Chg.Frequency should be specified as BSNSS only.</p>
            <p>   But the start date of Charge Frequency can be different from Current Frequency.</p>
            <p>   Ie. STO's Current.Frequency is given as 20030109BSNSS &amp; Chg.Frequency can be given as 20030110BSNSS to indicate charges to be collected from 10th Jan 2003.</p>
            <p>   To Collect charge one time, in Charge frequency specify the date on which it should be collected. </p>
            <p>   Ie. For above STO, if Charge to be collected on 12th Jan 2003 , then specify 20030112 in Chg.frequency field.</p>
            <p>   Over rides are generated-When Charge frequency &amp; end date specified without charge type, When Charge frequency start date not same as Current.frequency date, Charge frequency date is Non-working day</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Associated multivalue field-Optional Input</p>
            <p>   Chg.Frequency if entered should be same as STO's current frequency</p>
            <p>   This field is sub-divided into two elements: 1. Date 1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters. 2. Frequency 1-5 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUPP.BAL.STO.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies a Supplementary Balance to be Transferred TO when a BI Standing Order transaction is generated by the System. </p>
            <p>   Example: </p>
            <p>   Let us suppose that a Customer requests to cover any overdrawn balance in his current account by a transfer from his savings account. If the current account balance is overdrawn by  150.00 and: </p>
            <p>   1.         Field 11 is left blank </p>
            <p>              In this case, an amount corresponding to exactly the            overdraft will be transferred into the current account,            i.e.  150.00.  This will mean that the next debit on this            current account will overdraw it again and trigger a new            BI transaction. </p>
            <p>   2.         Field 11 has an Amount input </p>
            <p>              In this case, not only the overdraft amount will be            transferred but also the amount specified in this field.            If  200.00 has been input in this field, the total amount            transferred will be equal to  350.00 i.e.  150.00            (overdraft amount) +  200.00.  The new balance of the            current account will be CR  200.00 and is not bound to            become overdrawn with the next debit activity. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input.  Only allowed for Standing Order type BI. Default: None.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the market in which standing order is to be executed. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1 numeric currency market code. No input for single market operations (default 1), Mandatory input for Multi Market. a)   If a currency market corresponding to FTCREDIT is set up on MU.MOVEMENT.DTLS and MU.TXN.GRP.CCY.MKT for FT, and the currency market corresponding to FTDEBIT is null, then the account to be credited, if it is a customer account must correspond to the FTCREDIT currency market. The debit account (if a customer acct) must correspond to currency market of FTCREDIT. b)   If FTDEBIT is set up and not FTCREDIT, then as (a) except that accounts must correspond to FTDEBIT. c)   If both FTCREDIT and FTDEBIT are set up the credit account must correspond to FTCREDIT and the debit account to FTDEBIT currency markets. d)   If neither FTCREDIT or FTDEBIT are set up then validation is as per default FT movement. e)   The currency market input must be the same as the currency market of the account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUT.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines any Future Frequency of the Standing Order for the amount specified in the previous associated field (Future amount - balance) or for Diary Instructions. </p>
            <p>   The User must be careful when entering the Future Frequency and must ALWAYS specify the Start Date before inputting the required frequency.  If the start date of each new frequency is not entered, the System will calculate the first date according to the frequency input and the Processing date will not generate the date requested by the Customer. </p>
            <p>   This field together with the previous associated field (Future Amount) and the next associated field (Future End Date) will allow the User to load in advance any number of future Standing Order instructions provided they are loaded in chronological date order. </p>
            <p>   The date input or generated will correspond to the first execution of the Standing Order amount specified in the associated field. </p>
            <p>   The first date calculated by the System will then be the date resulting from the frequency applied to the Processing Date.  If a date was input first, the frequency will be applied on this date and not on the Processing date. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   This field is sub-divided into two elements: 1. Date    1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters. 2. Frequency    1-5 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character    alpha) characters.  (Optional input for Standing Order type BI, BO, FI, and  DIARY. Not allowed for types PP, BP, PPI and DD.)</p>
            <p>   The start date must be greater than the date specified in the Current End Date field for the First Future instruction and must be greater than the date specified in the previous Future End Date field.</p>
            <p>   Input mandatory when the associated Future amount - balance field has been input except when it concerns a Diary Standing Order type.</p>
            <p>   'DAILY' frequency is not allowed for Standing Order types BI and BO, ('BSNSS', every working day is allowed.)</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed when the associated Future Amount - balance field has been left blank except when it concerns a Diary Standing Order type.</p>
            <p>   An override will be required if the date input is a non-working day and the frequency is 'BSNSS'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.REFERENCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the reference which is given to the beneficiary of the standing order. </p>
            <p>   The contents of this field will be placed in the CREDIT.THEIR.REF field in the Funds Transfer. </p>
            <p>   For local clearing validation rules see the section 'Local Clearing Rules'. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 27 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Input may only be 27 characters for BC pay method, for all other types the maximum length is 16 characters. (Optional Input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is updated at end of day when an accrual payment takes place. It contains the number of days within the start and end period of previous accrual cycles.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   A no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FT.LOC.REF.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the LOCAL.REFERENCE element to be used defined for Funds Transfers on the LOCAL.REF.TABLE file by it's position. </p>
            <p>   The contents of this field identify the LOCAL.REFERENCE element to be used. It must be one that is defined on LOCAL.REF.TABLE for the Funds Transfer application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1 - 3 numeric characters. Associated multivalue field. (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUT.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a Future End date of the Standing Order for the Amount and Frequency specified in the previous associated fields Future Amount and Future Frequency. </p>
            <p>   This field together with the previous associated fields (Future Amount and Future Frequency) will allow the User to load in advance any number of future Standing Order instructions provided they are loaded in chronological date order. </p>
            <p>   Example: </p>
            <p>   The following example will illustrate the use and the relation existing between the first nine fields. </p>
            <p>   Let us suppose that you want to pay the Rates on your house on a monthly basis and that the amount of the Rates which is equal to GBP 1,000.50 needs to be paid in 10 payments.  The following Standing Order instructions will then be loaded: </p>
            <p>   Field No.  Field description  Field Input </p>
            <p>   1          Type               FI 2          Pay Method         BC (for example) 3          Currency           GBP 4          Current Amt-Bal    100.50 5          Current Frequency  02 MAY 85 M0102 6          Current End Date   02 MAY 85 7.1        Future Amt-Bal     100.00 8.1        Future Frequency   02 JUN 85 M0102 9.1        Future End Date    02 FEB 86 </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 9 type D Date characters (date format in range 1950-2049).  (Optional input. Not allowed for types PP, PPI and DD.)</p>
            <p>   Date input must be equal or greater than the date specified in the associated field Future Frequency.</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed if a Future frequency has not been defined.</p>
            <p>   Input mandatory when further future instructions exist.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the ID of the BENEFICIARY table is input, the details defined in the BENEFICIARY table get defaulted in the FT Transaction.Accepts ID of the BENEFICIARY table. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BULK.CODE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enables the following four fields to be updated automatically, i.e.: .  Beneficiary .  Beneficiary Account Number .  Account With Bank .  Bank Sort Code </p>
            <p>   This field defines a code that has already been created on the STO.BULK.CODE table to enable the most frequently used Standing Orders to be loaded in a table and avoids repetitive input of these four fields in the Standing Order instructions. </p>
            <p>   If, for example, many customers have given the bank Standing Order instructions in favour of the same beneficiary, eg annual subscription to the AA, it will be in the interest of the User to define in the STO.BULK.CODE table these common beneficiaries and thus avoid the repetition and risk of error in defining each time the four above mentioned fields in each Standing Order. </p>
            <p>   The input of the Bulk Code Number will then be sufficient to automatically generate the values of the next four fields. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 10 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>   The Bulk Code input must have been previously created on the STO.BULK.CODE table.</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed for the Standing Order type DIARY, BI, BO, BP and DD or when the Pay Method field has received a value of AC.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETRY.ORIG.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used only by records that have been generated by the auto-retry process when a Standing Order fails due to lack of funds. It contains the ID number of the original standing order was due to be processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.BALANCE.B.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies, for the BI type, the Minimum Balance to be maintained on the Account from where the funds will be taken to feed the Standing Order account. </p>
            <p>   When insufficient funds are available on the beneficiary account to execute the payment, an unauthorised Funds Transfer transaction will be generated with a status of IHLD and the override Field will specify: </p>
            <p>              -    Amount required,            -    Amount available            -    Minimum balance to be kept in the beneficiary                 account (only applicable for Balance Maintenance                 Standing Order types). </p>
            <p>   The User will then need to determine the action to be taken. </p>
            <p>   As a general rule, the Application will never overdraw on an Account to feed another Account.With this field, the User can limit the realisation of the Standing Order instruction by stipulating a Minimum Amount to be kept in the Account from where the funds are taken. </p>
            <p>   Example: </p>
            <p>   If an amount of 500.00 has been specified in this field, no activity will be generated by the BI Standing Order types when the balance of the Account specified in the file Beneficiary account number is below 500.00. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point.  (Optional input for the types BI not allowed for types  BP, PPI, BO, FI, PP, DIARY and DD.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TREASURY.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the Treasury rate to be applied for this Standing.Order.</p>
            <p>   The exchange rate given here will be used as a Treasury rate while processing the Standing order.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Allowed only when the Debit &amp; Credit account currency not the same</p>
            <p>   When Value is entered in this field, Base currency is mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEDUCT.TAX.MARKER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies a tax code that specifies the percentage of tax that is to be deducted before effecting the payment. </p>
            <p>   The calculated tax amount will be deducted from the Amount specified and all accounting entries are for the reduced amount. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1 Numeric character.  (Optional input. Only allowed for the Standing Order  types FI, PPI and PP.  For all other ones it not allowed.)</p>
            <p>   The code input must have been previously defined in the FT.APPL.DEFAULT table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify commission Frequency for this Standing Order and based on this frequency, commission will be collected during Funds.Transfer creation and this is valid till the end date if any specified in the next field.</p>
            <p>   Frequency can be specified as date (for one time execution) or date with valid frequency. If Commission frequency is specified, then it should be same as STO's Current.Frequency.</p>
            <p>   Ie. STO's Current.Frequency is specified as BSNSS, then Comm.Frequency should be specified as BSNSS only.</p>
            <p>   But the start date of Commission Frequency can be different from Current.Frequency.</p>
            <p>   Ie. STO's Current.Freuqnecy is given as 20030109BSNSS &amp; Comm.Frequency can be given as 20030110BSNSS to indicate charges to be collected from 10th Jan 2003.</p>
            <p>   To Collect commission one time, in Commission frequency specify the date on which it should be collected. </p>
            <p>   Ie. For above STO, if Commission to be collected on 12th Jan 2003 , then specify 20030112 in Comm.frequency field.</p>
            <p>   Over rides are generated-When Commission frequency &amp; end date specified without commission type, When Commission frequency start date not same as Current.frequency date, Commission frequency date is Non-working day.</p>
            <p>   When Commission type or Charge type is specified with or without charge frequency/End date, after each STO execution irrespective of whether the Funds transfer contract created or not (due to override / Exception ), Last.Chg.Date will be updated with that run date.</p>
            <p>   Incase of STO's created during retry, Commission /Charge details will be copied except the Commission/Charge frequency &amp; Commission/Charge end date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Associated multivalue field-Optional Input</p>
            <p>   Comm.Frequency if entered should be same as STO's current frequency</p>
            <p>   This field is sub-divided into two elements: 1. Date 1-9 type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters. 2. Frequency 1-5 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.VALUE.GAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the credit value date calculation rules. You can combine 1 or 2 date operations, always based on the frequency date, each operation being "+" or "-", followed by a number of days, and followed by "C" or "W", meaning calendar or working days. "+" and "C" are taken by default. If nothing is entered here, default calculation will be done thru the Funds Transfer calculation rules, depending on the payment method. Examples : "+01C-01W" which means "Last working day before the processing date" "-02C" means processing date less 2 calendar days, and so on ... </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 8 type ANY (alphanumeric) characters. "+" and "C" are optional, and zeros will be added if needed. Example : "1-1W" will be taken as "+01C-01W". Optional input, blank means default FT calculation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.FOR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   This field is used to specify whether the corresponding charge amount entered is due to the sending bank or the receiving bank. If the standing order pay method is OT and the system has been set to produce SWIFT message MT103 - Single Customer Credit Transfer</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Sender - the corresponding charge amount entered is due to the sending bank.</p>
            <p>   Receiver &amp;#8211; the corresponding charge amount entered is due to the receiving bank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Permitted values are Sender      or Receiver, for pay method of OT with a message type of MT103 the default      is Sender.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   If the standing order pay      method is set to OT and the system is set to produce message type MT103      there must at least one senders charge or commission present.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETRY.ORIG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used only by records that have been generated by the auto-retry process when a Standing Order fails due to lack of funds. It contains the date the original standing order was due to be processed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Date</p>
            <p>   No Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGES.ACCT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the Account Number where the commissions and charges are to be debited, when Commission and charges are to be collected from a separate account instead of Debit Account. Account entered here mapped to Charges.Acct.No in Funds Transfer Application.</p>
            <p>   See Charges.Acct.No in Funds Transfer Application for more details.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Standard Numeric Account Number or 3-10 character Account Mnemonic (uppercase alpha, numeric or '.') - Type MNE or 6-12 character Internal Account number (uppercase alpha/numeric, first character alpha) - Type SS. (Optional input) </p>
            <p>   Input will not be allowed when the Commission code and the Charge code both indicate the value of W (waive) or C (Credit less     charges)</p>
            <p>   Nostro account Not allowed </p>
            <p>   Internal account if inputted should match with the Charge.Claim.Account as     given in FT.APPL.DEFAULT application.   </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Dealer desk which has to be used by this Standing.Order while creating FT can be specified here. </p>
            <p>   Detail given here is mapped to DEALER.DESK field in Funds.Transfer. If nothing is entered here, then FT will be using the default Dealer desk "00".</p>
            <p>   The dealer desk code is held on the position record so that the exchange position can be displayed at dealer desk level.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional Input.   </p>
            <p>   2 alphanumeric character dealer code in the range A-Z, a-z, plus 0-9. </p>
            <p>   Should be a Valid record in DEALER.DESK table. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERMED.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   Identifies the Intermediary Bank through which the associated funds must pass prior to receipt by the Beneficiary Bank or Account With Bank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   3-10 character Agency       Mnemonic (Uppercase alphanumeric or '.') or 1-6 Numeric character Agency       code or </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Up to maximum 4 lines of 35 characters (uppercase alpha or Numeric characters) </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input for       Transaction Types OD, OT otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   The Intermediary Bank cannot       be the same as the : Account With Bank , Receiver Bank , Receiver       Correspondent Bank , Beneficiary Bank.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   For outward payments by       telex. If this field is input then ACCOUNT WITH BANK must be input,       unless both DEBIT and CREDIT accounts are NOSTRO accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   If both ACCOUNT WITH BANK       and RECEIVER CORRESPONDENT BANK are null and intermediary bank has been       entered, then either ACCOUNT WITH BANK or RECEVER BANK must be input,       unless both CREDIT and DEBIT accounts are NOSTRO accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory when Cover.Method       is Third-Inst.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the market in which the account being debited &amp; credited  is to be used. Based on the Currency market appropriate exchange rates are picked up, when the debit and credit account currency is different. The currency market entered here gets defaulted in FT contact generated.</p>
            <p>   If value entered here then conversion type (next field) is mandatory.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   The currency market must exist on the currency table for local currency.</p>
            <p>   Numeric - valid currency market code.</p>
            <p>   No input for single market operations (default 1)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.DELIVERY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of working days to be added onto the current frequency date to give you the value date for the Funds Transfer record that will be created by this standing order. This FT value date is then used to match against value dated balances on the account record in order to use the appropriate balance for standing order calculations. If left blank then the FT debit value date is also left blank and the ONLINE.CLEARED.BAL will be used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Only valid if VALUE.DATED.BAL = 'Y'</p>
            <p>   Range = 1 - 3</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Beneficiary name and address of the Standing Order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. A maximum of 4 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed. (Mandatory input or not allowed as defined in <p>Validation Rules:</p>)</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed when the Standing Order type is equal to DIARY or BI.</p>
            <p>   Input mandatory for the Standing Order types DD and for all Pay Methods except for AC where it is not allowed.</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed when a Bulk code has been input in the previous field. For local clearing payment method (BC), see the section 'Local clearing rules' for the relevant clearing system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DIARY.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows any free form narrative. This field is only applicable to the DIARY type Standing Orders. </p>
            <p>   The details input in this field will be stored in an internal file Sto.Diary together with the identification of the User who can request, during end of day STO process, to see the contents of this internal file and take any appropriate action. More details on this Sto.Diary file can be found in the Internal files Section.</p>
            <p>    Effective from G14.1, a routine can be added to this field, so that when the Standing Order is authorised, an AC.EXPECTED.RECS record is generated online with the details mentioned in Standing Order. However this functionality is available only when the USER.ROUTINE in STO.TYPE application set to "YES" for  DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   Sample routine "STO.GEN.EXP.RECS" has been released with accepts the following arguments:</p>
            <p />
            <p>   INCOMING:</p>
            <p>   MODE - will be either CREATE or UPDATE</p>
            <p>   AC.EXP.ID - AC.EXPECTED.RECS ID, </p>
            <p>   AC.EXP.REC - AC.EXPECTED.RECS Record</p>
            <p>   OUTGOING:</p>
            <p>   AC.EXP.ID</p>
            <p>   ERR - Error Message (If Any)</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Mandatory     input for the DIARY type, not allowed for the other types).</p>
            <p>   User defined routine can be given by prefixing @ and which will be used for generation     of AC.EXPECTED.RECS record on authorisation of Standing.Order-provided the     USER.ROUTINE is set to "Y" in STO.TYPE for DIARY record.</p>
            <p>   If a routine is attached to this field, then Multivalue cannot be     inputted.</p>
            <p>   Routine attached should be a valid record in PGM.FILE application</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The profit and loss category for the accrual entries. The accounting rules are as follows :</p>
            <p>   1. The bank is the Lessee</p>
            <p>   Daily Accrual Entries</p>
            <p>   DR the suspense account</p>
            <p>   CR the P+L category</p>
            <p>   Repayment Entries</p>
            <p>   DR the customer account</p>
            <p>   CR the suspense account</p>
            <p>   2. The bank is the Leassor</p>
            <p>   Daily Accrual Entries</p>
            <p>   DR the P+L category</p>
            <p>   CR the suspense account</p>
            <p>   Repayment Entries</p>
            <p>   DR the suspense account</p>
            <p>   CR the customer account</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Must be a valid category in the range 50000 - 69999</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   Identifies how charges are to be applied to the standing order.</p>
            <p>   Commission can be waived or altered using the following commission related   fields during the standing order end of day process.</p>
            <p>   Debit Plus charges          -  for debit plus charges</p>
            <p>   Credit Less charges       -  for credit less charges </p>
            <p>   Waive                              - for waive charges</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Must       be either Debit Plus charges , Credit Less charges, Waive or blank</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   If       the standing order pay method is set to OT and the system is set to       produce message type MT103, if field BEN.OUR.CHARGES is set to OUR       then this field must be set to debit plus charges, if BEN.OUR.CHARGES is       set to BEN then this field must be set to credit less charges.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTERMED.BANK.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account Number of the Intermediary Bank can be specified here and mapped to same field in Funds.Transfer.</p>
            <p>   The Account Number inputted here along with the Intermediary Bank details as given in INTERMED.BANK will be used in  tag 56 of Swift message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input   </p>
            <p>   Up to 34 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type S.   </p>
            <p>   Allowed only when INTERMED.BANK is entered.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BK.TO.BK.OUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The details entered here is mapped to field Bktobk.Out of Funds Transfer.</p>
            <p>   No validation is done during STO for the valid swift code words for the message type since it depends on the message types which are going to get generated during Funds Transfer Processing.</p>
            <p>   Mention the appropriate BktoBk Information for the Send.To.Party and same will be used in all swift messages in Tag 72 which are sent to that Party.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Allowed only when SEND.TO.PARTY is entered and BktoBk Info field is null.   </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - Type S. Multivalue     field. A maximum of 6 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed.   </p>
            <p>   If this field is used, the first multivalue must contain a code word     followed by further information.   </p>
            <p>   All code words must be present on the SWIFT.CODE.WORDS file for the     appropriate application. Code word     must be used between slashes.   </p>
            <p>   Further code words and information can be entered in subsequent multivalue, but additional information continued on a new line must be     preceded by double slashes '//'.   </p>
            <p>   Duplicate code words Not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SIGNATORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the customers who are signing this particular transaction .In case of bank user this field is entered manually whereas for external users this field is automatically updated with external user key </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>
                    <p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  1. Accepts only valid customers.</p>
            <p>  2. Duplicate customer not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the customer whose account is being debited in relation to the Standing Order. Normally this is the customer whose account is specified in Field 0 STANDING.ORDER, the ID of the Standing Order. For  "Credit" Type Standing Orders (with the field REV.DR.CR.ACCT='Y'), this is the customer whose account is specified in Field CPTY.ACCT.NO.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   (Internal field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the commission types applicable to the standing order. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 11 character type A (alphanumeric) commission type code. Associated multivalue field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>   Must exist on the FT COMMISSION.TYPE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERFORM.ACCRUAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether or not accruals are to take place </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Valid options are 'YES' or 'NO' </p>
            <p>   Entry is only allowed for 'OL' type standing orders and         is mandatory when this is the case.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURR.FREQ.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the date component of field CURRENT.FREQUENCY. Used to select standing order for COB process </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   For CVD type STO, Adjusted Date as per DAYS.PRIOR will be updated in this field  </p>            
            <p>   NOINPUT filed (Internal field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.OUR.CHARGES</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value entered here is used to signify who will be responsible for charges and details entered here will be mapped to BEN.OUR.CHARGES field in FT</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional field</p>
            <p>   Input allowed only for OT Pay.Type.</p>
            <p>   Valid values : "BEN" or "OUR" or "SHA".</p>
            <p>   If the standing order pay method is set to OT and the system is set to     produce message type MT103, if COMMISSION.FOR or CHARGE.FOR are set to debit     plus commission this field must be set to OUR, if COMMISSION.FOR or     CHARGE.FOR are set to credit less commission then this field must be set to     BEN.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>The end date of the current accrual period. If left blank it will default from the start period date and the standing order current frequency. For a date cycle example see Start Period help text</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Input only with 'OL' type standing.order and         PERFORM.ACCRUAL = 'YES'</p>
            <p>   Either the start period or end period must be entered.</p>
            <p>   Mandatory if the payment is in advance.</p>
            <p>   Either the start or end period must equal the standing         order current frequency date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.SPREAD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Customer's Exchange Spread to be applied while processing this Standing Order.</p>
            <p>   The Customer Spread defined in this field will be applied to the Treasury (buy/sell) Rate to generate the final Rate of the transaction, i.e. the exchange rate which is applicable to the Customer. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.SORT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Bank Sorting Code of the bank and branch to whom the payment is to be sent.  This field is only applicable to the Local clearing pay method (BC Pay Method), and any outgoing pay method. </p>
            <p>   The code entered must exist on the BC.SORT.CODE file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   6 numeric characters.</p>
            <p>   Mandatory input for pay method BC.</p>
            <p>   Optional input for outgoing pay methods.</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed for internal transfer pay method.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.THEIR.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Debit side reference comments, when meaningful. </p>
            <p>   This field will be transferred to the DEBIT.THEIR.REF field of the next generated FT transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 16 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  In BC payments, specific checking will be achieved in the same manner as in FUNDS.TRANSFER application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of Standing Order. </p>
            <p>   The User will first need to define the various types of Standing Orders in the Standing Order Type table which will be used to provide the enrichment of the Standing Order type being defined. When creating the Standing Order Type table, care must be taken to define exactly the 8 different types in the same format as described above. These types have been hardcoded in the Standing Order program and any other code will be refused by the Application. </p>
            <p>   The following types will be accepted: </p>
            <p>   Balance Maintenance Standing Order Types </p>
            <p>   BI The Account is to be maintained at a minimum balance and will make Payments In when the balance of this account is below the specified balance. The abbreviation BI stands for Balance maintenance In and the sequential number will be between 900 and 999. </p>
            <p>   BO The account is to be maintained at a maximum balance and will make Payments Out when the balance of this account is in excess of the specified balance. The abbreviation BO stands for Balance maintenance Out the sequential number will be between 900 and 999. </p>
            <p>   BP The balance on a fixed length savings account is to be paid away on maturity date. </p>
            <p>   Regular Payments Standing Order Types </p>
            <p>   FI The Customer has given instruction to the bank to pay on a regular basis a Fixed amount and debit one of his accounts. </p>
            <p>   PP The Customer has authorised the bank to pay bills from third parties upon presentation of these bills. The amount will vary and there is no definitive frequency. Therefore, whenever an amount is input, the payment will be made that day and the payments program will delete the amount from the Standing Order record. </p>
            <p>   PPI The interest capitalising on a savings account is to be paid away on a periodic basis. </p>
            <p>   RC Set up to indicate a payment due on a revolving credit account. Payments are made on a regular basis and the amount due can be determined using a locally developed routine. The purpose of the RC standing order is to record the amount due using the Past Due module (PD). No actual accounting entries will be produced by RC type standing orders. The RC type standing order is only applicable to systems with the PD module installed and with revolving credit accounts set up. The key should be in the 900 to 999 range.</p>
            <p>   3. Diary Standing Order Type </p>
            <p>   DIARY Used to define any type of Diary instructions on a specific account. When this Standing Order type is used, input will then become mandatory in the Field Diary Details of the Standing Order record. </p>
            <p>   This type of Standing Order instruction will be created by the User for any type of Memo instructions which are to be recorded in the System and will then provide an on-line reminder of the action to be taken when the User displays the contents of the file STO.DIARY. Specific instructions received in advance are another example of details which could be loaded as a Diary Standing Order type. </p>
            <p>   Each time that the User is creating a DIARY Standing Order item, the System will automatically update an internal file STO.DIARY which will allow Users to review, whenever desired, their own list of Diary instructions or the complete list of Diary instructions outstanding in the Application. Any diary item will remain in that list until a positive action has been taken by the User to eliminate the entry from the file. This will be done by the Standard Reverse function (code R) which, for this particular file, will not need to go through the Authorisation process. </p>
            <p>   Direct Debit Standing Order Type </p>
            <p>   DD The bank has a direct debit mandate from the Customer which authorises the bank to accept direct debits received on the Account. This type of Standing Order will be completely passive in the sense that its sole purpose is to provide the User with an on-line retrieval facility of Direct Debit mandates held by the bank. When direct debits are received by the bank, the User can then verify on-line if proper authority has been received from the Customer. </p>
            <p>   Operating Lease Standing Order Type</p>
            <p>   OL type Standing Orders cater for Operating Leasing contracts and the accrual of the Standing Order amount.</p>
            <p>   Examples: </p>
            <p>   The following are typical examples of the above Standing Order types. </p>
            <p>   1. Type BI -The customer has requested the bank to cover automatically any overdraft in his current account by debiting, for example, his savings account. In this case, the specified balance will be 0 and when the balance will be below 0 an automatic transfer will then be generated from the savings account to feed the current account. </p>
            <p>   2. Type BO - The customer has requested the bank to transfer automatically from his current account any amount in excess of a specified balance by crediting for example, his savings account. In the case the specified balance would be GBP 1,000.00 and when the balance is in excess of this amount, an automatic transfer will then be generated by the Application by which the excess of GBP 1,000.00 will be transferred out of the current account to the savings account specified by the Customer. </p>
            <p>   3. Type FI -The customer has requested the bank to pay every month, for example, the rent for his house. In this example, the amount will be specified by the Customer and in that sense the amount of the Standing Order is Fixed. To project cash flows, forward entries raised for the Internal/Customer accounts given in the Standing Order with STO.TYPE as "FI". </p>
            <p>   Under this Type, it is possible to define Credit</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   4. Type PP - The customer has requested the bank to pay, whenever received, the bills received from the Telephone company or the Electricity board, the Gas board etc. In this case, the amount will not be specified by the Customer but only the name of the companies for which bills may be accepted and paid automatically on their receipt by the bank. For this type of Standing Order (which is also called domiciliation on the Continent), the Customer will also have informed the relevant companies to send their bills directly to his bank. </p>
            <p>   5. Type DD -The customer has authorised the bank to accept direct debits remitted by the Building Company to pay the monthly instalments of the Mortgage loan that the Customer has contracted with the Building company. The amount is not always specified for Direct Debits Standing Order and, if entered, will only be considered as an information field. </p>
            <p>   6. Type OL - The customer may lease an asset from the bank in which case the Standing Order id is a valid customer acount and accrual entries are a debit to the suspense account and a credit to th P+L category. On repayment the customer account (from the ID) is debited with the SO amount and the suspense account ( the counterparty account no) is credited with the SO amount . The bank may lease an asset from a customer in which case the id must be a valid suspense account and the counterpary account is a valid customer account. Accrual enteries are a debit to the P+L category with the accrual amount and a credit to the suspense account. On repayment there is a debit of the standing order amount to the suspense account and a credit to the customer account</p>
            <p>   7. Type RC - A customer has a revolving credit account with payments due on a monthly basis, the amount due can vary depending on the balance of the RC account. An RC standing order is set up on a monthly frequency making use of the CUR.AMT.ROUTINE field to call a locally developed routine to calculate the amount due. When the standing order is activated the amount will be determined and used to populate the CUR.AMOUNT.BAL field. A PD.PAYMENT.DUE record will be created with a contingent balance to indicate the amount due. When a credit entry is posted to the revolving credit account with the THEIR.REFERENCE field on the STMT.ENTRY set to the RC account number, the PD record will be credited with the amount on the entry , before the amount is credited to the RC account. When the PD has been cleared it will be written to history.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Up to 5 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters as defined         in the Details. Any other value will be refused.         (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>   The Standing Order type must first have been defined on         the Standing Order type table and only the above values         will be accepted.</p>
            <p>   The same balance maintenance Standing Order type can only         be used once per account as defined below: 900 A number         in this range will 999 always be assigned to Balance         Maintenance Standing Order types BI BO and BP.</p>
            <p>   When a Standing Order number 900 to 999 has been input by         the User, the value of this field can only be BI or BO or         BP.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is updated at end of day when an accrual payment takes place. It holds the accrual end periods of previous accrual cycles.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   A no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CPTY.ACCT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Counterparty account number.</p>
            <p>   This field is the one that will be credited, after being transferred in the CREDIT.ACCT.NO field of the FT new transaction produced.</p>
            <p>   For credit type STO, ie. when the flag REV.DR.CR.ACCT is 'Y' then the account specified in this field will be debited, after being transferred in the DEBIT.ACCT.NO field of the FT new transaction produced.</p>
            <p>   For an OL type Standing Order this field will contain a customer account number or a suspense account number depending on whether the bank is a lessor or a leasee of an asset. When the bank is a lessor then the id must be a customer account number and this field must be a suspense account number. The reverse applies when the bank is the leasee.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   For validations on the currency refer to help on       STO.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>   Optional input When SUPPRESS.FT is equal to Y.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency and charge amount to be applied for the previous charge type for this standing order. </p>
            <p>   Entry of this field will override the default rates of the charge type specified in the previous field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   3 character type SSS (uppercase alpha) or 1 to 3 character numeric currency code. '.' is mandatory if a numeric currency code is used. 1 to 14 characters plus decimal point, type AMT (standard amount format).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COVER.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the cover method to be used when Funds transfer contract is created from this STO. Value entered here mapped to Cover.Method in FT.</p>
            <p>   Based on the cover method and Customer Number given in Beneficiary or Ben.Bank, from AGENCY for the currency and application, values will be defaulted in bank fields-ACCT.WITH.BANK, RECEIVER.BANK, REC.CORR.BANK, INTERMED.BANK and same will be used during FT Creation.</p>
            <p>   See Cover.Method in Funds.Transfer for more details.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Input allowed only for "OTxx" Txn.type with MESSAGE.TYPE as       "103" in FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION.</p>
            <p>   Valid Values : COVER-DIRECT , COVER-NEAR, SERIAL, THIRD-INST</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Current End Date of the Standing Order for the Currency, Amount and Frequency specified in the previous fields. </p>
            <p>   A Current End Date should be input by the User in the two following cases: </p>
            <p>   1.         When the bank has received from the Customer clear            instructions which stipulate that the Standing Order must            only be executed during a determined period of time.  In            this case, the User will enter in this Field the date of the            last execution of the Standing Order. </p>
            <p>   2.         When the Customer has requested the bank to pay a            certain amount during a determined period of time and            then another amount starting from that date.  In this            case, the User will enter in this field the end date of the            first Standing Order amount.  After that date the second            amount will then be executed. </p>
            <p>   Any input made in this field for the Standard Order type DD will only be for information purposes. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 9 type D Date characters (date format in range 1950-2049). (Optional input except not allowed for the Standing Order type PP)</p>
            <p>   This field should only be input by the User when the Customer has provided the bank with a specific end date for the Standing Order itself or for the current amount and currency specified in the previous fields.</p>
            <p>   The date input must be greater than or equal to the first date input or calculated by the current frequency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PD.RATE.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define a locally developed routine which can be used to determine a value used to populate the CUR.AMOUNT.BAL field.</p>
            <p>   The routine must accept 4 arguments 3 input and 1 returned</p>
            <p />
            <p>   STO.ID input, the @ID of the standing order</p>
            <p>   R.STO input, the standing order record</p>
            <p>   R.ACC input, the account being debited</p>
            <p>   PD.RATE returned, the ratet used to populate the PD.RATE         field which will be passed to the PD application</p>
            <p>   An example routine source STO.PD.RATE.EXAMPLE is released and available.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Must be defined as a type "S" program on the PGM.FILE application</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FT.LOC.REF.DATA</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the data to be input to the LOCAL.REFERENCE field defined in FT.LOC.REF.NO. </p>
            <p>   The contents of this field will be placed in the corresponding local reference field on the Funds Transfer produced. The input must of course match the requirements for the local reference field defined on LOCAL.TABLE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 characters as defined in the LOCAL.TABLE definition for the LOCAL.REFERENCE field whose position is in FT.LOC.REF.NO. Associated subvalue field. (Optional or mandatory input if corresponding FT.LOC.REF.NO input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FT.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   Identifies the subroutine which will be executed  after the FT generated by the Standing Order (or by  the system created resubmitted Standing Order)  has been processed in the Batch. The routine would be called with two arguments - the ID and Status of the FT  generated by the Standing Order. When  no FT is generated (as in the case of  Standing Orders not submitted due to inadequate funds and  would be resubmitted in the next Batch processing), the subroutine would not be executed.  </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Name of the subroutine should be prefixed with the       symbol  @.</p>
            <p>   Subroutine must be identified as a record in the       application PGM.FILE with the type equal to 'S' for subroutine. </p>
            <p>   The routine must be compiled and cataloged with an       entry in the T24 account VOC file.</p>
            <p>   The routine must accept 2 arguments, both input:</p>
            <p>             Argument  1  :    ID of the FT  generated by the Standing Order </p>
            <p>            Argument  2  :    Record status of the  FT generated by the Standing Order</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the charge types applicable to this standing order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 11 characters type A (alphanumeric) charge type code. Associated multivalue field (Optional input)</p>
            <p>   Must exist on the FT.CHARGR.TYPE table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.PERIOD.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>The start date of the current accrual period. The accrual period is built around the standing order current frequency date. If the start period date is LT the standing order current frequency date then the accrual is deemed to be in arrears otherwise it is in advance. The date cannot be changed once the standing order has been authorised. If left blank then it will be defaulted using the end period date and the standing order current frequency. When the end of an accrual frequecy period is reached i.e. the accrual frequency date is GT the next working day then the start and end periods are cycled . For example :</p>
            <p>   Payment In Advance</p>
            <p>   Standing Order Frequency = 01/01/99 M0401</p>
            <p>   Accrual Frequency = 02/01/99 M0102</p>
            <p>   Start Period = 01/01/99</p>
            <p>   End period = 01/04/99</p>
            <p>   The accrual takes place monthly for a 4 month period. The accrual date cycles monthly and the accrual start and end periods cycle when the current standing order frequency date is reached (holidays and non working days are concidered when deciding to cycle).</p>
            <p>   Accrual Frequency = 02/04/99</p>
            <p>   Start Period = 01/04/99</p>
            <p>   End Period = 01/08/99</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Payment In Arrears</p>
            <p>   Standing Order Frequency = 01/01/99 M0401</p>
            <p>   Accrual Frequency = 31/12/98 M0131</p>
            <p>   Start Period = 01/10/98</p>
            <p>   End period = 01/01/99</p>
            <p>   Cycled dates :</p>
            <p>   Accrual Frequency = 02/01/99</p>
            <p>   Start Period = 01/01/99</p>
            <p>   End Period = 01/04/99</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Input only with 'OL' type standing orders and         PERFORM.ACCRUAL = 'YES'</p>
            <p>   Either the start period or end period must be entered.</p>
            <p>   Mandatory if the payments are in advance.</p>
            <p>   Either the start or end period must equal the standing         order current frequency date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SO.RETRY.NUMO</field>
<desc>
            <p>The number of retry days the Standing Order has been resubmitted on failing for insufficient funds. The maximum number of days is set in the application FT.APPL.DEFAULT, field NO.RESUBMSSN.DAYS.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   No Input Field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FUT.AMOUNT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines any Future Amount to be effected after the current payment instructions have been completed. </p>
            <p>   This field, when input, will always be associated with the next two fields and for any Future Standing Order instructions (excluding DIARY), an amount will always be mandatory. </p>
            <p>   It will allow the User to load in advance any number of future Standing Order instructions provided they are loaded in chronological date order. </p>
            <p>   This field, together with its associated fields, should be input by the User as soon as the instructions have been received from the Customer. There is no need to wait until the first execution date of the new instructions to enter the details in the Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point. Multivalue field. (Mandatory when Future Standing Order instructions are loaded in advance otherwise Optional.  Default Value: None.)</p>
            <p>   Input will only be allowed when the Current end date and Current Amount Balance fields have been entered.</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed for Standing Order types DIARY, PP and DD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.TRANSFER.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Minimum Amount required to justify a transfer activity for the Balance Maintenance Standing Order types.  The Currency of this amount will be taken from the Currency input in the Currency field i.e. the Currency of the Standing Order. </p>
            <p>   The purpose of this field is to avoid generating Balance Maintenance transactions for insignificant amounts. </p>
            <p>   Example: </p>
            <p>   If an amount of 10 has been specified in this field, no activity will be generated by the Standing Order for the types BI, BP and BO before the Balance Maintenance, which needs to be effected, is at least for an amount equal or greater than 10. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 14 type AMT (Standard Amount Format) characters plus a decimal point.  (Optional input for Standing Order types BI, BP and BO. Not  allowed for types FI, PP, PPI, DIARY and DD.)</p>
            <p>   If this field is not input, the Standing Order Application will check in the table FT.APPL.DEFAULT if the fields MIN.STO.CCY and MIN.STO.AMOUNT have been defined.  If not the System will use, as a default, the MIN.STO.AMOUNT in the Currency of the Standing Order or, if this Currency does not exist, the equivalent of the local currency MIN.STO.AMOUNT.  When these two fields have not been input on the FT.APPL.DEFAULT table, no default will be taken and a transfer transaction will be effected when the balance differs, irrespective of the amount.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify the conversion type to be used while calculating an exchange rate for the currency market defined in the previous field.</p>
            <p>   Allowed only when the currency market is entered.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Valid values are Buy or Sell or Mid</p>
            <p>   Mandatory when currency market is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency and commission amount to be applied for the previous commission type for this standing order. </p>
            <p>   Entry of this field will over-ride the defaults rates of the commission type specified in the previous field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   3 characters type SSS (uppercase alpha) or 1 to 3 character numeric currency code '.' is mandatory if a numeric currency code is used. 1 to 14 characters plus decimal point, type AMT (standard amount format).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the final exchange rate applied to this transaction and maps to Customer.Rate field in FT.</p>
            <p>   Input in this field is allowed only when the Treasury Rate or Customer Spread is Null</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   1-12 type R (Standard Rate Format - up to 8 integer and 6 decimal)     characters plus a decimal point or 1-15 type R (Up to 8 integer and 9     decimal) characters plus a decimal point when EXTENDED.PREC in SPF is set to     Y. (Optional input. Default as defined in Details.) </p>
            <p>   Input is not allowed when the Debit Currency and the Credit Currency are     the same.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATED.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enter yes or no to specify whether you wish to use the value dated accounting functionality when calculating the standing order amounts for balance maintenance standing orders. If set to yes then the system will try to match the FT DEBIT VALUE DATE on the standing order with a value date on the account record. Where possible the corresponding value dated balance is used if there is no match then the last value dated balance will be used.  If none are present, then the ONLINE.CLEARED.BAL on the account record is used.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Only valid when T24 is set up to use value dated accounting on the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER file.</p>
            <p>   Only valid with balance maintenance type standing orders</p>
            <p>   Must be either 'YES' or 'NO'. It will default to 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Print instructions in relation to the Standing Order.  Valid print instructions are: </p>
            <p>   The code input will be stored in the Standing Order record at validation time and will be blanked out at Authorisation once the output message has been handed over to the Delivery Application. </p>
            <p>   Note:      Standing order advices will not be created for            STO-DIARY instructions. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Y    A Standing Order Advice has to be printed (except for DIARY standing order type). N    A Standing Order Advice does not need to be printed. ALL  A Standing Order advice needs to be printed for all Standing Orders on this account. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.ADJUSTMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies how the date should be adjusted if the standing order processing date falls on a non working day.</p>
            <p>When PROC.DATE.TYPE = CVD, setting in this field would be used to adjust the credit value date of the FT generated from STO, if the credit value date falls on a non-working day.</p>            
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Accepted inputs:</p>
            <p>   Null - Standard processing, no adjustment of date.</p>
            <p>   PRECEDING - Processing will take place on the prior         working day.   FOLLOWING - Processing will take place on the following         working day.</p>
            <p>   MODIFIED - Processing will take place on the next working         day unless this date is in the following month, in which         case the processing will take place on the previous         working day.</p>
            <p>MBACKWARD - The processing date will be set to the previous working day, but if that previous working day falls in the previous month then it will be set to the next working day.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUS.DAY.DEFN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds the record ID of HOLIDAY table and defines which HOLIDAY setup must be followed to process the STANDING.ORDER record.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.ACCT.WITH.BANK</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds IBAN of the ACCT.WITH.BANK.ACC	</p>
        <p>If value is entered, it will be validated against IN.IBAN.STRUCTURE file, else an equivalent IBAN will be retrieved from a bank account record with alternate account type set as T24.IBAN</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.BEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds IBAN of the BEN.ACCT.NO</p>
        <p>	If value is entered, it will be validated against IN.IBAN.STRUCTURE file, else equivalent IBAN will be retrieved from a beneficiary account record with alternate account type set as T24.IBAN</p>
        <p>This is a HOT FIELD, When valid IBAN number is entered, BIC code will be derived and displayed in BIC.IBAN.BEN field along with Bank Name and country in the BIC.IBAN.BEN.NAME, BIC.IBAN.BEN.CTRY fields</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.CPTY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds IBAN of the CPTY.ACCT.NO	</p>
        <p>If value is entered, it will be validated against IN.IBAN.STRUCTURE file, else an equivalent IBAN will be retrieved from a counter party account record with alternate account type set as T24.IBAN</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.INTERMED.BANK</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds IBAN of the INTERMED.BANK.ACC	</p>
        <p>If value is entered, it will be validated against IN.IBAN.STRUCTURE file, else an equivalent IBAN will be retrieved from an intermediary bank account record with alternate account type set as T24.IBAN</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.REC.CORR.BANK</field>
<desc>
        <p>Holds IBAN of the REC.CORR.BANK.ACC	</p>
        <p>If value is entered, it will be validated against IN.IBAN.STRUCTURE file, else an equivalent IBAN will be retrieved from an account with receiver correspondent bank account record and with alternate account type set as T24.IBAN</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.ACT.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is updated at end of day when an accrual payment takes place. It contains the unrounded accrued amount of previous accrual cycles.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   A no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is updated at end of day when an accrual payment takes place. I t contains the rounded accrual amounts from previous accrual cycles.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   A no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.DATE.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date that the accrual is performed with a mandatory frequency code.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Input only allowed with 'OL' type standing orders with         PERFORM.ACCRUAL = 'YES' in which case it is mandatory.</p>
            <p>   Upto 17 characters and must be a valid date and         frequency.</p>
            <p>   Must be within the accrual pereiod i.e GE start period         and LT the end period</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.REC.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the reference of the AC.EXPECTED.RECEIPT record created from USER.ROUTINE for DIARY type STO</p>
            <p>   No input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the customer whose account is to be credited in relation to the Standing Order. Normally this is the customer whose account is specified in Field 16 BENEFICIARY.ACCTNO of the Standing Order. For Credit Type Standing Orders (with the field REV.DR.CR.ACCT='Y'), this is the customer whose account is specified in Field 0 STANDING.ORDER, the ID of the Standing Order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   (Internal field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.ACCT.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Account Number of the Beneficiary Account if different from the credited account (which is CPTY.ACCT.NO). </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 34 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. (Mandatory input or not allowed as defined in <p>Validation Rules:</p>)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Bank which is the ultimate receiver of the funds transferred by the sending bank.</p>
            <p>   The account of the Beneficiary Bank will receive the funds from a Bank-to-Bank transfer.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   3-10 character Customer Mnemonic (Uppercase alphanumeric or '.') or 1-6 numeric character Customer code or Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Multivalue field. A maximum of four lines, of 35 characters each, will be allowed. (Optional input for Pay Method equal to OT, otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Either Beneficiary or Bank may be input, but not both.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   For the PAY METHOD (Outward by Telex) either a Beneficiary or a Beneficiary Bank is mandatory.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   An override is generated when BEN.BANK is the same as ACCT.WITH.BANK.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.CORR.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   Identifies the Correspondent Bank for the Receiver Bank (i.e. the bank servicing the Account held by the Receiver Bank in the Currency of the Credit Amount).</p>
            <p>   The Receiver Correspondent Bank is the location where the funds will be made available for the Receiver.</p>
            <p>   If this field is not entered it will default automatically from the data stored in the Receiver Bank's Agency record.</p>
            <p>   A Receiver Correspondent Bank value is always mandatory when the Receiver Bank field is given along with Cover.method as Third-Inst. (the field may be manually input or defaulted from Agency file)-Otherwise optional field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   3-10 character Agency       Mnemonic (Uppercase alphanumeric or '.') or</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   1-16 numeric character       Agency code or</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Up to maximum 4 lines of 35       characters (uppercase alpha or Numeric characters) </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input for       Transaction Types OD, OT otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   This field will not be       allowed unless the Receiver Bank is input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   The Receiver Correspondent       Bank cannot be the same as : Account With Bank , Beneficiary Bank ,       Intermediary Bank.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   When this field is input and       the Intermediary Bank is blank ; the country of the Receiver       Correspondent Bank must be the same as the Credit Currency country.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.FROM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is updated at end of day when a accrual payment takes place. It holds the accrual start periods of previous accrual cycles.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   A no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ORDERING.CUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency that is used as the base when an exchange rate is being quoted on an FT transaction created using this STO that involves two different currencies.</p>
            <p>   Currency given here is mapped to Base currency field in FT application.</p>
            <p>   When STO is created with different Debit &amp; credit account currency and this field is left as Null, then FT will default the base currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   3 character Currency code (uppercase alpha or numeric) - Type SSS. </p>
            <p>   Mandatory when the Treasury Rate/Customer Rate is specified.</p>
            <p>   Optional when Customer Spread is Specified-otherwise Not allowed.</p>
            <p>   The base currency input in this field can only be either the Debit     Currency or the Credit Currency. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Cheque number, when meaningful. </p>
            <p>   This field will be transferred to the CHEQUE.NUMBER field of the next generated FT transaction. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 16 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies any overrides that may have occured on the payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   (Internal multivalue field.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STANDING.ORDER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents the ID by which each Standing Order is uniquely identified. </p>
            <p>   A maximum of 999 Standing Orders can be defined on the same account.  During the creation of new Standing Orders, this number will be generated automatically by the System.  Balance Maintenance Standing Order types must always have a number of 900 to 999 and for this reason, must be specifically input by the User. </p>
            <p>   When the User wants to change an existing Standing Order, it will be necessary to enter the complete Standing Order reference number i.e. the Account Number and the sequential Standing Order number separated by a . (dot). </p>
            <p>   When the field REV.DR.CR.ACCT in the Standing Order is set to 'Y' (for Standing Orders with Type=FI and PAY.METHOD=AC),  the Account number specified in the ID will be taken as the   Credit Account. </p>
            <p>   Examples of Standing Order references are: </p>
            <p>   111112.1   The first Standing Order existing on the Account 111112. </p>
            <p>   222224.7   The seventh Standing Order existing on the Account            222224. </p>
            <p>   444448.900 The Balance Maintenance Standing Order existing on the            Account 444448 where a minimum balance has been defined            below which funds will be transferred to the Account. </p>
            <p>   444448.901 The Balance Maintenance Standing Order existing on the            Account 444448 where a  maximum balance has been            defined above which funds will be transferred out of the            Account. </p>
            <p>   Note:      (1)  In the four examples above, the Standing Order                 numbers which follow the Account Number                 represent the sequential number which is always                 generated automatically by the Application. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   2-20 alphanumeric characters as follows: -    The first part of the ID will identify the Account Number for which the User wants to define Standing order instructions. -    The second part of the ID will be separated from the Account Number by a '.' and will be a three numeric characters sequential number.</p>
            <p>   During the creation of a new Standing Order the Account must be input as the System will always generate the next sequential Standing Order number.  For balance maintenance Standing Order types, this number must be entered by the User.</p>
            <p>   For the Change function the User will need to enter the complete key including the sequential Standing Order itself.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.TO.PARTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The party to whom the Bank to Bank Info. to be sent can be mentioned here and same is mapped to FT field. </p>
            <p>   When the FT is authorised, based on FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION and details given in the FT, appropriate Swift messages will be sent to Credit Customer, Debit Customer, Collection - Remitting Bank and Receiver Bank.</p>
            <p>   Mention the Party to whom the BktoBk info (Tag 72) to be sent here. This BktoBk info will be used for all swift messages which are sent to that Party in Tag 72.</p>
            <p>   If values entered then next field (BktoBk Out)  is mandatory.</p>
            <p>   BktoBk information can be specified only here or in field BktoBk info Not in both.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Valid values DRCUST,CRCUST,RCVBK,COLL.REM.BK   </p>
            <p>   Duplicate vales of SEND.TO.PARTY Not allowed </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>   Identifies the payment method to be used to execute the Standing Order instruction when the order is passed to the Funds Transfer Application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    The Pay Method input in this field will be enriched with the Transaction Type 35 character Description defined in the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION table.  The following Pay Method codes will be allowed:</p>
            <p />
            <p>    AC         Account Transfer.  An Inhouse transfer of funds, i.e. where no external payment is involved in the execution of the Standing Order instruction.  This Pay Method code will be always applicable for the Balance Maintenance Standing Order types.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    OC        Outward by cheque.  The issuing by the bank, of a local currency Manager cheque or Bank cheque to execute the Standing Order instruction.  The Customer for example, would have requested to Wonder Bank London, to pay every month by the debit of his current account GBP 100,00 to Mr R Perryman living in London.  The bank could then choose to pay the beneficiary by Manager cheque.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    OD        Outward by Draft.  The issuing by the bank of a bank Draft (usually in foreign currency) to execute the Standing Order instruction.  The Customer would, for example,  have requested Wonder Bank London, to pay every month by the debit of his current account BEF 20,000 to Mr T Champagne living in Brussels.  The bank could then choose to pay by Bank Draft.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    OT         Outward by Telex.  The issuing by the bank of a Telex payment to execute the Standing Order instruction.  The Customer would for example, have requested Wonder Bank London, to pay every month by the debit of his current account DEM 20,000.00 to Mr D Holland living in Frankfurt.  The bank could then choose to pay by Telex if the bank and the Account number of the beneficiary of the Standing Order has been indicated by the Customer.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    OB         Outward by Bankers Payment.  The issuing by the bank of a Banker payment to execute the Standing Order instruction.  This method of payment is followed in the United Kingdom to perform local currency interbank payments.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    BC         Outward by Local Clearing.  This Payment method can only be used if the clearing system is defined on FT.LOCAL.CLEARING.</p>
            <p>    ______________________________________________________________________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (1) 2 type AAA (alpha characters) (Mandatory input or not allowed as defined in <p>Validation Rules:</p>.)</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (2) Input mandatory for the Standing Order types FI, PP, BO, BI, BP and PPI.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (3) Input not allowed for the Standing Order types DIARY and DD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (4) Input must be one of the codes defined in Details.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (5) For the Standing Order type BI only the Pay Method code AC will be accepted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (6) The Pay Method must first have been defined in the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION table which will provide the enrichment to this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (7) For Standing Order type BO and BP Pay methods AC, BC and OT will be accepted</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (8) The eight Pay Method codes have been hardcoded in the program and the User must make sure to create the same ones in the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION table.  Any other code will be refused by the Application.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUR.AMT.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used to define a locally developed routine which can be used to determine a value used to populate the CUR.AMOUNT.BAL field.</p>
            <p>   The routine must accept 4 arguments 3 input and 1 returned</p>
            <p />
            <p>   STO.ID input, the @ID of the standing order</p>
            <p>   R.STO input, the standing order record</p>
            <p>   R.ACC input, the account being debited</p>
            <p>   CUR.AMOUNT returned, the amount used to populate the         CUR.AMOUNT.BAL field</p>
            <p>   An example routine source STO.AMOUNT.EXAMPLE is released and available.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Must be defined as a type S program on the         PGM.FILE application</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.OFFICER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Account Officer responsible for the Standing Order. </p>
            <p>   It will be enriched by the Area code defined on the Dept.Acct. Officer table. </p>
            <p>   If not input it will be generated automatically by the System which will default to the Account Officer from the Account of the Standing Order. </p>
            <p>   If the field USE.STO.ACCT.OFF is set to Y in FT.APPL.DEFAULT the value in this field will be added to the PROFIT.CENTRE.DEPT field in the resultant Funds Transfer record. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 4 numeric characters. (Optional input.  Default : None.)</p>
            <p>   It must be a valid code on the Dept.Acct. Officer table</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.AMOUNT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the amount of the Standing Order, or for the Balance Maintenance Standing Order types, will define the Balance to be maintained in the Account. </p>
            <p>   Balance Maintenance Standing Order types will always make reference to the CLEARED Balance. </p>
            <p>   For the DD Standing Order type, this field is only for information purposes and the System will take no action if the amount of the Direct Debit received differs from the amount specified in this field.  This is often when the amount is not known in advance. </p>
            <p>   For the PP Standing Order type, whenever an amount is input, the payment will be made that day and the payment program will delete the amount from the Standing Order record after execution of the payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   1 to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point. (Mandatory or not allowed as defined in <p>Validation Rules:</p>.)</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed for Standing Order type DIARY or PPI.</p>
            <p>   Input mandatory for Standing Order types BI, BO, BP and FI.</p>
            <p>   Input optional for Standing Order types DD and PP.</p>
            <p>   When both Balance Maintenance types (BI and either BO or BP) have been defined on the same account, the amount specified in the Current amount balance field must be smaller in the BI type than in the BO or BP type.</p>
            <p>   For the Balance Maintenance Standing Order types BI, BO and BP an amount of 0 (zero) will be accepted. In any other case an 0 amount will be refused.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Current End Date of the Charge frequency if specified in the previous field.</p>
            <p>   Charges will be calculated as per frequency specified in the previous field upto this date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Associated multivalue field-Input allowed only when Charge frequency is specified       along with Date.</p>
            <p>   Up to 9 type D Date characters (date format in range 1950-2049).</p>
            <p>   The date input must be greater than or equal to the first date input or calculated by the       Charge frequency.</p>
            <p>   This field should only be input by the User when the bank wants to collect       Charges upto a specific date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REV.DR.CR.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   Identifies whether the Account specified in the Record ID is the Credit Account. </p>
            <p />
            <p>   When this Field  is set to 'Y'  for Standing Orders with TYPE=FI and PAY.METHOD=AC, the account specified in the Record ID would be  passed to the FT</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   would be </p>
            <p />
            <p>   This could be used  to create Credit</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Input allowed only for Standing orders with TYPE='FI' and       PAY.METHOD='AC'.</p>
            <p>   Default value is Null.</p>
            <p>   When the value is 'Y',  all the existing validations       on the Currency and Type of Debit and Credit accounts hold good (Account       specified in the Record ID being the Credit Account and CPTY.ACCT.NO being the Debit       Account).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NETTING.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specify here whether the MT202 or MT203 to be generated for the FT's generated from this Standing.Order </p>
            <p>   From FUNDS.TRANSFER application, MT202 messages can be generated or individual MT202 messages can be grouped together and a MT203 can be sent.</p>
            <p>   If 'N' is specified here then resultant FT will be creating MT202. </p>
            <p>   Incase this field is left as null then based on the NETTING.ALLOWED field in DE.MESSAGE for message type 202 &amp; NETTING.PAYMENT in DE.PARM , message type 203 is generated from FT instead of MT202.</p>
            <p>   Details entered here is mapped to FUNDS.TRANSFER field NETTING.STATUS &amp; for more information refer to this field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional Input   </p>
            <p>   Valid values allowed through manual Input- 'NO' or Null </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency of the Standing Order payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters or    1 to 3 numeric character Currency code. (Mandatory input or not allowed as defined in <p>Validation Rules:</p>).</p>
            <p>   The Currency code must be a valid code on the Currency table.</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed for the Standing Order type DIARY.</p>
            <p>   Input optional for the Standing Order type DD.</p>
            <p>   Input mandatory for the Standing Order types BI, BO, FI, PP, BP and PPI.</p>
            <p>   For the Standing Order types BI, BO and BP, the Currency code specified in this field must be the same as the Currency of the Standing Order account.</p>
            <p>   For the Pay Method AC, the Currency code specified in this field must be the same as the Currency of the  Account defined in the Beneficiary Account Number field or the currency of the account of the standing order.</p>
            <p>   In all the circumstances where the Currency of the Standing Order may differ from the Currency of the Standing Order account, an override will be required.</p>
            <p>   For the Pay Method OB and OC, the Currency code specified in this Field must be equal to the Local Currency code.</p>
            <p>   For the Pay Method OT and OD, if the Currency Code specified in this field is equal to the local currency code, the Funds Transfer record generated will be placed on hold because for these payment types a Credit Account number is mandatory for local currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMM.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Current End Date for the Commission frequency if specified in the previous field.</p>
            <p>   Commission will be applied as per frequency specified in the previous field upto this date.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Associated multivalue field-Input allowed only when Commission frequency     is specified along with Date.</p>
            <p>   Up to 9 type D Date characters (date format in range 1950-2049).</p>
            <p>   The date input must be greater than or equal to the first date input or     calculated by the commission frequency.</p>
            <p>   This field should only be input by the User when the bank wants to collect     commission upto a specific date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.FOR</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   This field is used to specify whether the corresponding commission amount entered is due to the sending bank or the receiving bank. If the standing order pay method is OT and the system has been set to produce SWIFT message MT103 - Single Customer Credit Transfer</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Sender - the corresponding charge amount entered is due to the sending bank.</p>
            <p>   Receiver &amp;#8211; the corresponding charge amount entered is due to the receiving bank.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   Permitted values are Sender      or Receiver, for pay method of OT with a message type of MT103 the default      is Sender.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>   If the standing order pay      method is set to OT and the system is set to produce message type MT103      there must at least one senders commission or charge present.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENT.FREQUENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Current Frequency of the Standing Order for the currency and amount specified in the previous fields. </p>
            <p>   The Standing Order Application will execute the Standing Order instruction (i.e. the currency and amount specified in the two previous fields) according to the frequency specified in this field up to and including the current end date specified in the next field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field is sub-divided into two elements: 1. Date 1-9         type D (date format in range 1950-2049) characters. 2.         Frequency 1-5 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first         character alpha) characters. (Mandatory input for the         Standing Order types BI, BO, FI, OL, BP PPI and DIARY.         Optional for type DD. Not allowed for type PP. No         default.)</p>
            <p>   Any input made in this field for the Standing Order type         DD will only be for information purposes.</p>
            <p>   The date input or generated will correspond to the first         execution of the Standing Order.</p>
            <p>   The first date calculated by the System (if not input         under 1. above) will be the date resulting from the         frequency applied to the Processing Date. If a date was         input first, the frequency will then be applied on this         date and not on the Processing date.</p>
            <p>   'DAILY' frequency is not allowed for Standing Order types         B1, BO and BP. (BSNSS, every working day, is allowed).</p>
            <p>   An override will be required if the date input is a         non-working day and the frequency is 'BSNSS'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCR.PRIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is updated at end of day when an accrual payment takes place. It contains the principle amounts that previous accruals was based on. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   A no input field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Payment Details to enable the Beneficiary to apply the payment. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Multivalue field. A maximum of 4 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed. (Optional input. Not allowed for the Standing Order type DIARY.)</p>
            <p>   For BC Pay Method, see the section 'Local Clearing Rules' for the relevant clearing system for validation details.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REC.CORR.BANK.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account Number of the Receiver Correspondent Bank can be specified here and mapped to the same field in Funds.Transfer.</p>
            <p>   The Account Number inputted here along with the Receiver Correspondent Bank details as given in REC.CORR.BANK will be used in tag 54 of Swift message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input   </p>
            <p>   Up to 34 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type S.   </p>
            <p>   Allowed only when REC.CORR.BANK is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.WITH.BANK.ACC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Account Number of the Account with Bank can be specified here and mapped to same field in Funds Transfer.</p>
            <p>   The Account Number inputted here along with the Account with Bank details as given in ACCT.WITH.BANK will be used in  tag 57 of Swift message.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input   </p>
            <p>   Up to 34 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - type S.   </p>
            <p>   Allowed only when ACCOUT.WITH.BANK is entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.CHG.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contain the each execution date of the STO when Commission/Charge type is specified with or without the commission/charge frequency.</p>
            <p>   This field is updated with the STO Execution date, even when the Funds Transfer contract is created for the STO or Not (due to Overrides / Errors / Exception) to keep track of dates on which STO selected for execution when Commission / Charge Details are given.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   For CVD type STO, Adjusted Date as per DAYS.PRIOR will be updated in this field.  </p>
            <p>   No input -Multivalue field.</p>
            <p>   Updated by system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.OUTREF</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the reference numbers allocated by Delivery for all payments, advices, messages sent by the Staning Order to the Delivery Application</p>
            <p>   No input field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.WITH.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the bank where the beneficiary maintains his account if this differs to the Receiving bank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Up to 35 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. A maximum of 4 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input or not allowed as defined in <p>Validation Rules:</p>)</p>
            <p>   Input not allowed for Pay Methods AC or the Standing Order types DIARY or DD.</p>
            <p>   If an input of less than 10 characters has been made, the System will check against the Agency file to see if the input corresponds to a valid Agent.  If this is the case, the short name of the Agent will be displayed and any expansion of the multivalue field will be refused.  If the input does not correspond to a valid Agent the System will allow the User to expand the Field to enter further information.</p>
            <p>   For pay methods other than BC this field must be blank if BANK.SORT.CODE (Field 18) is used. For local clearing payment method (BC), see the section 'Local clearing rules' for the relevant clearing system.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BIC.IBAN.BEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>When a valid IBAN number is input in the field IBAN.BEN, BIC code of the IBAN number will be derived based on IN.IBAN.PLUS table and updated in this field, when system does not find the BIC code then this field will be open for user input.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P>System updated BIC code or any valid DE.BIC record id.</P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BIC.IBAN.BEN.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Stores the bank name of the BIC code entered in the field BIC.IBAN.BEN. This is derived from INSTITUTION field of DE.BIC record when a valid BIC.IBAN.BEN is given; otherwise it is allowed for user input.</p>
		<p>If the BIC id is valid but a record is not found in DE.BIC table, INSTITUTION NAME from the IN.IBAN.PLUS table corresponding to the BIC code will be populated</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P>System updated BIC bank name or any valid user input.</P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BIC.IBAN.BEN.CITY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Stores the city of the bank (BIC code). This is derived from field CITY of DE.BIC record when a valid BIC.IBAN.BEN is given; otherwise it is allowed for user input.</p>
		<p>If the BIC id is valid but a record is not found in DE.BIC table, COUNTRY value from the IN.IBAN.PLUS table corresponding to the BIC code will be populated</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P>System updated BIC bank city or any valid city name.</P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PER.OVER.CAB</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is used to specify a percentage value, which would be applied on the accounts excess amount(Accounts cleared balance - CURRENT.AMOUNT) to arrive at the transfer amount.</p>
        <p>When percentage and minimum transfer amount is given, then, minimum check would consider the amount calculated with this percentage value.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>   This is optional Field.</p>
            <p>   PER.OVER.CAB can be used only for BO  type. </p>
            <p>   Input in this field is mutually exclusive with 'CUR.AMT.ROUTINE' field. </p>
            
        </p>        
        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUPPRESS.FT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to indicate if the payment is to be processed by FT or TPS or Payment Order</p>        
        <p>When 'Y' is defined in this field, Standing Order will be processed by TPS</p>
        <p>When 'N' or null is present in the field, Standing Order will be processed by FT</p>
        <p>When 'PAYMENT' option is selected, Standing order will be processed using the default payment system of the company i.e. when PAYMENT.ORDER.PARAMETER is present for the company, Payment order will be considered as the default Payment system for the company and Standing order will be processed using Payment Order i.e STO will generate Payment order. If PAYMENT.ORDER.PARAMETER is not present for the company, then Standing order will be processed using FT</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>   Input only allowed when PP product or PI product is installed else NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>   Valid options are 'Y' or 'N' or 'PAYMENT' </p>            
        </p>                
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLG.NATURE.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The Clearing Nature Code of the payment is matched with this field. If it is set to * then the Clearing Nature Code is not used in the match criteria.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>   Input only allowed when PP product is installed else NOINPUT field.</p>
	    <p>   Up to 20 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>            
        </p>        
        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTRA.COMP.PYMT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is used for identifying an intra-company payment, if both the debit and credit account belong to the same client/client group.</p>
        <p>The value of this field should be populated as "Y" by the Standing order application to denote if it's an Intra company payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>   Input only allowed when PP product is installed else NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>   Valid options are 'Y' or 'N' </p>
            
        </p>        
        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MSG.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
        <p>To indicate whether a payment is Urgent and thereby undergo faster processing</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>   Input only allowed when PP product is installed else NOINPUT field.</p>
	    <p>   Valid options are 'U' or 'N' </p>            
        </p>        
        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REG.REPORT</field>
<desc>
        <p>The details entered here is mapped to Regulatory Reporting(77B) in swift messages.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>   Input only allowed when PP product is installed else NOINPUT field.</p>
	    <p>   Up to 35 characters (uppercase alpha or numeric) - Type S. Multivalue     field.</p>            
        </p>        
        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROC.DATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the generation of FUNDS TRANSFER from STANDING.ORDER, 'n' days prior to the Frequency Date as mentioned in DAYS.PRIOR</p>
            <p>Example: For Credit Value Dated(CVD) STANDING.ORDER, assume DAYS.PRIOR to be 1W and Frequency Date to be 20th JAN 2014 with no holidays in between, then FUNDS TRANSFER will be generated on 19th JAN 2014</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input</p>            
            <p>   Valid values are CVD and Blank</p>
            <p>   Allowed only when DAYS.PRIOR is entered</p>
			<p>   Defaulted with values from STO.TYPE, when PROC.DATE.TYPE and DAYS.PRIOR are blank and PROC.DATE.TYPE in STO.TYPE is set as CVD</p>                                    
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.PRIOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the number of days prior to the frequency date, on which the FT is to be generated</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input</p>
            <p>   Valid values are nW, nC and Blank, where 'n' stands for the number of days</p>
            <p>   Allowed only when PROC.DATE.TYPE is entered</p>
            <p>	  Calendar Value is allowed only when DATE.ADJUSTMENT is provided.</p>
			<p>   Defaulted with values from STO.TYPE, when PROC.DATE.TYPE and DAYS.PRIOR are blank and PROC.DATE.TYPE in STO.TYPE is set as CVD</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specifiy the country of the beneficiary customer of the STO transaction. This is tied to EB.LOOKUP records with id like STO.BEN.TYPES.</p>
        <p>This is mainly introduced to identify those transaction which has its beneficiary customer based in US. This is for information purpose only and no processing would done based on this information within STO. Reports or enquries can be made to use this field to derive US region specific sto records.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Should be a valid entry from EB.LOOKUP table STO.BEN.TYPES values</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.STP</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specifiy if the FUNDS.TRANSFER record generated via STO processing should be put on hold or should this be created immediately. If this is set to YES, then, FT would be put on hold for user modification else FT would be generated immediately and authorised by system automatically.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Valid values are YES OR left blank</p>
            <p> Default from STO.TYPE record in case if it is not given here</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FT.VERSION</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specify the FUNDS.TRANSFER version to be used while generating the FT from STO.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Should be a valid ID in the VERSION table and the version should be for FUNDS.TRANSFER application.</p>
            <p> Default from STO.TYPE record in case if it is not given here</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXECUTION.STAGE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to indicate at which stage of COB the STO is to be processed.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Valid values are EOD, SOD or Blank.</p>
            <p>For BI and BO type STO, EOD is not allowed since it is the Default Execution Stage.</p>
            <p>For STO with types other than BI and BO, SOD is not allowed since it is the Default Execution Stage.</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.PURPOSE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to define additional information related to SEPA standing order transactions which can be provided when a payment is initiated within T24 to be processed through payment suites</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Input allowed only when PP product is installed else this will be a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when SUPPRESS.FT field is set to YES, currency as EUR (SEPA payments) and STO type is either BI or BO or FI.</p>
            <p>Should be a valid record in the table PAYMENT.PURPOSE.CODE.</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to define additional information related to SEPA standing order transactions which can be provided when a payment is initiated within T24 to be processed through payment suites</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Input allowed only when PP product is installed else this will be a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when SUPPRESS.FT field is set to YES, currency as EUR (SEPA payments) and STO type is either BI or BO or FI.</p>
            <p>Should be a valid record in the table PAYMENT.CATEG.PURPOSE.</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p> This is used for updating beneficiary details in TAG59F. </p>
        <p> Multi-value field is used to Input the Beneficiary Name. </p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 33 characters is allowed for user input.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.ADDRESS</field>
<desc>
        <p> This is used for updating beneficiary details in TAG59F. </p>
        <p> Multi-value field is used to Input the Beneficiary Address. </p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 33 characters is allowed for user input.</p>
        <p> This field can be input only when BEN.NAME is input.</p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
        <p> This is used for updating beneficiary details in TAG59F. </p>
        <p> This field is used to Input the Beneficiary Country. </p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A valid Country Code.</p>
        <p> A maximum of 2 characters country code is allowed for user input.</p>
        <p> This field can be input only when BEN.NAME is input.</p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.TOWN</field>
<desc>
        <p> This is used for updating beneficiary details in TAG59F. </p>
        <p> Multi-value field is used to Input the Beneficiary Town. </p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 33 characters is allowed for user input.</p>
        <p> This field can be input only when BEN.NAME is input.</p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PO.PRD.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to define the Payment order product to be used in the Payment Order generated for the STO when SUPPRESS.FT is set to PAYMENT</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Should be a valid record in the file PAYMENT.ORDER.PRODUCT</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when PI product is installed else this will be a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when SUPPRESS.FT field is set to PAYMENT and PAYMENT.ORDER.PARAMETER is present for the Company </p>            
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PO.VERSION</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specify the PAYMENT.ORDER version to be used while generating the Payment Order from STO when SUPPRESS.FT is set to PAYMENT</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Input allowed only when PI product is installed else this will be a NOINPUT field.</p>
            <p>Input allowed only when SUPPRESS.FT field is set to PAYMENT and PAYMENT.ORDER.PARAMETER is present for the Company </p>
            <p>Must be valid Payment order version record</p>
            <p>If not defined in Standing order, the version will be defaulted from STO.TYPE record for the respective Payment order product</p>
            <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>INVOICE.REFERENCE</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Invoice reference</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:Free Text of 35 characters. Optional. No validation</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>STRUCTURED.COMMUNICATION.CODE</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Used for SEPA</p>
    <p>Validation Rules: </p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>STRUCTURED.ISSUER</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Used for SEPA</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:Free Text of 65 characters. Optional. No validation</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>STRUCTURED.CREDITOR.REFERENCE</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Used for SEPA</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:Free Text of 25 characters. Optional. No validation</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>END.TO.END.REFERENCE</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Used for SEPA</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:Free Text of 35 characters. Optional. No validation</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>INSTRUCTION.ID.REF</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Used for SEPA</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:Free Text of 35 characters. Optional. No validation</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.METHOD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to define method of transfer being initiated, which is required when it is to be processed through payment suites.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Should be a valid record in the lookup PAY.ORDER.PAY.METHOD.</p>
	    <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DEBTOR.AGENT.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Name of the debtor agent of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Deafulted with Current lead company name when left undefined.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBTOR.AGENT.ADDR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Address type to be used for the Debtor Agent of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Valid value from PASTAL.ADDR.TYPE lookup table.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBTOR.AGENT.ADDR.LINE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Address fields of Debtor Agent of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Maximum of 7 multi value set allowed.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBTOR.AGENT.BIC</field>
<desc>
        <p>BIC code of Debtor Agent of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Valid record from DE.BIC application</p>
             <p>Optional field. Defaulted to current company BIC if left undefined.</p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>DEBTOR.AGENT.CLEAR.CODE</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Clearing code or sort code of the Debtor Agent</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
    <p>Optional field.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>DEBTOR.AGENT.IDENTIFIER</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Other Identification Code for Debtor Agent.</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
    <p>Optional field.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>DEBTOR.AGENT.RESERVED5-1</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Reserved fields of Debtor Agent.</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
    <p>Optional field.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Name of the Ultimate debitor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.ADDR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Address type to be used for the Ultimate debtor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Valid value from PASTAL.ADDR.TYPE lookup table.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.ADDR.LINE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Address fields of Ultimate debtor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Maximum of 7 multi value set allowed.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.BIC</field>
<desc>
        <p>BIC code of Ultimate debtor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Valid record from DE.BIC application.</p>
             <p>Optional field.</p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Country of Ultimate debtor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Valid record from Country appplication.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.RESERVED.5-1</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Reserved fields of Ultimate creditor.</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
    <p>Optional field.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.CRED.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Name of the Ultimate creditor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.CRED.ADDR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Address type to be used for the Ultimate creditor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Valid value from PASTAL.ADDR.TYPE lookup table.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.CRED.ADDR.LINE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Address fields of Ultimate creditor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Maximum of 7 multi value set allowed.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.CRED.BIC</field>
<desc>
        <p>BIC code of Ultimate creditor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Valid record from DE.BIC application.</p>
             <p>Optional field.</p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ULTIMATE.CRED.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
        <p>Country of Ultimate creditor of payment.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: Valid record from Country appplication.</p>
             <p>Optional field. </p>
        </p>
        <p />
        <P></P>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>ULTIMATE.CRED.RESERVED.5-1</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Reserved fields of Ultimate creditor.</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
    <p>Optional field.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>INSTRUCTION.CODE</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Instruction code which has to be sent to account with bank.</p>
    <p>Validation Rules: Valid record from lookup table PAYMENT.INSTRUCTION.CODE.</p>
    <p>Optional field. MUltivalue field.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>INSTRUCTION.CODE.TEXT</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Text to describe the instruction code which has to be sent to account with bank.</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
    <p>Optional Free Text field.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>PYMT.INFO.SER.LEVEL.CODE</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Payment service level code to be sent to account with bank, which describes the priority and execution type of payment.</p>
    <p>Validation Rules: Valid record from lookup table PAYMENT.SERVICE.LEVEL.CODE</p>
    <p>Optional field.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>ACCT.WITH.BANK.COUNTRY</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Country for account with bank</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:OtherIdentification code for Beneficiary. Valid record from Country application</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t>
  <field>INTERMED.BANK.COUNTRY</field>
  <desc>
    <p>Country of Intermediary bank.</p>
    <p>Validation Rules:Will be NOINPUT when transfer is not done through beneficairy.</p>
    <p></p>
  </desc>
</t>
<t><field>ORD.CUST.ACCT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>PRIORITY.NUMBER</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>RETRY.ORIG.CR.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>STRUCTURED.COMM.CODE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>STRUCTURED.CRED.REF</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DEBTOR.AGENT.RESERVED.5</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DEBTOR.AGENT.RESERVED.4</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DEBTOR.AGENT.RESERVED.3</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DEBTOR.AGENT.RESERVED.2</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DEBTOR.AGENT.RESERVED.1</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.RESERVED.5</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.RESERVED.4</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.RESERVED.3</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.RESERVED.2</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.DEBT.RESERVED.1</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.CRED.RESERVED.5</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.CRED.RESERVED.4</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.CRED.RESERVED.3</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.CRED.RESERVED.2</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ULTIMATE.CRED.RESERVED.1</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
