<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AC</product>
        <title>STMT.ENTRY</title>
        <table>STMT.ENTRY</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This is the internal file which contains details of all entries over Customer and Internal Accounts.</p>
            <p>  Entries are generated in this file by every on-line and batch process which involves debiting or crediting Accounts.</p>
            <p>  This file is used by any process which needs details of entries over Accounts, e.g. Account Statements.</p>
            <p>  Only the See, Print and List functions may be used in this Application.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the amount of the Entry expressed in Local Currency.</p>
                <p>  This field is present in all Entries, including those over foreign currency Accounts.  If the Local Currency Amount is not entered in the originating transaction, it is generated by the system, using the Rate input or a Rate from the CURRENCY table.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus decimal point (standard amount format, type AMT), signed. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AUTHORISER</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BALANCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BANK.SORT.CDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to store the bank sort code associated with the accounting entry. Bank Sort codes could be populated into the accounting entry file in the following situations:</p>
                <p>  Bank Draft issued to a client who holds an account with         the bank. In this case the cheque number will appear in         the debit entry made to the underlying client account         account and the credit entry to the Nostro A/c attempting         to collect the payment.</p>
                <p>  Cheques being deposited by clients who have an account         with the bank will result in credit entries to the         underlying client accounts to have the cheque number         field populated.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOOKING.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the run date on which the Entry was generated.</p>
                <p>  The run date is normally, but not necessarily the actual date at the time the Entry is generated, e.g. if the previous day's business is still being processed after midnight, the actual date changes, but the run date is still the previous day.</p>
                <p>  The date used is from the Today Field in the DATES record (ref: General Tables) for the Company being processed.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Standard Date format. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CARD.NUMBER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the CARD NUMBER of the DEBIT account.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rules:</p>
                <p> No input field-Updated by system </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
         <t>
            <field>TAX.DATA</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field which holds the tax data that is needed for updating the tax.report at the accounting stage. Application which raises tax entries has to update this field while forming the entry record for raising tax entries and pass it to core accounting</p>
                <p>Core accounting would use this information to update ST.TAX.REPORT.DETAILS, the central tax reporting file</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CARD.TXN.DETAIL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Multi-Value field that contains the details of CARD NUMBER used. Normally this will be populated from the switch ware with information such as ATM location, merchant id etc,</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation rules:</p>
                <p>   No input field -Updated by system</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHEQUE.NUMBER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to store the cheque number associated with the accounting entry. Cheque numbers could be populated into the accounting entry file in the following situations:</p>
                <p>  Cheque issued to client accounts that have been presented         for payment will result in the debit accounting entry to         the underlying account number to contain the cheque         number on it.</p>
                <p>  Bank Draft issued to a client who holds an account with         the bank. In this case the cheque number will appear in         the debit entry made to the underlying client account         account and the credit entry to the Nostro A/c attempting         to collect the payment.</p>
                <p>  Cheques being deposited by clients who have an account         with the bank will result in credit entries to the         underlying client accounts to have the cheque number         field populated.</p>
                <p>  If more than one cheque of the same type are entered on the application raising the entry all the cheque numbers will be held separately in multi-values on the accounting entry.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHQ.COLL.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>In case an accounting entry being raised is associated with the an out clearing cheque and the procsessing involved creates a CHEQUE.COLLECTION item to record the details of the underlying cheque being deposited into a clients account, the CHEQUE.COLLECTION item's ID will be recorded into this field as a link to the CHEQUE.COLLECTION record.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHQ.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AA.ITEM.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the branch or office where the Account is held.</p>
                <p>  The Company Code is in the format CCGGGLLLL</p>
                <p>  whereCC is the Country Code                 GGG is the Company Group Code            and  LLLL is the Local Code to identify the different                 processing companies (e.g. branches) within one                 Country.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  9 type A (alphanumeric) character Company Code. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONSOL.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONTRACT.BAL.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONTRACT.INT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONTRACT.INT.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COUNTERPARTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the counterparty with whom the Bank has arranged a transaction.</p>
                <p>  System generated field.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1 to 6 Numeric character Customer Number</p>
                <p>  Must refer to a valid Customer.</p>
                <p>  (Display only)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRF.CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The currency for which the CRF movement is to be raised, if different to the currency of the entry.</p>
                <p>  When the 'other' side of the accounting entry is the CRF type, the system will raise a CONSOL.ENT.TODAY record in the same currency as the entry, unless the CRF.CURRENCY is specified.  In some circumstances the currency of the deal may be different to the entry raised, for example where a deal in BEF allow settlement in LUF accounts.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  3 character currency code.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRF.MAT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The maturity date associated with the resultant CRF entry.</p>
                <p>  This date may be present where maturity splitting of CRF date is required.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  8 character standard date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRF.PROD.CAT</field>
            <desc>              
            <p>This field is used to store the product category code associated with the contract.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p>No input field.</p>
            <p>Must have a valid record in category table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRF.TXN.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The transaction code to be used for the CRF movement for the CRF.TYPE.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  3 alpha character code</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Account which is updated by this Entry.</p>
                <p>  The Account may belong to a Customer or may be Internal.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Standard Account Number format. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRF.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The CRF Asset Type which corresponds to the 'other' side of the accounting entry.</p>
                <p>  The system will automatically generate the 'other' side of accounting entries if this field is specified.  The system will raise a record to the CONSOL.ENT.TODAY file if this type is specified for the opposite amount of the entry, or the CRF.AMOUNT and CRF.CURRENCY if specified.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  3 - 12 character consolidation asset type.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURR.NO</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The SWIFT Currency Code for the entry. The Currency of the Account in Field 1.  Not used in Entries over local currency Accounts.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  3 type S (upper-case alpha or numeric) characters Currency Code, or blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates which type of currency funds are being used for those currencies where there is more than one type. Different exchange rates may be quoted for the different markets.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1 numeric character Currency Market code, or blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the Customer of the Account, where applicable, for information purposes. Accounts such as Internal Accounts have no Customer name so will not display here.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  System generated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CYCLE.FORWARD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes whether forward entries should be cycled to the next working day when the value date on the emtry is reached.</p>
                <p>  Some applications may raise forward entries with a value date, but no processing may occur on the value date. For example a Fiduciary order, a security order or a Past Due record. It is important for these application to leave the entry as the impact on the cash-flow is required for the account. In these cases the value of this field should be set to Y, which will cause the date to cyled every night instead of being removed.</p>
                <p>  Other applications such as LD, Swaps and Bond Processing in securities, allow adjustment of the value date on non-working days, so that it is possible to get a back dated entry for an event to be processed in the future. For these situations thisi field can contain the date on which the event is to be processed, amd therefore the date the forward entry expires. The system will cycle such entries forward when the value date is less than the system date until the expiry date is reached.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No input allowed</p>
                <p>  May contain a Y or a Standard format date</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DATE.TIME</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DD.ITEM.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field has the reference id of DD.ITEM which got created because of this STMT.ENTRY.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  No input field-Updated by SYSTEM.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DD.MANDATE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DD.MANDATE.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The DD.DDI mandate reference related to this transaction is populated here. When forward entries created by Application which is linked to Direct Debit module, this field is automatically updated with the related mandate reference, currently MG.MORTGAGE application is using this feature.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  No input field -Updated by system</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Account Officer code from Account record for Account in Field 1 or, if the Account record has no Account Officer code, the Account Officer code from the Customer record.</p>
                <p>  In case of applications like LD, MM etc, it is possible to input account officer in individual contract and in that case this field will be populated from the deal concerned.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  1-4 numeric characters Department Account Officer code. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEAL.CCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEAL.EXCH.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEALER.DESK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEPARTMENT.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Department where the original transaction was input.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1-4 numeric characters Department Account Officer code. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DRAWN.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If a cheque is returned, this field will be populated with the account number of the account that the cheque was attempted to be drawn from. The actual account number that the STMT.ENTRY refers to is the return suspense account.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  NOINPUT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXCHANGE.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For Entries over foreign Currency Accounts, this field contains the Rate which was used to convert the Currency Amount to the local equivalent (Field 3) at the time of the originating transaction.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1-10 numeric characters and decimal point, (standard Rate format, type R), or blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXP.SPLIT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will contain the exposure amount split according to the rules defined in the exposure conditions table. The field is automatically updated by the system whenever either of the following happens:</p>
                <p>  1. The transaction code used on this entry had default exposure key defined on it pointing to the EXPOSURE.CONDITIONS file which in turn would define the exposure date ladder rules.</p>
                <p>  2. The sort code used on the teller transaction from where this entry would have originated had an exposure key defined on it in the BC.SORT.CODE file.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXP.SPLIT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will contain the exposure date split according to the rules defined in the exposure conditions table. The field is automatically updated by the system whenever either of the following happens:</p>
                <p>  1. The transaction code used on this entry had default exposure key defined on it pointing to the EXPOSURE.CONDITIONS file which in turn would define the exposure date ladder rules.</p>
                <p>  2. The sort code used on the teller transaction from where this entry would have originated had an exposure key defined on it in the BC.SORT.CODE file.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXPOSURE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The date on which the available balance will be credited with the Entry, i.e. the date on which the Entry can be drawn against and is given value for credit limit position processing.</p>
                <p>  This date can only be present in Credit Entries or Debit Entries which are reversals of Credit Entries.</p>
                <p>  It may be input manually in the application generating the Entry, or it may be generated automatically depending on rules specified in the application or in the TRANSACTION code table.</p>
                <p>  If this field is blank, the Exposure Date is assumed to be the same as the Booking Date.</p>
                <p>  Note:      This date does not affect the Value Date on which the            Entry updates the Balance for interest purposes.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Standard date format, or blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INPUTTER</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNTING.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LIQUIDATION.MODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MASK.NARRATIVE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MASK.PRINT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MASTER.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NARRATIVE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A multivalue field containing a variable number of lines of 34 characters which may be printed on descriptive statements in addition to the standard narrative and/or reference.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Up to 34 type S (upper-case alpha or numeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.REF.NUM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the dealer's reference number quoted when an exchange rate was booked with the dealers department. Never used in local currency Entries.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1-5 numeric characters or blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NET.PARAM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIG.AMOUNT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIG.CCY.MARKET</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCRUAL.DATA</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIG.LOCAL.EQUIV</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIGINAL.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will hold the original account number to which this entry was posted.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIGINAL.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the amount in the original currency.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIGINAL.CCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the original currency on the entry.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIGINAL.EXCH.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will hold the original exchange rate that existed on this entry before auto payment was applied.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No Input Allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OUR.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the Reference given to the transaction/deal by the Bank. In most cases this reference provides the link between the Statement Entry (STMT.ENTRY) file and the master file of the originating application, but for Entries input via DATA.CAPTURE it is only present if input manually.</p>
                <p>  Consolidated STMT.ENTRY</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  For the consolidated statement entry, the field will contain NET-consolidated id.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OUTSTANDING.BAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains details of any overrides relevant to the Entry which were required in order for the transaction generating the Entry to be accepted.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.APPLIED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.PERIOD.END</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADDL.TRANS.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Not used in Statement Entry records.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PM.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates which exchange position this Entry falls into. Always blank in local currency Entries.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  2 type AAA (alpha) characters or blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROCESSING.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Category Code from Account record for Account in Field 1.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  4 or 5 numeric characters Category code. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REPAYMENT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REPAYMENT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REPAYMENT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REVERSAL.MARKER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates that the Entry is the reversal of a previous Entry with the same Transaction code.  Amounts and volumes of Entries accumulated for charging and MIS purposes will be reduced.  (There is no system checking between a reversal Entry and the original Entry.)</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  R or blank (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMOUNT.DEAL.CCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.ENTRY.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A unique key by which the Entry may be identified. It is generated by the system, based on the date, system user number and time (in hundredths of a second) at which the transaction is input and a sequence number.</p>
                <p>  The key is made up as follows: (a) 5 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st December 1967.</p>
                <p>  (b) 5 digit user number, the system user number of the inputter. First introduced in release G8.1.00</p>
                <p>  (c) Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers and (usually) 2 decimals. If the time is an exact number of seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted.</p>
                <p>  (d) Sequence number. If a transaction generates several Entries, all the Entries have parts (a) (b) and (c) the same and are distinguished from each other by their Sequence numbers.</p>
                <p>  The Forward Entry key is made up as follows F Prefix YYYYMMDD Value date . Decimal point TTTTT Seconds since midnight S Sequence Number</p>
                <p>  Consolidated STMT.ENTRY:</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  If consolidated statement entries as a result of the CONSOLIDATE.ENT being set in ACCOUNT or CATEGORY record , then the statement entries are consolidated by the following consolidation criteria:</p>
                <p>  Entry Type</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  Account Number or P&amp;L category</p>
                <p>  Currency</p>
                <p>  System Id</p>
                <p>  Transaction Code</p>
                <p>  Value Date</p>
                <p>  Exposure Date</p>
                <p>  Reversal Marker</p>
                <p>  Currency Market</p>
                <p>  Suspense Category</p>
                <p>  Terminal Number</p>
                <p>  Account Officer (P&amp;L only)</p>
                <p>  Product Category (P&amp;L only)</p>
                <p>  Plus any additional elements defined in AC.CONSOLIDATE.COND</p>
                <p>  The combined key is structured as follows, the &amp;#8220;!&amp;#8221; character is used as a delimeter, for example a consolidated entry from the FT application may look like:</p>
                <p>  S!12345678!GBP!FT!210!20021126!!!1!!89</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A multivalue field linking together all the Statement Entry records and Category Entry records generated at the same time by the same transaction/deal.</p>
                <p>  The keys to the Statement Entry file (STMT.ENTRY) and the Category Entry file (CATEG.ENTRY) are made up of 2 parts, Statement Number and Sequence Number.</p>
                <p>  If a transaction generates several Entries, all the Entries have the same Statement Number, the Entries on the same file are distinguished from each other by their Sequence Numbers.</p>
                <p>  The Statement Number consists of:</p>
                <p>  1. 4 digit date expressed as the number of days since 31st December 1967.</p>
                <p>  2. Time in seconds since midnight, consisting of 5 integers and (usually) 2 decimals. If the time is an exact number of seconds since midnight, the decimals are omitted.</p>
                <p>  The Sequence number is a 4 digit number from 0001 to 9999.</p>
                <p>  Every Entry generated by the same transaction/deal has the same values in Fields 26.1 to 26.3.</p>
                <p>  Field 26.1 contains the Statement Number which is the first part of the key for all the Statement Entries and Category Entries.</p>
                <p>  Field 26.2 contains the range of Sequence Numbers used for the Statement Entries. If there are no Statement Entries, this field will be blank.</p>
                <p>  Field 26.3 contains the range of Sequence Numbers used for the Category Entries. If there are no Category Entries, this field will be blank.</p>
                <p>  Example:</p>
                <p>  If a transaction processed on 3rd June 1986 at 30.5 seconds after 11.15 a.m. generates 3 Statement Entries and 2 Category Entries -</p>
                <p>  The Statement Number is 672940530.50 made up as follows -</p>
                <p>  Date 6729 Time 40530.50</p>
                <p>  The Entries generated have the following Ids -</p>
                <p>  Statement Entries Category Entries</p>
                <p>  672940530.500001 672940530.500001 672940530.500002 672940530.500002 672940530.500003</p>
                <p>  All the Entries have the following values in Fields 26.1 to 26.3 -</p>
                <p>  Field 26.1 672940530.50 Field 26.2 1-3 (3 Statement Entries) Field 26.3 1-2 (2 Category Entries)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  For the consolidated statement entry, the field will the number of statement entries consolidated under that consolidated id</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT1.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT2.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUPPRESS.POSITION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether the entry should be considered when calculating the effect on the Position file.</p>
                <p>  The accounting system will maintain positions automatically where suppression is not indicated.  The statement and CRF entries passed to the accounting program will be totalled by currency, and a position against the local currency will be raised for the net amount in each currency.  Category entries will only be considered when suppression is set to "C".</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  "Y" or "C"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUSPENSE.CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The suspense category to be used for split value dated transactions.</p>
                <p>  When a split value dated transaction is processed in a value dated accounting system then the first 'leg' will be balanced against a suspense account.  This will be washed out when the second leg reaches value date.  The suspense account that is used is determined by the category of the second leg entry.</p>
                <p>  This category code is derived from the SUS.CATEGORY in the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER file for the PRODUCT.CATEGORY of the entry being suspensed.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Numeric 10000 - 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUSPNSE.VALUE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The value date of the entry if the entry has been suspensed in a value dated accounting system.</p>
                <p>  If value dated accounting is in operation (field 2 VALUE.DATED.ACCTNG on the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER file is set to 'Y'), then any transactions entered from applications capable of value dated accounting (currently Funds Transfer, Data Capture, Teller, and Foreign Exchange), that generate split value dated entries will have this field updated.  The value date will indicate the latest value date of entry pairs.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Standard Date format. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the system by which the Entry was generated and the file from which further details may be obtained.</p>
                <p>  The following is a list of possible codes and the corresponding files containing further details:-</p>
                <p>  SYSTEM ID APPLICATION Interest and Charges IC1 STMT.ACCT.CH IC2 STMT.ACCT.CR IC3 STMT.ACCT.CR2 IC4 STMT.ACCT.DR IC5 STMT.ACCT.DR2</p>
                <p>  Foreign Exchange FX FOREX</p>
                <p>  Funds Transfer FT FUNDS.TRANSFER SYSTEM ID APPLICATION Loans and Money Market MM MM.MONEY.MARKET MMP LMM.PAYMENT.ENTRY MMR LMM.RECEIPT.ENTRY MMA LMM.ADJUSTMENT.ENTRY</p>
                <p>  Data Capture DC DATA.CAPTURE</p>
                <p>  Securities SC SC.BUY.SELL SC FORWARD.TRADE SC POSITION.TRANSFER SC SECURITY.TRANSFER SC OPT.PURCHASE.SALES SC OPT.OPTION.TAKEUP SCBD REDEMPTION.BAL SCBL BOND.LENT.MASTER SCCP DIV.POST.CHECK SCCI CAPTL.INCREASE.DET SCNI NI.ADMIN.MASTER SCSF SAFEKEEP.DET SCSD STOCK.DIV.DET Others STMT.ENTRY</p>
                <p>  Consolidated STMT.ENTRY</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  For the consolidated statement entry, the field will contain the system id followed by NET</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TAX.EXCH.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>THEIR.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reference given to the transaction/deal by the Customer/correspondent bank, e.g. Their reference for SWIFT, cheque serial number.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Up to 16 type S (upper-case alpha or numeric) characters. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMOUNT.FCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For Entries over foreign Currency Accounts, this field contains the Amount of the Entry in the Currency of the Account.  Not used in Entries over local Currency Accounts.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point (standard amount format, type AMT) signed, or blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRADE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>An optional trade date field that can be supplied. This will be used to store a trade dated balance adjustment in a new field in ACCT.ACTIVITY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANS.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the reference number by which the originating transaction may be accessed in the front end Application system which generated the Entry .</p>
                <p>  For most systems this is the same as OUR REFERENCE (Field 17), but not for systems like Data Capture where Our Reference is an input field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  Consolidated STMT.ENTRY</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  For the consolidated statement entry, the field will contain NET-consolidated id</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANSACTION.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the type of transaction.  The code is used to determine what references and narratives will be printed on statements and for M.I.S. and charging details.</p>
                <p>  The TRANSACTION table contains details such as Description, SWIFT Narrative and M.I.S. information.</p>
                <p>  The standard Narrative for each Transaction code which appears on account statements is specified in the DELIVERY system.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
                <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
                <p> (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VALUE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The date on which the entry is to be given value for interest purposes.  Not used for Entries over Internal Accounts.</p>
                <p>  If the Value Date is not entered in the originating transaction, a default date may be generated by the system depending on rules specified in the application or the Transaction code record.</p>
                <p>  If it is neither input nor generated, the Value Date is assumed to be the same as the BOOKING DATE, Field 25.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Standard date format or blank. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMOUNT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the amount of the Entry expressed in Local Currency.</p>
                <p>  This field is present in all Entries, including those over foreign currency Accounts.  If the Local Currency Amount is not entered in the originating transaction, it is generated by the system, using the Rate input or a Rate from the CURRENCY table.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus decimal point (standard amount format, type AMT), signed. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
         <t>
            <field>POS.EXP.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>  This date will be updated only for the entries raised for Position Accounts.</p>
                <p>  Refers to the date on which the Position will be afected.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  1-14 numeric characters plus decimal point (standard amount format, type AMT), signed. (Internal file, no input.)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        
    <t><field>ACCOUNT.NO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACCOUNT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACCT.SEL</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACCOUNT.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACCOUNT.SEL</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>FWD.ACCT.IDS</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>STATEMENT.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INTERNAL.CATEGORY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACCOUNT.NUM</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INCLUDE.LIQ.INT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>SELECT.ACCOUNT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>STMT.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>STMT.FREQ</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INCLUDE.FWD.ENT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>SHOW.NARRATIVE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>APPL.DRILLDOWN</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>LONG.POS.SIGN</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DRAFT.PAYEE.NAME</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ENTRY.IDS</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>RMB1.ACCOUNT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>NO.OF.ENTRIES</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>MAX.HISTORY.MONTHS</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TXN.DATA</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>IN.START.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>IN.END.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>PROCESS.FORWARD</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACCT.VB.NO</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACCT.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>INCL.SUB.ACCT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>SHOW.REVERSAL</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TXN.DATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>AA.SUSPENSE.REF</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t>
    <t>
            <field>CUS.PL.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>  This field holds the customer account number related to the entry.</p>
                <p>  For TAX accounting entry this field will hold the debit customer account number and based on the setup in INTERCO.PARAMETER when booking TAX at customer company is turned on for this entry account's category (Internal Tax Account category)  then entry has to be booked in the company of this account.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  Customer account number populated by the transaction applications </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
         <t>
            <field>TDGL.DETAILS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>  Multi-value field to hold the details of the accounting set-up and additional details applied to the entry</p>
                <p>  TDGL.DETAILS.1 will hold the accounting set-up as 'TDGL' when the entry is under trade dated general ledger accounting. </p>
                <p>  TDGL.DETAILS.2 will hold the target account (Nostro or Customer's account) passed by the underlying application for suspense payable or receivable under actual settlement. </p>
                <p>  TDGL.DETAILS.3 will hold the third party counterparty passed by the underlying application(the customer id of the broker, applicable for actual and contractual settlement). </p>
                <p>  TDGL.DETAILS.4 will hold the value 'OFFSET' which is a flag to indicate if the entry is the offsetting entry for an actual settlement </p>
                <p>  TDGL.DETAILS.5 will hold the value 'USE.PAY.REC' as a flag to indicate that USE.PAY.RECEIVE has been applied to the entry </p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No input field -Updated by system </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
         <t>
            <field>ADD.DETAIL.NAME</field>
            <desc>
            	<p>  Multi-value field to hold the additional details in STMT.ENTRY that is passed through the Soft Accounting Mechanism. </p>
                <p>  The Information in this field is the Name of the Additional Detail Field that is passed from Soft Accounting. </p>
                <p>  The Information to be populated in this field is passed through soft accounting entry mapping provided in AC.POSTING.DETAIL.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No input field </p>
                <p>  Upto 35 characters - Type S (can hold Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
         <t>
            <field>ADD.DETAIL.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
            	<p>  Multi-value field to hold the additional values in STMT.ENTRY that is passed through the Soft Accounting Mechanism. </p>
            	<p>  ADD.DETAIL.VALUE is associated with ADD.DETAIL.NAME </p>
            	<p>  The Information to be populated in this field is passed as sub-value associated with ADD.DETAIL.NAME through soft accounting entry mapping provided in AC.POSTING.DETAIL.</p>
                <p>  Validation Rules</p>
                <p>  No input field </p>
                <p>  Upto 35 characters - Type S (can hold Uppercase alpha or numeric) characters </p>
            </desc>
        </t>                  
		<t><field>RC.DETAIL.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
