<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>STO.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table will be used to define the eight Standing Order types which are covered within the Standing Order Application.  The only purpose of this file is to allow the User to define Descriptions in various languages for each one of the eight types.  This table will be used by the Standing Order main Application and needs, therefore, to be created before starting to load Standing Order instructions. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>USER.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.DELIVERY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides a default value for the field DAYS.DELIVERY  in STO for the STO type of STO.This specifies the number of working days to add to the STO frequency date to give the value date of a standing order.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the Standing Order Type and is used to provide the enrichment of the code. </p>
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the standing order type in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the Language table and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 35 type A (Alphanumeric) characters Multilanguage field. Multivalue field. (Mandatory Input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STO.ORDER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the type of the Standing Order. </p>
            <p>The eight different types of Standing Order must be defined in the same format as described below.  These types have been hardcoded in the program and any other code will be refused by the Application. </p>
            <p>The following values will be accepted: </p>
            <p>Balance Management Standing Order Types </p>
            <p>BI        Balance Maintenance In.  An account is to            be maintained at a minimum balance level            and Payments In needs to be effected when            the balance is below the specified balance. </p>
            <p>BO      Balance Maintenance Out.  An account to be            maintained at a maximum balance level and            that Payments Out need to be effected when            the balance is in excess of the specified            balance. </p>
            <p>BP      Principal amount on the account paid out.            A fixed term savings account that needs to            pay out the balance on the account at the            end of its term can use this type. </p>
            <p>Regular Payments Standing Order Types </p>
            <p>FI        The customer has given instructions to the            bank to pay on a regular basis a Fixed            amount by the debit of one of his accounts. </p>
            <p>PP      The customer has authorised the bank to            pay bills from third parties upon            presentation of these bills.  The amount,            for this type of Standing Order is unknown. </p>
            <p>PPI     The customer gives instructions to the             bank to pay away any interest capitalised             on a savings account to another account. </p>
            <p>Diary Standing Order Types </p>
            <p>DIARY Used to define any type of Diary              instructions on a specific account. </p>
            <p>Direct Debit Standing Order Type </p>
            <p>DD     The bank has a direct debit mandate from            the Customer which authorises the bank to            accept direct debits received on the            Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 5 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters as defined in Details.  Any other value will be refused. (Mandatory input. No default.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field is used to specify the events for which delivery message has to be generated for a STANDING.ORDER. Events like modification, cancellation or expiry of a STO record could be setup here to generate advices. When this is left blank, the default delivery advice would be generated only during creation or modification of a standing order record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Valid values are AMEND, EXPIRY, CANCEL, ALL or blank</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROC.DATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the STO.TYPE supports generation of FUNDS TRANSFER from STANDING.ORDER, 'n' days prior to the Frequency Date as mentioned in DAYS.PRIOR</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input</p>            
            <p>   Valid values are CVD and Blank</p>
            <p>   Allowed only when DAYS.PRIOR is entered</p>                        
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.PRIOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the number of days prior to the frequency date, on which the FT is to be generated</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Optional input</p>
            <p>   Valid values are nW, nC and Blank, where 'n' stands for the number of days</p>
            <p>   Allowed only when PROC.DATE.TYPE is entered</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEN.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field is used to specify the events for which delivery message has to be generated for a STANDING.ORDER. Events like modification, cancellation or expiry of a STO record could be setup here to generate advices. When this is left blank, the default delivery advice would be generated only during creation or modification of a standing order record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Valid values are AMEND, EXPIRY, CANCEL, ALL or blank</p>
            </p>
            <p>Optional field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.STP</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specifiy if the FUNDS.TRANSFER record generated via STO processing should be put on hold or should this be created immediately. If this is set to YES, then, FT would be put on hold for user modification else FT would be generated immediately and authorised by system automatically.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Valid values are YES OR left blank</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FT.VERSION</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specify the FUNDS.TRANSFER version to be used while generating the FT from STO.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Should be a valid ID in the VERSION table and the version should be for FUNDS.TRANSFER application.</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FT.TXN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specify the FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION id. If given this would be defaulted in the STO that is created for this sto type.</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Should be a valid ID in the file FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION.</p>
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PO.PRD.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specify the PAYMENT.ORDER.PRODUCT id. If defined, then the respective version record will be defaulted in the STO record when the STO type is used</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Input allowed only when PI product is installed else this will be a NOINPUT field.</p> 
            <p>Should be a valid record in the file PAYMENT.ORDER.PRODUCT</p>                       
	        <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PO.VERSION</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field is used to specify the PAYMENT.ORDER version to be used while generating the Payment Order from STO when SUPPRESS.FT is set to PAYMENT</p>
        <p>
            <p>Validation Rules: </p>
            <p>Input allowed only when PI product is installed else this will be a NOINPUT field.</p>            
            <p>Must be valid Payment order version record</p>            
            <p>Optional field</p>            
        </p>        
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>
