<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AC</product>
<table>STO.BULK.CODE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table will enable the User to load, in a central place, specific details on the most frequently used Standing Orders.  These details concern the: </p>
            <p>      .Beneficiary       .Beneficiary account number       .Account with banks       .Bank sort code </p>
            <p>If, for example, many customers have given the bank Standing Order instructions in favour of the same beneficiary,(eg the annual subscription to the AA or RAC), the User will wish to define in this table these common beneficiaries to avoid the repetitive input and the risk of error in specifying the content of four fields in each Standing Order record.  The input of the Bulk Code number in the Standing Order record will then be sufficient to automatically generate the value of these four data elements. </p>
            <p>This table is not mandatory to run the Standing Order Application but is provided as an additional facility to the User. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>BULK.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the ID by which the Bulk code will be identified. </p>
            <p>This field represents the ID which will be input in the Standing Order record.  The values defined in the next four fields will then be automatically generated in any Standing Order record where the ID is input. </p>
            <p>When defining the ID, the User should, whenever possible, choose characters which will facilitate the identification of the Bulk code. </p>
            <p>Examples could be: </p>
            <p>           AA : for Automobile Association            RAC: for Royal Automobile Club, etc. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 to 10 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.WITH.BANK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Bank where the Beneficiary maintains his Account. </p>
            <p>If an input of less than 10 characters has been made by the User, the System will check against the Agency file to see if the input corresponds to a valid Agent.  If this is the case, the short name of the Agent will be displayed and any expansion of the multivalue field will be refused.  If the input does not correspond to a valid Agent, the System will then allow the User to expand the field to enter further information. </p>
            <p>For BACS payments, this field will define the bank to whom payment is to be made and is only used for Standing Order statement purposes to print the name of the bank and branch to whom payment is to be made. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Multivalue field. A maximum of 4 lines of 35 characters each will be allowed. (Optional Input; No Default Value.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.SORT.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Bank Sorting Code of the bank and branch to whom the payment is to be sent.  It is only applicable to the BAC payments. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>6 numeric characters. (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>For the time being, any number of 6 numeric characters will be accepted without any further validation.  No enrichment will be displayed after the input of the code.  This bank sorting code is only used in United Kingdom for the BACS payments.</p>
            <p>In Standing Order records, this field will be mandatory when the Pay Method selected is equal to BC.  For all other Pay Methods, any value in this Field will be refused.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY.ACCTNO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Account Number of the beneficiary Account. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 34 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters . (Optional input.) When the Bulk code is used in a Standing Order instruction where the Pay Method is equal to BC, this field will be accepted in the Standing Order instruction only if it is 8 characters in length (allowing for preceding zeros).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BENEFICIARY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Beneficiary name and address of the Standing Order. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 to 18 type S (uppercase alpha or numeric) characters. Multivalue Field. A maximum of 4 lines of 18 characters each will be allowed. (Mandatory input.) When the Bulk code is used in a Standing Order instruction where the Pay Method equals BC, only one line will be accepted in the Funds Transfer transaction and the maximum number of characters in that line is 18.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

