<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>ATM</product>
        <title>ATM.TERMINAL.ACCT </title>
        <table>ATM.TERMINAL.ACCT</table>
    </header>
  <overview>
    <ovdesc>
      <p>ATM.TERMINAL.ACCT</p>
      <p>
      </p>
      <p>The ATM terminal/POS machine ID details are stored in this file. This file stores information on Accounts to be used for transaction, by transaction type or the default accounts and also captures which branch and Company in T24 the terminal/POS machine belongs to. Id of each record is universally agreed and is passed to T24 by the ISO Message.</p>

    </ovdesc>
    <ovimage>
    </ovimage>
  </overview>  
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Description for the table, free field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROC.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains different Processing codes, required for dispensing cash via ATM Terminal or for approving POS transactions. The different transaction codes are defined in table ATM.PROCESSING.CODE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCT.CCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Currency code. No input field, system defaulted value based on the account mentioned in the PAY/RECV Accounts.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAY.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Debit account for the specific currency mentioned above. This account is used if USE.DEF.ACCT is set to No.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RECV.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Credit account for the specific currency mentioned above. This account is used if USE.DEF.ACCT is set to No.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>ACCT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to indicate what role the terminal/machine plays for the processing code. The terminal ID might be the same but processing can be done both for cash withdrawal and POS transactions. So this field will indicate the role or the type of transaction attached to the processing code. The value for the field is provided in the lookup table ATM.PROC.ACCT.TYPE. The existing set of records are provided in the list available in Data records section. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>DEF.PAY.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Debit account to be used for transactions.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>DEF.PAY.ACCT.CCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Currency of the debit account. No-input field, system defaults the currency of the DEF.PAY.ACCT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>DEF.RECV.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Credit account to be used for transactions.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>DEF.RECV.ACCT.CCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Currency of the Credit account. No-input field, system defaults the currency of the DEF.RECV.ACCT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>DEF.ACCT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to indicate what role/s the terminal/machine for transactions using the default account type</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>USE.DEF.ACCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If set to YES, account stored in DEF.PAY.ACCT or DEF.RECV.ACCT will be used. If set to NO, account stored based on currency and the processing code will be proceeded(which is from PAY.ACCT or RECV.ACCT)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>CUSTOMER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field to capture the T24 customer number linked to the terminal/POS ID. For information purpose only</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field stores the Company Code where the ATM terminal belongs.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>LOCAL.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use for local references</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RESERVED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved fields for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		        

</menu>
</t24help>
