<t24help>
  <header>
    <product>ATM</product>
    <title>ATM.PARAMETER</title>
    <table>ATM.PARAMETER</table>
  </header>
  <overview>
    <ovdesc>
      <p>ATM.PARAMETER</p>
      <p>
      </p>
      <p>This is the parameter table for ATM </p>
      <p>The id should be SYSTEM. </p>
    </ovdesc>
    <ovimage>
    </ovimage>
  </overview>
  <menu>
     <t>
      <field>BANK.IMD</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is a mandatory field which stores the unique IMD for the bank for the ATM </p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>NETWORK.IMD</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is an Optional field which is used to include the network groups(IMD) in bank own network (apart from BANK.IMD value).</p>
       </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>FILE.TYPE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Stores the name of the file type used for processing balances like VISA PROCESS, BALANCE FILE</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>FILE.NAME</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This will store the file name that is used to upload the balances before EOD</p>      
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>FILE.PATH</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is the path where the balance upload file is to be stored</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>DAYS.IN.HIST</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Days before the log file are to be archived</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
   	<t>
      <field>OFS.USER</field>
      <desc>
        <p>User Sign on to be used by OFS.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>OFS.PASSWORD</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Password of the user entered above.</p>
	  </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>DEF.ATM.BRANCH</field>
      <desc>
        <p>If Terminal Id was not configured for every terminal in ATM.TERMINAL.ACCT, then default Terminal id stored here will be taken and processed.</p>
      </desc> 
    </t>
    
	<t>
      <field>DEF.ATM.BIN</field>
      <desc>
        <p>If Other Bank Bin was not configured for every terminal in ATM.TERMINAL.ACCT, then default bin stored here will be taken and processed.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
      
	  	<t>
      <field>DEF.POS.MRCNT</field>
      <desc>
        <p>If any Bank owned POS device id for every device was not configured in ATM.TERMINAL.ACCT, then default device id stored here will be taken and processed.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
    <t>
      <field>DEF.POS.BIN</field>
      <desc>
        <p>If Other Bank Pos Device Id for every device was not configured in ATM.TERMINAL.ACCT, then default device id stored here will be taken and processed.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
    <t>
      <field>CHG.CCY.POS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Currency position for raising charge entries</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
    <t>
      <field>TXN.CCY.POS</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Currency position for raising charge entries</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
    <t>
      <field>MSG.ID</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This is a mandatory field stores the type of ISO Message format used for validating the incoming requests. IF 5002 is set, then BASE24 based Messages can be posted. If 5003 is set, then standard ISO Messages can be posted. If 5004 is set, then PHOENIX based messages can be posted. </p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
    <t>
      <field>UNIQUE.ID</field>
      <desc>
        <p>ISO Message Fields will be stored here. Data from these fields will be generated as Unique Id for each transaction.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>GEN.COM.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Default Company Code.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>LOCK.PERIOD</field>
      <desc>
        <p>For Authorization request transactions, the lock period mentioned will be used for locking the amount. User has to input it as e.g.:+10C.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
	
    <t>
      <field>DUAL.TXN.ID</field>
      <desc>
        <p>ISO Message Fields will be stored here .Unique id for releasing the locked amount and raising accounting entry. Customized routine can also be attached here</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>CHG.OFS.SOURC</field>
      <desc>
        <p>OFS SOURCE stored here can be used for raising charges or can be used in any customized hook routines for raising Separate Transactions.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>ATM.GEN.MSG.ID</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field stores the type of ISO Message format used for initiating ISO Message from T24 side.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>ATM.GEN.API.ID</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field stores java EB.API for connecting to switch.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>PHX.BAL.FMT.TYPE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field used only in PHOENIX Interface. If ACTUAL is set, then Actual Balance alone will be sent for all transactions. If AVAILABLE is set, then Available Balance alone will be sent for all transactions. If BOTH is set, Actual and Available balance will be sent for all transactions.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>LOG.TYPE</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Stores whether the log type is DUMP or LOG4J.Allowed values are stored on the lookup files for ATM.LOG.TYPE </p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>LOG.RTN</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This routine will be called from within the log message routine. Any additional processing required can be handled through this routine. For future use</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>LOG.PATH</field>
      <desc>
        <p> Stores the file path where the incoming ISO requests are stored.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>AMT.FMT</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field is used for formatting the amount to be returned in ISO Response Message. The formats are specified in EB.LOOKUP for ATM.FMT. The balance amount being processed for statement generation will use add the credit/debit indicators as mentioned in the format</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>AMT.LENGTH</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Provides the length of the amount field which will be returned in ISO Response message. </p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>REQ.VERSION</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Valid version used for online bill payments needs to be provided.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>REQ.MAPPING</field>
      <desc>
        <p>Valid INTRF.MAPPING record created for ONLINE bill payments need to be inputted.</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
  </menu>
</t24help>
