<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>ATM</product>
        <title>INTRF.MESSAGE</title>
        <table>INTRF.MESSAGE</table>
    </header>
  <overview>
    <ovdesc>
      <p>The application holds the skeleton of the ISO message that will be processed in the system. It captures the details like, field position in the ISO message, field length, field properties and field name in ISO message. It also holds information on the logic to be formed to calculate the mapping record to be used for an instance, the conversion logic to be used for translating the data, etc</p>
    </ovdesc>
    <ovimage>
    </ovimage>
  </overview>    
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Description for the table, free field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>TRACK.FILE.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Routine attached to this field will be called in the pre-processing routine to perform any additional processing on the ISO message before being processed by the pre-processing routine attached to OFS</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.PRE.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field hold routine name. Routine attached here should have one argument value passed. Customized hook routines can be attached here for pre-mapping validations.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>MAPPING.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the values for forming INTRF.MAPPING data record Id. A routine can be attached here or data values i.e. ISO‖ 0 3 70 (In different multi-values) can be stored here</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.HEAD.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Interface specific Header name. In reference to ISO to be used as names in the specification. Ex: Message Type Indicator. If no header is used. This field can be left as null</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.HEAD.DELIM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.HEAD.POS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Header position. Represents Header field numbers. If no header is used. This field can be left as null</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.HEAD.LEN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Length of the field. If no header is used. This field can be left as null</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.HEAD.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field type in case of ISO ex: FIXED, VARIABLE, BITMAP. If no header is used. This field can be left as null</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.HEAD.S.M</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.HEAD.MAND</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>NTRF.FLD.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Interface specific field name. In reference to ISO to be used as names in the specification. Ex: Message Type Indicator</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.FLD.DELIM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.FLD.POS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field position. Represents ISO field numbers in case ISO Messages.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.FLD.LEN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Length of the field (Max length in case of ISO)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.FLD.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field type in case of ISO ex: FIXED,VARIABLE,BITMAP</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.FLD.S.M</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.FLD.MAND</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>TXN.FIELD.POS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a multivalve set. ATM.TRANSACTION field positions are mapped here. Customized hook routines can be attached here for updating the fields in ATM.TRANSACTION.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>MV.RESERVED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>INTRF.POST.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field hold routine name. Routine attached here should have one argument value passed. Customized hook routines can be attached here for post-mapping validations.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>MSG.FORMAT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates which type of transaction for which the record is created. i.e. ISO_BASE24_PHOENIX</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>LOCAL.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use for local references</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RESERVED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved fields for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		
</menu>
</t24help>
