<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>ATM</product>
        <title>INTRF.MAPPING</title>
        <table>INTRF.MAPPING</table>
    </header>
  <overview>
    <ovdesc>
      <p>This is a mapping file, which stores various details like T24 application, user name, password, version to be used and mapping between each message field to its T24 application field.  This table will hold the information that will be used for transforming the ISO message to OFS. Multiple options are provided in this table with provision to attach hook routines in multiple places. This helps in customizing the incoming request according to each specific requirement</p>
    </ovdesc>
    <ovimage>
    </ovimage>
  </overview>    
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Description for the table, free field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MSG.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Informative field displays whether the mapping is for Request, Response or Error</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DELIMITER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future Use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UPLOAD.PATH</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future Use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>PRE.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a multivalve set. Customized Hook Routine can be attached here and can be triggered to perform any additional functionality needed to be executed within the Transaction</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>APPLICATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Valid T24 application</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>OFS.FUNCTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the OFS function for be performed while forming the OFS Request</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>OFS.OPERATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the Processing Flag of either PROCESS or VALIDATE. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>OFS.UTIL.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will hold the version name or enquiry name to be used by OFS.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>COMP.COD.MODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates which company the transaction has hit, the customer account company or the company to which the ATM machine is attached. This field holds the value CUST or ATM. .</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>OFS.COM.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds routine which loads the Company. If CUST is selected in above field, then Company Id is loaded based on customer account. If ATM is selected, then Company Id is loaded based on Company code configured in Terminal
</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ID.GEN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Will accept Y or N contains information about the id of the application being updated by OFS.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>OFS.USER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User Sign on to be used by OFS.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>OFS.PASSWORD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Password of the user entered above.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RES.MAP.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Response mapping id for the request</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.FLD.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a multivalve set. Interface field name (Part of the message, descriptive) is provided here.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>INTRF.FLD.PS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Position of this field within the message.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>GLO.FLD.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Corresponding T24 application field name given in OFS Format, ie, Field name as per the Standard selection record concatenated by Value marker number and sub value marker number, separated by ‘:’. Eg, ACCOUNT.NUMBER:1:1</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>GLO.FLD.LN.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Length of the field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>GLO.CONSTANT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the value to be passed to this T24 field is a constant, data should be entered here.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>FIELD.SOURCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will decide whether the value to be passed is a constant or a part of the message data element or external or should be arrived through a routine. Allowed values are listed below
				i)	INT
				ii)	EXT
				iii)	RTN
				iv)	CON
				v)	ENQ.SEL
				vi)	ENQ.VAL
		</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>FIELD.SRC.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will hold the routine name if a routine is specified in FIELD.SOURCE. Customized routines can be attached here for passing the value to the GLO.FLD.NAME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RES.Y.N</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the value of Y or N decides Currently not used. For future use .</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ERROR.CONV.TAB</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use in error mapping</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>TYPE.OF.TXN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the value of ENQ or FIN decides whether the transaction is Financial or Enquiry. Mandatory field for non-financial request mapping record with value as ENQ.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>TXN.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MESSAGE.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>To capture the INTRF.MESSAGE records which support/use the mapping record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	<t>
            <field>LOCAL.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use for local references</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RESERVED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved fields for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		        

</menu>
</t24help>
