<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>ACCOUNT.STATEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The purpose of this table is to specify the dates and frequencies for producing Account statements.</p><p>   Statements may be produced daily (every working day), every 1-9 weeks, twice a month (on the 15th and the last day of the month) or every 1-12 months on any day of the month.</p><p>   Upto 9  statement cycles may be specified for each Account, and each statement cycle is independent.</p><p>   Statements for each cycle show details of all entries since the last statement in the same cycle, regardless of the other cycle.</p><p>   Within a Statement cycle, it is possible to define multiple frequencies say a combination of  Weekly and Monthly, such that Statements are produced on the dates specified by both frequencies, but only contain details of entries since the last statement in that  cycle. For example, if in Cycle 3, a frequency of Weekly (with next statement date: 6th) and Monthly (next statement date: 10th) is defined, then statement for Cycle 3 would be generated on 6th and again on 10th with entries from 7th to 10th.</p><p>   If there have been no entries since the last statement, the statement may be suppressed; In such cases when there are no movements, it is possible to print the statements after a specified period defined in  AC.STMT.PARAMETER (Field: MIN.MONTHS.STMT) has elapsed. Such a  facility to suppress statement printing is available for each cycle.</p><p>   For each Cycle, special interim statements, showing details of all entries since the last regular cycle  statement, may be produced without affecting the regular statement cycles. In such a case, the next regular statement in the cycle would contain the entries since the special interim statement.</p><p>   If the account has a passbook then no regular statements are produced - the passbook is viewed as the statement. In this case ACCOUNT.STATEMENT simply holds details regarding the passbook balance &amp; the next available line.</p><p>   This table is also used to specify whether or not advices are to be produced when interest and charges are applied, and whether detailed interest statements (interest scale) should be produced.</p><p>   Whenever a new Account is opened, an Account Statement record is automatically generated by the system. This record specifies only one Statement Cycle. Interest and charges advices, interest statements and other details are set to the values defined in AC.STMT.PARAMETER if present, otherwise they are set to 'NO'. If required, the details in this record can be changed manually.</p><p>   The frequency of the first Statement Cycle generated automatically by the system depends on the Statement Group to which the Account belongs. This is determined by the rules defined in the Statement General Condition table (STMT.GEN.CONDITION). These rules are based on Customer and Account details such as Residence, Sector and Account Category. The frequency may be Daily (every working day), Weekly, or every n (1-9) Weeks, Monthly, Every n Months, Quarterly, Six Monthly or Yearly and the first date is calculated by adding the frequency to the date on which the Account is opened. For Daily statements, the first date is the date on which the Account is opened.</p><p>   If the details of the Account and Customer records do not match any of the STMT.GEN.CONDITION records, the default Statement Cycle frequency is Monthly.</p><p>   Internal Accounts always have a default Statement Cycle frequency of monthly.</p><p>   Delivery:</p><p /><p>   Account Type </p><p>     Cycle No. Application Component of </p><p>   DE.PRODUCT</p><p>   ID</p><p>   Customer accounts</p><p>   1 to 9 ACC1 to ACC9 Nostro  accounts  1 to 9 ACN1 to ACN9 Internal  accounts 1 to 9 ACI1 to ACI9 </p><p>   For example, for Nostro Account No. 19739, Statement Cycle No.5 and Message Type 950, a </p><p>   DE.PRODUCT record could be specified with ID:  US0010001.A-19739.950.ACN5 (where US0010001 is the ID of COMPANY). </p><p /><p>   Above referred definition of DE.PRODUCT records  is not mandatory. (For detailed information on  DE.PRODUCT records, refer to the appropriate documentation for   DE.PRODUCT).</p><p /><p>   If  PRINT carrier is specified for an Account Statement Message in   DE.PRODUCT, then the Application Format component of the related Message Type's DE.FORMAT.PRINT record should be  as follows: </p><p /><p> Account Type        </p><p>   Cycle No.          Application Component of DE.FORMAT.PRINT</p><p>    ID </p><p /><p>   Customer accounts</p><p>   1 to 9</p><p>   1 to 9</p><p>   Nostro  accounts  </p><p>   1 to 9</p><p>   11 to 19</p><p>   Internal  accounts  </p><p>   1 to 9</p><p>   21 to 29</p><p /><p>   For example, for a Nostro Account,  Statement Cycle No.5 and Message Type 950 with carrier defined as PRINT in DE.PRODUCT, a DE.FORMAT.PRINT   record should exist  with an ID:  950.15.1.GB. The above referred definition of DE.FORMAT.PRINT key IDs is mandatory. (For detailed  information on DE.FORMAT.PRINT records, refer to the appropriate documentation for DE.FORMAT.PRINT).</p><p /><p>   However, in case of SWIFT (Carrier defined as SWIFT in DE.PRODUCT) messages, since only one format message is allowed per message type, the Application format would be 1, irresepctive of  type of Account and any Cycle No. For example, for SWIFT message type 940, the DE.FORMAT.SWIFT record ID would be 940.1.1, irrespective of any conditions. </p><p /><p>   It would be possible to bypass the Delivery system for specific Statement Message Type's  printed messages. For example, to bypass the Delivery system for printed Message Type  950 (with carrier specified as PRINT in  DE.PRODUCT), 950 should be defined as a  value of  p&gt;PRINT.BYPASS in </p><p>   DE.PARM. However, in this case Messages with Type 950  for which the carrier is SWIFT or TELEX would continue to be processed through the Delivery system. Notes:</p><p>   (i) If Tax Advices are required, this is specified in this record, but the processing must be defined as a local requirement. At present requesting Tax Advices has no effect.</p><p>   (ii) Descriptions of Account Categories and Transaction codes and details of format, address(es) and copies for account statements, interest and charges advices and interest statements are specified within the Delivery system.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FQU2.LAST.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Holds the date when the last  Statement for the cycle was produced.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p><p>   Associated with the fields from STMT.FQU.2 to SW.STMT2.TYP.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.FLOOR.LIMIT</field>
<desc><p>Used in conjunction with the MT942 fields. This value is used for the floor limit indicator for the debit transaction on the Interim Transaction Report, and is used to exclude smaller entries from the message details. On this message when only one value is used, the floor limit applies to both debit and credit amounts. If left blank then a value of zero is used which means all entries are detailed.</p><p /><p>   Where a value entered is 100,000 (for a USD Account) then only entries where the amount is greater than USD 100,000 (debit or credit) are detailed. Smaller entries are only included in the entry totals and count.</p><p>   Incase a value entered in this field as 100,000 (for a USD Account) and in next field (Cr.Floor.Limit) 500,000 is given, then only debit entries where the amount is grater than USD 100,000 &amp; credit entries greater than USD500,000 are detailed. Smaller entries are only included in the entry totals and count. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Optional Input</p><p>   Input allowed only MESSAGE.TYPE = 942 &amp; SEND.MSG.TYPE     ="Y" or when XML.STMT.TYPE is CAMT052 -Otherwise input not allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TIME</field>
<desc><p>MT942 or CAMT052 messages can be generated on an ad-hoc basis (using </p><p>   Messages can only be sent automatically if this field contains data.</p><p>   Input is in the hh:mm format where:</p><p>   hh is the hour (in 24 hour format). Hours of 01 to 09 can also be entered as 1 to 9.</p><p>   mm is the minutes past that hour.</p><p>   The input of </p><p /><p /><p>   945, 0945 or 09:45 all equate to 9:45 am</p><p>   1630 or 16:30 equate to 16:30 pm</p><p>The value in this field will update the concat file DE.MT942.SEND.TIME for MT942 and XML.SENT.TIME for CAMT052 message</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Optional Multi value field </p><p>   Must be valid time format</p><p>   Input allowed only when XML.STMT.TYPE = "CAMT052" or MESSAGE.TYPE = "942" &amp;       SEND.MSG.TYPE ="Y"-Otherwise Not allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.MT942.STMT.NO</field>
<desc><p>The statement number on the last MT942 message sent. This value is incremented on the generation of each MT942 and is reset to zero on the 31 December each year. The first new messages sent on or after 1st Janauary will begin with 1 as per the requirements on S.W.I.F.T.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.STMT2.NO</field>
<desc><p>Hold the last statement number for Statements of this Cycle, sequentially allocated, produced.</p><p>   The Statement numbers for each cycle is independently maintained starting with 1 for the cycle.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   5 numeric characters.   </p><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p><p>   Associated with the fields from STMT.FQU.2 to SW.STMT2.TYP.     </p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.MT941.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Holds the date as reported in the last MT941 in field 62F. This field is updated only when a MT941 statements generated through inward MT920 processing.</p><p>   When MT941 generated through Inward processing of MT920, the Last date and balance details available here &amp; the last date and balance as available for frequency 1 are compared and whichever is earlier  is taken for tag 60F (opening date &amp; opening balance) in MT941 and transaction done after the latest date is taken for processing.</p><p>   The Outward delivery reference related to this statement is available in the respective statement request.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Valid Date format.   </p><p>   This is a NO INPUT field-Update by System.</p><p>   Applicable only for MT941 generated through inward MT920 processing.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IF.NO.MVMT.FQU2</field>
<desc><p>  Specifies whether or not the Statements for  the related cycle, should be printed if there have been no movements over the Account since the last statement for the cycle.</p><p>   If this field contains 'Y', statements will be produced on the dates specified, regardless of whether or not there have been any movements.</p><p>    If there are no movements since last Statement for the cycle, a value of NO in this field will suppress statements unless the minimum period (specified in the field MIN.MONTHS.STMT in AC.STMT.PARAMETER)  has been exceeded. If the field contains 'NO' and MIN.MONTHS.STMT value  is NONE, statements for the cycle will only be produced when the account moves in the period since the last statement for the cycle.</p><p>   This field cannot be input if the account has a passbook.</p><p>   If no value is input in this field for a new cycle, on commiting the record the value defined in the field IF.NO.MOVEMENT in  AC.STMT.PARAMETER would be defaulted in this field.</p><p>   Note: This field has no effect on the production of Special Statements (see SPECIAL.STATEMENT).</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Y(es) or N(o). (Optional input. Default is NO.)</p><p>   Associated with the fields from STMT.FQU.2 to SW.STMT2.TYP.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Date on which statement produced. This is a multivalued field associated with DELIVERY.REF field. The latest date is first. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   11 character standard T24 date field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FQU2.LAST.BAL</field>
<desc><p>Holds the 'balance brought forward' from the last Statement  for the Cycle.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   19 Amount characters.   </p><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p><p>   Associated with the fields from STMT.FQU.2 to SW.STMT2.TYP.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSBOOK.ID</field>
<desc><p>ACCOUNT. STATEMENT</p><p>   PASSBOOK. ID</p><p>   This field will take the Teller. Passbook. id or any other id as input by the user.  The id of course should have been defined in Teller. Passbook application.</p><p>   By default the input in this field would be "System" unless input otherwise.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FQU1.LAST.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Holds the date when the last  Cycle 1 statements was produced.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc><p>Statement handoff ID and message type ID for statements, both being separated by a "-". </p><p>   Multivalued field associated with STATEMENT.DATE. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   46 alphanumeric characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IF.NO.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether or not Cycle 1 Statements should be printed if there have been no movements over the Account since the last statement. </p><p>   If this field contains 'Y', statements will be produced on the dates specified, regardless of whether or not there have been any movements.</p><p>    If there are no movements since last Statement, a value of NO in this field will suppress statements unless the minimum period (specified in the field MIN.MONTHS.STMT in AC.STMT.PARAMETER)  has been exceeded. If the field contains 'NO' and MIN.MONTHS.STMT value  is NONE, statements will only be produced when the account moves in the period since the last statement. </p><p>   An account statement can be produced automtatically on the first Statement date  to serve as confirmation of opening the account. The value of  FIRST.STMT on AC.STMT.PARAMETER will determine whether the first statement is to be printed even when no movement has taken place.</p><p>   This field cannot be input if the account has a passbook.</p><p>   When Account Statement records are generated automatically on Account opening, this field is set to the value defined in AC.STMT.PARAMETER if present, otherwise the field is set to 'NO', but it can subsequently be amended manually if required.</p><p>   Note: This field has no effect on the production of Special Statements (see SPECIAL.STATEMENT).</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Y(es) or N(o). (Optional input. Default is NO.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.MT941.BAL</field>
<desc><p>Holds the balance as reported in the last MT941 in field 62F for the date as available in the previous field.</p><p>   This field is updated only when a MT941 statements generated through inward MT920 processing.</p><p>   When MT941 generated through Inward processing of MT920, the Last date and balance details available here &amp; the last date and balance as available for frequency 1 are compared and whichever is earlier  is taken for tag 60F (opening date &amp; opening balance) in MT941 and all transaction done after the latest statement date is taken for processing.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   19 Amount characters.   </p><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p><p>   Applicable only for MT941 generated through inward MT920 processing.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.MT941.STMT.NO</field>
<desc><p>The statement number on the last MT941 message sent. This value is incremented on the generation of each MT941.</p><p>   This field is updated only when a MT941 statements generated through inward MT920 processing.</p><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SW.STMT2.TYP</field>
<desc><p>  SWIFT message type for the Cycle.</p><p>   Must be one of following:</p><p>   940 Customer statement 941 Balance Report 950 Statement CAMT053 Account Statements CAMT054A Debit/Credit Notification(Payment List) CAMT054B Debit/Credit Notification(Incoming Reference List)</p><p>   If no value is specified,  Statement with Message Type 950  would be generated.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Up to 10 Alpha numerics. Must be defined on DE.MESSAGE or REPORT.CONTROL</p><p>   Associated with the fields from STMT.FQU.2 to SW.STMT2.TYP.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPECIAL.STATEMENT</field>
<desc><p>This field may be used to request a special statement any day for cycle 1 without affecting the regular statements of the  cycle.</p><p>   A statement is produced on the date specified, containing of all entries since the last Cycle 1 statement. The date of the next Cycle 1 statement is not affected. The next regular Cycle 1 statement would contain entries after the Special Statement Date.</p><p>   If the date specified is not a working day, the statement is produced on the previous working day.</p><p>   This field cannot be input if the account has a passbook.</p><p>   Note: Special statements are produced when requested even if there have been no entries since the last Cycle/Statement, regardless of IF.NO.MOVEMENT.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Up to 9 date characters. (Optional input) Cannot be earlier than today's     date.</p><p>   Date cannot be same as any of the regular Cycle 1 Statement Dates     (STMT.FQU.1).</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.FQU.2</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the next date and subsequent frequency for producing the Account Statement for additional statement cycles  (2 to 9).</p><p>   For each cycle, the field could be sub-valued in which case, a  statement  containing entries from the statement last printed in that  frequency cycle,  would be generated for  each sub-valued date.</p><p>   For example, if field 13.1.1 STMT.FQU.2 is 29 JUN 2003 WEEK1 and field 13.1.2 STMT.FQU.2 is 1 JUL 2003 M0101, one statement would be generated for the Second Frequency on 29 JUN 2003 and the next statement would be generated on 1 JUL 2003 containing entries from 30 JUN 2003 to 1 JUL 2003.</p><p>   This field cannot be input if the account has a passbook.</p><p>   The first part of the field specifies the next date on which the  statement for the related cycle  will be produced, the 2nd part specifies the frequency for producing the statements for that cycle.</p><p>   The next date is updated automatically by the system every time a  statement is produced for the cycle. If the next date falls on a non-working day, the statement is produced on the previous working day. The date is then updated as if the statement had been produced on the day specified, i.e. the cycle is not affected.</p><p>   When amending this field manually, if the next date is omitted, the system automatically generates it as follows:</p><p>   FREQUENCY NEXT DATE</p><p>   B(snss) (Every business day) Next     working day after today   </p><p>   T(wmth) (Twice a month, 15th and     last day) The next 15th or month end from today, whichever is sooner   </p><p>   Wn (Every n weeks) n weeks from     today     </p><p>   It is possible to enter the above     frequency options by the letter alone. The date will then default in     accordance with the frequency rules as detailed above, e.g. option 1 would     be the next working day from the system date. It is also possible to input a     frequency with a date.</p><p>   Mnndd (Every nn months on the dd     day)</p><p>   If today's date is less than dd, the next date is day dd in nn months from last month, otherwise it is day dd in nn months form the current month. If this date does not exist (e.g. 30th February) the previous day is assumed (28th or 29th February).</p><p>   Note - Checks are performed to ensure that the  statements are requested for production not more than 12 months from the last requested date or if the account is being opened, the account opening date. Should either of these situations be encountered, it gives ride to an override situation but you may continue subject to being able to satisfy the relevant override class. However, the frequency cannot be more than 12 months.</p><p>   The first Statement in the additional Cycles  would contain entries from the last printed Cycle 1 Statement.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   This field is in two parts: Next Statement Date and a Frequency</p><p>   Next Statement Date: 1-9 Date     characters. Default value calculated by the system depending on the     Frequency.   </p><p>   Frequency :1-5 type SS (uppercase     alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters. The frequency cannot be     longer than 12 months. The next date must not be less than today's date. The     next date may be more than 12 months from the date of the last statement, or     the date of opening the Account if no statements have been produced yet but     is subject to override.</p><p>   This field is mandatory apart from     when an account is indicated as a PASSBOOK account</p><p>   When multi-valued, a frequency of      " BSNSS" could not be duplicated in two sub-values of the     frequency, irrespective of next date.</p><p>   When multi-valued, a frequency of      " Mnndd"  could not be duplicated in two sub-values of the     frequency,  irrespective of next date.</p><p>   Associated with the fields from STMT.FQU.2 to SW.STMT2.TYP.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINT.STMT</field>
<desc><p>This field is inputtable only for Internal Accounts.</p><p /><p>   Yes or Null indicates that the statements will be printed as normal.</p><p>   No indicates that statements will be bypassed.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Yes, No or Null.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CLOSING.ADVICE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether or not an advice should be produced when interest and charges are applied. </p><p>   When Account Statement records are generated automatically on Account opening, this field is set to the value defined in AC.STMT.PARAMETER if present, otherwise the field is set to 'NO', but it can subsequently be amended manually if required. </p><p>   Note:      Details of format, address(es) and copies are specified within the Delivery system. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Y(es) or N(o). (Optional input. Default is NO.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPT.STATEMENT</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether or not statements should include any Customer Narrative entered at the time contracts etc. are input. </p><p>   Some of the transaction processing systems within T24 include the facility to enter one or more lines of Customer Narrative, each 34 characters long.  If this field contains 'Y', the Customer Narrative may be printed on Account Statements, in addition to the standard Transaction Narrative (possibly including a Reference) as defined in the TRANSACTION table and DE.TRANSLATION table. </p><p>   When Account Statement records are generated automatically on Account opening, this field is set to the value defined in AC.STMT.PARAMETER if present, otherwise the field is set to 'NO', but it can subsequently be amended manually if required. </p><p>   This field cannot be input if the account has a passbook. </p><p>   Note: (i)  Details of format, address(es) and copies are specified within the Delivery system.      </p><p>             (ii)  If a single line of Customer Narrative is entered and it is not translatable (i.e. does not start with '::'), it is used for the Additional Narrative in SWIFT statements, regardless of whether this field contains 'Y' or 'NO'.  If this field contains 'NO' the single line of Customer Narrative replaces the standard narrative for printing on Account Statements. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Y(es) or N(o). (Optional input. Default is NO.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FQU1.LAST.BALANCE</field>
<desc><p>Holds the 'balance brought forward' from the last Cycle 1  statement OR the last balance on the passbook.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   19 Amount characters.   </p><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NUMBER</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the Account to which the Statement details in this record apply. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   2-14 numeric character Customer Account number.  6-12 type A (alphanumeric) characters Internal Account number   or 3-10 character Account Mnemonic.  A corresponding record must exist on the ACCOUNT file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONS.SB.PASSBOOK</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether consolidation of entries must happen for a Passbook Savings Account.</p><p>   If the number of transactions during the day after last print in a Passbook Savings account exceeds the number specified in AC.STMT.PARAMETER in field SB.PB.CONS.MAX then the entries would be consolidated and printed as total of Debit and / or Credit entries in the Passbook.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Accepts only the Alpha "YES' or a NULL as a valid input. If input       as "YES" consolidation of entries would happen.</p><p>   Input "YES" would be accepted only if the account category is a savings bank account as classified in table ACCOUNT.CLASS. </p><p>   The account should be a Passbook account as defined in the ACCOUNT table in field PASSBOOK as "Y". </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.FLOOR.LIMIT</field>
<desc><p>Used in conjunction with the MT942 fields. This value is used for the floor limit indicator for the credit transaction on the Interim Transaction Report, and is used to exclude smaller entries from the message details. On this message when only one value is used in the DR.FLOOR.LIMIT, the floor limit applies to both debit and credit amounts. If left blank then a value of zero is used which means all entries are detailed.</p><p /><p>   Incase a value entered in this field as 500,000 (for a USD Account) and in previous field (Dr.Floor.Limit) 100,000 is given, then only debit entries where the amount is grater than USD 100,000 &amp; credit entries greater than USD500,000 are detailed. Smaller entries are only included in the entry totals and count. </p><p>   Amount entered here should not be same as DR.FLOOR.LIMIT- ie In DR.FLOOR.LIMIT &amp; CR.FLOOR.LIMIT cannot be mentioned as 10000.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Optional Input</p><p>   Input allowed only when or when XML.STMT.TYPE is CAMT052 or MESSAGE.TYPE = 942 &amp; SEND.MSG.TYPE     ="Y" -Otherwise input not allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc><p>Holds the currency of the account. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   3 alphabetic characters.</p><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEND.MSG.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Enables the sending of message MT941 (Balance Report) / MT942 (Interim Transaction Report) whether on an ad-hoc or timed daily basis.</p><p>   If set to "Yes" with MESSAGE.TYPE as "942" in the previous field then MT942 message can be generated through  DE.MT942.REQUEST or through Phantom process. If left blank or set to "No"-interim transaction report cannot be generated. Refer "AI" User guide for more details.</p><p>   To generate MT941/MT942 through automatic process on receipt of Inward MT920 (Request Message), specify this field as "STP" with Message type as either 941 or 942 in the previous field. Refer Application Delivery user guide for more details.</p><p>   Applicable value for 941 - "STP' (To generate MT941 through Inward MT920 Processing)</p><p>   Applicable values for 942 - "Yes" (To generate through DE.MT942.REQUEST/Phantom process) , "STP" (To generate MT942 through Inward MT920 processing), "No" (None of the above)</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Optional Input of  STP or Null for 941 &amp; " Y " or " No"  or "STP"     or Null for 942.   </p><p>   Input allowed only when previous field is given either with 941 or 942. </p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREQ.NO</field>
<desc><p>  Specifies the Account Statement Frequency (Cycle) No.  for additional frequencies.</p><p>   Care must be taken when modifying this field. A modification of this field value is equivalent to deleting an existing Statement Cycle  and inserting a new one. For example, if the value is modified from 2 to 3, then the Statements for Cycle 2 would no longer be printed. Statements for Cycle 3 would begin  to be printed from the next cycle date, containing  entries from the last printed Cycle 1 Statement.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Mandatory field.</p><p>   Should be a value from 2 to 9.</p><p>   Should not be duplicated.</p><p>   Associated with the fields from STMT.FQU.2 to SW.STMT2.TYP.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.SCALE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether or not a detailed interest statement (scale) should be produced whenever interest is applied. </p><p>   When Account Statement records are generated automatically on Account opening, this field is set to the value defined in AC.STMT.PARAMETER if present, otherwise the field is set to 'NO', but it can subsequently be amended manually if required. </p><p>   Note:      Details of format, address(es) and copies are specified            within the Delivery system. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Y(es) or N(o). (Optional input. Default is NO.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ADVICE</field>
<desc><p>Reserved for future use. Once requirements for Tax Advices have been defined (a local requirement), this field will specify whether or not an advice should be produced. </p><p>   When Account Statement records are generated automatically on Account opening, this field is set to the value defined in AC.STMT.PARAMETER if present, otherwise the field is set to 'NO', but it can subsequently be amended manually if required. </p><p>   Note: (i)  Requirements for Tax Advices must be defined as a local            requirement.  At present this field has no effect. </p><p>        (ii)  Details of format, address(es) and copies must be specified            within the Delivery system. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Y(es) or N(o). (Optional input. Default is NO.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPL.STMT.FQU2</field>
<desc><p>  This field may be used to request a special statement any day without affecting the regular statement cycle(s).</p><p>   A statement is produced on the date specified, containing of all entries since the last statement for the cycle. The date of the next  statement for the cycle is not affected. The next regular statement for the cycle would contain entries after the Special Statement Date.</p><p>   If the date specified is not a working day, the statement is produced on the previous working day.</p><p>   This field cannot be input if the account has a passbook.</p><p>   Note: Special statements are produced when requested even if there have been no entries since the last Cycle/Statement, regardless of IF.NO.MVMT.FQU.2.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Up to 9 date characters. (Optional input) Cannot be earlier than today's     date.</p><p>   Date cannot be same as any of the regular Cycle  Statement Dates     (STMT.FQU.2).</p><p>   Associated with the fields from STMT.FQU.2 to SW.STMT2.TYP.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.STMT.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>SWIFT message type for the Cycle 1 Statement. </p><p>   Must be one of following:</p><p>   940 Customer statement 941 Balance Report 950 Statement CAMT052 Account Report CAMT053 Account Statements CAMT054A Debit/Credit Notification(Payment List) CAMT054B Debit/Credit Notification(Incoming Reference List)</p><p>   If no value is specified,  Statement with Message Type 950  would be generated.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Up to 10 Alpha numerics. Must be defined on DE.MESSAGE or REPORT.CONTROL</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Specify the Message type here as either 941 or 942 and in the next field how these messages to be generated incase special request received.</p><p>   Applicable values for 941 - STP (To generate MT941 during the day on receipt of Inward MT920 )</p><p>   Applicable values for 942 - Yes (To generate through DE.MT942.REQUEST) , No , STP (To generate MT942 on receipt of  Inward MT920)</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Optional field.</p><p>   Valid values 941 or 942.</p><p>   Associated multivalue set.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.FQU.1</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the next date and subsequent frequency for producing the regular (cycle 1) account statement.</p><p>   The field could be multi-valued in which case, a  statement  containing entries from the statement last printed in the cycle 1,  would be generated for  each multi-valued date.</p><p>   This field is automatically generated by the system when a new Account is opened to ensure that statements are produced for every Account.</p><p>   It can be altered manually.</p><p>   This field cannot be input if the account has a passbook.</p><p>   The first part of the field specifies the next date on which the Cycle 1 statement will be produced, the 2nd part specifies the frequency for producing Cycle 1 statements.</p><p>   The next date is updated automatically by the system every time a Cycle 1 statement is produced. If the next date falls on a non-working day, the statement is produced on the previous working day. The date is then updated as if the statement had been produced on the day specified, i.e. the cycle is not affected.</p><p>   When amending this field manually, if the next date is omitted, the system automatically generates it as follows:</p><p>   FREQUENCY NEXT DATE</p><p>   B(snss) (Every business day) Next     working day after today   </p><p>   T(wmth) (Twice a month, 15th and     last day) The next 15th or month end from today, whichever is sooner   </p><p>   Wn (Every n weeks) n weeks from     today     </p><p>   It is possible to enter the above     frequency options by the letter alone. The date will then default in     accordance with the frequency rules as detailed above, e.g. option 1 would     be the next working day from the system date. It is also possible to input a     frequency with a date.</p><p>   Mnndd (Every nn months on the dd     day)</p><p>   If today's date is less than dd, the next date is day dd in nn months from last month, otherwise it is day dd in nn months form the current month. If this date does not exist (e.g. 30th February) the previous day is assumed (28th or 29th February).</p><p>   Note - Checks are performed to ensure that the first cycle statements are requested for production not more than 12 months from the last requested date or if the account is being opened, the account opening date. Should either of these situations be encountered, it gives ride to an override situation but you may continue subject to being able to satisfy the relevant override class. However, the frequency cannot be more than 12 months.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   This field is in two parts.</p><p>   Next Statement Date: 1-9 Date     characters. Default value calculated by the system depending on the     Frequency.   </p><p>   Frequency :1-5 type SS (uppercase     alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters. The frequency cannot be     longer than 12 months. The next date must not be less than today's date. The     next date may be more than 12 months from the date of the last statement, or     the date of opening the Account if no statements have been produced yet but     is subject to override.</p><p>   This field is mandatory apart from     when an account is indicated as a PASSBOOK account</p><p>   When multi-valued, a frequency     of  "BSNSS" could not be duplicated in two multi-values of     cycle 1, irrespective of     next date.</p><p>   When multi-valued, a frequency of      "Mnndd"  could not be duplicated in two multi-values of cycle     1, irrespective of next     date.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSBOOK.NEXTLINE</field>
<desc><p>Holds the next passbook page and line to print on. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   5 Alphanumeric characters in the format: PAGE.LINE e.g. 2.11</p><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.STATEMENT.NO</field>
<desc><p>Hold the last statement number for Cycle 1 Statements, sequentially allocated, produced.</p><p>   The Statement numbers for each cycle is independently maintained starting with 1 for the cycle.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   5 numeric characters.   </p><p>   This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>XML.STMT.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>No inputtable field. For producing XML Statement SWIFT.STMT.TYPE field should be used.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CYCLE.NO</field>
<desc><p>This CYCLE.NO and NEW.STMT.NO fields allow to manually change the Statement number for each Statement cycle. Here the Cycle number must be defined.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Should be a value from 1 to 9.</p><p>   Should not be duplicated.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEW.STMT.NO</field>
<desc><p>This will allow to manually input a new statement number to overwrite the automatically updated statement number. If input, the statement processor will use the NEW.STMT.NO</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Mandatory when cycle number is defined.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

