<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>ADHOC.MESSAGES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This application contains the details of the statements requested through MT920 for an account along with the details of whether any statement is scheduled through frequency 1 in ACCOUNT.STATEMENT Application.</p><p>This application is used to control the generation of duplicate statements. </p><p>For example : On 01 Jan, there is a MT950 statement scheduled for Account 12345 for frequency 1 in ACCOUNT.STATEMENT and also MT920 requested is received to send out MT950 for that day. In such case this application holds both details and during End of day statement generation process, only one statement is generated using the frequency 1 details as given in ACCOUNT.STATEMENT Application.</p><p>This application &amp; the ADHOC.STATEMENTS are updated during MT920 inward processing and cleared during end of day processing.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.MSG</field>
<desc><p>This contains the message requested through Inward MT920.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No input Updated by System</p><p>Applicable values 940 or 950</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADHOC.ACCT</field>
<desc><p>Id to this application is valid T24 Account for which special statement request (MT940/MT950) has been received through Inward MT920</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No input field-updated by System</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REGULAR.STMT</field>
<desc><p>This field specified whether regular statement is scheduled for the day on which special statement is requested.</p><p>When a statement (either 940/950) is scheduled for a day in frequency 1 (in field STMT.FQU.1) and also a request to send MT940 or MT950 is received through incoming MT920 processing -then this field is updated as "Y" and only one statement is generated as per the details given in frequency 1.</p><p>Incase there is no statement scheduled in frequency 1 - this field is updated as Null and the statement as requested through MT920 is generated during EOD.</p><p>The delivery reference number for statements will be available in the appropriate DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST record.</p><p>In ACCOUNT.STATEMENT application, when the date/frequency is changed in STMT.FQU.1, this field is also updated as per the above .</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No input field-Updated by System.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.ID</field>
<desc><p>It contains the DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST id related to the message type as available in the previous field.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Update by System</p><p>Valid record in DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

