<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>ASCII.VALUES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The ASCII.VALUES table is used to define ASCII value codes and ranges which may be used by particular IN2 routines which validate entry to particular fields. </p><p>Standard tables are provided for each IN2 routine but there is also the provision for user-definable tables at a language and application level. Therefore different tables may be set up for particular languages and applications. The application level definitions may be further subdivided into different tables for different languages. </p><p>See the relevant helptext for ASCII.VAL.TABLE, which is where the actual ranges and values are defined. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAN.VALUE.TBL</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to specify which ASCII.VAL.TABLE record is to be used for validation for the language specified in field LANGUAGE. It is used in conjunction with field LANGUAGE when defining special validation for particular languages where the standard table in field DEF.VALUE.TBL is not sufficient. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-20 alphanumeric (type 'A') characters which must be the key to a record on the ASCII.VAL.TABLE table.</p><p>Multivalue field associated with field LANGUAGE. </p><p>Mandatory input if corresponding field LANGUAGE entered otherwise optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LANGUAGE</field>
<desc><p>This field defines the language for which a non-standard ASCII.VAL.TABLE record is to be used for validation. This is for special cases where the standard table defined in field DEF.VALUE.TBL is not sufficient. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The input to this field must be the key of a record on the MNEMONIC.LANGUAGE file.</p><p>Mandatory input if the corresponding LAN.VALUE.TBL is present otherwise optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.VALUE.TBL</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to specify which ASCII.VAL.TABLE record is to be used as the default for validation for the IN2 routine specified in field 0 ID. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-20 alphanumeric (type 'A') characters which must be the key to a record on the ASCII.VAL.TABLE table.</p><p>Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.LANG</field>
<desc><p>This field defines the language for which a non-standard ASCII.VAL.TABLE record is to be used for validation at an application level. This is for special cases where the standard table defined in either field DEF.VALUE.TBL or APP.VALUE.TBL is not sufficient. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The input to this field must be the key of a record on the MNEMONIC.LANGUAGE file.</p><p>Subvalue field associated with fields APPLICATION, APP.VALUE.TBL and APP.USE.VAL.</p><p>Mandatory input if the corresponding field APP.USE.VAL is present otherwise optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.USE.VAL</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to specify which ASCII.VAL.TABLE record is to be used for validation for the language specified in field APP.LANG at an application level. It is used in conjunction with field APP.LANG when defining special validation for particular languages within applications where the standard table in either field DEF.VALUE.TBL or APP.VALUE.TBL is not sufficient. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-20 alphanumeric (type 'A') characters which must be the key to a record on the ASCII.VAL.TABLE table.</p><p>Subvalue field associated with fields APPLICATION, APP.VALUE.TBL and APP.LANG.</p><p>Mandatory input if the corresponding field APP.LANG is present otherwise optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.VALUE.TBL</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to specify which ASCII.VAL.TABLE record is to be used for validation for the application specified in field APPLICATION. It is used in conjunction with field APPLICATION when defining special validation for particular applications where the standard table in field DEF.VALUE.TBL is not sufficient. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-20 alphanumeric (type 'A') characters which must be the key to a record on the ASCII.VAL.TABLE table.</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields APPLICATION, APP.LANG and APP.USE.VAL.</p><p>Mandatory input if corresponding field APPLICATION entered otherwise optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc><p>This field defines the application for which a non-standard ASCII.VAL.TABLE record is to be used for validation. This is for special cases where the standard table defined in field DEF.VALUE.TBL is not sufficient. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 35 characters which must be the key to a record on the PGM.FILE file with one of the following types: 'H', 'U', 'L', 'T', 'W' or 'A'.</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields APP.VALUE.TBL, APP.LANG and APP.USE.VAL.</p><p>Mandatory input if corresponding field APP.VALUE.TBL entered otherwise optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc><p>This field contains the ID of the ASCII.VALUES table. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The ID must be one of the following IN2 routines:            (iii) IN2AAA            (iv)  IN2ANY            (v)   IN2MNE            (vi)  IN2S            (vii) IN2SS            (viii)IN2SSS            (ix)  IN2SW            (x)   IN2SX            (xi)  IN2TLX</p><p>Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc><p>This field contains all the overrides which the user agreed to during input. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Internal field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

