<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>BASIC.RATE.TEXT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This table defines Descriptions of the Basic Interest Rate table IDs to enable the user to identify each one of them easily. </p><p>Each Description must be defined prior to creating Rates records for the corresponding ID in the BASIC.INTEREST rate table and will be used as the enrichment to the corresponding ID when it is displayed or printed during T24 processing. </p><p>Up to 999 descriptions may be defined. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MARGIN.ROUTINE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.RATE.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Code word for a basic rate type to be passed to Delivery for output if rate change advices are in use. See the BASIC.RATE.CNG.ADV flag in this application. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Optional input. Can be blank.</p><p>If used this field must contain one of the following code words:     BASE     CALL     COMMERCIAL     CURRENT     DEPOSIT     NOTICE     PRIME</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASIC.RATE.CNG.ADV</field>
<desc><p>Y/N Flag. Indicates whether rate change advices will be produced or not for this particular rate change during EOD processing for Loans and Deposits. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>'Y' or 'N'. Optional input. Blank entry in this field indicates that no rate change advices will be produced.</p><p>If this field is set to 'Y' then rate change advices will be produced for a given rate change during LD EOD.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS.NOTICE</field>
<desc><p>Days Notice for this particular rate type when a rate change advice is produced. Entry in this field is only valid if basic rate change advices are in use (see the next field). </p><p>If rate change advices are to be produced this field will be passed to Delivery for output when a rate change advice is produced during Loans and Deposits EOD for this rate type. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard up to 2 character numeric field.</p><p>Range between 1-99.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Basic Interest Rate Table ID to enable it to be easily identified. </p><p>This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the Description of the Basic Interest Rate in various languages.  Each expansion of the file will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table and will indicate to the user the language in which the Description must be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-15 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. Multivalue field. (Mandatory Input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc><p>This is the numeric code by which the Basic Rate Text can be identified. </p><p>This ID forms part of the key when defining the BASIC.INTEREST rate table. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 numeric characters in the range 1-9999.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

