<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>BASIC.INTEREST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This table allows various frequently used floating Rates, e.g. Base Rate, Prime Rate, Overnight Rate etc., to be defined separately for each Currency and stored in a central place where they can be accessed by T24 Applications as required. </p><p> 'Prime records' with the same Interest conditions can be linked directly to a Basic Interest ID in this table, rather than defining the Interest Rate details on each Transaction record.  For example, if the overdraft interest conditions for Currency Accounts are related to the base rate, each current Account or group of Accounts (when conditions are applicable at group level), should refer directly to the Basic Interest Rate ID defined in this table and not contain the value of the Rate itself. </p><p> When a Rate change takes place, the User will then only need to update the Basic Interest Rate IDs defined in this table with the new Rate(s) and the date on which it is to become effective.  This will then automatically update all the Transaction records which are tied to each Interest ID. </p><p> A Description of each Rate is held in the BASIC.RATE.TEXT table to allow the User to easily identify each one of the Basic Interest Rate table ID's. For this reason, a description is not included in the input parameters of this table.  The BASIC.RATE.TEXT table of Descriptions must be defined prior to creating this table. </p><p> E.B.S. also provides a PERIODIC.INTEREST Rate table to cater for Transactions where the Interest Rate conditions may change on a pre-defined periodic basis, e.g. LIBOR, and also according to the current balance on the 'Prime Record'.  The linking of 'Prime Records' to a Basic Interest Rate ID or a Periodic Rate ID will depend on the conditions existing for various products within the bank. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RECORD.STATUS</field>
<desc><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BCCY</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.RATE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the Interest Rate. </p><p> This is the Interest Rate that is linked via the Basic Interest Rate ID to 'Prime Records' from the effective date until new instructions are input. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p> 1-10 type R (Standard Rate Format, up to 6 integer and 9 decimal) numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p><p> Not more than 6 integers may be entered.</p><p> Not more than 9 decimals may be entered.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc><p>This is the Basic Rate code, Currency and effective date by which the Basic Interest Rate can be identified. </p><p> When Prime Records refer to a Basic interest Rate of this table, only the first part of the key (Basic rate code) will be entered in the Prime record.  The Currency will be taken directly from the Prime record. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p> 5-16 characters: a)   1-4 numeric characters Basic Rate code. b)   3 type SSS SWIFT characters, or 1 to 3 numeric characters      Currency code. c)   1-9 characters.  Standard Date Format.  Input of a), b) and c) must each be separated by a '.' if a numeric currency code is entered in b).  If a SWIFT code is entered these are not required. (Mandatory input for a and b.  The date part of the key will be defaulted to the Run date if it has not been entered.)</p><p> Input a) must be the code of an existing Basic Rate Text record.</p><p> Input b) must be the code of an existing Currency record.</p><p> Input c) must contain a valid date.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEG.INT.RATE</field>
<desc><p>Negative rate of interest that can be used in applications (at present the applications that can use negative interest rate had been restricted to SW, MM and DX applications and conditional use with credit interest in IC) is given in this field.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p> Standard rate format with a minus sign</p><p> Optional input</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

