<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>BILATERAL.AGREEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This application is used to specify the agreement details between the Account owner and the send of MT920 &amp; this functionality is applicable only for Inward processing of MT920.</p><p>When an agreement record exists for the combination of Account owner, sender of MT920 and the message type, a record in DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST is created with the incoming details.</p><p>Interim statements (MT941/MT942) is produced online and statements (MT940/MT950) produced during End of day processing using the frequency 1 details as given in ACCOUNT.STATEMENT.</p><p>Incase the agreement is not available for any of the above combination, the inward MT920 is put on Hold Status with the relevant values in  DE.STATEMENT.REQUEST  application for information purpose.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Specify the start date of the agreement as entered here.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory Input.</p><p>Date entered should be Equal or Greater than Today.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Specify the Message type for which agreement is received.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory Input-Associated Sub Value</p><p>Allowed values 940, 941 , 942 &amp; 950.</p><p>Null or Duplicate values not allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGREEMENT.CUST</field>
<desc><p>Specify  Bilateral agreement details along with the Customer with whom the Agreement is entered to process an incoming MT920 request and related outward Message which needs to be generated as STP (Straight Through Process).</p><p>When an Incoming MT920 is received, whether the existence of bilateral agreement is checked here for the combination of Account owner, sender of MT920 &amp; the requested message type. </p><p>All the accounts of the Customer are linked under this agreement and when an request for MT940 or MT950 is received, same is generated during that day 's end of day processing.</p><p>However incase of Interim statements - (ie. MT941 &amp; MT942), along with the Bilateral Agreement check,  to generate statements on-line as STP process , for the respective Account record, the SEND.MSG.TYPE should be set as "STP" in ACCOUNT.STATEMENT Application. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Must be a valid Customer ID</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AGREEMENT.REF</field>
<desc><p>Specify the Agreement reference number here.</p><p>The fields Agreement.Ref to End.Date forms a associated multi value set.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory field</p><p>Free text format.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CPARTY</field>
<desc><p>Specify the Institution wherein the above mentioned customer is maintaining the Account and from where the Incoming MT920 will be received (ie. sender of MT920 &amp; receiver of the requested message)</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Either a Valid Customer Number or a BIC prefixed with 'SW-'</p><p>Mandatory field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Specify the agreement upto what date is in force.</p><p>The agreement is valid only between the date specified between the Start.Date &amp; End.Date specified here.</p><p>Incase the end date has not specified, then the Agreement is in force from the date as mentioned in the previous field without end period.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional field</p><p>If Date entered should be greater than today as well as the Start date       as given in the previous field.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

