<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>BROKER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This table allows the user to identify the brokers that the bank authorises its dealers to deal through.  Rates applicable for each type of transaction the broker deals in can be defined for automatic calculation purposes during deal input stages.</p><p>During the deal input stages for Money Market, Loans and Deposits, and Future Rate Agreement contracts, if a broker code is entered then details from this file are obtained in order to calculate the brokerage amount (if no amount is entered by the user), and to determine the transaction code to credit the brokerage amount to.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the transaction code to be used for credit entries to the broker's account.</p><p>This transaction code is used when a match is found for the type of deal specified in the fields SYSTEM.ID to CURRENCY.</p><p />
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p />
<p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
<p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
<p>Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p><p>Must exist on the TRANSACTION file.</p><p>Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc><p>Used to define different rates depending on the currency of the deal.</p><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types.  The parameters system id, category code, term, currency and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (i.e. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount.</p><p>The currency from the deal is matched against the currency list here, if a match is found then the rate within this sub-value set is used.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>3 characters. (Optional Input)  Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.  Subvalue field associated with fields CURRENCY to NON.BNK.COMM.</p><p>Must be a valid currency on the currency file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.FOR.PAYMENT</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the valid currencies for payment allowed for this broker.</p><p>When a broker code is input on a deal without a broker currency code, then the first value in this multivalue field will be used as the default currency for the broker credit entry.  If a broker currency is entered on the deal, then this field is checked to ensure that the currency entered is allowable to make a credit entry to the broker.</p><p>Fields CCY.FOR.PAYMENT and PAYMENT.ACCOUNT form a related multi value set.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>3 Type SSS (Upercase alpha) characters     or 1-3 numeric character currency code. Multivalue field (First value mandatory)</p><p>No duplicate values allowed.</p><p>Currency entered must be a valid currency on the CURRENCY file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc><p>Used to identify the system for which the rate field below applies.  If no value is entered, then the rate field is applicable for all system types.</p><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types.  The parameters system id, category code, term, currency and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (i.e. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount.</p><p>This field will identify a product type that the rates within the multivalue set are applicable to.  Duplicate values are allowed and in many cases necessary.</p><p>Examples:</p><p>If a record on this file were set up as :</p><p>SYSTEM.ID          MM</p><p>CATEGORY.FROM      21000</p><p>CATEGORY.TO        21999</p><p>TIME               1M</p><p>CURRENCY           USD</p><p>BANK.RATE          0.0001</p><p>NON.BNK.RATE       0.0002</p><p>CURRENCY           GBP</p><p>BANK.RATE          0.001</p><p>NON.BNK.RATE       0.005</p><p>CURRENCY</p><p>BANK.RATE          0.01</p><p>NON.BNK.RATE       0.02</p><p>SYSTEM.ID</p><p>CATEGORY.FROM</p><p>CATEGORY.TO</p><p>TIME</p><p>CURRENCY</p><p>BANK.RATE          0.1</p><p>NON.BNK.RATE       0.5</p><p /><p>Example 1 : If a Money Market deal was input with Category code '21050', with days from value date to maturity date as '15', with deal currency as 'GBP', and with a bank type customer, then the rate used in order to calculate the brokerage amount would be '0.001'.</p><p /><p>Example 2 : If a Money Market deal was input with Category code '21050', with days from value date to maturity date as '15', with deal currency as 'JPY', and with a non-bank type customer, then the rate used in order to calculate the brokerage amount would be '0.02'.</p><p /><p>Example 3 : If a Money Market deal was input with Category code '22050', with days from value date to maturity date as '15', with deal currency as 'JPY', and with a non-bank type customer, then the rate used in order to calculate the brokerage amount would be '0.5'.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Valid values are 'TF', 'MM', 'LD', 'FR', 'SW', 'MG' and 'FD'. (Optional input)  Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.BNK.COMM</field>
<desc><p>Indicates the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE to be used for brokerage calculations if the customer of the deal is a non bank type customer.</p><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE, are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types.  The parameters system id, category code, term, currency and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (i.e. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount.</p><p>The FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE entered here will be applied if a match is found for any deal satisfying the above selection criteria and the counterparty of the deal is a non bank type customer.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Must be a key to a record on either the FT.CHARGE.TYPE file or the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p><p>Subvalue field associated with fields CURRENCY to NON.BNK.COMM.</p><p>Either NON.BNK.RATE or NON.BNK.COMM may be defined for each subvalue group, but not both.</p><p>Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc><p>The short name of the broker, used as an enrichment for the broker code field on contracts.</p><p>Free format short name used for enrichment purposes on contract input screens when a broker code is used.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>1-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p><p>Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY.FROM</field>
<desc><p>Used with field CATEGORY.TO below to define a range of category codes to be matched for the rates defined below.  If no values are defined, then all category codes will successfully match.</p><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE, are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types.  The parameters system id, category code, term, currency, and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage, and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (i.e. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount. This field together with field CATEGORY.TO below are used to determine the category ranges.  This can be used to identify separate deal types within the product type defined in field SYSTEM.ID above.  So for example MM Loans can be distinguished from MM Deposits, etc.</p><p /><p>Examples:</p><p>If a record on this file were set up as :</p><p /><p>SYSTEM.ID          MM</p><p>CATEGORY.FROM      21000</p><p>CATEGORY.TO        21999</p><p>TIME               1M</p><p>CURRENCY           USD</p><p>BANK.RATE          0.0001</p><p>NON.BNK.RATE       0.0002</p><p>CURRENCY           GBP</p><p>BANK.RATE          0.001</p><p>NON.BNK.RATE       0.005</p><p>CURRENCY</p><p>BANK.RATE          0.01</p><p>NON.BNK.RATE       0.02</p><p>SYSTEM.ID</p><p>CATEGORY.FROM</p><p>CATEGORY.TO</p><p>TIME</p><p>CURRENCY</p><p>BANK.RATE          0.1</p><p>NON.BNK.RATE       0.5</p><p /><p>Example 1 : If a Money Market deal was input with Category code '21050', with days from value date to maturity date as '15', with deal currency as 'GBP', and with a bank type customer, then the rate used in order to calculate the brokerage amount would be '0.001'.</p><p /><p>Example 2 : If a Money Market deal was input with Category code '21050', with days from value date to maturity date as '15', with deal currency as 'JPY', and with a non-bank type customer, then the rate used in order to calculate the brokerage amount would be '0.02'.</p><p /><p>Example 3 : If a Money Market deal was input with Category code '22050', with days from value date to maturity date as '15', with deal currency as 'JPY', and with a non-bank type customer, then the rate used in order to calculate the brokerage amount would be '0.5'.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>5 digits. (Optional Input)</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY.TO</field>
<desc><p>Used with field CATEGORY.FROM above to define a range of category codes to be matched for the rates defined below.  If no values are defined, then all category codes will successfully match.</p><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE, are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types.  The parameters system id, category code, term, currency, and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage, and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (i.e. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount.  This field together with field CATEGORY.FROM above are used to determine the category ranges.  This can be used to identify separate deal types within the product type defined in field SYSTEM.ID above.  So for example MM Loans can be distinguished from MM Deposits, etc.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>5 digits. (Optional Input)</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the default transaction code to be used for credit entries to the broker's account.</p><p>This transaction code is used when no transaction code is defined in the TXN.CODE field for the type of deal defined on this record on which brokerage is being taken.</p><p />
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p />
<p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
<p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
<p>Must exist on the TRANSACTION file.</p><p>Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAYMENT.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc><p>This field holds the customer account number where the BROKER wishes funds to be paid for the currency defined in the related CCY.FOR.PAYMENT field. The account defined in this field must be an account on the T24 system, for the currency defined in the related field and must belong to the BROKER.</p><p>The account cannot be a NOSTRO account.</p><p>If no account is defined in this field then an internal account number will be used. This internal account number is defined as:</p><p>[CCY][Broker Category][Broker Sub Div]</p><p>Where:</p><p>CCY - the broker currency as defined on the contract.</p><p>Broker Category - the category defined on the ACCOUNT.CLASS record BROKER.</p><p>Broker Sub Div - 4 digit subdivision code.</p><p>Fields CCY.FOR.PAYMENT and PAYMENT.ACCOUNT form a related multi value set.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Standard account format relating to a customer account.</p><p>The account specified must be for the currency defined in the related CCY.FOR.PAYMENT field.</p><p>The account specified must belong to the BROKER.</p><p>Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TIME</field>
<desc><p>Used to match separate time periods for the term of deals to distinguish different brokerage rates defined below.</p><p /><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types.  The parameters system id, category code, term, currency and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (ie. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount.</p><p /><p>The term from the deal is defined as the number of days from the value date to the maturity date.  This figure is extracted at deal input time and is used to find a match here.  The values in this field should be defined incrementally, i.e. 0D for call/notice deals, 7D, 1M, 3M, 6M, 1Y, etc.</p><p /><p>If no value is entered here then all terms will match successfully.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>In the format:</p><p>[N][TYPE] where N can be 1-3 numeric digits and TYPE can be either 'D' - Days, 'M' - Months or 'Y' - Years.</p><p>(Optional Input)</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>This field defines whether the brokerage calculation will be carried out on either a FIXED basis, a PERIOD basis or a PRESENT.VALUE basis.</p><p>For the FIXED basis the brokerage calculated igonres the period of the contract and returns an amount based solely on the contract principal.</p><p>Example: A loan matches a deal type defined on the BROKER record which will use the FIXED basis. The principal on the contract is 1,000 GBP. If the percentage rate for the deal type is set at 1% and the broker currency set to GBP the resulting brokerage amount will be 100 GBP.</p><p /><p>For the PERIOD basis the length of the contract is used in the calculation of the brokerage amount. The unit period for calculation (360 or 365 days) is based on the default basis of the contract currency.</p><p>Example: A deposit matches a deal type defined on the BROKER record which will use the PERIOD basis. The principal on the contract is 10,000 GBP for a period of two years. If the percentage rate for the deal type is set at 1% the resulting brokerage amount will be 10 GBP for each year, for a total of 200 GBP.</p><p>N.B.  Unless FIXED is specified on this record for the deal type defined for the sub value group, the calculation uses the PERIOD basis, except for brokerage taken on Letter of Credit Drawings, the FIXED basis is always used regardless of contents of this field.</p><p /><p>For PRESENT.VALUE the PV formula will be used in the brokerage calculation.</p><p>The PRESENT.VALUE calc.type is primarily for the brokerage calculation of the interest rate swap contracts.</p><p /><p>For Example: An IRS of GBP 10M with Bank A paying 6.72% fixed semi-annually and receiving floating from Bank B. Value date is 03 Apr 1998 and maturity date is 03 Apr 2002. With brokerage rate set to 0.01% and applying the above formula, the brokerage will be calculated as GBP 3,457.15.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Must either be FIXED, PERIOD or PRESENT.VALUE.</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p><p>Subvalue field associated with fields CURRENCY to NON.BNK.COMM.</p><p>Optional input.</p><p>If PRESENT.VALUE is specified no BANK.COMM and NON.BNK.COMM will be allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.BNK.RATE</field>
<desc><p>Indicates the rate to be used for brokerage calculations if the customer of the deal is a non-bank type customer.</p><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types.  The parameters system id, category code, term, currency and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (i.e. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount.</p><p>The rate entered here will be applied if a match is found for any deal satisfying the above selection criteria and the counterparty of the deal is a non-bank type customer.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Standard Rate Format 6,9</p><p>(Maximum 10 digits plus a decimal point)</p><p>(Mandatory input).</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p><p>Subvalue field associated with fields CURRENCY to NON.BNK.COMM.</p><p>Only one of the fields NON.BNK.RATE and NON.BNK.COMM may hold a value for each sub value group.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.COMM</field>
<desc><p>Indicates the FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE to be used for brokerage calculations if the customer of the deal is a bank type customer.</p><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE, are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types.  The parameters system id, category code, term, currency and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage, and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (i.e. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount.</p><p>The FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE entered here will be applied if a match is found for any deal satisfying the above selection criteria and the counterparty of the deal is a bank type customer.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Must be a key to a record on either the FT.CHARGE.TYPE file or the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE file.</p><p>Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.</p><p>Subvalue field associated with fields CURRENCY to NON.BNK.COMM.</p><p>Either BANK.RATE or BANK.COMM may be defined for each subvalue group, but not both.</p><p>Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.RATE</field>
<desc><p>Indicates the rate to be used for brokerage calculations if the customer of the deal is a bank type customer.</p><p>The set of fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE are used to determine different brokerage rates applicable to specific deal types. The parameters system id, category code, term, currency and customer type are taken from the deal at input stage and a match is located within this record.  If one is found then that rate can be used for automatic brokerage calculations.  If one is not found and no default value exists (i.e. a multivalue group that has all match parameters blank), then no automatic calculation can be performed and the user will be required to enter a manual amount.</p><p>The rate entered here will be applied if a match is found for any deal satisfying the above selection criteria, and the counterparty of the deal is a bank type customer.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Standard Rate Format 6,9 (Maximum 10 digits plus a decimal point) (Mandatory input).  Multivalue field associated with fields SYSTEM.ID to TXN.CODE.  Subvalue field associated with fields CURRENCY to NON.BNK.COMM.</p><p>Only one of the fields BANK.RATE and BANK.COMM may hold a value for each subvalue group.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the Brokers with whom the Bank is dealing.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>1-10 numeric character Customer number or 3-10 characters Customer mnemonic. The broker must already exist on the customer file before entry will be accepted.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BROKER.SUB.DIV</field>
<desc><p>Allows any classification of the brokers.  Used for the last four digits of the internal account make up for brokerage credit entries.</p><p>When broker credit entries are made via applications using brokers, then the credit account to make the credit will be defined in the form:</p><p>           [CCY][Broker Category][Broker Sub Div]</p><p>Where:</p><p>CCY             - The broker currency as defined on the contract at input stage.</p><p>Broker Category - The category code defined on the ACCOUNT.CLASS record for BROKER.</p><p>Broker Sub Div  - The value entered here formated to four digits.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>1-4 numeric characters.</p><p>(Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

