<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>CATEGORY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>Category codes used to classify financial transactions on T24 according to the type of business operation or product.</p><p>The use of these codes, together with personal Customer characteristics, e.g. Residence, Status, Industry and Sector codes etc., will enable the bank to produce balance sheets and returns reflecting a co-ordinated and structured view of its operation, by directing business transactions to their appropriate place oEn the report.</p><p>The first two digits of the Category code represent the highest level of classification and the next three digits represent a sub-classification which provides a clear definition of the profit and loss or product type.</p><p>Care should be taken when defining additional sub-classifications that sufficient detail does not already exist to provide the required breakdown. For example, it does not warrant defining separate Category codes for resident and non-resident Customers or for local and foreign currency transactions, since this information is already available on an individual Prime record.</p><p>A table of possible values and definitions of the first two digits of Category codes have been pre-defined within T24 and is included in the documentation of the record ID of this table.  The sub-classifications will be defined separately within each System.</p><p>In built Validation will prevent 'Prime Records' from being assigned a Category code which is totally irrelevant to the business operation.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MI.CATEG.GROUP</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to specify the MI.CATEG.GROUP to which this category code belongs and is used within the MI module to make analysis simpler and more efficient.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 6 alphanumeric characters.  </p><p>Must be a valid record on the MI.CATEG.GROUP file.</p><p>This field cannot be input if MI is not installed as a product, otherwise optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.IND</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the System to which the Category code belongs.</p><p>This field identifies the System to which the Category code relates.  This indicator enables T24 to ensure that a transaction is not assigned a Category code which is totally irrelevant to the business operation.</p><p>The Codes are defined as follows:</p><p /><p>AC = Account                 </p><p>BD = Bonds (not available)                 </p><p>DG = Disagio                 </p><p>FD = Fiduciaries                 </p><p>FF = Financial Futures(not available)                 </p><p>FR = Forward Rate Agreement                 </p><p>FX = Foreign Exchange                 </p><p>LC = Letters of Credit                 </p><p>LD = Loans and Deposits                 </p><p>MD = Miscellaneous Deals                 </p><p>MG = Mortgage Loans                 </p><p>MM = Money Market                 </p><p>PD = Past Due Payments                 </p><p>PL = Profit and Loss                 </p><p>SC = Securities                 </p><p>SL = Syndicated Loans (not available)                 </p><p>SW = SWAPS</p><p /><p>Note : At the present time the codes defined above are the only inputs allowed for this field, but these will be updated as required to        include other system codes.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>2 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character System code: </p><p>AC, BD, DG, FD, FF, FR, FX, LC, LD, MD, MG, MM, PD, PL, SC, SL, SW </p><p /><p>Mandatory input</p><p>PL Category 50000-69999 only</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>The position that accounts related to the category fall within. If not set will be designated as TR, for multi-gaap the position type would be the value of the reporting method used (IA, IF etc). Only used for internal account category range. Once set it cannot be changed if any account has been created using the category.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Only valid for range 10000 - 19999</p><p>No change if category has an account using it.</p><p>Must be a valid FX.POS.TYPE record</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Describes, in a short form, the Category code.</p><p>This field holds the abbreviated description, of the Category code in the specified Language, which can be used for reporting and enrichments.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-15 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters.  Multilanguage field.  </p><p>Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.ENTRY.TYPE.DFT</field>
<desc><p>The default MI.ENTRY.TYPE for the category is specified in this field. MI.ENTRY.TYPEs are used within the MI module to identify the type of profit and loss entry being processed.</p><p>The value in this field will be used as the default entry type within the MI.ENTRY, MI.AUTO.ENTRY and CATEG.ENTRY applications.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p>Must be a valid record on the MI.ENTRY.TYPE file.</p><p>Input only allowed for profit and loss categories, i.e. category codes greater than 49999.</p><p>This field c annot be input if MI is not installed as a product, otherwise optional.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC</field>
<desc><p>Specifies an alternative easy means of referencing the Category.</p><p>Any value can be entered in this field with the exception that the first character must be alpha.</p><p>Like the ID, the Mnemonic must be unique across T24.</p><p>Note : For each Category, the System will automatically update the internal file "MNEMONIC.CATEGORY" which allows the User to display the CATEGORY codes in Mnemonic sequence instead.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-10 type MNE (Uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha,      or ".") characters.  </p><p>Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MI.PL.ALLOC2.ID</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to determine which rules will be checked (in addition to those specified on the CATEGORY record) during the MI.PL.ALLOCATION.2 processing for entries which fall into this category grouping.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Must be a valid record on the MI.PL.ALLOCATION.2 table.</p><p>This field c annot be input if MI is not installed as a product, otherwise optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.CONTINGENT</field>
<desc><p>This field is populated by the ACCOUNT application when the account record is authorised.</p><p>Possible defaulted values are</p><p>CONTINGENT</p><p>NON.CONTINGENT</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>At the time of setting up contingent categories in ACCOUNT.PARAMETER none of the Category codes within the ranges should have value</p><p>NON.CONTINGENT</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY.CODE</field>
<desc><p>This is the code by which Category details can be identified.</p><p>This code classifies profit and loss and product types.  Each business transaction of T24 will be allocated a Category code which will enable reports to be constructed that give an accurate view of the bank's operation.</p><p>The first two digits (the highest level of classification) have pre-defined use within T24 as detailed in the following table.</p><p /><p>Note : When entering the key, the user may insert, if so desired, the '-' sign anywhere in the key after the first numeric character. When displayed on the screen, the '-' will appear as a divider between the main classification (first 2 digits) and the sub-classification        (last 3 digits).</p><p /><p /><p>PRE-DEFINED CATEGORY CODES</p><p>==========================</p><p>ACCOUNTS : 01 - 19</p><p>01 - 09 = Customer Accounts            </p><p>10 - 19 = General Accounts</p><p /><p>CONTRACTS/TRANSACTIONS/PRIME RECORDS : 20 - 49</p><p>20 = Foreign Exchange                 </p><p>21 = Loans and Deposits                 </p><p>22 = Securities                 </p><p>23 = Trade Finance                 </p><p>24 = Bonds</p><p /><p>PROFIT AND LOSS RELATED TO PRODUCTS : 50 - 59</p><p>50 = Interest paid                 </p><p>51 = Interest received                 </p><p>52 = Commission                 </p><p>53 = Exchange</p><p>NON-PRODUCT RELATED PROFIT AND LOSS : 60 -69</p><p>60 = Personnel                 </p><p>61 = Premises                 </p><p>62 = Other operating expenses                 </p><p>63 = Taxes</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>4 or 5 numeric characters:  </p><p>a)   Product/P&amp;L classification in the range 1-99.  </p><p>b)   Sub-classification of product/P&amp;L in the range 000-999.  </p><p>Mandatory input</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOLIDATE.ENT</field>
<desc><p>If entries are to be consolidated the field CONSOLIDATE.ENT should contain the id to the AC.CONSOLIDATE.COND record that describes rules for consolidation. This must be set for consolidating entries raised for PL category. Then categ entries will be </p><p>consolidated by the following consolidation criteria:</p><p>Entry Type</p><p>P&amp;L category</p><p>Currency</p><p>System Id</p><p>Transaction Code</p><p>Value Date</p><p>Exposure Date</p><p>Reversal Marker</p><p>Currency Market</p><p>Suspense Category</p><p>Terminal Number</p><p>Account Officer (P&amp;L only)</p><p>Product Category (P&amp;L only)</p><p>Plus any additional elements defined in AC.CONSOLIDATE.COND</p><p /><p>The combined key is structured as follows, the ! character is used as a delimeter:</p><p /><p>S!12345678!GBP!FT!210!20021126!!!1!!89</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Category code.</p><p>This Description can be used for reporting in the specified Language.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  </p><p>Multilanguage field.  </p><p>Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

