<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>CHEQUE.REGISTER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>CHEQUE.REGISTER (CHEQUE HOLDINGS OF ALL ACCOUNTS)</p><p>This table holds details of cheque types and numbers held by each account on the system. It is automatically updated by the cheque control system and only restricted functions are allowed to update the usage of cheques held.</p><p>The keys to the file are the account numbers concerned and for each account the number of cheques issued in the current charging period, the number used and the number currently held is recorded.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CHQ.TYPE.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Cheque type and account number.</p><p>A cheque register record is maintained automatically for each cheque type held for each account. The ids therefore consist of the cheque type and the account number separated by a '.'. There are no specific validation rules because new records cannot be created on this table.</p><p>The cheque control system creates cheque register records as required when issues are made.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 alphanumeric characters:'.':Standard account number format.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUED.THIS.PD</field>
<desc><p>The number of cheques of this type which have been issued to the account in this charging period.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>5 numeric characters.</p><p>System updated field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOP.RETURNED</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc><p>Reserved For Future Use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUED.LAST.PD</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the number of cheques of this type issued to this account during the previous charging period.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>5 numeric characters.</p><p>System updated field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STOPPED.CHQS</field>
<desc><p>Field to hold the number of cheques stopped for the cheque type of the ID account.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc><p>Reserved For Future Use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc><p>Reserved For Future Use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc><p>Reserved For Future Use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.9</field>
<desc><p>Reserved for future use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USED.THIS.PD</field>
<desc><p>The number of cheques of this type which have been used in this charging period.</p><p>This field is used to record the number of cheques of this type used during the current charging period. It may be updated by the user if required but would normally be increased as each incoming cheque debit is processed. This value will determine the periodic usage charges to be raised if any are defined in the CHEQUE.CHARGE table.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>1-5 numeric characters</p><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.PD.CHG.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the STMT.ENTRY references for any charges made by periodic usage processing.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>System updated field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc><p>Contains the STMT.ENTRY references for any charges made at authorisation of the issue.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>System updated field.</p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc><p>Reserved For Future Use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc><p>Local reference fields may be defined to contain additional information required about cheque issues. Fields may be setup according to the T24 structure of local reference data elements and validation rules.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>As defined in the appropriate local table definitions.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc><p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p><p>This is a NOINPUT, no copy field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENTED.CHQS</field>
<desc><p>This field is now obsolete.  Lists of cheque numbers that have been presented for payment are now stored in the application CHEQUES.PRESENTED.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNUSED</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQ.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc><p>Reserved For Future Use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUE.PD.START</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the start date of the current issuing period.</p><p>According to the setup of the CHEQUE.CHARGE table a certain number of cheques may be allowed free in each charging period. These charge calculations rely on the holdings being flushed at certain frequencies, ie to start a fresh issue period. This field records the date when the current charging period started.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>8 numeric characters.</p><p>Standard date format.</p><p>System updated field</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USED.LAST.PD</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the number of cheques of this type which were used during the last charging period.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>5 numeric characters.</p><p>System updated field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc><p>Reserved For Future Use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETURNED.CHQS</field>
<desc><p>This field can be used to indicate that a cheque has been returned. Only a cheque that has not been previously presented or stopped can be flagged as being returned.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional Input</p><p>Must be a valid cheque number issued to the account</p><p>Must not have been presented or stopped earlier</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.PERIOD.CHG</field>
<desc><p>Records charges raised for usage of cheques during the previous charging period.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>1-19 numeric characters.</p><p>System updated field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USED.TO.DATE</field>
<desc><p>The number of cheques of this type which have been used since the opening of the account.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>5 numeric characters.</p><p>System updated field</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISSUED.TO.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the number of cheques issued to this account since it was opened.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed.</p><p>5 numeric characters.</p><p>System updated field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.HELD</field>
<desc><p>The number of cheques of this type which are currently held by the account.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>5 numeric characters.</p><p>System updated field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc><p>Reserved For Future Use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.EVENT.SEQ</field>
<desc><p>A unique sequence number identifier for each issue record. Provides the next sequence number to be used when the next issue of cheques of this type is made to this account.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p><p>7 numeric characters.</p><p>System updated field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.NO</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.CHEQUE.NO</field>
<desc><p>Range of  auto cheque no is populated here when Auto.Reorder.Type is "Cheque.No" in CHEQUE.TYPE.</p><p>During the Cheque issue, based on the minimum holding for the cheque.type, auto cheque no is arrived and starting cheque no stored in Cheque.Issue and full sequence stored in the Cheque.Register. On presenting any of these cheque no Auto reorder process will be done.</p><p>However, if a record is available in Cheque.Issue for that account with Request Status Less than 90 (Cheque issue), then reorder will not be done.</p><p>For example:</p><p>In Cheque Type CURR minimum holding specified as 5 and auto cheque type is "Cheque.No".  If a cheque book is issued with Cheque type as "CURR" and start no as 1 with no of leaves as 10. In Cheque Issue, auto cheque no is populated as 6 and in Cheque register, as 6,7,8,9,10. On presenting any of the cheque no, auto reorder will be done with appropriate Request status and in cheque register, auto cheque no will be populated as "Requested"</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUE.NOS</field>
<desc><p>A record of the ranges of cheque numbers issued to the account.</p><p>Each issue of cheques must specify a cheque start number.</p><p>This field contains a list of the ranges of cheque numbers held based on the starting cheque number entered in each issue record.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed if the CHEQUE.REGISTER field on         ACCOUNT.PARAMETER is set to 'YES'</p><p>Contains cheque number ranges such as 100001-100025</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUE.REGISTER.ID</field>
<desc><p>The id of this file is the same as the CHEQUE.ISSUE file to which it relates. The majority of processing is done by the system in maintaining this file, so new records are created by the system only.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Created by System only existing records can be modified,         no new user input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED10</field>
<desc><p>Reserved for future use</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No Input Allowed</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

