<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>CHEQUE.STATUS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This is used to define various cheque issue status and the same can be used in cheque issue application.</p><p>The various status can be Cheque Issue request received, Sent for Printing , Issued, Dispatched etc.</p><p>Validation Rules</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STATUS.ID</field>
<desc><p>This is the code by which this cheque status can be identified.</p><p>The code must be in the range 1-99 and represents the ID of the table.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>1-2 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p><p>Default value 90 is used for ISSUED</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.FORMAT</field>
<desc><p>This allows the format of advices to be defined at the CQ type level. When input is valid in this field, appropriate records should be created on the DE.FORMAT.PRINT file. </p><p>The value in this field will form the second part of the key to the file DE.FORMAT.PRINT. The key will be derived appending the value in this field to the literal 'CQ'. For example, input of a '2' in this field will mean that the key to DE.FORMAT.PRINT will be 700.CQ2.1.GB instead of the default 700.1.1.GB.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>4 numeric characters.   </p><p>Optional input. Default is 1 if left blank.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASS.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>User defined class types can be specified here.</p><p>This is defaulted when cheque is issued through CHEQUE.ISSUE.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>    Valid values USERDEFINE.1 to USERDEFINE.9</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>This field defines the nomenclature of the stage for the code keyed in the id field</p><p>Descriptions may be entered in each of the languages defined in the LANGUAGE table.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Mandatory. </p><p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MESSAGE.CLASS</field>
<desc><p>This Field links CHEQUE.STATUS record with a message class for advice format. There Should be a valid entry for this message class in EB.MESSAGE.CLASS.</p><p>This is defaulted while issuing cheque through CHEQUE.ISSUE.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Should be a record  in EB.MESSAGE.CLASS</p><p>Optional Input</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

