<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>CHEQUE.CHANGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p /><p>In Outward clearing process, whenever clearing entries created through front ends like Teller, FT, DC etc, system generates CHEQUE.COLLECTION records for each entry with details of the outward clearing.</p><p /><p>These CHEQUE.COLLECTION records can be grouped into a single batch according to requirements.</p><p /><p>For processing further on the batches or collection records,  like re-batch, selective combination and changing status of records selected from various batches etc., CHEQUE.CHANGE application is used.  </p><p /><p>By using the application CHEQUE.CHANGE, the following process could be done:</p><p /><p /><p /><p>All     or selected  Cheque Batches can be combined into a single batch. The ID     of the new batch created  will be displayed by the system. All the     cheque collection records of the new batch will bear the new batch ID for     future reference.</p><p /><p /><p>Cheque     collection records or batches meeting a certain selection criteria can be     processed further for RE-BATCH, or changing status to CLEARED/ RETURNED</p><p /><p /><p>An     existing enquiry based on Cheque Collection or Cheque Batch also can be used     for selection and further processing </p><p /><p /><p /><p>The application is to be used in VERIFY mode.</p><p /><p /><p /><p /></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SEL.DATA</field>
<desc><p>Defines the value of the selected field for picking up the data as per the operand for further processing.</p><p>Example:</p><p>CCBA0007300012, CCBA0007300015</p><p>@ID EQ CCBA0007300012 CCBA000730015 will pick up the two cheque batches with ID as defined above for further process like Re-Batch</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Any valid data</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc><p>Determines the method by which the selected field has to be operated with the data defined for  further process.</p><p>Example:</p><p>EQ ( Equal to), LK (like), GT (Greater than)</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>All valid operands are allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERATION</field>
<desc><p /><p>CHEQUE.CHANGE </p><p>OPERATION</p><p>Defines the operation to be done by the system on the data selected as per selection criteria.</p><p>In the case of  CHEQUE.COLLECTION records selected based on a criteria, operations like CLEARED, RETURNED and DATE. CHANGE  could be done </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Permitted operations are CLEARED, RETURNED, RE-BATCH and DATE.CHANGE.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBATCH.ID</field>
<desc><p>The ID allotted by the system to the new batch generated out of the Re-batch operation</p><p>All the Cheque Collection records grouped under the new batch will bear this Rebatch Id as a reference</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>No input field</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSURE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.FLD</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the field name of the selected based on which the value of the data will be determined for further processing.</p><p>Example:</p><p>@ID  - a field selected from CHEQUE.BATCH or CHEQUE.COLLECTION which has been defined under the field APP.ID</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Should be a valid field of the application already defined under APP.ID</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GB.DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Defines the detailed description of the Application.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Any Alphanumeric characters of length 35</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQ.ID</field>
<desc><p>Already existing enquiry can be defined here for the purpose of further processing</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Must be an existing enquiry based on CHEQUE.BATCH or CHEQUE.COLLECTION</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.ID</field>
<desc><p>This field specifies the ID of the application based on which the records will be selected by the system for further  processing  activities, like re-batch, Cleared, or Returned etc..</p><p>For example, if CHEQUE.BATCH is specified here as application, and if  'REBATCH' is selected, then the system will select all open Cheque Batches and combine them.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Allowed values are CHEQUE.BATCH and CHEQUE.COLLECTION</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BATCH.ID</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQ.CHANGE.ID</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Identification of a record created under this file. Any Alphanumeric characters are allowed.</p><p>For example...</p><p>'RE-BATCH' , 'SELECTIVE BATCH',  </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>15 Alphanumeric characters</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

