<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>COMPANY.GROUP</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The standard T24 function codes (I for Input, A for Authorisation, D for Delete, etc...) are used within the COMPANY.GROUP Application.  The Reverse function (function code R) is not permitted. </p><p>Company Group Codes are used to identify the various operating companies, using the T24 system.  The Company Group code is part of the 'T24 Company' key and as such will help in identifying for a particular operating company the 'T24 Companies' that have been set up for it. This will help in reports etc. being grouped/combined. </p><p>Thus for each of the T24 Company records for the same operating company the Company Group must be the same.  Therefore the same Company Group codes will need to be created at each of the locations where the organisation is operating the T24 system. </p><p>The format of the Company Code is: </p><p>           CC GGG LLLL </p><p>Where: </p><p>           CC   is  Country Code </p><p>           GGG  is  Company Group Code </p><p>           LLLL is  Local Code </p><p>Note : Local code must be different for each location/ branch within one        country even if the processing is run in different environments. </p><p>The Company Group Code thus forms the centre portion of the individual Company records. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.GROUP.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the code which associates various companies into a group. </p><p>The Company Group Code is used to identify the operating company that the processing company using the T24 system belongs to.  Use of this code will thus help multi-location organisations to group all their subsidiary companies for reporting purposes. </p><p>This is achieved by using the same Company Group code for all of the T24 company records for the one operating company across all installations. </p><p>The Company Group code is part of the T24 Company code which is formatted as follows: </p><p>           CC GGG LLLL </p><p>Where:            CC    is   Country Code            GGG   is   Company Group Code            LLLL  is   Local Code </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-3 numeric characters, in the range 001 to 999.  (Mandatory Input  Cannot be changed)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Name of the group of associated companies. </p><p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the description of the COMPANY.GROUP in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE Table and will indicate to the user the Language in which the Description must be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field.  Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

