<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>COMPANY.CHECK</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This live table i.e. updated from T24 with no user input, contains data related to the multi company set up.</p><p>There are several records in this table:-</p><p>CCY.FILE contains details of the local currencies used in the EMC database</p><p>CURRENCY - details of the companies that own the currency table and the companies that share them</p><p>CUSTOMER - details of the companies that own the customer tables and the companies that share them</p><p>FIN.FILE - the lead companies that own the financial level data and the companies that share this data e.g. ACCOUNT</p><p>FINANCIAL - the companies that own and share the financial descriptive data i.e. where the file classification is FTD, an example would be BASIC.INTEREST</p><p>MASTER - the master company, this will be the first company created in a T24 database</p><p>NOSTRO - the company that owns ad the companies that share the nostro accounts, file classification NOS, example NOSTRO.ACCOUNT</p><p>SUB.DIVISION - shows the link between a companies sub division code and the company key</p><p /></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>USING.MNE</field>
<desc><p>The company mnemonic of the company that shares the data owned by the company set up in the associated COMPANY.CODE</p><p>Sub valued within the multi valued COMPANY.CODE set</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>USING.COM</field>
<desc><p>The company that shares the data owned by the company set up in the associated COMPANY.CODE</p><p>Sub valued within the multi valued COMPANY.CODE set</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc><p>The company that owns the related data.</p><p>Multi valued.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.MNE</field>
<desc><p>The company mnemonic if the company that owns the related data.</p><p>multi valued</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE.KEY</field>
<desc><p>The key to the company check record.</p><p>Will be one of the following ( see overview)</p><p>     CCY.FILE</p><p>     CURRENCY</p><p>     CUSTOMER</p><p>     FIN.FILE</p><p>    FINANCIAL</p><p>       MASTER</p><p>       NOSTRO</p><p> SUB.DIVISION</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

