<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>COMPANY.CREATE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This application is used to cut down on the amount of work required to create a new company.</p><p>When this application is Verified using the V function control is passed to the COMPANY application with the new company record populated with the data entered here, plus data from the DEFAULT.COMPANY record if this field is populated.</p><p>When the COMPANY record is committed the new company will be created.</p><p /></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>FINANCIAL.MNE</field>
<desc><p>If a Lead company is being created then the value in this field must be equal to the MNEMONIC of this record.</p><p>If a branch is being created then the menmonic must be equal to the mnemonic of the company defined in the FINANCIAL.COM field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME.ADDRESS</field>
<desc><p>The Name and Adress values, used to populate the same fields on the new company record.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINANCIAL.COM</field>
<desc><p>This field will indicate whether a Lead Company or a Branch Company is to be created. If company code in this field is equal to the company code of the key of this record then a new Lead company and all its associated files will be created. If the company code in this field is the same as that of an existing Lead Company then a Branch is being created. If a Branch is being created the branch company and its Lead company must belong to the same company group and the company in this field must be a lead company. You cannot link a branch to another branch.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC</field>
<desc><p>This is the mnemonic for the new company. It must not be an already existing company mnemonic value.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.DIVISION.CODE</field>
<desc><p>The sub division code for the new company. It must not be an already existing sub division code.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY</field>
<desc><p>This indicates the comany code of the company to be created. It must conform to the company code format and must not be an existing company record key.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.NAME</field>
<desc><p>This is the name of the new company .</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATION.DATE</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future use, and will have no effect.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.COMPANY</field>
<desc><p>Indicates an existing company record that can be used to populate the new company record. It will still be possible to amend the copied data fields if this is allowed. THe purpose of this field is to cut down on the amount of input required for the new company record, for example the application fields etc.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOLIDATION.MARK</field>
<desc><p>The CONSOLIDATION.MARK value in the company being created.</p><p>Option are N,C,R and A</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.DIVISION.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the sub division code of the company being created, if the company being created is a type N or a type A company, then it must be the last 4 digits of the new company, i.e. record key, and it must be blank if the company being created is a type C or Type R.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

