<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>COMPANY.CONSOL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This file holds the descriptions and the details of grouping of Companies for combined CRF reports. </p><p>The group number is part of the data entered at report production stage. </p><p>Each record is independent of the others and there is no hierarchical relationship between them. </p><p>The default currency for any report produced for the group is entered. </p><p>With regard to the exchange rates used at report production time. Special rates can be used or the standard rates from the currency file(s) can be used. These rates maybe taken from one file or maybe from a currency file for each local currency. When producing a combined report the local currency amount or the local currency equivalent amount is converted into the reporting curreny. The original currency figures are not used. Therefore it is necessary to enter some default conditions on these records. These default conditions are: a) The currency file to be used, when the rates are to be taken from one    file. b) Where there are two or more currency files for the same local currency    which company's currency file is to be used. </p><p>               FIELD NO        FIELD NAME </p><p>                 0             COM.CONSOL.NO                  1.1           COM.CON.NAME                  2             COM.CONSOL.TO                  3.1           COM.CONSOL.FROM                  4             DEFAULT.RPT.CCY                  5             DEFAULT.CCY.COM                  6.1           LCL.CCY                  7.1           CCY.COMPANY </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LCL.CCY</field>
<desc><p>The local currencies for the companies in the field COM.CONSOL.FROM. </p><p>This field contains a list of the local currencies from the companies to be combined together. </p><p>Only needs to be entered when there is more than one currency file for the same local currency. Suppose that company C and company D both have there Local currency as DEM and for specific reason the exchange rates to be used in each company must be different. Then either company C's or D's exchange rates must be used when creating a combined report using exchange rates from a local currency file. For this to be done then DEM must be entered in this field and either company C or D in CCY.COMPANY. </p><p>The system will default the list of the local currencies for this group. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The 3-digit currency code or the 3-digit numeric currency code.  Multi-value field associated with field CCY.COMPANY.  Optional input.</p><p>Must be a valid Currency code on the currency file.</p><p>Must be the local currency for one of the companies being combined in the report.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.CCY.COM</field>
<desc><p>The company code for the currency file when defaulting rates at report time. </p><p>This is the company code for the currency file which is to be used when ever the exchange rates are to be taken from one file or when no a special rate is miising for a particular currency. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The 9-digit company code or the 3-digit company mnemonic.  Mandatory input.  Must be a valid Company code on the company file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.CONSOL.TO</field>
<desc><p>Company code to identify the company heading for the group report. </p><p>The Company that is specified in this field is the company whose name is printed at the top of the report(s). </p><p>If an operative company code is entered in this field no financial details for the company are extracted unless the company code is repeated in the list of company codes in the field COM.CONSOL.FROM (this is the next field). </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The 9-digit company code or the 3-digit company mnemonic.  Mandatory input.  Must be a valid Company on the Company file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.RPT.CCY</field>
<desc><p>The currency that combined reports for the group are to be produced in if no other currency specified at report time. </p><p>This is the currency in which the reports for this group are normally printed. At report production time it is possible to specify a different currency if so required. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The 3-digit currency code or the 3-digit numeric currency code.  Mandatory input.  Must be a valid Currency code on the currency file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.COMPANY</field>
<desc><p>The company code for the local currency Curreny file when taking rates at report time from the Local cuurency Currency files. </p><p>This field contains the Company code whose currency file is to be used when the exchange rates are to be taken from the Currency file for each local currency. </p><p>Only needs to be entered when there is more than one currency file for the same local currency. Suppose that company C and company D both have the Local currency as DEM and for specific reason the exchange rates to be used in each company must be different. Then either company C's or D's exchange rates must be used when creating a combined report using exchange rates from a local currency file. For this to be done then DEM must be entered in the previous field LCL.CCY and either company C or D in this field. </p><p>The values in this field are defaulted by the system when there is only one Currency file for each Local currency. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The 9 digit company code or the 3 digit company mnemonic.  Multi value field associated with LCL.CCY.  Optional input.</p><p>Must be a valid Company code on the company file.</p><p>The local currency for this company must be equal to the currency specified in the corresponding multivalue in the field LCL.CCY.</p><p>A Company code must be entered when there is more than one Currency file for the Local cuurency in field LCL.CCY.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.CON.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Narrative (description) to describe the group. </p><p>This description is used for enrichment on screen input when entering the report request details. This field is not used in the printed reports. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Mandatory input.  Multivalue field to cater for the printing of the description in several languages.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.CONSOL.FROM</field>
<desc><p>Company code to identify the companies whose details are to be included. </p><p>In this field are listed the Companies whose financial details are to be included in a combined report. </p><p>The Companies specified can only be the operative companies. It is not possible to specify a consolidation company in this field. </p><p>For each group all the base operational companies to be included in that group must be specified. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The 9-digit company code or the 3-digit company mnemonic.  This is a multivalue field.  Mandatory input.</p><p>Must be a valid Company on the Company file.</p><p>Must be an operative (non consolidation) Company.</p><p>Company code can not be duplicated within this field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COM.CONSOL.NO</field>
<desc><p>Numeric Number to identify a grouping of companies. </p><p>The number used has no special meaning and is used when requesting combined reports so as to identify the companies whose details are to be combined. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 numeric characters.  Mandatory input.  Must be a three digit number in the range 001 to 999.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

