<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>COUNTRY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This table contains the static details of each individual Country, for example, Country Name, Currency Code(s) etc. </p><p>  The use of the I.S.O Country codes are recommended as a standard for the key of this table. </p><p>  Dummy Country codes may be used for entities that do not have an official Country code but have a Currency Code, for example, the European Currency Unit. </p><p>  Up to 999 additional elements may be defined to accommodate further local requirements. </p><p>  The CURRENCY table must be set up before this table can be created. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Indicates the Country Name which may be used for enrichments and reporting purposes. </p><p>  The Country Name may be entered in any of the Languages defined in the LANGUAGE table. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>  3-35 type AA characters, (alphanumeric, first character alpha).  Multilanguage field.  Multivalue field.  (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the local Currency Code(s) for the Country. </p><p>  This field must be a valid code in the CURRENCY Table and identifies the local Currency Code(s) for the Country.  Where a Country has more than one local currency, e.g. Belgium, all the local Currency Codes can be specified. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>  3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters       or 1-3 numeric characters.  Multivalue field.  (Optional input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGH.RISK</field>
<desc><p>Indicates whether this country is considered high risk.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the abbreviated name for the Country. </p><p>  The Country name is specified in an abbreviated form which can then be used for reporting or screen display when space is limited.  The Short Name may be entered in each of the Languages specified in the LANGUAGE table. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>  3-15 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters.  Multivalue field.  Multilanguage field.  (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRESENTATION.CODE</field>
<desc><p /><p /><p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>  Up to 4 type 'S' (SWIFT) characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GEOGRAPHICAL.BLOCK</field>
<desc><p>Country's geographical block. </p><p>  Options are: </p><p>  ID                DESCRIPTION                COUNTRY ==                ===========                ======= AMERICA           The Americas               AR CA UM US VG VI ASIA              Far East/Asia              AU ID EMERGING          Emerging Markets           AL CL HU IL SA EUROPE            Continental Europe         AD BE ES EU FR GI GR IE IT                                              KY MC NO PT SE SM VA GERMAN            Dem Block - Europe         AT CH DD DE LI LU JAPAN             Japan                      JP MULTINAT          Multi-country              XE OTHER             Unallocated New Countries  TJ UK                United Kingdom             GB GG IM JE </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc><p>This is the code by which the static Country details can be identified. </p><p>  This field is normally the SWIFT code for the Country to which the table refers. If dummy Countries are used the code can be any unique combination of two SWIFT characters. By using the code any T24 Applications can access the static details of the Country.</p><p>  Additionally records may be entered that include the year suffix, for example US.1999. These records are used only for captial gains processing where different index values are issued by the tax authorities for each calendar year. In this case the transactions will apply the index values for the trade date year record, for example a transaction with trade date 01 Jan 1999 will use US.1999, and a transaction with trade date 27 Dec 1998 will use US.1998.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>  2 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters. (Mandatory input)</p><p>  Additional year suffix, optional input.</p><p>  If the year suffix is specified the country record must         be present without a year suffix.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACER.DAYS</field>
<desc><p>Accepts valid days format. If defined, will be used to default TRACER.DAYS field in EB.FREE.MESSAGE file.</p><p>  Eg : +2W or 25W etc</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p> :</p><p /><p /><p>  Tracer days should be like +NW or NNW, where N stands for Number of days and W stands for Working days.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUSINESS.CENTRE</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to define the main business centre for the relevant country. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>  Upto 35 type S characters.  Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CENTRAL.BANK.CODE</field>
<desc><p /><p /><p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>  Up to 5 type 'S' (SWIFT) characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INDEX.DATE</field>
<desc><p>This multi-value field is used to define an apply to date for the index level in the INDEX field.</p><p>  The dates should be in descending order and the last (multi-value-1) date field should be blank to indicate that it's the current period.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>  Valid date format</p><p>  Cannot be in the future</p><p>  The first multi-value field must be blank</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CG.INDEX</field>
<desc><p>This field contains the inflation index associated with the country and the date recorded, unless the date field is blank to indicate that the index is current.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>  Standard numeric with 2 decimals.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

