<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>CUSTOMER.POSITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CPE.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.CCY</field>
<desc><p>Contains the other currency of the deal and type whose details are contained in this record where 2 currencies are involved. This is currently only populated for FX transactions. </p><p>The Other currency is taken from the currency used in the Limit system, from the LIMIT.DAILY.OS records with the following exceptions: </p><p>EB.SYSTEM.ID     CURRENCY ------------     -------- FX               SELL.CCY (as PER LIMITS) FXBUY            SELL.CCY FXSELL           BUY.CCY FXBPL            BUY.CCY FXBPL            SELL.CCY </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.LCY.AMOUNT</field>
<desc><p /><p>Contains the current local equivalent of the DEAL.AMOUNT. </p><p>The local equivalent is calculated at Mid Rate when the records are created. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DETAIL.NEXT.LEVEL</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.INT.CHG.DTE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the next date for payment / receipt of additional interest or charges if applicable for the transaction in question. The current rate used is contained in the field OTH.INT.CHG.RTE. The committed amount on this date is contained in OTH.INT.CHG.AMT. </p><p>Some applications allow additional interest / commissions to be calculated, this information should be stored here. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLL.RIGHT</field>
<desc><p>Stores the collateral right id.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERC.LCY.AMOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the current local equivalent of the PERC.AMOUNT. </p><p>The local equivalent is calculated at Mid Rate when the records are created. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.INT.CHG.ACC</field>
<desc><p>Contains the accrued amount of additional interest or charges if applicable for the transaction in question. The current rate used is contained in the field OTH.INT.CHG.DTE. </p><p>Some applications allow additional interest / commissions to be calculated, this information should be stored here. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLL.RGHT.COVER</field>
<desc><p>Stores the collateral right id.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.CCY</field>
<desc><p>Contains the currency of the deal and type whose details are contained in this record. </p><p>The Deal currency is taken from the currency used in the Limit system, with the following exceptions: </p><p>EB.SYSTEM.ID         CURRENCY ------------   -------- FX             BUY.CCY (as PER LIMITS)  FXBUY          BUY.CCY  FXSELL                 SELL.CCY  FXBPL                 LOCAL currency  FXBPL           LOCAL currency  LIAL            LIMIT currency  LIUT            LIMIT currency  SC              Reference currency from SEC.ACC.MASTER </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the Maturity Date of the deal linked to the customer position record. The maturity date may be a date or a number days notice. </p><p>The Maturity Date is extracted from the Limits system LIMIT.TXNS record, with the following exceptions: </p><p>LIUT / LIAL EXPIRY.DATE from the LIMIT record. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REBUILD.DATA</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERC.AMOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the percentage or margin amount of the deal and type whose details are contained in this record in the DEAL.CCY. This represents the percentage or margin value of a particular transaction. </p><p>The Percentage amount is extracted from the limits system, from the LIMIT.TXNS records with the following exceptions: </p><p>EB.SYSTEM.ID  LIMIT.REF      CURRENCY ------------  ---------      -------- FXBUY                        Same as DEAL.AMOUNT FXSELL                       Same as DEAL.AMOUNT FXBPL                        Diff between original local buy                              equivalent and latest forward projection FXSPL                        Diff between original local sell                              equivalent and latest forward projection LIAL                         ONLINE.LIMIT for the LIMIT record LIUT                         TOTAL.OS from the LIMIT record SC                           The total margin value of customer                              holdings converted to reference currency at                              mid-rate FDOR                         Calculated as Margin Rate percentage of the                              deal amount. AC             CURRACC,D,Z   WORKING.BALANCE of the account LD             COMMIT        Current Outstanding balance CO             COLL          EXECUTION.VALUE from the collateral record </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMITTED.INT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the amount of committed interest, if known for the transaction in question to be paid / received in the INT.DATE. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The amount is in the DEAL.CCY</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.RATE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the current interest rate applicable to the deal, and in the case of Forex deals, the relevant deal exchange rate. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the CUSTOMER.POSITION file. </p>
            <p>Each CUSTOMER.POSITION record is identified by the following components separated by a "*": </p>
            <p>1) Liability Number    This is a 1-10 numeric CUSTOMER number identifying the Liability group    to which the Customer belongs. </p>
            <p>2) Customer Number    This is a 1-6 numeric Customer number </p>
            <p>3) Application system id    This is one of the following:    - The alpha part of the transaction key E.g FX (FX9512312345) FDOR      (FDOR9512312312)    - FXBUY for the Buy side of a forex deal    - FXSELL for the Sell side of a Forex deal    - FXBPL for the profit on the Buy side of a FX deal    - FXSPL for the profit on the Sell side of a FX deal    - LIAL for the limit amount allocated    - LIUT for the limit amount utilised    - LCM for the main LETTER.OF.CREDIT record    - LCD for the DRAWINGS records    - SC for securities portfolio security holdings    - CO for non T24 Collateral held </p>
            <p>4) Company Mnemonic    The 3 character company mnemonic for the company in which the    transaction resides. </p>
            <p>5) Limit Reference    This contains the 7 digit limit reference where the underlying    transaction is linked to the limits system. </p>
            <p>   In the case of transactions which are not linked to the limits system    the following values are used: </p>
            <p>   SCPORT  - Securities Portfolio    COLL    - Non system collateral    COMMIT  - Commitments    CURRACD - Accounts not linked to limits with a Debit balance    CURRACC - Accounts not linked to limits with a Credit balance    CURRACZ - Accounts not linked to limits with a zero balance </p>
            <p>6) Deal / Account number    Contains the deal reference / account number / limit / collateral id </p>
            <p>   Customer Position records are built when CUSTOMER.POSITION enquiries    are run. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.AMOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the full amount of the other side of the deal and type whose details are contained in this record, where the deal involves 2 currencies. This is currenltly populated for FX deals. </p><p>The Other Deal amount is extracted from the limits system, from the LIMIT.DAILY.OS record, field OTHER.AMOUNT with the following exceptions: </p><p>EB.SYSTEM.ID  LIMIT.REF      CURRENCY ------------  ---------      -------- FXBUY                        SELL.AMOUNT FXSELL                       BUY.AMOUNT FXBPL                        BUY.AMOUNT FXSPL                        SELL.AMOUNT </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.CCY</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.PERC.AMOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the percentage or margin amount of the other side of the deal and type whose details are contained in this record, where the deal involves 2 currencies. This is currenltly populated for FX deals. </p><p>The Other Perc amount is extracted from the limits system, from the LIMIT.DAILY.OS record, field OTHER.AMOUNT with the following exceptions: </p><p>EB.SYSTEM.ID  LIMIT.REF      CURRENCY ------------  ---------      -------- FXBUY                        SELL.AMOUNT FXSELL                       BUY.AMOUNT FXBPL                        BUY.AMOUNT FXSPL                        SELL.AMOUNT </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc><p>Contains the Category code of the transaction where a category code is present. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.INT.CHG.AMT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the committed amount of interest or charges if applicable for the transaction in question. This amount is to be paid / received on the OTH.INT.CHG.AMT.DTE. </p><p>Some applications allow additional interest / commissions to be calculated, this information should be stored here. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPLAY.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTH.INT.CHG.RTE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the rate used for calculation of additional interest or charges if applicable for the transaction in question. The committed amount on this date is contained in OTH.INT.CHG.AMT, the accrued to date figure is held in OTH.INT.CHG.ACC. The due date for the additional amount is contained in OTH.INT.CHG.DTE. </p><p>Some applications allow additional interest / commissions to be calculated, this information should be stored here. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.CCY</field>
<desc><p>Contains the local currency of the company in which the Customer Position file was last updated. </p><p>The DEAL.LCY.AMOUNT and PERC.LCY.AMOUNT are converted into LOCAL.CCY from the DEAL.AMOUNT and PERC.AMOUNT at the current mid-rate. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.TO.LCY.RATE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the exchange rate used to calculate the local equivalent fields DEAL.LCY.AMOUNT and PERC.LCY.AMOUNT. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCL.JOINT.INFO</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.AMOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the full amount of the deal and type whose details are contained in this record. </p><p>The Deal amount is extracted from the limits system, from the LIMIT.TXNS records with the following exceptions: </p><p>EB.SYSTEM.ID LIMIT.REF CURRENCY ------------ --------- -------- </p><p>FXBUY BUY.AMOUNT </p><p>FXSELL SELL.AMOUNT </p><p>FXBPL Diff. between BUY mid rate now and at deal time </p><p>FXSPL Diff. between SELL mid rate now and at deal time </p><p>LIAL MAXIMUM.TOTAL for the LIMIT record LIUT TOTAL.OS from the LIMIT record </p><p>SC The total value of customer holdings converted to reference currency at mid-rate AC CURRACC,D,Z WORKING.BALANCE of the account </p><p>LD COMMIT Current Outstanding balance </p><p>CO COLL NOMINAL.VALUE from the collateral record </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COLLATERAL.RIGHT</field>
<desc><p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 13 characters may be entered.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the next interest payment date for the transaction where interest is due to be paid / received. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Contains the value date of the underlying transaction. </p><p>The transaction is extracted from the underlying deal. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LIMIT.LEVEL</field>
<desc><p>Denotes the level of the Limit record from which the data was extracted. </p><p>This field may contain the values: </p><p>GLOBAL  when extracted from a GLOBAL limit record PRODUCT when extracted from a PRODUCT level limit record, including         products under a Global limit. SUB     for SUB product limits, including those sub-products under a         Global limit. </p><p>Transaction data is extracted at both PRODUCT and SUB product level (although not at Global level), so a single transaction may appear twice in the CUSTOMER.POSITION file with 2 different limit references in the key. In enquiries based on transaction information, records with a value of SUB in this field should gemerally be ignored, as all information will be included in the PRODUCT level record. </p><p>GLOBAL records will only contain a value for LIMIT records defined at that level. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.NO.DAYS</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUED.INT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the current amount of accrued interest expresed in Deal Currency for a transaction, where interest is calculated. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.LIAB.MARKER</field>
<desc><p>Defines whether the record is an Asset (A) or a Liability (L). </p><p>The record is termed an Asset if the Deal Amount is positive, and a Liability if the Deal Amount is negative. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BEN.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

