<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>CUSTOMER.STATUS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The Customer Status codes defined in this table are assigned to Customer records of T24 to enable the bank to classify their Customers on any kind of criteria defined locally. </p><p>This enables standard codes to be used when there is a requirement to highlight specific information relating to Customer, for example, "Customer Deceased" or "Customer In Jail" etc. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.STATUS</field>
<desc><p>This is the code by which the Customer Status can be identified. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)  The code must be in the range of 1 - 9999, and represents the ID of the table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Customer Status code and is used for enrichment of the Code. </p><p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the description of the Customer Status code in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES) and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field.  Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Customer Status in an abbreviated form, which can be used for reporting when space is limited. </p><p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter a short description of the customer Status Code in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES) and will indicate to the User the Language in which this short description must be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-15 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters.  Multilanguage field.  Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

