<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>CUSTOMER.CHARGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This module has two functions.  Firstly, to record the charge group for T24 applications and secondly, recording the details regarding the periodic charges to be levied against the customer. </p><p>A record for each customer will be automatically created whenever a new "customer" record is authorised.  Default values for the application charge groups will be inserted.  This is cone via the use of the CONDITION PRIORITY file. </p><p>The following fields are used for recording the application group numbers other than securities:- </p><p>XX.NN      APPLICATION XX.NN      DEFAULT.GROUP CC.NN      ACTUAL.GROUP </p><p>The following fields are used for recording group number for the securities charge applications:- </p><p>XX.NN      SC.APPLICATION XX.NN.NN   PORTFOLIO XX.NN.NN   SC.DEF.GROUP XX.NN.NN   SC.ACT.GROUP XX         DEPOSITORY.GROUP </p><p>These two multi-valued groups will be expanded for each of the applications installed.  If an application is not present on the Company record then no data will be defaulted for that application. The field DEFAULT.GROUP and ACTUAL.GROUP will initially be defaulted and both will be the same. </p><p>The ACTUAL.GROUP may then be updated by the user if he wishes to override the system default value. </p><p>In the case of Securities when the customer charge record is first created the "PORTFOLIO" field will be set to "ALL" as at this stage no portfolios have been created.  This sub-value will then be the default for all portfolios for that customer.  The user may specify special conditions by creating a new sub-value set and entering the portfolio number and its associated group. </p><p>The last field in the securities group is the customer group number to be used when a customer is a depository and defines the group for calculating safekeeping charges for the Depository. </p><p>A further set of fields will record the periodic charge data.  These will not be defaulted when the record is created but will need to be entered by the user.  These fields are:- </p><p>XX.NN      CHARGE.FREQ XX.NN      DEBIT.ACCOUNT XX.NN.NN   CHARG.CODE </p><p>A charging frequency date will be entered with an account number to debit. These fields are multi-valued to allow for multiple charging periods. Within each frequency a sub-valued list of charges may be taken by entering the relevant charge codes. </p><p>A separate account used for all commissions and charges payable can be specified.  This amount will be used, if specified, in the Funds Transfer application only. </p><p>Example: </p><p>ID    CUSTOMER NUMBER  123456          T JONES 1.1   APPLICATION      FUNDS TRANSFER 2.1   DEFAULT.GROUP    01              NON RESIDENTS 3.1   ACTUAL.GROUP     01              NON RESIDENTS 4.1   APPLICATION      SC.TRADING 5.1.1 PORTFOLIO.NO     ALL 6.1.1 DEFAULT.GROUP    03              SYSTEM DEFAULT 7.1.1 ACTUAL.GROUP     03              SYSTEM DEFAULT 4.2   APPLICATION      SC.MANAGEMENT 5.2.1 PORTFOLIO        ALL 6.2.1 DEFAULT.GROUP    03              SYSTEM DEFAULT 7.2.1 ACTUAL.GROUP     03              SYSTEM DEFAULT 4.3   APPLICATION      SC.SAFEKEEPING 5.3.1 PORTFOLIO.NR.    ALL 6.3.1 DEFAULT.GROUP    04              SPECIAL CONDITION 7.3.1 ACTUAL.GROUP     04              SPECIAL CONDITION 8     DEPOSITORY.GROUP 99              DEPOSITORY CONDITIONS 9.1   CHARGE.FREQ      19921231 M1231 10.1  DEBIT.ACCOUNT    022`347863      T.JONES 11.1.1CHARGE.CODE      PC01SD          SAFETY DEPOSIT 12.1.2CHARGE.CODE      PC01AC          NUMBERED ACCOUNT </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CHG.COM.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Defines the account number to be debited when the customer is required to pay commission/charges. </p><p>This account will be used in the Funds Transfer application only, when the customer is required to pay commission/charges. </p><p>An override will be required if the account customer is not the same as the customer of the record. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1 to 14 numeric account number  3 - 10 alphanumeric account mnemonic  (Optional Input)</p><p>Must exist on the Account file.</p><p>Cannot be an internal amount.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc><p>Defines the key to the Customer charge record. </p><p>The customer number entered is validated against the customer file and enriched with the customer short name. </p><p>Creation of new records is not allowed. </p><p>In addition to the customer number  ,  company code may can be appended with a hypen. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Input is mandatory.</p><p>Company code appended with hypen is optional.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.COMPANY</field>
<desc><p>This field holds a valid company id.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Should have an entry in COMPANY file.</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.REF</field>
<desc><p>The reference of the advice generated for charges if required. </p><p>A charge advice may be generated if CHG.ADV.REQD is set to Y. In this case the id in the delivery system will be held here. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>System generated.  This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.ACT.GROUP</field>
<desc><p>Defines the actual securities application, customer group. </p><p>Initially this field will have the same value as the securities default group.  Amendment to this is allowed as long as this is a valid group condition for "NNN" or "C-NNN". </p><p>For every portfolio, within the securities application, an associated charge group must be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Input is mandatory.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.DEF.GROUP</field>
<desc><p>Defines the customer group default. </p><p>This field holds the customer group defaulted for the portfolio within each securities application. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 numeric digits (no change allowed).</p></desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>TR.APPLICATION</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Treasury application which is FX.MARGIN, used to apply the margin or spread percentage to derive the contract rate.</p></desc>

<p>
   <p>Validation Rules: </p>
   <p> Input is mandatory. </p>
   <p> Accepts only FX.MARGIN. </p>
</p>
</t>


<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO.ID</field>
<p> Defines the suffix for a portfolio. </p>
<p> When a record is created the value in this field is "ALL". </p>
<p> For a Customer, if there are multiple Portfolios and each one of them falls under different FX.GEN.CONDITION IDs, details of the same can be seen updated in CUSTOMER.CHARGE table. </p>

<p>
   <p>Validation Rules: </p>
   <p> Input is Mandatory. The customer number together with the portfolio number is used to validate the input against the SEC.ACC.MASTER. i.e. Key is: Customer: "-":PORTFOLIO. </p> 
   <p> Duplicate portfolios within the same application is not allowed. </p>
</p>
</t>

<t>
<field>TR.DEF.GROUP</field>
<desc>
<p>Holds the Group ID defaulted for the customer. </p>
<p>This field holds the customer group defaulted for the portfolio defined for FX.MARGIN </p>
<p>
   <p>Validation Rules: </p>
   <p> No input field. </p>
</p> </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.ACT.GROUP</field>
<desc>
<p>Holds the actual group for FX.MARGIN. </p>
<p>For every portfolio, within the FX.MARING application, an associated group must be entered. </p>
 </desc>
</t>
 
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the account to be charged according to the following charge codes. </p><p>Accounts entered may not necessarily belong to this customer. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard numeric account number      or  3 to 10 character type MNE account Mnemonic (uppercase alpha or numeric)                             or  6 to 12 character type SS internal account number ( uppercase alpha or numeric)                          or  5 character numeric P &amp; L category code preceded by 'PL'.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ACT.GROUP</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Actual Tax Group which the customer is a member of for the associated TAX TYPE. </p><p>This will be equal to the TAX.DEF.GROUP when the Customer record is initially input or amended, but may be overriden by input of a valid Group. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 character numeric TAX GEN CONDITION key.  (mandatory if associated TAX TYPE is present)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc><p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 14 characters may be entered.</p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.1</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.ADV.REQD</field>
<desc><p>Defines if an advice is required when the charge amount dcerived from the defined CHARGE.CODE is taken. </p><p>T24 will generate a message type 1960 when this field is set to Y. </p><p>Default value NO. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Y or NO. (Mandatory Field)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.ACCOUNT.1</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.DEF.GROUP</field>
<desc><p>Defines the TAX Group which the Customer is calculated to be a member of for the associated TAX TYPE. </p><p>This is automatically calculated by the system. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 character TAX GEN CONDITION id.</p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Tax type for which the associated TAX.DEF.GROUP and TAX.ACT.GROUP apply. </p><p>This field is automatically updated when the Customer is created. A value will be present for each TAX TYPE defined on the TAX TYPE table. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must be 3-10 alpha numeric characters.  Must exist on the TAX TYPE file as a valid record.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PORTFOLIO</field>
<desc><p>Defines the suffix for a portfolio. </p><p>When record is created the value in this field is "ALL". </p><p>This can be expanded so that several portfolio customer groups may be added for each of the securities applications. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Input is Mandatory.  The customer number together with the portfolio number are used to validate the input against the SEC.ACC.MASTER.  i.e.  Key is:  Customer: "-":PORTFOLIO Duplicate portfolios within       the same application is not allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>System field.  This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSITORY.GROUP</field>
<desc><p>Defines the depository charge group. </p><p>This holds the customer depository charge group in the form "NNN" or "C-NNN" which must be a valid group condition.  This is used when calculating safekeeping charges for the depository. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Input is optional unless the customer security type is "DEPOSITORY".</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SC.APPLICATION</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Securities applications. </p><p>There are at present three different Securities applications which will use this table to calculate commissions and charges:- </p><p>           SC.TRADING         -    Securities Trading            SC.SAFEKEEPING     -    Safekeeping charges            SC.MANAGEMENT      -    Portfolio Management fees </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Input is mandatory.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc><p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.GROUP</field>
<desc><p>Defines the customer general condition. </p><p>This field is defaulted to when first creating the record. </p><p>This is determined by the condition priority for the application as to which of the groups matches the data on the customer record. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 digit numeric (no change allowed)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.GROUP</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Customer's actual charge group for the application. </p><p>This field has the same value as the default group when the customer charge record is first created. </p><p>If a customer level record in XX.GROUP.CONDITION files is authorized  (For FT, FD and LC), it's ID (C-CUSTOMER.NUMBER) automatically gets defaulted here. In that case, its value could not be changed.  When the customer level record in XX.GROUP.CONDITION files (For FT, FD and LC) is reversed then value of  DEFAULT.GROUP field is automatically defaulted here. For the FT, FD and LC applications, the processing checks for the customer level record in XX.GROUP.CONDITION first. </p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1. Cannot change if the value is C-Customer No.</p><p>2. Can be changed only to a value in XX.GROUP.CONDITION.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc><p>Defines non-Securities applications. </p><p>Valid applications which may be entered are FUNDS.TRANSFER and FIDUCIARY. </p><p>Input is validated against the Condition priority file. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Input is mandatory.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the charge record to be used in calculating periodic charges for an account entered in the previous field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 11 character type A (alphanumeric) charge type code.  Must exist on the FT.CHARGE.TYPE table or the FT.COMMISSION.TYPE table and must be for a flat amount.  Must be in the currency of the account specified in the previous field or in local currency.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.FREQ</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the current frequency of the customer charge for the following accounts and charge codes. </p><p>The customer charge end of day process will apply charges to the following accounts as specified by the following charge codes and at the frequency specified in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Date, 1 to 9 character type D ( date format in range 1950-2049  and  Frequency, 1 to 5 characters type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha).</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

