<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>CUSTOMER.DEFAULT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>To minimize the Input of data required in the creation of new Customer records, T24 provides the User with the Customer Default table.  This allows him to define any frequently used combination of an Industry, Account Officer, Target, Nationality, Customer Status and Residence code to be linked together by means of the Sector code.  When the Sector code is input on the Customer record the associated codes will then be retrieved from this table and automatically assigned to the Customer record if no other input has been made.  This simplifies the opening of a new Customer record and reduces the amount of Input necessary. </p><p>When the User creates a new record in this table the Application will request, as a minimum, the definition of one default value. </p><p>It is important to note that the Customer Application will refer to this table ONLY during the creation process of new Customer records.  Any further maintenance on the Sector code of authorised Customer records will not generate new default values. </p><p>If a default value is defined in the VERSION file (Ref: UTILITIES) it will take preference over the value defined in this table, when the user is creating a new customer record using a special version. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.STATUS</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the Customer Status code default value which is associated with the Sector code. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 numeric character Customer Status code. (Optional input.  No default value.)  The field must contain a valid code on the CUSTOMER.STATUS table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STREET.NON.MANDAT</field>
<desc><p>Specifies  whether the fields STREET in CUSTOMER and STREET.ADDR in DE.ADDRESS (for PRINT carrier) applications is non-mandatory for customers whose Sector code equal to the ID of the CUSTOMER.DEFAULT record. </p><p>For Customers associated with this CUSTOMER.DEFAULT record  and with a value of 'Y' in this field, the fields STREET in CUSTOMER and STREET.ADDR in DE.ADDRESS (for PRINT carrier) applications  would be non mandatory. </p><p>For customers associated with this CUSTOMER.DEFAULT record  and with a value of 'N' or no-value (Null)  in this field, the fields STREET in CUSTOMER and STREET.ADDR in DE.ADDRESS (for PRINT carrier) applications would be mandatory. This also applies to Customers for whom no associated  CUSTOMER.DEFAULT record exists.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Allowed values are  'Y' and 'N'</p><p>Default value is Null.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the Industry code default value which is associated with the Sector code. </p><p>Identifies the Industry in which the Customer is trading. </p><p>Each User can define their own industry codes according to the use they want to make of them.  Production of central bank reports classified by Industry codes or the monitoring of the overall credit exposure by Industry type are typical examples of uses of this code. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 numeric characters. (Optional input.  No default value.)  The field must contain a valid code on the INDUSTRY table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.OFFICER</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the other Account Officer(s) responsible for the Customer. </p><p>Only codes included in the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES) are allowed. </p><p>The definition of a second Account Officer should serve the purpose of indicating who will take care of the Customer Relationship when the main ACCOUNT.OFFICER is on holiday, sick, or absent for any other reason. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 Numeric character Account Officer code.  Multivalue field.  (Optional input.  No default value.)  The field must contain a valid code on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES).</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NATIONALITY</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the Country code default value which is associated with the Sector code and indicates the Nationality of the Customer. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>2 type SSS (Uppercase alpha) character, Country Code. (Optional input.  No default value.)  The field must contain a valid code on the COUNTRY table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES).</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the Country code default value which is associated with the Sector code and indicates the Country of Residence of the Customer. </p><p>When no inputs are entered in this table, an error message will be displayed next to this field to remind the User that at least one field must have an input. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>2 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters, Country code. (Optional input.  No default value.)  The field must contain a valid code on the COUNTRY table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES).</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTOR</field>
<desc><p>This is the Sector code by which a group of default values are identified. </p><p>When this Sector code is input on a Customer record the associated default values will automatically be retrieved from this table except if any specific value has been input by the user. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 numeric character Sector code. (Mandatory input)  The field must contain a valid code on the SECTOR table which must be in the range 0001 to 9999.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DUPLICATE.CHECK</field>
<desc>
<p>This field is used to define the duplication check required for Customer.</p>
<p> This is used to verify for Duplicates during creation of new records and the corresponding action.</p>
<p> Validation: </p>
<p> Should be a valid value from the EB.DUPLICATE.TYPE. </p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET</field>
<desc><p>Specifies how the Customer is considered by the bank and how he fits in with the Account Officer's overall marketing strategy. </p><p>Examples of this field are: "Prime Customer", "No Potential" etc. but it must be a valid code on the TARGET code table.  The values of the field should be defined according to the bank's overall marketing strategy. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 numeric character Target code. (Optional input.  No default value.)  The field must contain a valid code on the TARGET table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.OFFICER</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the main Account Officer responsible for the Customer. </p><p>This code will be defaulted on all Customer transactions within T24 except if it is overriden by another Account Officer code at the transaction or product level.  The existence of the Account Officer code on every Customer transaction will allow generation of M.I.S. information at the Account Officer level. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 numeric characters. (Optional input.  No default value.)  The field must contain a valid code on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES).</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

