<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>DEALER.DESK</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This table allows the bank to specify to the system how its dealing room activity is organised.  When applicable, dealer desks can be defined for the major currencies.  The dealer desk is used as part of the key to the POSITION file.  This enables the bank to view their currency position by dealer desk, if required and to book the revaluation Profit/Loss at dealer desk level. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>R6</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ELEMENT.ID</field>
<desc><p>Not yet implemented. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SOURCE</field>
<desc><p>No yet implemented. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Provides the operator with an enrichment whenever the two digit dealer desk number is entered.  The narrative is free-format and may include the dealers name or activity (e.g. USD/DEM dealer). </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-34 characters.  Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.REVAL.CATEG</field>
<desc><p>This field holds the PL Category for Asset and Liability Debit revaluation. The default value should be the previous CR.REVAL.CATEG. This field is mandatory when the associated  CURRENCY.MARKET has been entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must exist in CATEGORY file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R9</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R7</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R3</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPLIT.POSITIONS</field>
<desc><p>Identifies whether the POSITION records are to be created in local currency on the value-dates for the FX transactions  in cross currencies.</p><p>If this field is set to YES, then </p><p>For the FX transactions in cross currencies, the position records are generated for the transactions done by this dealer for the two cross currencies online.  On the value-date these records are split and position records for buy currency against Local currency and  for sell currency against Local currency are created.  </p><p>If this field is set to NO or NULL then </p><p>For the FX transactions in cross currencies, the position records are generated for the transactions done by this dealer for the two currencies online.  On the value-date these records are not split as above</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Acceptable values are YES , NO or NULL</p><p>Default is YES</p><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.FOR.REVAL</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the department to which profits/losses will be allocated for this dealer desk.  This field will be used during the revaluation process. </p><p>If it is desirable to keep the profitability at the dealer desk level, it is important to specify a different Profit Center code for each dealer desk. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-4 digit numeric code. (Mandatory input)  The department entered must relate to an element on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NUMBER</field>
<desc><p>Fields APPLICATION, FIELD.NUMBER &amp; DEF.VALUE are for Information only. </p><p>Indicates the fields corresponding to the APPLICATION. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1 to 3 numeric characters.  (Subvalue field associated with sub value DEF VALUE;  Multivalue associated group with fields APPLICATION and DEF.VALUE).</p><p>Must be a valid field number on the application file.</p><p>No duplicates.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R4</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R5</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEALER.DESK.NO</field>
<desc><p>Allows more than 2 thousand dealer desks to be defined on the table. </p><p>Dealer desks will be typically created for a Dollar/Mark, Dollar/Paris, Cable, Dollar/Belge... dealing room organisation. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>2 digit alphannumeric code in the range A-Z, a-z, plus 0-9 (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc><p>Fields APPLICATION, FIELD.NUMBER &amp; DEF.VALUE are for Information only </p><p>Identifies which application file defaults are set for first level input. </p><p>This allows defaults to be set for various applications.  (e.g. FOREX, MM.MONEY.MARKET).  This helps in faster input of deals in first level as, once the default values are set up, the dealer is required to inout only a minimum number of fields. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1 to 25 characters type A.  (Multivalue associated group with fields FIELD.NUMBER and DEF.VALUE).</p><p>Must be a valid application file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUSINESS.GROUP</field>
<desc><p /><p>To classify the current Dealer Desk under Hedge or Trading group</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p />Valid inputs are H  Hedge , T  Trading<p /><p /><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.REVAL.CATEG</field>
<desc><p>Category code to hold PL Category for Asset and Liability Credit revaluation. </p><p>Multivalue field associated with CURRENCY.MARKET. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Only one value for each CURRENCY.MARKET allowed.</p><p>Must exist in CATEGORY file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
<desc><p>Fields CURRENCY.MARKET to DR.REVAL.CATEG form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered.</p><p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the CURRENCY.MARKET file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.VALUE</field>
<desc><p>Fields APPLICATION, FIELD.NUMBER &amp; DEF.VALUE are for Information only. </p><p>This is the value of the Dealer Desk for the field nominated in FIELD.NUMBER. </p><p>  (i) There are two formats: </p><p>      a.  Alphanumeric characters       b.  ID in quotes. </p><p> (ii) If it is 'ID' then the key of DEALER.DESK will be the default. </p><p>(iii) N.B. Defaults are only set for input fields that are allowed for            input in 1st level FX &amp; MM. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1 to 35 characters, type A.  Sub value field associated with sub value FIELD.NUMBER; Multivalue associate group with fields APPLICATION and FIELD.NUMBER.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>R8</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

