<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The purpose of this table is to identify each Department and Account Officer in the bank by means of a code. </p><p>   An Account Officer code will be assifned to each Customer record, but may be overriden at transaction level when necessary.  This enables accurate M.I.S reports to be produced at the Account Officer level. </p><p>   In the same way, a Department code or an Account Officer code will be assigned to each User.  This will be recorded in the User Profile and will allow an easy identification of any User of the T24 System. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MV.ALERT.RES1</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROHIBIT.COMPS</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the companies (or branches) in which this Department Account Officer code may not be used. </p><p>   If this Department Account Officer code may only be used in certain Companies (or branches), either the Companies in which it may not be used are specified in this field, or the Companies in which it may be used are specified in RESTR.TO.COMPS. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Company ID:  cc-ggg-nnnn                     or Company Mnemonic:  2-3 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.')                    characters.  Multivalue field.  [Optional input.  Not allowed if RESTR.TO.COMPS is input.  No input in either of these fields means the Department Account Officer code may be used in all Companies].</p><p>   Must be the Code or Mnemonic of an existing Company on the COMPANY table.</p><p>   Duplicates are not allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.LEVEL</field>
<desc><p>This fields indicates the level of this department within the departmental hierarchy. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Must be a valid entry of the DEPT.LEVEL file.</p><p>   Mandatory if DEPT.PARENT is input, otherwise optional.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.ALERT.RES2</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTR.TO.COMPS</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the companies (or branches) in which this Department Account Officer code may be used. </p><p>   If this Department Account Officer code may only be used in certain Companies (or branches), either the Companies in which it may be used are specified in this field, or the Companies in which it may not be used are specified in PROHIBIT.COMPS. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Company ID: cc-ggg-nnnn              or Company Mnemonic:  2-3 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.')                    characters.  Multivalue field.  [Optional input.  Not allowed if PROHIBIT.COMPS is input.  No input in either of these fields means the Department Account Officer code may be used in all Companies.]</p><p>   Must be the Code or Mnemonic of an existing Company on the COMPANY table.</p><p>   Duplicates are not allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DELIVERY.POINT</field>
<desc><p>Indicates the internal office location for delivery of reports. </p><p>   The purpose of this field is to indicate a Delivery Point for the delivery of reports, etc. to the corresponding Department/Account Officer. Information like the name of the Building or the Floor number where this area is located are typical examples of information applicable to this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   1-16 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.ALERT.RES3</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPERAND</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.ALERT.RES4</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.ACCT.OFF.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the Department or Account Officer. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   1-4 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)  This code must be in the range 0001-9999 and represents the ID of the table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FAX.NO</field>
<desc><p>Free format field for the entry of an account officers fax number. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Up to 15 alphanumeric characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAME</field>
<desc><p>Indicates the name of the Department Head or the name of the Account Officer, working in the area specified. </p><p>   The actual name of the Account Officer or Department Head should be entered in this field. </p><p>   When an Application refers to a Department or Account Officer, the content of this field will be shown as the enrichment of the code being input/ displayed. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   3-35 type A (alphanumeric) (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC</field>
<desc><p /><p>   MNEMONIC</p><p>   Specifies an alternative method of referencing the Department Account Officer. </p><p>   The Mnemonic code rather than the Account ID may be used at any time to </p><p>   reference the Department Account Officer details. It can be used in situations</p><p>   the bank would like to identify account officers using alphanumeric fields.</p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   3 - 10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or '.') characters. </p><p>   The Mnemonic code must be unique.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.ALERT.RES6</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TELEX.NO</field>
<desc><p>Free format field for the entry of an account officers telex number. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Up to 8 alphanumeric characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.ALERT.RES5</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TELEPHONE.NO</field>
<desc><p>Free format field for the entry of an account officers telephone number. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Up to 15 alphanumeric characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.ID</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPT.PARENT</field>
<desc><p>This fields refers to another DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER record that is the 'parent' of this one in the departmental hierarchy. For example, if this record represents a dealer desk then the DEPT.PARENT may point to the record representing 'Treasury'. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Must be a valid entry on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p><p>   The DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER specified here must be of a higher level than the current record.</p><p>   Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REQUEST.ID</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPARTMENT</field>
<desc><p>DEPARTMENT</p><p /><p>   This field can be used when the account officer is part of an account key if the DAO ID</p><p>   is greater than 4 digits.</p><p /><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>   Up to 4 numeric characters are allowed.</p><p>   It must exist as a record in DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCEPT.MESSAGE</field>
<desc><p>This field specifies whether this account officer will accept secure messages. Functionaly, this field is</p><p> linked with the table EB.SECURE.MESSAGE which establish secure messaging between bank user and customer.</p><p /><p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p>:</p></p><p>  Must be allowed to input YES or Blank</p><p>  If the input is YES then account officer will accept messages triggered from the customers.</p><p>  Otherwise it will not accept messages.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.DEPT.LEVEL</field>
<desc><p>This fields indicates the level of this department within the alternative departmental hierarchy. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Must be a valid entry on the ALT.DEPT.LEVEL file.</p><p>   Mandatory if ALT.DEPT.PARENT is input, otherwise optional.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALT.DEPT.PARENT</field>
<desc><p>This fields refers to another DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER record that is the 'parent' of this one in the alternative departmental hierarchy. For example, if this record represents a dealer desk then the ALT.DEPT.PARENT may point to the record representing 'Treasury'. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   Must be a valid entry on the DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER file.</p><p>   The DEPT.ACCT.OFFICER specified here must be of a higher level than the current record.</p><p>   Optional Input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AREA</field>
<desc><p>Free format description of the Area of responsibility for the Account Officer. </p><p>   When the code being created refers to a Department (Foreign Exchange, Funds Transfer Unit, Money Market, etc.), the name of the Department should be entered in this field. </p><p>   If the code being created refers to an Account Officer, the name of the area where the Account Officer is working (e.g. Private Banking Group, Financial Institutions, etc.) should be entered in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

