<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>FT.CHARGE.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This table defines the conditions relating to various types of standard 'flat' charges used by T24. </p><p>Charges in local currency must be entered and foreign currency charges can also be specifically defined if required.  The Currency of the Account bearing the Charge determines the Charge Currency applied.  Where no charges exist in the Account Currency the default local currency charges will apply and the System will take the currency equivalent using the rates held on the Currency file. </p><p>In all cases the charge amount will be a 'Flat' Amount, regardless of the monetary value of the Transaction. </p><p>Where necessary, the Charge can be defined according to the destination Country Zone, defined as the residence of the Credit party.  This facility should only be used in respect of charges for telex, or postage where various charges are applicable due to the locality. The entire charge can be waived depending on whether the ordering customer is resident or non-resident within certain countries. </p><p>In addition CHARGE.TYPES can be linked to allow different charge structures, tax codes etc to be applied depending on the residence of the ordering customer. For example charges can be defined for EEC and NON-EEC resident customers. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the Tax record, or Tax Type COndition record which specifies the tax calculation and processing applicable to the Charge Type. </p><p>This would be applicable to countries where banking services are subject to local taxes (e.g. VAT).  The Application will then calculate taxes on the Charge according to the Tax Rate defined in the Tax table. </p><p>The Tax Code, or Tax Code derived from the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION record used in this field is passed to Delivery as a suffix to the tax code TAX.  This combined code will be used within Delivery to provide meaningful text for credit/debit advices. </p><p>Note : The entry in the Tax table should only contain one rate because        multiple tax rate codes will not be allowed within the Funds        Transfer main program when the User processes a transaction. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-2 numeric character TAX CODE             or up to 16 character TAX.TYPE.CONDITION id prefixed with a "*".  (Optional input.)</p><p>It must be a valid code on the Tax table.</p><p>Tax Type Condition ids must exist on the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION file. These ids are prefixed with a "*" character.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.AMT</field>
<desc><p>Defines the amount to be charged for this Charge Type in the Currency defined in the associated Charge currency. </p><p>For Currencies where no Charge has been specified, the System will take the equivalent (at the currency table middle rate) of the local currency amount which must be entered for each Zone group. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 14 type AMT characters (standard amount format).  Associated sub-value field.  (Mandatory if associated field of Charge Currency, is input otherwise not allowed.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.DATE</field>
<desc><p>This system updated field will hold all future dated entered records for this CHARGE type that are presently on file. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLUDE.FROM.EIR</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ZONE</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Zone to be used when the destination country of the remittance/advice has not been defined in COUNTRY. </p><p>Any destination country which has not been specifically defined within this record will automatically fall within this default Zone and its corresponding Charge. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 2 numeric characters.  [Mandatory input if Currency is blank, otherwise not allowed.]</p><p>It must be a Zone number defined within this record.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE.DR</field>
<desc><p>Defines the (optional) transaction code to be used on the debit entry generated by the application for this Charge Type. </p><p>This field defines the default transaction code which will be assigned to the debit entry to the account bearing the charge.  However, the application may assign its own transaction code if for example the transaction is debit plus charges or the charges are consolidated before posting. </p>
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
<p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
<p>Any Transaction code where DATA.CAPTURE has been defined with 'Y' will be refused.</p><p>Transaction codes with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = to 'CREDIT' will not be allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>This is the code by which this Charge Type can be identified. </p><p>When defining the Charge ID by means of an alpha key the User should try to use meaningful codes to facilitate easy identification of the Charge Type.  Examples could be: </p><p>           TT = Telex Charges            PO = Postage Charges            TE = Telephone Charges </p><p>The codes defined in this field are passed to Delivery as a suffix to the charge code FTCHG.  The combined code will be used within Delivery to provide meaningful text for credit/debit advices. </p><p>Charges can be linked together by using an ID in the format XXXXX.YYYYY. All codes with the prefix XXXXXX will be 'linked'.  Consequently when ANY charge code with the prefix XXXXX is used all linked records will also be processed. This is primarily used for defining different charges for resident and non-resident customers. </p><p>e.g. </p><p>Codes      Amounts      Residence/Non residence HC         5.00         resident *EEC HC.NEEC    10.00        non-resident *EEC </p><p>When either HC or HC.NEEC is used both will be examined and the correct charge calculated based on the residence of the ordering customer. NOTE : A linked record cannot be input without a corresponding master record, i.e. XXXXX.YYYYY cannot exist without charge code XXXXX. </p><p>Charges can be entered for future dates by using an ID in the format XXXXX.YYYYY-YYYYMMDD.  All codes with a suffix in the above date format separated by the delimiter '-' are for future charge changes. Only future dated existing charge types can be entered in the above format. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>11 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESIDENCY</field>
<desc><p>Defines the COUNTRY and/or the COUNTRY.GROUP(s) where if the ordering customer is resident then the charge WILL be applied. </p><p>This field allows you to relate the charge to customers resident in specific countries, or groups of countries. If the ordering customer is not resident in a country defined here then this charge will not be applied. </p><p>If RESIDENCY and NON.RESIDENCY are blank then the charge will be applied. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>6 alphanumeric characters.</p><p>Input must be in the format:          XX   where XX is a valid code on the COUNTRY file. or         *ZZZZ where ZZZZ is a valid code on the COUNTRY.GROUP file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.PERIOD</field>
<desc><p>Defines the minimum number of months which comprise the smallest allowable charging period, used in conjunction with the CHARGE.PERIOD defined. </p><p>The minimum period may be defined as monthly, quarterly, half-yearly, nine-monthly, annually, or bi-annually. The contract period will be divided into a number of charging periods as defined in CHARGE.PERIOD. This will then be compared against the MINIMUM.PERIOD, if the the minimum period yields a large value, this will be used to calculate the final chargeable amount. </p><p>Currently only used in the Trade Finance module. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1, 3, 6, 9, 12 or 24 months.</p><p>Optional input</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.NARR</field>
<desc><p>Swift narrative used only for Letters of Credit (Trade Finance) </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLAT.AMT</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Amount to be charged for this Charge Type in the Currency defined in the preceding field. </p><p>For Currencies where no Charge has been specified, the System will take the equivalent (at the currency table middle rate) of the local currency amount (which must be input) if any Flat Amount is to be levied. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 14 type AMT characters (standard amount format).  Associated multivalue field.  (Mandatory input if Currency is input otherwise not allowed.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINK</field>
<desc><p>Contains a list of all charge codes 'linked' to the master charge. </p><p>See field 0 for more details. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a system maintained, NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE.CR</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Transaction code to be used on the credit entry automatically generated by Funds Transfer for this Charge Type. </p><p>This field defines the Transaction code which will be assigned to the Credit Charge entry generated (as a result of using this Charge Type) in the Profit and Loss category code or the internal Account as specified in Category/Account field. </p><p /><p>Note : For charges calculated on Foreign Exchange Contracts, this code is        also used in the debit entry. </p>
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
<p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
<p>Any Transaction code where DATA.CAPTURE has been defined with 'Y' will be refused.</p><p>Transaction codes with the DEBIT.CREDIT.IND = to 'DEBIT' will not be allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.8</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future use. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ZONE</field>
<desc><p>Assigns a unique number for the Zone being defined in order that the default conditions can be identified. </p><p>The following example demonstrates the use of the Zone fields: </p><p>Example:   Field Name              Field Input </p><p>           Default Zone                1            Zone                        1            Currency                GBP (local)            Amount                      1.00            Currency                USD            Amount                      1.50 </p><p>           Zone                        2            Country                 VE            Country                 BR            Country                 AR            Currency                GBP (local)            Amount                      2.00            Currency                USD            Amount                      3.00 </p><p>           Zone                        3            Country                 HK            Country                 JP            Currency                GBP (local)            Amount                      3.00            Currency                USD            Amount                      4.50 </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 2 numeric characters.  Associated multivalue field.  (Mandatory input if no Flat Charge details are entered, otherwise not allowed.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY</field>
<desc><p>Defines the destination Country(ies), of the associated payment, to which the Zone charge will apply. </p><p>To minimize the input, the User should not include any Country code for the default Zone and only define the exception countries in the other Zone(s). </p><p>The destination of the payment will always be determined from the residence of Credit A/C Customer. </p><p>Example: </p><p>If the telex charges to all countries except Japan and Australia are GBP 2.00 the following should be input: </p><p>           Field Name              Field Input </p><p>           Default Zone                 1 </p><p>           Zone                         1            Country                      -            Currency                    GBP            Amount                      2.00 </p><p>           Zone                         2            Country                     JP (Japan) </p><p>           Country                     AU (Australia)            Currency                    GBP            Amount                      5.00 </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>2 type SSS (Uppercase alpha) character Country code.  Associated sub-value field.  (Mandatory input unless defining charges for Default Zone when it is optional.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESCR</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Charge Type in an abbreviated format which can be used for reporting where space is limited. </p><p>This multivalue field is used to enter a Short Description for the Charge Type code in various languages.  Each expansion will correspond to a new Language as defined in the Language Table and will indicate to the User the Language in which this Short Description must be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-15 type AA (alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters.  Multilanguage field.  (Mandatory input.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.6</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.CCY</field>
<desc><p>The definition of the currency which is to be used as the default for calculation of the commissions. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character          or 1-3 numeric character Currency code.  Must be defined in the field CURRENCY.  (Mandatory input  if the Local currency is not defined in the CURRENCY field)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPECIAL.ACCR.COMM</field>
<desc><p>Reserved for future use. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>INAU</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.7</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future use. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field. (Internal field.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CCY</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Currency of the Charge input in the associated field. </p><p>Charges must  be specified in default or local currency and if special Charges are to be applicable to different Currencies then Charges must also be specified for each applicable Currency. </p><p>The Currency refers to the Currency of the Account bearing the charge. </p><p>Both the Currency and the Flat Amount fields will be used when the Charge being defined does not vary according to the Region.  If, however, the User is defining, for example, the telex charge which varies from one country to another, the Destination group of multivalue fields would be used. </p><p>If a charge is to be taken in a currency not defined, the default currency charge definition is used, otherwise the local currency definition. </p><p>If a default currency is defined and CURRENCY is not being entered then the default currency charge definition is mandatory, otherwise the local currency definition is mandatory </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 type SSS (Uppercase alpha) character              or 1-3 numeric character currency code.  Associated sub-value field.  (Mandatory input if no 'Flat-Charge' details are entered, otherwise not allowed.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MTHLY.AMORTISATION</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether, depending on the type of contract involved, the charge should be amortised. </p><p>YES indicates that the charge will be amortised (taken into P&amp;L over the life of the contract), NO indicates that the charge will be treated on a cash basis. </p><p>Note : This option is only relevant for certain contract types, e.g.        Letters of Credit. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 Alphanumeric   YES or NO.  Mandatory input.</p><p>Once input this field cannot be changed.</p><p>Must be YES or NO.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMORTISN.PERIOD</field>
<desc><p>This field specifies the period over which the charge should be amortised. </p><p>The following examples show the format of the amortisation period: </p><p>           1M to 11M    range = 1 to 11 months            1A to 99A    range = 1 to 99 years </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-3 alphanumeric characters.</p><p>Once input this field cannot be changed.</p><p>Mandatory if MTHLY.AMORTISATION is YES, NOINPUT if MTHLY.AMORTISATION is NO.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APPLICATION</field>
<desc><p>Reserved for future use </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.AMT.ON</field>
<desc><p>Reserved for future use </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Profit &amp; Loss category or internal account to which the Charge should be credited. </p><p>Normally the Charge being collected from the Customer is always in favour of a bank and consequently a valid Profit and Loss category code should be entered.  However, if for any reason, the bank is also acting as a collecting agent for a third party (e.g. Government), then an internal Account number should instead be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>4-5 numeric character Category code                         or  6-12 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha)      character local currency internal Account number       or  3-10 type MNE (uppercase alpha or numeric or ".") character Account      Mnemonic.  (Mandatory input.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PERIOD</field>
<desc><p>Defines the number of months that comprise a charging period. </p><p>A charge may be made periodically, e.g monthly, quarterly, etc. This field determines he length of time for which the charge type record applies. </p><p>The period of the contract will be split in the number of periods defined in this field to calculate the total charge amount, for example a contract lasting one year, with CHARGE.PERIOD set to 3, would incur 4 times the defined commission amount, since the period has been defined as quarterly. </p><p>The corresponding field MINIMUM.PERIOD can be used to specify the minimum number of periods to be considered. </p><p>Note that this is currently utilised only by the Trade Finance module. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1, 3, 6, 9, 12 or 24.</p><p>Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc><p>Defines the Currency of the Amount input in the associated FLAT.AMT field. </p><p>Charges must  be specified in default or local currency and if special Charges are to be applicable to different Currencies then Charges must also be specified for each applicable Currency. </p><p>The Currency refers to the Currency of the Account bearing the charge. </p><p>Both the Currency and the Flat Amount fields will be used when the Charge being defined does not vary according to the Region.  If, however, the User is defining, for example, the telex charge which varies from one country to another, the Destination group of multivalue fields would be used. </p><p>If a charge is to be taken in a currency not defined, the default currency charge definition is used, otherwise the local currency definition. </p><p>If a default currency is defined and Zone is not being entered then the default currency charge definition is mandatory, otherwise the local currency definition is mandatory. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character             or 1-3 numeric character Currency code.  Associated multivalue field.  (Mandatory input if Zone is not being entered otherwise not allowed.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.RESIDENCY</field>
<desc><p>Defines the COUNTRY and/or the COUNTRY.GROUP(s) where if the ordering customer is NOT resident then the charge WILL be applied. </p><p>This field allows you to relate the charge to customers non-resident in specific countries, or groups of countries. If the ordering customer is resident in one of the countries defined here then this charge will not be applied. </p><p>If RESIDENCY and NON.RESIDENCY are blank then the charge will be applied. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>6 Alphanumeric characters.</p><p>Input must be in the format:         XX   where XX is a valid code on the COUNTRY file.  or        *ZZZZ where ZZZZ is a valid code on the COUNTRY.GROUP file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Charge Type. </p><p>This field provides a Description of the Charge Type and is used for the enrichment in Funds Transfer or Standing Orders. </p><p>It can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the Charge Type in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the Language table, and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field.  (Mandatory input.)</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

