<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>GLOBAL.CUSTOMER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The global Customer Table is used to identify in one single place all the multi-national Customers to whom the bank wants to assign on a worldwide basis a unique identification number. </p><p>The Global Customer number can then be entered in a Customer record to link together various Customer records. </p><p>If for example you have defined in your Customer Database different records for Citibank Brussels, Citibank London, Citibank Tokyo, Citibank Sao Paulo, etc.., each of these customer records can be linked together by means of the Global customer number which would refer, for example, to 'CITIBANK N.A.' </p><p>Ideally, this list of Global Customer names and numbers should be defined by your Head office which could then request from all its branches to send on a regular basis management information on any activity they have with these customers.  Your Head-office will then be in a position to consolidate the branches data on a worldwide basis (e.g. global account profitability, global credit exposure item). </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>GLOBAL.CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc><p>This is the code by which the Global Customer can be identified. </p><p>The list of Global Customer numbers should be unique across your institution and for this reason should be defined centrally by your Head-office. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-10 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the name of the Global Customer and will be used for on-line enrichments in any field where a Global Customer number can be input. </p><p>This field can be expanded to allow the user to enter the short name of the Global Customer in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES) and will indicate to the user the language in which the short name must be entered. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Multilanguage field.  Multivalue field.  (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

