<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>INT.MOVEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This is a "Live" file holding details of all Interest and Tax Movements across all accounts in the database. </p><p>Depending on the way INT.MOVEMENT.PARAM is setup, this file will hold Credit, Debit and Tax entries. This file is keyed on "Deal - Date" where the date can be either the Booking or the Value date. The Tax returns will be generated based on the contents of this file. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>GROSS.NET.IND</field>
<desc><p>Fields TRANS.REF to 29.1 form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>A maximum of 5 characters may be entered.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.SECTOR</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Description of this record. </p><p>This field will not contain any data unless a record has been input in the file INT.MOVEMENT.ADJ. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Language based description field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.LIQ.ACCT</field>
<desc><p>Contains the Interest Liquidation Account associated with this Transaction. </p><p>The account to which the Interest is liquidated will be held in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard T24 Account Number format.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc><p>The SYSTEM Refrence of the Transaction. </p><p>This field will contain the T24 Application that generated this Transaction. </p><p>Examples of valid T24 SYSTEM.IDs are AC, IC1, IC2, MM, LD etc. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Any T24 Application Id.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future use. </p><p>This field is part of the Multi value set and is reserved            for future use. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Noinput field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.NO</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NO</field>
<desc><p>The STMT.ENTRY key(s) associated with thistransaction. </p><p>Sub valued to enable more than one STMT.ENTRY record to included in one Multi value set. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must be an ID to the STMT.ENTRY file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY</field>
<desc><p>The Currency of this transaction is defined here. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must exist on the CURRENCY file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.INT.FCY</field>
<desc><p>The Credit Interest amount if the Currency is not the Local Currency. </p><p>The amount recogonised by the system as a Credit Interest entry in a foreign currency will be stored in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard amount format depending on the currency of this transaction.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.NO</field>
<desc><p>The CRF No associated with this transaction. </p><p>This field will be used in Money Market when the Interest is capitalised as in this case no Accounting entry is generated for the Interest amount. This field is Sub valued to enable more than one CRF entry being generated for one transaction. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must be an Id to RE.CONSOL.SPEC.ENTRY file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>The Value date associated with this transaction. </p><p>Contains the Value date of the transaction. Will be the same as the date on the Key of this record if the DATE.TO.USE field on the file INT.MOVEMENT.PARAM specifies "Value date". </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard date format.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Fields TRANS.REF to RESERVED.1 form a related multi value set. Standard T24 numeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 10 characters may be entered.</p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.INT.LCY</field>
<desc><p>The Credit Interest amount in the Local Currency. </p><p>The amount recogonised by the system as the credit interest entry in the Local Currency of the database (either the Local equivalent or the Local Currency amount) will be stored in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard amount format for the Local Currency of the database.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.REF</field>
<desc><p>The T24 Transaction Reference associated with this record. </p><p>In most cases, this field will contain the same data as the ID of this record except in Account capitalisations when this field will contain the Id to STMT.ACCT.CR, CR2, DR or DR2 files.  This is the start of the Multi Value set. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard T24 Transaction Reference. In case of Account Capitalisations this field will have the ACCOUNT-Capitalisation date stored in this field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.NO</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.CODE</field>
<desc><p>This field is part of the Multi value set and is reserved for future use. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CCY.MKT</field>
<desc><p>The Currency Market associated with this transaction. </p><p>The use of this field will only be applicable for those countries where the exchange authorities have defined different markets for foreign currency dealing. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>One digit Currency Market Code.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc><p>The exchange rate associated with this transaction. </p><p>The exchange rate applicable for foreign currency transactions is stored in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard Rate format (Type "R").</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.FCY</field>
<desc><p>The Tax amount if the Currency is not the Local Currency. </p><p>The amount recogonised by the system as a Tax entry in a foreign currency will be stored in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard amount format depending on the currency of this transaction.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future use. </p><p>This field is part of the Multi value set and is reserved            for future use. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Noinput field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ACCOUNT</field>
<desc><p>Fields TRANS.REF to 29.1 form a related multi value set. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>A maximum of 14 characters may be entered.</p><p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the ACCOUNT file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JNT.ACC.HLDR</field>
<desc><p>The Joint Holder Customer number associated with this account record will be stored here for denoting the Tax amount for the Joint Holder customer for an account with joint holders.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Joint Holder Customer Number</p><p>Sub-valued if more than one Joint Holder in the Account record.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.HIS.NO</field>
<desc><p>The Customer associated with this transaction will be stored here. </p><p>The Customer number associated with this record will be stored in this field. The Customer Number can be optionally followed by a ";" and a History Number, in which case that History Number should be used for getting the Customer details. </p><p>This field will be used if the static data on the CUSTOMER file has changed and the correct static data can be accessed using this History Number on the Customer record. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Customer Number followed optionally by a ";" and the History Number.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MMDEAL.NO</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.LCY</field>
<desc><p>The Debit Interest amount in the Local Currency. </p><p>The amount recogonised by the system as the Debit interest entry in the Local Currency of the database (either the Local equivalent or the Local Currency amount) will be stored in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard amount format for the Local Currency of the database.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.LCY</field>
<desc><p>The Tax amount in the Local Currency. </p><p>The amount recogonised by the system as the Tax entry in the Local Currency of the database (either the Local equivalent or the Local Currency amount) will be stored in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard amount format for the Local Currency of the database.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future use. </p><p>This field is part of the Multi value set and is reserved            for future use. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Noinput field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE</field>
<desc><p>The transaction code associated with this transaction. </p><p>Specifies the Transaction Code(s) associated with this entry. Sub Valued to enable recording more than one transaction code per multi value set. Such a situation could arise in Money Market for example, when the Credit Interest and the tax are applied as one multivalue set in this file (Interest applied Net of tax). </p><p>The codes in this field must be present on the TRANSACTION file. </p>
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
<p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL.DATE</field>
<desc><p>The ID of the record. </p><p>There will be one record in this file for each Interest or Tax entry for each Deal within the database. The "Date" in this field will be either the Booking date or the Value date depending on the field "DATE.TO.USE" in the field INT.MOVEMENT.PARAM. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The format will be Deal Id "-" Date, where the Deal Id is either the Account Number or the Contract Number and the Date is either the Value date ot the Booking date.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BOOK.DATE</field>
<desc><p>The Booking date associated with this transaction. </p><p>Contains the Run date on which this transaction was generated. Will be the same as the date on the Key of this record if the DATE.TO.USE field on the file INT.MOVEMENT.PARAM specifies "Booking date". </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard date format.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.LIQ.CUST</field>
<desc><p>This field contains the Customer associated with the Interest Liquidation account. </p><p>The Customer Number in this field is optionally followed by a History number which can then be used to identify changes in Customer staitc data. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Customer Number optionally followed by a ";" and a History Number.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JNT.HLDR.TAX</field>
<desc><p>The Tax amount in the Local currency for the joint holder customer for this transaction account record is displayed here. Will be displayed for accounts with joint holders and Tax to be computed customer wise based on their tax status.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Standard amount format for the Local Currency of the database.</p><p>Sub-valued if more than one joint holder for the account record.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEAL</field>
<desc><p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Mandatory input.</p><p>A maximum of 40 characters may be entered.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PURGE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MM.CATEGORY</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.FCY</field>
<desc><p>The Debit Interest amount if the Currency is not the Local Currency. </p><p>The amount recogonised by the system as a Debit Interest entry in a foreign currency will be stored in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Standard amount format depending on the currency of this transaction.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc><p>The Tax code associated with this transaction. </p><p>The Tax code is held in this field for transactions that are recogonised by the system as a Tax entry. The tax code held in this field will optionally include the effective date of the TAX record. If the effective date is not stored in this field then it has to be computed using the Booking date of this transaction. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Tax code as specified on the "TAX" file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.CATEGORY</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.CUST.TAX</field>
<desc><p>The Tax amount in the Local currency for the main customer for this transaction account record is displayed here. Will be displayed for accounts with joint holders and Tax to be computed customer wise based on their tax status.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Standard amount format for the Local Currency of the database.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc><p>The Main Customer number associated with this account record will be stored here for denoting the Tax amount for the main customer for an account with joint holders.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Main Customer Number</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.NO</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

