<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>INT.MOVEMENT.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This is a Parameter file that is used in the extraction of Interest (both Credit and Debit) and Tax entries within T24. </p><p>The extraction of the data is based on T24 Transaction codes which have to be defined on this table. </p><p>There can only be one record in this table with an ID of "SYSTEM". </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field.</p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRF.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Defines the CRF TXN code which should be used to extract interest/charge information to be stored in the INTEREST.MVMT files. </p><p>RE.CONSOL.SPEC.ENTRY records will be examined to see if the specified transaction matches for the associated system id. For example all capitalised interest may be required fro MM and can be found by specifying the "CAP" transactions </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 alpha character field.  Optional input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.PL</field>
<desc><p /><p>This indicates to the Debit category code the debit entries to be posted.</p><p>Should be a profit and loss category.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional field, should be a valid profit and loss category code</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc><p>The Key to this record. </p><p>There can only be one record in this file and it has to have the ID of "SYSTEM". </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Only the value "SYSTEM" is accepted.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVMT.BY.COMP</field>
<desc><p><p>This field is to specify whether company mnemonic should be added to the ID or not for the files INT.MOVEMENT, TX.INT.MOVEMENT.DATE &amp; TX.SEC.TXN.LIST</p></p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p><p>The following values are permitted:       YES       NO     </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Noinput field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.YEAR.START</field>
<desc><p>Defines the date from which the Tax year starts. </p><p>The date input in this field is checked when the Interest and Tax movements are extracted. Any Interest or Tax movement that is dated prior to this date will not be extracted into the INT.MOVEMENT file. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Any valid date is allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.INT.CODES</field>
<desc><p>Defines which Transaction codes are used to post Debit Interest entries, or Tax on Charges (VAT). </p><p>The transaction code in this field has to be present in the file TRANSACTION. When the extract of the Interest Movements is done the system will check the Transaction code of the entry with this field and move the entry details as a Debit Interest movement, if it matches the transaction code in this field. The transaction code defined here must not be Duplicated in either the Credit or the Tax transaction code. </p>
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p>Optional field </p> 
<p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
<p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>  
<p> Sub valued to enable input of more than one transaction code.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PURGE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the date after which data from the INT.MOVEMENT file will be purged. </p><p>Any Interest or Tax entry in the file F.INT.MOVEMENT that is prior to the date in this field will be purged by the system. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Any valid date is allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODES</field>
<desc><p>Defines which Transaction codes are used to post Tax entries. </p><p>The transaction code in this field has to be present in the file TRANSACTION. When the extract of the Interest Movements is done the system will check the Transaction code of the entry with this field and move the entry details as a Tax entry, if it matches the transaction code in this field. The transaction code entered in this field must not be duplicated either as a Debit or a Credit transaction code. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Optional field, up to 3 character numeric data.  Sub valued to enable input of more than one transaction code.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROSS.NET.INT</field>
<desc><p>Flag to determine if Interest if paid Gross or Net of Tax for the associated T24 Application. </p><p>This flag indicates if Interest is paid to the customer gross or net of tax. It is to be noted that applications like MM, LD etc are hard-coded within T24 to post only the Net Interest to the Customer. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Mandatory field and only the values "GROSS" or "NET" are accepted.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.YEAR.END</field>
<desc><p>Defines the date on which the Tax year ends. </p><p>The date input in this field is used to determine if an Interest or Tax entry is to be extracted into the file F.INT.MOVEMENT. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Any valid date is allowed.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc><p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.LAST.RUN</field>
<desc><p>Multivalue field giving details of when the Tax Returns were last produced. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Field having details of User, Date and Time when the last Tax Returns were produced.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.ENT.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Defines whether or not the associated DR.INT.CODES are to be extracted when processing Account or Profit and Loss entries, or both. </p><p>The entry will be only be extracted if the TRANSACTION.CODE matches the associated DR.INT.CODES and is of the specified type, which may be: </p><p>        STMT  - Account entries found on STMT.ENTRY         CATEG - Profit and Loss entries found on CATEG.ENTRY         BOTH  - The entry will be extracted in either case </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Alpha characters, must be STMT, CATEG or BOTH.  Default value STMT.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc><p>Start of a Multi value set defining the extract conditions. </p><p>The contents in this field will define any valid T24 APPLICATION for which the rest of the Multi Value set applies. </p><p>This field is Sub-Valued to enable input of more than one Application Id. The value "ALL" is also allowed in which case it refers to ALL T24 Applications. Care must be taken if "ALL" is input since the Transaction codes defined in the following fields will have to be unique across all applications within T24. </p><p>Valid Applications can be AC, IC1, IC2, MM, LD, etc. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Mandatory field, 2 to 5 characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TO.USE</field>
<desc><p>Defines if the Booking Date ot the Value date is to be used as the key of the extracted information. </p><p>The details of Interest and Tax movements are extracted and stored in the file F.INT.MOVEMENT with a Key of "Deal ID - Date". The "date" on this Key can be either the Booking date or the Value date of the entry depending on the Value of this field. </p><p>When the Tax returns are produced the date in the Key of the file INT.MOVEMENT is used to determine if that record has to be included in the returns or not. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Mandatory field.  Can have the value "BOOKING.DATE" or "VALUE.DATE".  The contents of this field can not be changed after authorisation.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Description of this record. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3 to 35 Alphanumeric characters.  Language dependent text.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADJ.CODES</field>
<desc><p>Defines which of the above transaction codes are used for Adjustment entries. </p><p>The transaction code used in this field will denote that this is used for posting adjustment entries.  It must exist in the file TRANSACTION and must have been defined as either a valid Debit, Credit or a Tax transaction code. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 3 Numeric character optional field.  Sub valued to enable input of more than one transaction code.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.ENT.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>            STMT  - Account entries found on STMT.ENTRY             CATEG - Profit and Loss entries found on CATEG.ENTRY             BOTH  - The entry will be extracted in either case </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Alpha characters, must be STMT, CATEG or BOTH.  Default value STMT.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.INT.CODES</field>
<desc><p>Defines which Transaction codes are used to post Credit Interest entries. </p><p>The transaction code in this field has to be present in the file TRANSACTION. When the extract of the Interest Movements is done the system will check the Transaction code of the entry with this field and move the entry details as a Credit Interest movement, if it matches the transaction code in this field. The transaction code defined in this field must not be duplicated in eithre the Debit or the Tax transaction code. </p>
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p>Optional field </p> 
<p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
<p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>  
<p> Sub valued to enable input of more than one transaction code.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.INT.PL</field>
<desc><p>Defines which Category codes used for Credit entries to be posted. </p><p>Should be a valid profit and loss category.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Optional field, should be a valid profit and loss category code</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

