<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>MARKET.RATE.TEXT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This table defines Descriptions of tradable interest rates which are recognised by S.W.I.F.T. </p><p>Each Description will be used as the enrichment to the corresponding ID when it is displayed or printed during T24 processing. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RATE.TEXT</field>
<desc><p>Must be a valid S.W.I.F.T. code word. This field specifies the Floating Rate Option of the swap transaction. The value in this field should be one of the valid code words as specified in the details for field 14F on MT360s. </p><p>Input should be in the form ; </p><p>     alpha/alpha/alpha </p><p>e.g. USD/LIBOR/ISDA </p><p>or if the code word is not known input should be OTHER. </p><p>Refer to the SWIFT manual and ISDA definitions for further details. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>24 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Multi-language field allowing the user to specify a description for the record. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>15 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc><p>This field is used as the key to the records on this table. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to six alphanumeric charaters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.KEY</field>
<desc><p>This field specifies a valid sequence number of the file PERIODIC.INTEREST. </p><p>This sequence number is part of the key to the PERIODIC.INTEREST rate table. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-2 numeric characters. Optional input field.</p></desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>SWIFT.CODE.WORD</field>
<desc>
	  <p>This field is meant for specifying the Bilaterally Agreed codes between the Parties involved in the Transaction.</p>
	  <p>Validation Rules:</p>
	  <p>When the value of field RATE.TEXT is OTHER, the value for SWIFT.CODE.WORD is mandatory.</p>
	  <p>When the value of field RATE.TEXT is not OTHER, the value for SWIFT.CODE.WORD should be null.</p>
	  <p>The content should be a valid record ID in the table SWIFT.CODE.WORDS.</p>
</desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

