<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>RELATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The Relation table is used to specify the various types of relation that could exist between Customers.  The purpose of identifying such relationship codes is to provide the bank with the ability to "group" various clients together (in the Customer file) for reporting or information purposes, by whatever criteria considered relevant.</p><p>   999 different relation codes can be defined in this table and, if necessary, up to 999 different Relation codes can be assigned to each Customer record.</p><p>   This table can be used to define corporate Customer Relations (Group, Subsidiary, Affiliate, Branch, etc.) as well as private Customer Relations (Father, Son, Mother, Sister, etc.).</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REVERSE.RELATION</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the relationship from the opposite point of view.</p><p>   The code identifies the reverse relationship.  For example, if the code represented by the ID code is Parent Company, then the code here could be SUBSIDIARY.</p><p>   The system will update the record held for the code in this field as well as the one in the ID (Field 0).</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   1-3 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p><p>   The relation code entered must be different to that on the ID.</p><p>   A relation record cannot already be present for this relation code.</p><p>   Both relation records cannot be amended at the same time.  In other words when the user wants to change the descriptions of two related codes, he must change and authorise each one in sequence because authorisation of the two related codes is not allowed when they are both in an unauthorised status.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Relation code and is used for the enrichment of the code.</p><p>   This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the Relation code in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE Table, and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATION.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the Relation Table details.</p><p>   The code must be in the range 1-999 and represents the ID of the table.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   1-3 numeric characters. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REV.REL.DESC</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Reverse Relation code and is used for the enrichment of the code.</p><p>   This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the Reverse Relation code in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE Table, and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>   3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. Multivalue field. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

