<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>ST.AGGREGATE.BALANCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p>This table contains aggregated balances of a customer. The positions are considered from 'AC' 'LD' 'MM' and 'SC' module.</p>
        <p>This is a live file and regulation name, customer number along with the date of the balance aggregation performed is the ID of the table.</p>
        <p>Aggregated balance will be created for each regulaion and customer.</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ST.REG.CUST.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>ID of the application, Regulation name, Customer number and Date will be the ID of the application.</p>        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will be updated as CUSTOMER or ACCOUNT based on relationship level defined in ST.AGGREGATION.PARAM.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SECTOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the SECTOR of the customer. This field is defaulted from CUSTOMER application.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDUSTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the INDUSTRY of the customer. This field is defaulted from CUSTOMER application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the CUSTOMER.STATUS of the customer. This field is defaulted from CUSTOMER application.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATED.CUSTOMER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will store related customers, provided the relationship with the parent customer is defined in ST.AGGREGATION.PARAM.</p>
            <p>This field will have value only when aggregation is done at CUSTOMER level. i.e. based on the value in CUSTOMER.TYPE</p>
            <p>This field is associated with RELATION.CODE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATION.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Relationship maintained by the RELATED.CUSTOMER with the parent customer. </p>
            <p>This field will have value only when aggregation is done at CUSTOMER level. i.e. based on the value in CUSTOMER.TYPE</p>
            <p>This field is associated with RELATED.CUSTOMER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.PORTFOLIO.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will have any one of the below values</p>            
                <p> I.   Account number </p>
                <p> II.  Portfolio number </p>
                <p> III. MM contract ID </p>
                <p> IV.  LD contract ID </p>
                                            
            <p> Fields starting from ACCT.PORTFOLIO.NO to ACC.BAL.IN.REP.CCY are associated fields. </p>
            <p> Each muti value set will hold the balance details of each ACCOUNT/MM Contract/LD Contract linked to the customer.</p>
            <p> When this field holds a portfolio number, all the security position of the portfolio will be aggregated in a single multi value set. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field will be updated as Depository or Custody. It will be Custody if portfolio balance (including account linked to a portfolio) is reported else the field will be updated as Depository.</p>
            <p>This is based on the account or portfolio in ACCT PORTFOLIO NO field above.</p>
            </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JOINT.OWNER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will store related customers, provided the relationship with the parent customer is defined in ST.AGGREGATION.PARAM.</p>
            <p>This field will have value only when aggregation is done at ACCOUNT level. i.e. based on the value in CUSTOMER.TYPE</p>
            <p>This field is associated with JNT.OWNER.REL.CODE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>JOINT.OWN.REL.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Relationship maintained by the RELATED.CUSTOMER with the parent customer. </p>
            <p>This field will have value only when aggregation is done at ACCOUNT level. i.e. based on the value in CUSTOMER.TYPE</p>
            <p>This field is associated with JOINT.OWNER.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.PORTFOLIO.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency in which the account or the contract has position. This field will not have a value, if ACCT.PORTFOLIO.NO holds a portfolio.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Balance of the account or contract in ACC.PORTFOLIO.CCY. This field will not have a value, if ACCT.PORTFOLIO.NO holds a portfolio.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.EXCH.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Exchange rate of ACC.PORTFOLIO.CCY against ACC.REPORTING.CCY is stored in this field. This field will not have a value, if ACCT.PORTFOLIO.NO holds a portfolio.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.REPORTING.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Currency in which the account or the contract has to be reported.</p>
            <p>This field value will be taken from REPORTING.CCY field of CRS.PARAMETER table for CRS regulation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACC.BAL.IN.REP.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>REPORTING.CCY equivalent of the position is stored in this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.AC.BAL.DEP.RCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>REPORTING.CCY equivalent of the total Depository balance.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.AC.BAL.DEP.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local currency equivalent of the total Depository balance.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.AC.BAL.CUS.RCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>REPORTING.CCY equivalent of the total Custody balance.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.AC.BAL.CUS.LCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Local currency equivalent of the total Custody balance.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INDIVIDUAL.ENTITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field says whether the customer is an individual or an entity. The value in this field is arrived based on the selection criteria given for customer in ST.AGGREGATION.PARAM.</p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Pre-Existing Individual Low, Pre-Existing Individual High, Pre-Existing Entity Low, Pre-Existing Entity High will be updated based on the amounts defined in CRS.PARAMETER for CRS Regulation.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>