<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>ST.AGGREGATION.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
        <p>Parameter to defines the balance aggregation rules for the regulation and the company to which the parameter record applies.</p>
        <p>ST.AGGREGATION.PARAM is a company level parameter table.</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ST.AGGR.PARAM.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>ID is the name of the regulation and company to which the record belongs.</p>
        <p>ID consists of two parts and separated by hyphen. Regulation name should exist in ST.REGULATORY.PARAMETER.</p>
        <p>If company code is blank, system defaults with the current logged customer company.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Allowed to create only for customer level companies.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATION.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to define the relation for balance aggregation process.</p>
        <p>The relationship can be defined at Customer Level (CUSTOMER) or account level (ACCOUNT).</p>
        <p>If the relationships are defined at customer level in T24 CUSTOMER, the field has to be set as CUSTOMER. It will be assumed that all the accounts are jointly held and the balance of all the accounts will be attributed to all the joint holders.</p>
        <p>If the field is set to ACCOUNT, the relationships will be checked at individual account level and only the balances of accounts that are held jointly will be attributed to all the joint holders.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Madatory field</p>
        <p>Allowed values are 'CUSTOMER' or 'ACCOUNT'</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATION.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to hold the relationship for a customer or an account.</p>
        <p>The relation codes, that need to be considered for aggregating the balances, need to be specified in this field.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Multi-value field to accept more than one relation for the regulation.</p>
        <p>Allows to define the valid relation from the 'RELATION' table.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXCLD.FOR.ACCT.AGG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field used to specify the categories of accounts/deposits that need to be excluded from the aggregation process.</p>
        <p>Any account of this category (not linked to a portfolio) will be excluded while determining the aggregate balance.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Should be a valid ID from CATEGORY table.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXC.RULE.APPL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to specify the name of the application, which are required to be excluded from the balance aggregation process.</p>
        <p>Fields from EXC.RULE.APPL to EXC.RULE.VALUE are associated multi-value set. Each multi-value set of the selection criteria will be considered with 'OR' condition.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <P>Currently SEC.ACC.MASTER alone is allowed to define in this field and the portfolios selected from this selection criteria are exempted from balance aggregation.</P>
        <p>EXC.RULE.APPL, EXC.RULE.FIELD, EXC.RULE.OPERAND, EXC.RULE.VALUE are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXC.RULE.FIELD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Valid fields from the application mentioned in EXC.RULE.APPL will be accepted.</p>
        <p>System fields and local reference fields from the application mentioned in EXC.RULE.APPL field are allowed to define.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>I-Descriptors and J-Descriptors fields are not allowed.</p>
        <p>EXC.RULE.APPL, EXC.RULE.FIELD, EXC.RULE.OPERAND, EXC.RULE.VALUE are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXC.RULE.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field accepts the operands 'EQ' 'NE'.</p>
        <p>Based on the operand, the records from the specified application will be excluded or included from balance aggregation.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>EXC.RULE.APPL, EXC.RULE.FIELD, EXC.RULE.OPERAND, EXC.RULE.VALUE are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXC.RULE.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Contains the value to be compared to the application defined in EXC.RULE.APPL field.</p>
        <p>Each sub value of this field will be considered with 'AND' condition. </p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>EXC.RULE.APPL, EXC.RULE.FIELD, EXC.RULE.OPERAND, EXC.RULE.VALUE are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.CUST.FIELD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Fields ENT.CUST.FIELD, ENT.CUST.OPERAND and ENT.CUST.VALUE are associative multi value fields. Each multi value set of the selection criteria will be considered with 'OR' condition. </p>
        <p>This multi-value set fields are used to identify customers who are to be classified as INDIVIDUAL or ENTITY.</p>
        <p>If the ENT.CUST.FIELD is set to 'INDUSTRY', the operand as 'EQ' and the ENT.CUST.VAL is '3200', any customer with the industry code set as '3200' will be considered as ENTITY. All other customers will be considered 'Individuals'.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Should be a valid field from CUSTOMER application.</p>
        <p>I-Descriptors and J-Descriptors are not allowed.</p>
        <p>ENT.CUST.FIELD, ENT.CUST.OPERAND and ENT.CUST.VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.CUST.OPERAND</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field accepts the operands 'EQ' 'NE'. </p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>ENT.CUST.FIELD, ENT.CUST.OPERAND and ENT.CUST.VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENT.CUST.VALUE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Field to hold the values, that are to be compared with the specified CUSTOMER field.</p>
        <p>Each sub value of this field will be considered with 'AND' condition.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>ENT.CUST.FIELD, ENT.CUST.OPERAND and ENT.CUST.VALUE fields are interdependent, all must be populated or blank.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.AGGR.RTN</field>
<desc>
        <p>A local routine can be attached here which will be called during balance aggregation batch jobs.</p>
        <p>This routine will take two arguments, first argument is the customer number, second one is ST.AGGREGATE.BALANCES record.</p>
        <p>This routine can be used to consider additional positions for balance aggregation.</p>
        <p>Customer number is the input argument and aggregate balance record is both input/output argument.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Should have a valid EB.API record.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE.BUILD.RTN</field>
<desc>
        <p>A local routine can be attached here which will be called during balance aggregation batch jobs.</p>
        <p>This routine provides the flexibility to build the customer balances record which is the input for the balance aggregation process.</p>
        <p>Contains three arguments, first argument is the customer number, second argument is the id's separated by field marker and the third argument is the array containing the respective customer information separated by field marker. It can be the customer position record.</p>
        <p>Validation rules </p>
        <p>Should have a valid EB.API record.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>