<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>ST.RATE.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Application to provide the base country for Calculating combined holiday definition which can be referred to decide the rest dates in FORWARD.RATES and PERIODIC.INTEREST table. Post set-up of the Application, the system will ignore the base (local) currency-country and use the Country setup here.</p>
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PI.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This setup along with PI.REGION will give International holiday for calculating Rest period of PERIODIC.INTEREST. This will be used instead of Local country.</p>
			<p>
			            <p>Multi value field.</p>
                        <p>Must be valid country code from COUNTRY table.</p>
						<p> No change field.</p>
			</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PI.REGION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Setup to accept the region code for getting International holiday based on which the rest period for PERIODIC.INTEREST will be calculated.</p>
			<p>
			            <p>Associated Sub Value Field</p>
			            <p>Field associated with PI.COUNTRY.</p>
                        <p>Should be a valid region of the Country specified in PI.COUNTRY. The first 2 chars should be same as the country code</p>
						<p> No change field.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.COUNTRY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This setup along with FWD.REGION will give International holiday for calculating Rest period of FORWARD.RATES. This will be used instead of Local country.</p>
            <p>
			            <p>Multi value field.</p>
                        <p>Must be valid country code from COUNTRY table.</p>
						<p> No change field.</p>
			            <p>When FORWARD.RATES are built from PERIODIC.INTEREST then International Country and region setup of PERIODIC.INTEREST will be picked for processing.</p>
			</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.REGION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Setup to accept the region code for getting International holiday based on which the rest period for FORWARD.RATES will be calculated.</p>
			<p>
			            <p>Associated Sub Value Field</p>
			            <p>Field associated with FWD.COUNTRY.</p>
                        <p>Should be a valid region of the Country specified in FWD.COUNTRY. The first 2 chars should be same as the country code</p>
						<p> No change field.</p>
			</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>COMPANY.CODE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
