<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>ST</product>
        <title>ST.TAX.REPORT.DETAILS</title>
        <table>ST.TAX.REPORT.DETAILS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
               <p>Tax report file used to store customerwise tax details against a single transaction</p>
            </ovdesc>
    </overview>
	<menu>
	<t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Transaction reference ID</p>
				<p>ID comprises of the underlying transaction's ID, passed by calling application. If calling application does not pass this, check if ID.NEW is available and take that as transaction reference</p>	
				<p>For an AA deposit arrangement, a credit interest is capitalised and a tax is calculated via an activity AAA1. Then a ST.TAX.REPORT.DETAILS record would be created with ID AAA1. For security, it would be security transaction id and for an account, it would be combination of AC number!Interest.date</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>


<t>
            <field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the contract ID of the underlying transaction</p>
				<p>In case of AA deposit, it would be the arrangement ID, for credit interest it would be the account number itself and for security transactions it could be the portfolio number. Application to pass this ID</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>


<t>
            <field>TRANS.COMPANY</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the company ID of the transaction If not given, this would be default to the current company id</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>RESERVED03</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>RESERVED02</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>RESERVED01</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>CUST.INCOME.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the contract customer "*" Income.source for this transaction like - credit interest, dividend on bonds, deposit payout, etc</p>
				<p>Customer id and income.type together should be unique, passed by application</p>
				<p>So, customer 'A', the primary owner, can have multiple incomes generated as part of a transaction like Interest or holdings, capital gains or there can be multiple customers against a transaction having same or different incomes gained from the transaction, like Customers 'A' and 'B' having two different portfolios and having interest income from the same security transaction </p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
<t>
            <field>TRANS.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Transaction date. If application does not pass the date, assumes this as TODAY</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
<t>
            <field>PORTFOLIO.ID</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the securities portfolio ID. For AA deposits, account transactions, this is the ID to which the underlying contract is attached. For security transactions, this is the underlying portfolio id. Should passed by application</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
<t>
            <field>TOTAL.INCOME</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the total income currency and amount of the transaction.Example: USD 100
</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>CUST.REL.ID</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the customer relationship ID.Should be passed by application. Example: CR10001</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
<t>
            <field>RESERVED04</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
<t>
            <field>RESERVED05</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
<t>
            <field>RESERVED06</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>JOINT.CUST.TAXID</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the joint holder customer id "*" tax.id appied</p>
				<p>The combination of joint customer id and tax.id should be a unique occurance under a customer*income.type combination. Joint customer id is taken from CUSTOMER.RELATIONSHIP record</p>
				<p>For example, lets say A is the primary owner who owns a portfolio jointly with another customer B in ration 70:30. In this case, there would be two sub-values of this field as: -</p>
				<p>10.1.1   A*10
				10.1.2   B*10</p>

				<p>Or customers A and B can have more than one tax (tax and link tax) applied, like
				10.1.1   A*10
				10.1.2   A*12
				10.1.3   B*20
				10.1.4   B*30</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>OWNING.PERC</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the income/tax percentage held by each customer of the joint relationship as defined in CR record Example: 40.00
</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>OWNING.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Income currency and amount of split income for each joint customer as per the owning.perc value Example: USD 40.00
</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>TAX.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the tax type applied to each joint customer</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>TAX.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the tax rate</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>TAX.AMT.SPLIT</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the currency and amount of tax on the split income amount that is applied for each joint customer Example: USD 10</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>TAX.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>The date on which tax was applied.Should be same as transaction date. If not passed, assume this as TODAY</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>TAX.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the internal account used to book the tax applied to each customer</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the credit transaction code for the tax entry</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Specifies the debit transaction code for the tax entry</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>RESERVED07</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
<t>
            <field>RESERVED08</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>RESERVED09</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>RESERVED06</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>

<t>
            <field>RESERVED10</field>
            <desc>
                
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
	
<t><field>INCOME.TYPE.DESC</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
	</t24help>
