<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>STATEMENT.CONTROL</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
</ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>BATCH.OUTPUT</field>
<desc><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Mandatory input.</p><p>A maximum of 3 characters may be entered.</p><p>The following values are permitted:       YES      NO</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID</field>
<desc><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 6 characters may be entered.</p><p>The following values are permitted:       SYSTEM</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NON.STMT.TXNS</field>
<desc><p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 numeric field. </p>
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p>Mandatory input.</p>
<p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
<p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p> 
<p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the TRANSACTION file.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAPPING.ROUTINE</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to attach a routine which will be called while preparing statement handoff record.</p>
<p>This routine will be called from DE.PRODUCT.SWIFT.STMT passing the current processing ENTRY.ID, ENTRY.RECORD, CURRENT.MULTIVALUE.POSITION and CARRIER.LIST for the account. Using this routine we can add the extra information required from the entry for local development in the handoff record</p>
<p>The information to be updated has to be returned to the core by this routine, MODIFIED.POSITION and MODIFIED.DATA core will update the modified data in the handoff record</p>
<p>Validation Rules:</p>
<p>Must be a valid compiled routine in the system</p>
<p>A maximum of 40 characters may be entered.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field> STMT.DATE.TYPE </field>
<desc>
<p> This Field is used to control the End date for Account statement produced through Swift and Print. For SWIFT end date is taken from Handoff record of 1.26th position and for Print End date  is taken from TO.DATE field of AC.STMT.HANDOFF</p>
<p>  Validation Rules : </p>
<p>  Allowed values are PERIOD, WORKING and BLANK </p>
<p>  Default in BLANK </p>
<p>  Setting as WORKING will update End date as TODAY </p>
<p>  Setting as PERIOD will update End date as PERIOD.END </p>
<p>  Setting as Blank  will update the End date as below  </p>
<p>  For Print - End date as PERIOD.END in value dated system . In fully Trade dated system End date as TODAY </p>
<p>  For Swift - End date as PERIOD.END in value dated and Trade dated system </p>
</desc>         
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>   
<t><field>STMT.INTEG.CHK</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
