<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>STMT.NARR.PARAM</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This application defines which STMT.NARR.FORMAT is to be used under specified conditions. For example a Money Market transaction may require a different narrative, or specific customers may need more detailes than others, even though the same basic transaction has taken place. </p><p>The conditions defined in this file are linked to individual TRANSACTION codes using the field NARR.TYPE in the file TRANSACTION. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NARR.FORMAT</field>
<desc><p>Field containing the ID for the Stmt.Narr.Format record This field is mandatory for each corresponding System.Id </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Multi valued field 1 to 8 alphanumeric characters</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc><p>Application System identifier eg(MM , FT , FX , MGP) Input of "ALL" is also allowed Mandatory field input of between 2 and 4 characters </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Single valued field 2 to 4 Alphanumeric characters</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.PRM.ID</field>
<desc><p>KEY for Statement Narrative Parameter records. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Alphanumeric character field 1 to 8 characters long</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.FILE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.NAME</field>
<desc><p>Optional field name corresponding to the above Application file ie Must exist on the Standard Selection for the above File Input not allowed if File = "ALL" Upon matching conditions set by the Field Name and Field Operand it is decided which Narr.Format record will be used </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Multi valued field</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.OPERAND</field>
<desc><p>Optional input field but mandatory for a corresponding Field.Name Input not allowed if no corresponding Field.Name The valid operators are as follows  (EQ LE GE NE LT GT LK UL RG) </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Multi valued field 2 character field</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIELD.VALUE</field>
<desc><p>This sub valued field contains the value/s that are to be used by selection criteria defined by Field.name and Field.Operand. Upon matching the set of criteria the corresponding Narr.Format record (ie soft narrative format) eg (VALUE.DATE GT 19930101 AND LT 19931231) </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Sub valued to allow one or more values to be input</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE</field>
<desc><p>Name of application file generating the Stmt Entry record ie (MM.MONEY.MARKET) File input must exist on File Control Input can be "ALL" Input not allowed if System id = "ALL" Input to this field must equal the field 'File' (unless this is null) on the corresponding 'Stmt.Narr.Format' file. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Alphanumeric character field Multivalued</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

