<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>STMT.NARR.FORMAT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This application defines the actual content of the statement narrative displayed. It will allow definition of text, and extraction of data from the contents of the record on the specified file. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LINE.LENGTH</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the maximum length for each line of the narrative to be constructed. </p><p>If the narrative exceeds the LINE.LENGTH specified the constructed narrative will be either trucated or automatically split into a further line according to the setting of WRAP.TRUNCATE. </p><p>Default value is 35. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Manadatory Field</p><p>1 to 2 numeric character field.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TEXT.DATA</field>
<desc><p>Specifies an element of text, or field whose content is to form part of the narrative being defined. </p><p>Contains either Field names,text strings or a new line indicator. </p><p>Field Names - A field name must exist on the Standard Selection record of FMT.FILE either as User or System defined. Any type "D", "I" or "J" field may be   used. </p><p>Text - A text string may be used and can include any characters except   double quotes ie( " ). The text string however must be surrounded by double quotes, ie( "text string" ) </p><p>New Line - A new line may be thrown in the narrative by specifying the sequence [NL] </p><p>The text may be defined in various languages, the appropriate language will be used where possible according to the output language, if not found the English will be used. </p><p>When the Narrative is constructed spaces will be trimmed. This means that leading, trailing spaces are removed, elements in the sentence are separated by single spaces. </p><p>Care should be taken when using narratives in output sent via SWIFT, to only use acceptable characters according to the SWIFT standards. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Alphanumeric field Sub valued where the sub valued set uses the multi Language application Input must be either - a valid field of TYPE D,I,J in the STANDARD.SELECTION record of the FILE - Any string of TEXT enclosed in "" - The characters [NL] to signify a new line is required</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.LINES</field>
<desc><p>Defines the maximum number of lines allowed for narrative. </p><p>Default value is 4. </p><p>Any narrative exceeding this maximum will be ignored. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Mandatory field</p><p>1 to 2 character numeric field</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARR.FORMAT.ID</field>
<desc><p>ID of Stmt.Narr.Format record </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1 to 8 alphanumeric characters.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WRAP.TRUNCATE</field>
<desc><p>Defines whether narrative exceeding the LINE.LENGTH should be TRUNCATED or should WRAP to form the start of a new line. </p><p>If the WRAP option is used the text will be broken prior to the word exceeding the line length. The word will then appear on the following line. </p><p>If the TRUNCATE option is used the line will be truncated at the character exceeding the LINE.LENGTH. Characters after this point will be ignored. </p><p>This can be illustrated by the following example: </p><p>TEXT = "THIS IS A LONG LINE" (length 19) MAX.LINES = 2 LINE.LENGTH = 12 </p><p>WRAP.TRUNCATE = "WRAP" The resulting narrative will be: </p><p> Line 1 THIS IS A  Line 2 LONG LINE </p><p>WRAP.TRUNCATE = "TRUNCATE" The resulting narrative will be: </p><p> Line 1 THIS IS A LO </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Mandatory field</p><p>TRUNCATE or WRAP only is allowed</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.FORMAT</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Description field for each Stmt narrative format </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Multi Valued Multi Language Alphanumeric field</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FILE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the FILE from which information is to be extracted to form the narrative. Any field specified in TEXT.DATA to be used as part of the narrative must be exist in the FILE specified here. </p><p>The default value is the STMT.ENTRY file. </p><p>If the specified file has a HISTORY record, the history record contents will be used should the record not exist in the LIVE file. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Mandatory field. Must exist in the FILE.CONTROL application</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORMAT</field>
<desc><p>Defines special formatting to be applied to fields extracted from the specified FILE. </p><p>-Amount fields    1) 'AMOUNT-LCY' - Formats amounts to the local currency    2) 'AMOUNT-FCY' - Formats amounts to the foreign currency    3) 'AMOUNT-'field name - formats according to the currency contained in        field name, which must be defined in the STANDARD.SELECTION record        of FILE. </p><p>-Date fields will be formatted as follows    1) 'DATE-D2/'   - 29/03/93    2) 'DATE-D2-'   - 29-03-93    3) 'DATE-D4/'   - 29/03/1993 </p><p>-Rate fields    1) 'RATE'       - eg 10 will display as 10.00 </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Optional field</p><p>Only allowed when associated TXT.DATA is a field name</p><p>Must begin DATE-, AMOUNT- or RATE</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.FILE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

