<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>STMT.GEN.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The purpose of this table is to define rules for determining the default statement frequency when opening new Accounts.</p><p>When a new Account is opened, an Account Statement record, specifying the date and frequency for printing Account statements, is generated automatically by the system.  This record may subsequently be amended manually, if required.</p><p>The default frequency is determined on the basis of Customer and Account details such as Residence, Sector and Account Category.  The criteria used and their order of priority are specified in the CONDITION.PRIORITY file in the record whose ID is STATEMENT.  A maximum of 4 fields may be used.  Only the fields selected in the CONDITION.PRIORITY file are included Statement General Condition records.</p><p>The default statement frequency may be Daily (every working day), Monthly, Quarterly or Six.Monthly.  Each Statement General Condition record specifies the various combinations of field values defining all Accounts with a particular default statement frequency.</p><p>If the details of an Account do not match the conditions specified in any Statement General Condition record, a default statement frequency of Monthly is used.</p><p>All internal Accounts have a default statement frequency of Monthly.</p><p>If the details of an Account match more than one Statement General Condition record, the Priority order is used to determine the default frequency. (The higher Priority field with a match wins. Priority 1 is the highest Priority.)</p><p>In order to stop production of Account Statements for specific Accounts, a record may be created with id 'NOSTMT' which will set PRINT.STATEMENT field as 'NO' in the respective Account Statement records.</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTIVALUE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIORITY</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONDITION.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the Statement General Condition details and specifies the default statement frequency for new Accounts whose details match the conditions specified in the rest of the record.</p><p>New Accounts whose details match the conditions specified for Condition Code 'DAILY' will have a default statement frequency of 'BSNSS' i.e. every working day.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>DA(ily), MO(nthly), QU(arterly) or SI(x.monthly).</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Statement General Condition record.</p><p>This field is used as a Description of the Statement General Condition which is used for reporting or enrichment.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters Multivalue field (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FREQUENCY.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies whether the statement due date is to be set up according to the anniversary of the opening date or the period end date.</p><p>This field is used to determine whether when opening a new customer account the first due date for the statement should be either from the anniversary of the opening of the account or the period end date. For period end date, the end date depends upon the key of the record -</p><p>KEY                DUE DATE            Monthly            Calendar end date of the month.            Quarterly          Calendar end date for the end of                               March, June, September or                               December.            Six.Monthly        Calendar end date for the end of                               June or December.            Yearly             Calendar end date for the end of                               December.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Either ANNIVERSARY or PERIOD.END. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEM</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

