<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>STOCK.REGISTER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This is a live file and whenever a record is added in STOCK.ENTRY, the system checks for the appropriate stock register and if it exists adds it to the existing STOCK.REGISTER otherwise into new STOCK.REGISTER.</p><p>This file has the stock entry related details like STOCK.REGISTER.ID, SERIES.ID, STOCK.START.NO and balance stock for a STOCK.REGISTER.</p><p>Validation Rules</p><p /><p /></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>STO.REG.BAL</field>
<desc><p>Total no of stock held for the stock register.</p><p>This is the total of various stock series held in a stock register.</p><p>If a Stock register balance comes to zero, then stock register and stock entry related to that stock register will be moved to History</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Rule 1</p><p>Rule 2</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STO.ENTRY.ID</field>
<desc><p>This field has the stock entry id corresponding to the above stock details.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Rule 1</p><p>Rule 2</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERIES.ID</field>
<desc><p>Stock series id is formed by Stock.Series, Stock.Acct. No and Cheque.type as defined in Stock.Entry joined with "*".</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Rule 1</p><p>Rule 2</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERIES.NO</field>
<desc><p>Range of stock as entered in the Stock.Entry is shown here.</p><p>Based on the transfer between the stock register, system updates range of stock.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Rule 1</p><p>Rule 2</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERIES.BAL</field>
<desc><p>Total stock held for the particular stock series is shown here.</p><p>After the transfer between the stock register, the total series balance will get changed.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Rule 1</p><p>Rule 2</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARD.CANCEL</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CARD.SCRAP</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc><p>Id to this file is STOCK.PARAMETER id with the stock.reg.id as defined for the corresponding stock parameter.</p><p>For example: For STOCK.PARAMETER-CHQ which is defined with stock register id as DEPARTMENT.CODE-LOCAL.TABLE, then the id is "CHQ.1-2" where 1 is department code and 2 is a local table no.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

