<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>TAX.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This application allows definition of the types of TAX which may be calculated within T24. The T24 Tax table may have different uses, depending on the local practice, different type of Tax may be calulated based on different types of transaction and product. </p><p>For example, INCOME tax may be calculated on interest earnt, and VAT may be taken on charges and commissions. Ther may be several types of VAT, such as GST (Government Service Tax), or a local regional tax. </p><p>Each type of TAX may have different criteria for defining whether a particular Customer is liable to the Tax. Conditions for applying tax for a given set of Customer conditions may be defined using the applications, CONDITION.PRIORITY (record TAX), TAX.GEN.CONDITION. Actual TAX rates to be applied for Tax Groupings are specified using the applications TAX.TYPE.CONDITION and TAX. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TAX.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>The type of Tax to be processed. May be any Tax type calculated according to local practice. E.g  VAT, INCOME, WITHOLD, GST </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Format : Upto 10 SWIFT type characters</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.CHK.RTN</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Tax Type. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Format : 3 to 35 alphanumeric characters</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.TAX.PARAM</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
    <t>
      <field>HIGHEST.TAX</field>
      <desc>
        <p>When performing tax calculation based on Joint customer relationship definition, would pick the tax which has highest percentage and apply that to all customers of the group </p>
        <p>Can be set to YES or NO or None</p>
        <p>When set to YES – calculation should consider the highest tax % for calculating the tax for all the customers of a customer relationship</p>
      <p>When set to NO/None – calculation would not consider the highest tax % logic and would calculate tax for individual customers based on the individual customer tax %</p>
     <p>Optional field. Default value is none</p>
      </desc>
    </t>
    <t>
      <field>APPLY.SPLIT</field>
      <desc>
        <p>This field is used to parameterize whether tax split can be applied for a specific tax type or not .Can be set to either YES or No or left blank</p>
        <p>Validation Rules</p>
        <p>YES - Tax split is allowed for a tax type . NO / None – Tax would not be split although joint customer are part of the transaction .Optional field.Default value is none </p>
      </desc>
    </t>
</menu>
</t24help>
