<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>TAX.GEN.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The purpose of this table is to identify, by means of </p><p>a User defined TAX General Condition number, a specific group of Customers which will then </p><p>be cross-related to the Group Condition Table to </p><p>define TAX conditions applicable to that group. </p><p>The key to this file is then specified on the TAX Type Condition file for specified Tax Types to allow definition of the applicable Tax rates. </p><p /><p>To create a Group Condition,the user must identify </p><p>the Group by means of the General Condition number </p><p>defined in this table.  The Group of Customers will </p><p>then be identified by means of the details held </p><p>within this table. </p><p /><p /><p>For a Customer to be selected, it must conform to every field value defined within the TAX General Condition to qualify for a specific Group. Amending a Customer record may therefore result in reclassification of the Customer (or Account) into another Group or even to return to the 'normal conditions'. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRIORITY</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALUE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Descibes the Group conditions for the group being defined. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must be 3-35 alpha numeric characters. Language Field (Mandatory Input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GROUP.ID</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the key to the Group for which conditions are to be defined. </p><p>The first part of the key defines the tax type as defined on the TAX.TYPE application. </p><p>Then a delimiter of '-' (minus sign). </p><p>Then the customer tax group which is also defined in the CUST.TAX.GRP field of TAX.TYPE.CONDITION. </p><p>The TAX.TYPE.CONDITION is used to defined specfic tax codes relating to type of tax, customer, and contract. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Made up of TAX.TYPE application key Then - (minus sign as delimiter) Then 3 numeric character prefixed with leading zeroes if necessary.  (Mandatory Input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ITEM</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTIVALUE</field>
<desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

