<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>TAX.TYPE.CONDITION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>TheTAX.TYPE.CONDITION file links types of customer to types of
 tax thus enabling T24 to calculate different levels of tax
 depending on the type of customer. Using this mechanism, for
 example, it is possible to charge a different rate of VAT to
 residents and non-residents. </p><p>To activate this facility the user must first set up the
 different taxes on the TAX.TYPE file. An example of a tax on this
 file would be VAT, value added tax. </p><p>Secondly the user must establish the rules by which the
 different types of customer are to be determined. This is done
 firstly by establishing a record for TAX on the
 CONDITION.PRIORITY file. This record will indicate the fields on
 the customer that are to be examined when determining the type of
 customer for tax purposes. For example the user may decide that
 the customer's tax status can be identified from the SECTOR and
 RESIDENCE codes. </p><p>Thirdly the user must define the different types of customer
 by setting up the TAX.GEN.CONDITION file. For example the user
 may decide that 'private individuals' that are 'resident' are a
 type of customer for tax purposes. </p><p>Fourthly the user must define the different rates of tax that
 may be charged on the TAX table. For example the user may input
 records for VAT full rate and VAT reduced rate and VAT zero rate.
 </p><p>Finally the user links these different tables together on the
 TAX.TYPE.CONDITION table. At least one record will be established
 on this table for each TAX.TYPE. The record then links the types
 of customer with the tax rates to be applied. For example a
 single record may indicate that for VAT, resident individuals are
 to be charged 15%, all non-residents are to be charged 0%, etc. </p><p>More than one record may be set up on TAX.TYPE.CONDITION for
 each type of tax by the addition of a numeric sequence. Thus VAT
 may exist but also VAT-001. This facility is used where there are
 more than one set of rates for a particular tax, for example full
 rate value added tax and reduced rate value added tax. </p><p>The tables link thus: </p><p>CUSTOMER</p><p>to</p><p>CONDITION.PRIORITY</p><p>to</p><p>TAX.GEN.CONDITION</p><p>to</p><p>TAX.TYPE.CONDITION &lt;===TAX.TYPE</p><p>to</p><p>TAX</p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc><p>Local reference fields if defined. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.CATEGORY</field>
<desc><p>Reserved for future use </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>System field no input</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.TYPE.PROD</field>
<desc><p>The key of the the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION file is TAX.TYPE and product. </p><p>The former must exist on the TAX.TYPE file (e.g. VAT). The latter is optional and is an incremental number (e.g. VAT-001). It is used when more than one variation on a tax exists, for example value added tax at full rate and at reduced rate. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>First part of field, tax.type, must exist on the tax type field.  If a product is entered then this must be separated from the tax.type by a '-'. The product must be a number between 001 and 999 with leading zeros.`</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.CODE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the tax code (from the TAX file) that holds the tax rate to be applied for this customer group. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must exist on the TAX table.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.CATEG</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the category code of the tax account to be credited with the tax. If specified it overrides the category code specified on the TAX record. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must be a valid CATEGORY in the range 0-19999</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.GRP</field>
<desc><p>Allows tax codes to be assigned to particular groups of contract as well as to the type of customer. </p><p>For example using this field and the customer charge conditions a specific tax code could be assigned to fixed deposits over a particular equivalent value for tax paying residents of a particular country. </p><p>The CONTRACT.GRP code is determined from the conditions defined in the  APPL.GEN.CONDITION record for the relevant application. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Five character alphanumeric Optional Input.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUST.TAX.GRP</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the type of customer for whom the related tax rate is to be applied. Input to this field is a customer tax group number from the TAX.GEN.CONDITION file. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must exist on the TAX.GEN.CONDITION file for the same type of tax. e.g. if this record is VAT (or VAT-001) and the group in put is 010</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc><p>Describes the type of tax condition. For example: </p><p>Value added tax </p><p>Value added tax reduced rate. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input).</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

