<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ST</product>
<table>TRANSACTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>The Transaction Table contains information about all the Transaction Codes which may be used within T24  For each Application a range of Transaction codes has been assigned to facilitate their recognition and identification within T24  The Transaction codes contain and identify important processing conditions which will be defaulted by the Applications if no other input has been entered at the transaction level.  The main identifying details of the Transaction code can be summarised as follows: </p><p>1. Reference number identification </p><p>In many cases, the System will be required to capture a reference number either to print or for verification against the Database.  This will be the case, when cheques are issued by customers on their account with the Bank. </p><p>It will be important to verify these cheques, when presented for payment, against the "stop payment" list and to receive a stop payment warning as soon as the transaction is processed.  By defining the appropriate details in this table, this control will be completely automated. </p><p>2. Transaction Charges </p><p>For each Transaction code it is also possible to define, if required, different types of charges applicable to the specific Transaction. Many banks, for example, charge their customer for services like standing orders, use of Cash Dispensers, issuance of cheques, etc. This table will allow identification of these charges at the Transaction Type level.  Any of these charges can then be processed by the Interest and Charge System, possibly depending on the minimum balance in the account. </p><p>3. Default Value and Exposure date </p><p>As a further facility, this table will allow the definition of the default Value Date and Exposure Date conditions for each Transaction code. This will prevent the operator from having to key the Value Date and Exposure Date repeatedly on transactions where a default can be applied. </p><p>4. MIS Information </p><p>A unit cost can also be associated with each Transaction code.  This will allow Customer and Account profitability to be produced taking into account not only the earnings detained from the Customer but also the cost included in providing the services to customers. </p><p>The other facilities available in this table are detailed within the Field descriptions. </p><p>The TRANSACTION.CHARGE table (ref: ACCOUNT) must be set up before any charge can be defined in a Transaction code. </p><p>For each Transaction code, the corresponding Narrative to be printed on the statement of Account must be defined in the DELIVERY TRANSLATION table (DE.TRANSLATION).  A clear and precise Narrative will eliminate the need to send additional advices to support statement entries. </p><p>5. Combining Entries. </p><p>The way that T24 combines accounting entries is defined in this table. It is possible to define rules for various categories, products and transaction code. </p><p>For example, it is possible to specify a transaction code that will be used as the combined transaction code for all Loans contracts using a specific transaction code. </p></ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NARR.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 8 characters may be entered.</p><p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the STMT.NARR.PARAM file.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TURNOVER.CHARGE</field>
<desc><p>Indicates whether the Transactions using this Transaction code are to be included in the calculation of the Debit/Credit Turnover or Number of Debits/Credits Charge. </p><p>This field, at the transaction code level will allow the user to eliminate any Transaction Code from the Turnover charge calculation. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Y    Transactions using this Transaction code will be included in the calculation of the Turnover Charge. or      N(O) Transactions using this Transaction code will be excluded from the calculation of the Turnover Charge. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Transaction code and may be used in reports. </p><p>This field is provided for future use.  It is not currently used by the system. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 15 type SS (uppercase alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters. (Optional input. No default.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DISPO.EXEMPT</field>
<desc><p>Dispo Exempt (DISPO.EXEMPT)</p><p>This field specifies whether a particular Transaction Type will be subject to Dispo processing.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><table><tr><td><p>YES</p></td><td><p>The transaction type IS exempt from Dispo processing</p></td></tr><tr><td><p>NO / Empty field</p></td><td><p>The transaction type is subject to Dispo processing.</p></td></tr></table></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.INT.POOLS</field>
<desc><p /><p>UPDATE.INT.POOLS</p><p>This field can be YES or NO. If set to YES it will cause all transactions for this code to be processed against the German Withholding Tax functionality provided the customer is liable.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMBINE.TXN</field>
<desc><p>The fields COMBINE.PROD.CAT, COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID and COMBINE.TXN are used to define the way that T24 combines accounting entries together. </p><p>For example, to specify that in the funds transfer application, contracts will have the entries combined for all product categories: </p><p>  20 COMBINE.PROD.CAT.. ALL                 All Categories   21 COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID. FT                  FUNDS TRANSFER </p><p>This field is used to specify the transactions code that may be netted under this transaction code. Entering a list of transaction codes will mean that any entry with any of the transaction codes may be netted under this new transaction: </p><p>  22. 1 COMBINE.TXN.... 1                   CREDITS   22. 2 COMBINE.TXN.... 2                   DEBITS </p><p>Entries must have the same value date, account and currency market to be netted. </p><p>Note:</p><p>In COMBINE.TXN field, along with other TRANSACTION codes that are to be combined with this selected TRANSACTION, the ID of this selected TRANSACTION code also is to be mentioned.</p><p>Example:</p><p>If Charge defined by TRANSACTION 231 and tax defined by TRANSACTION 464 are to be combined with the charge defined by TRANSACTION 622 (ID of the selected TRANSACTION) , then select the multi value COMBINE.TXN field in TRANSACTION 622 and enter codes 231, 464 and  622 also.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p>Must be a key to a valid record on this file, or ALL.</p><p>Where ALL is defined, no other transaction codes may be defined.</p><p>Duplicates not allowed.</p><p>Defaults to ALL if either the COMBINE.PROD.CAT field on the COMBNE.SYSTEM.ID field is populated.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NARR</field>
<desc><p>Description of Transaction. </p><p>This field is provided for future use.  It is not currently used by the system.  The narrative to be printed on Account Statements is defined in the DELIVERY TRANSLATION table (DE.TRANSLATION). </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 25 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters. (Optional input.  Default is corresponding Short Description.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXP.KEY</field>
<desc><p>This field contains a code that points to the EXPOSURE.CONDITION file record that defines the exposure ladder rules for the sort code in view. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Optional Input</p><p>If entered must be a valid EXPOSURE.CONDITIONS record.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UNIT.COST</field>
<desc><p>Specifies a Unit Cost for each Transaction. </p><p>This field specifies a Unit Cost for each Transaction which is used to provide statistics for an account profitability report of service costs. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input.  No default value.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NARR.REF</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether or not a reference is to appear on Account Statements as part of the narrative, and if so, which of the three possible references in a Statement Entry should be used:-  Our Reference, Their Reference or the System generated Transaction Reference. </p><p>Short and long transaction narratives for printing on Account Statements are defined in the DELIVERY TRANSLATION table (DE.TRANSLATION). </p><p>This field specifies whether or not a reference should be included in the narrative to be printed on Account Statements, and if so, which reference. </p><p>The end of day account statements program (PRINT.ACCOUNT.STMT) provides the necessary details for the DELIVERY System to format and print the statements as specified within the DELIVERY System. </p><p>The narrative which is available for printing is determined as follows: </p><p>1.         If the statement entry generated by the originating            transaction (e.g. FUNDS.TRANSFER) contains a single            line of Customer Narrative which is not translatable            (i.e. does not start with 2 colons '::'), this is the            narrative which may be printed. </p><p>2.         If there is no Customer Narrative, or if the Customer            Narrative consists of more than 1 line, or is translatable            (starts with '::'), the narrative to be printed is the            long transaction narrative from the Delivery Translation            table, or the short transaction narrative from the            Delivery Translation table plus the reference specified            in this field. </p><p>3.         If the Customer Narrative consists of more than 1 line or            is translatable (starts with '::'), this may be printed in            full, in addition to the narrative from the Delivery            Translation table, if Descriptive Statements are            requested in the ACCOUNT.STATEMENT table. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 5 type AAA (alpha) characters as follows: O(ur)     for Our Reference T(heir)   for Their Reference TR(ans)   for Transaction Reference (Optional input.  No default.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IMMEDIATE.CHARGE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies when the charge is to be applied to the Account. </p><p>In its present version, the System will only take action by means of the Interest and charges Module which means that the value of Y (immediate charge) will have no effect on the transaction. When this field is defined as NO (not immediate charge), the Interest and Charges Application will take these transactions into account when the charges are applied to the appropriate Account. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Y = Charge must be levied immediately, i.e. when the transaction is booked.  This process has not yet been included in the system and consequently should not be used presently because no action will be taken. or      N(O)=  Charge must not be levied when the transaction is booked but instead on the closing date of the charges.  In this case, the Interest and Charges Application will take over and handle these charges as defined in the Transaction Charge record specified in Field 6. (Mandatory input when CHARGE KEY [Field 6] is entered.  Otherwise not allowed.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INITIATION</field>
<desc><p>Specifies who is responsible for initiating the Transaction. </p><p>This field specifies whether this Transaction is initiated automatically by the System, by the bank or by the Customer.  This information is then used to determine which Transaction details fields should be updated on the ACCOUNT file (e.g. Amount Last Credit Auto, Amount Last Credit Bank or Amount Last Credit Customer) and, therefore, ensuring that exact details are maintained for all Transactions of the Account. </p><p>Note:      The Inactive status on Customer Accounts will only be            activated by the Transaction codes which have been            identified with the value of C (customer). </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-8 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters: A(uto) or     B(ank) or     C(ustomer) (Mandatory input.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NARRATIVE</field>
<desc><p>Describes the Transaction code and is used for enrichment and on reports. </p><p>This field can be expanded to allow you to enter the Narrative of the Transaction code in various languages.  Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table, and will indicate the Language in which the Narrative must be entered. </p><p>The narrative to appear on Account Statements is defined in the DELIVERY TRANSLATION table (DE.TRANSLATION).  To avoid confusion it is advisable to enter the same details in this field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>3-30 type SS (uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha) characters Multivalue field. Multilanguage field. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FORCE.DEF.EXP.DATE</field>
<desc><p>This field will be actioned when the user wants to force in the Data Capture Application the default exposure date associated with the transaction code.  In other words, it will then not be possible to change the default exposure date in the transaction. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>The values allowed for this field are: 'Y': force the default exposure date. 'blank': does not force it. (Optional Input;  No default.)</p><p>Input of 'Y' in this field is not allowed when EXPOSURE DATE (field 9) is equal to 'NO'.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SWIFT.NARRATIVE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies the SWIFT description of the Transaction. </p><p>This field is the SWIFT narrative corresponding to the Transaction code and must conform to the rules specified in the SWIFT User Handbook.  Since these rules may be changed from time to time, E.B.S. does not validate this field fully.  It is the User's responsibility to ensure valid codes are entered.  Currently the rules are as follows: </p><p>1.         For entries related to SWIFT transfer instructions and            subsequent charges messages. </p><p>           Format: Snnn </p><p>           S = SWIFT </p><p>           Where a sender wishes to identify specifically an entry            as based on a SWIFT message, the last three characters            must indicate the message type of the SWIFT message            causing the entry. </p><p>2.         For entries related to payment and transfer instructions            including related charges messages not sent through            SWIFT or where an alpha description is preferred. </p><p>           Format: Nxxx </p><p>           N = Non-SWIFT </p><p>           The last three characters however, must be one of the            SWIFT codes listed hereafer indicating the reason for            the entry. </p><p>3.         For entries being first advised by the statement. </p><p>           Format: Fxxx </p><p>           F =  first time that this entry is made known to the                 "Account Owner".  It refers to items originated                 by the "Account Servicing" Bank. </p><p>           The last three characters must be an appropriate code            (see below) indicating the reason for the entry. </p><p>SWIFT Codes for Options (2) and (3) </p><p>BOE        Bill of Exchange BRF        Brokerage Fee CHG        Charges and Other Expenses CHK        Cheques (see Note in Subfield 7) CLR        Cash Letter/Cheques Remittance COL        Collections (used when entering a principal amount) COM        Commission DCR        Documentary Credit (used when entering a principal amount) DIV        Dividends - Warrants EQA        Equivalent Amount ECK        Eurocheques FEX        Foreign Exchange LDP        Loan Deposit LBX        Lock Box INT        Interest RTI        Returned Item SEC        Securities (used when entering a principal amount) STO        Standing Order TRF        Transfer TCK        Traveller's Cheques VDA        Value Date Adjustment.  Used with an entry made to            withdraw an Incorrectly dated entry.  It will be followed            by the correct entry with the relevant code. MSC        Miscellaneous </p><p>           New entries </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>4 type SS (uppercase alphanumeric, first character alpha) characters. (Mandatory input)</p><p>Linked to the virtual table EB.LOOKUP. Input can have an entry in EB.LOOKUP table with key id like "SWIFT.NARRATIVE*Swift Narrative Code. E.g. SWIFT.NARRATIVE*NTRF. Enrichment will be displayed based on the Description given for the swift code in EB.LOOKUP and if it is not defined in EB.LOOKUP, enrichment will display the Swift Narrative Code</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.KEY</field>
<desc><p>Indicates which, if any, Charges are to be applied for this Transaction code. </p><p>This field identifies the record in the TRANSACTION.CHARGE table (ref: ACCOUNT) which contains details of the bank charges to be applied for this particular Transaction.  For example, cash dispenser, standing order, direct debit, etc.  When the value of the next field is defined as NO (not immediate charge), the Interest and Charges Application will take all these charges into account for the calculation and application of the charges to the relevant accounts. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>1-3 numeric character Transaction Charge code. Multivalue field (Optional input.  Default Value = Blank (i.e. no charge).</p><p>It must be an existing TRANSACTION.CHARGE record.</p><p>Date of TRANSACTION.CHARGE record must be less than or equal to the Run Date.  (Run Date is the date of the data being processed which may not always be today's date.  If different, the Run Date is displayed next to your User ID on the screen).</p><p>Allowed to enter only 1 transaction based calculated charge. This means that no two transaction charges with the CHARGE.PERIOD field on TRANSACTION set to 'T' may be entered.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHEQUE.IND</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether the inclusion of a cheque number is to be mandatory for entries input via the DATA.CAPTURE System, and using this transaction code. </p><p>The purpose of this field is twofold: </p><p>1.         For forcing the user to enter a cheque number, the            System can then verify the PAYMENT.STOP file (ref:            Data Capture) and ascertain that no stop has been            placed on the cheque. </p><p>2.         The input of Y will also ensure that the cheque number            is available for printing on the Customer statement            which will allow easy reconciliation for the Customer. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Y    Any transaction using this Transaction code will request the input of a cheque number. or    blankInput of a cheque number will be optional. (Optional input.  Default value = blank)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHQ.TYPE</field>
<desc><p>This field is used to specify a cheque type that can be linked to this transaction code.</p><p>By linking a transaction code to a cheque type the accounting process will automatically perform additional validation on the cheque number/s being used. The extra validation performed by the process will include the following:</p><p /><p>Ensure that the cheque number/s has/have been issued to the client account </p><p>Ensure that the cheque number/s has/have not been stopped </p><p>Ensure that the cheque number/s has/have not been presented before </p><p>It is important to set up a different transaction code for every different cheque type using this functionality. These unique transaction codes must be used in passing transactions for the type of cheque involved. A concat file CHQ.TYPE.TRNS will be updated to record the linkage between these fields.</p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p /><p /><p>Optional Input</p><p>If entered it must be a valid CHEQUE.TYPE</p><p>Can be entered only when the CHEQUE.IND flag is set to 'Y'</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMBINE.PROD.CAT</field>
<desc><p>The fields COMBINE.PROD.CAT, COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID and COMBINE.TXN are used to define the way that T24 combines accounting entries together. </p><p>This field is used to specify the product categories that may be netted under this transaction code. </p><p>For example, to specify that all entries for the loans and deposits contracts will have the entries combined for product category 21050: </p><p>  20 COMBINE.PROD.CAT.. 21050               LOANS   21 COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID. LD                  LOANS AND DEPOSITS   22. 1 COMBINE.TXN.... ALL                 All Transactions </p><p>Entries must have the same value date, account and currency market to be netted. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must be a key to a record on the CATEGORY file, or ALL.</p><p>Defaults to ALL where either of the fields COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID or COMBINE.TXN have been populated.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MANDATORY.REF.NO</field>
<desc><p>Specifies whether the inclusion of a Reference Number is to be mandatory for Transactions input via DATA.CAPTURE  when using this Transaction code. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Y    The user will be forced to enter a Reference Number at transaction level. or     blankInput of a Reference Number is not mandatory for this Transaction code. Input must be Y if CHEQUE INDICATOR (Field 3) is Y. (Optional input.  Default value = blank)</p><p>If this field is Y it will be necessary to enter a Reference Number with the Transaction.  If CHEQUE INDICATOR (Field 3) is Y, then the cheque number must be input as a Reference Number.</p><p>Also when this field is Y, the DATA.CAPTURE Application will force the user to enter reference details in the THEIR REFERENCE (Field 5 in Main File of DATA.CAPTURE).</p><p>This field can have a value of Y even if CHEQUE INDICATOR (Field 3) has been left blank.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID</field>
<desc><p>The fields COMBINE.PROD.CAT, COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID and COMBINE.TXN are used to define the way that T24 combines accounting entries together. </p><p>This field is used to specify the applications that may be netted under this transaction code. </p><p>For example, to specify that all entries for the loans and deposits contracts will have the entries combined for product category 21050: </p><p>  20 COMBINE.PROD.CAT.. 21050               LOANS   21 COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID. LD                  LOANS AND DEPOSITS   22. 1 COMBINE.TXN.... ALL                 All Transactions </p><p>Entries must have the same value date, account and currency market to be netted. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Must be a key to a record on the EB.SYSTEM.ID file, or ALL.</p><p>Defaults to ALL where either of the fields COMBINE.SYSTEM.ID or COMBINE.TXN have been populated.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.CREDIT.IND</field>
<desc><p>Indicates if the Transaction code is to be used for Debit or Credit entries. The use of this indicator will mainly be used by core applications such as DATA.CAPTURE. This information is used by the system to verify the sign of the Transaction. Once the Transaction code has been authorised, the value of this field cannot be changed. For other applications it will be disregarded because all the bookkeeping entries are generated automatically by each Transaction Processing Application. </p><p /><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Up to 6 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters: </p><p>C(redit) D(ebit) </p><p>Input must be D(ebit) if CHEQUE INDICATOR (Field 3) is Y and the CHQ.TYPE is blank. </p><p>Mandatory input if DATA CAPTURE indicator is Y, otherwise optional. No default. Cannot be changed. </p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc><p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATA.CAPTURE</field>
<desc><p>Specifies if the Transaction code can be used in the DATA.CAPTURE Application. </p><p>This field controls whether this Transaction Code can be used in DATA.CAPTURE, or may only be used in entries generated automatically by other transaction processing Applications. </p><p>When this field is left blank, the transaction code will not be allowed in the DATA.CAPTURE Applications. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Y    May be used in DATA.CAPTURE Application. or     blankCannot be used by DATA.CAPTURE Application. (Optional input.  Default value = blank, i.e. cannot be used by DATA.CAPTURE Application.)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EXPOSURE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies the Default Exposure Date which will be assigned to Transactions where this transaction code has been used.  (It will specify the date on which the funds will be available to the Customer). </p><p>If Y, or NO is entered the inputs (a) to (f) are not allowed.  (a), (bb), (c) specify the number of calendar or working days to be added to the Run Date in order to obtain the Default Exposure Date as follows: </p><p>(a) +      Indicates that days are to be added to the Run Date.            The - sign is obviously not applicable for a default            exposure date and will always be refused. (bb) 01-99 Indicates the number of days to be added. (c) C      If (bb) are calendar days,     W      If (bb) are working days. </p><p>           If it are necessary to add any other days to those            specified in (bb) before obtaining the Default Exposure            Date then (d), (ee), (f) are used as follows: </p><p>           (d)  As for (a) previously.            (ee) As for (bb) previously.            (f) CIf (ee) are calendar days.                WIf (ee) are working days. </p><p>           It must be noted that the day type ('C' or 'W') can only            be used once in an equation. </p><p>Note:      For the time being only the DATA.CAPTURE            Application makes use of the condition defined in this            field to define their default exposure date for credit            entries. </p><p>This field allows a Default Exposure Date to be specified for credit transactions, either on the Run Date, or a number of working or calendar days forward from the Run Date can be specified.  This controls when funds are available to the Customer and prevents the operator from repeatedly having to key the Exposure Date on Transactions where the default can be applied.  It can be overridden at Transaction level when required. </p><p>Example </p><p>+03W       will mean that the default value date is 3 working days            forward from the Run Date. </p><p>+01C + 02W  will mean that the default value date is 1 calendar day +            2 working days forward from the Run date. </p><p /><p>Example: </p><p>The following example will clarify the use and the relations between the Default Value Date and Default Exposure Date fields.  Let us suppose that: </p><p>1.         Local currency cheques deposited by customers on their            account are credited immediately in the Customer            Account with a one working day Forward Value Date and            two working days Forward Exposure Date, i.e. the            funds will be cleared only two days after the cheque has            been deposited by the Customer. </p><p>2.         Foreign currency cheques, however, are credited, with            five working days Forward Value Date and eight            working days Forward Exposure Date, i.e. the funds            will be available to the customer only eight days after he            has deposited the cheque with you. </p><p>If these assumptions would be applicable then create two Transaction codes with the following values: </p><p>           Field Name         Field Value </p><p>1.         ID                 001            Narrative          Cheque Deposit Local ccy            Deb/Cred Indicator C(redit)            Default value date + 01W            Default expos. date+ 02W            This transaction (001) will then be used to record local            currency cheque deposits. </p><p>2.         ID                 002            Narrative          Cheque Deposit Foreign ccy            Deb/Cred Indicator C(redit)            Default value date + 05W            Default Expos. date+ 08W </p><p>           This transaction code (002) will then be used to record            foreign currency cheques deposit. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Y    If the Default Exposure Date is to be the Run Date. or    N(O) If a Default Exposure Date is not to be generated automatically.  In this case, input of the exposure date will be requested at transaction level, when this transaction code is used. or    (a)(bb) (c) (d) (ee) (f) As defined in the example below. (Mandatory input when Field 2, DATA CAPTURE = 'Y', and Field 5, DEBIT CREDIT IND = 'C', otherwise not allowed.)</p><p>Run Date is the date of the data being processed which may not always be today's date.  If different, the Run Date is displayed next to the User ID on the screen.</p><p>The same day type can only be used once in an equation i.e. +01C + 02C will not be accepted.</p><p>When defining the Default Exposure Date for a credit Transaction code, the user must carefully check what has been entered for the Default Value Date. Very often the  conditions applicable to the Default Exposure Date will depend on the condition defined for the Default Value Date.</p><p>No input is allowed in this filed for transaction codes which have been flagged with the value of D in the field Debit/Credit indicator,  because all debit entries will always reduce the cleared balance immediately.</p><p>The CLEARED balance of the Account where the transaction is booked will be updated according to the value defined in this field.</p><p>Except for Reversals the Default Exposure is only applicable for Credit entries, all debit entries will reduce the CLEARED balance of the Account immediately regardless of the Value Date of the Transaction. (For Reversals, the opposite applies.)</p><p>When both working and Calendar days are entered, the sign must be the same i.e. +01C - 02W will not be accepted.</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION.CODE</field>
<desc><p>This is the code by which the Transaction details can be identified. </p>
<p>The following ranges have been assigned within EBS: </p>
<p>           001 - 099  = Data Capture            100 - 199  = Internal &amp; General use            200 - 249  = Funds Transfer            250 - 299  = Money Market/Fiduciaries            300 - 349  = Foreign Exchange            350 - 399  = Interest &amp; Charges            400 - 499  = Commercial Loans &amp; Deposits            500 - 599  = Trade Finance            600 - 649  = Securities            650 - 699  = Financial Futures            700 - 749  = Retail Banking            750 - 799  = Bonds Note:      Most Applications have hard-coded their transaction            codes.  The user should refer to the appropriate            Application system guide to find this detailed list and            load each one within this table. </p>
<p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p>
<p> 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
<p> The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>  
<p>To facilitate the recognition of the Transaction code number with the Application to which they refer, ranges have been assigned to each Application as specified in the details. (Mandatory input)</p></desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc><p>Identifies for the DATA.CAPTURE Application, the Default Value Date which will be assigned to all transactions where this Transaction code has been defined.  This Default Value Date can always be overridden by entering the Value Date directly at transaction level. </p><p>If Y, or N(O) are entered the inputs (a) to (f) are not allowed. </p><p>(a), (bb), (c) specify the number of calendar or working days to be added/subtracted to/from the Run Date in order to obtain the Default Value Date as follows: </p><p>(a) +      If days are to be added to the Run Date.  The '+' sign            should normally be used for credit Entries.            -        If days are to be subtracted from the Run                     Date.  The '-' sign should normally be used                     for Debit entries. </p><p>           (bb) 01-99Indicates the number of days to be added or                     subtracted. </p><p>           (c) C    If (bb) are calendar days,                W    If (bb) are working days. </p><p>           If it is necessary to add/subtract any other days to            those specified in (bb) before obtaining the Default            Value Date then (d), (ee), (f) are used as follows: </p><p>           (d)      As for (a) previously. </p><p>           (ee)     As for (bb) previously. </p><p>           (f) C    If ee are calendar days.                W    If ee are working days. </p><p>           It must be noted that the day type ('C' or 'W') can only            be used once in an equation. </p><p>Note:      It is important to realise that the conditions defined in            this field are only Applicable for the DATA CAPTURE            Application.  All other Applications have their Value            Date conditions defined by their own tables. </p><p>This field allows a Default Value Date to be specified for a DATA.CAPTURE transaction either, equal to the Run Date, or the Run Date plus or minus a number of working or calendar days.  This prevents the operator from having to key the Value Date on DATA.CAPTURE transactions repeatedly, where a default can be applied.  It can be overridden at Transaction level when required. </p><p>Example: +03W       will mean that the default value date is 3 working days            forward from the Run Date. </p><p>+01C + 02W  will mean that the default value date is 1 calendar day +            2 working days forward from the Run date. </p><p><p>Validation Rules:</p></p><p>Y    If the Default Value Date is to be the Run Date. or      N(O) If a Default Value Date is not to be generated automatically.  Value Date must  then be input manually when Transaction Code is used. or      (a) (bb) (c) (d) (ee) (f) As defined in the example below (Mandatory input when Field 2, DATA CAPTURE = 'Y', otherwise not allowed.)</p><p>Run Date is the date of the data being processed which may not always be today's date.  If different, the Run Date is displayed next to the User ID on the screen.</p><p>When defining the default value date for a CREDIT transaction code, the user must be careful when specifying the value of the next field (Default Exposure Date).  Very often the Default Exposure Date will depend on the Default Value Date.</p><p>The same day type ('C' or 'W') can only be used once in an equation ie. +01C + 02C will not be accepted.</p><p>When both working and calendar days are entered, the sign must be the same i.e. +01C - 02W will not be accepted.</p></desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

