<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>RE</product>
<table>RE.EXTRACT.PARAMS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to set up details required for creating output file from the routine RE RETURN EXTRACT.  This file provides the details of the information to be stored in the file created by the RE RETURN EXTRACT routine. </p>
            <p>The functions (I)nput, (C)opy, (L)ist, (P)rint, (R)eversal and (S)ee functions are available. </p>
            <p>The routine RE.RETURN.EXTRACT is to be used in order to create a disk output file for any CRF report. The details to be stored in this output file are decided by the parameters set up in the RE EXTRACT PARAMS file. </p>
            <p>The key to this file is report name. The output file created by RE RETURN EXTRACT stores components of consolidation key, line narratives and associated amounts. These details are to be specified here for the required report. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>INCL.PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRB.REPORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PL.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.KEY.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field gives details of profit consolidation key components that have to be output to the disk file. </p>
            <p>The profit consolidation key is made of 1 fixed and up to 12 variable components. This field defines which of the variable components are to be stored and in the order in which they are to be stored. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric characters in the range between 1 &amp; 12. Multi valued field associated with Field 2 (PROFIT KEY POS). (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>The component should be defined in CONSOLIDATE.COND file - PROFIT&amp;LOSS record.</p>
            <p>In case there are more than one value, then this field cannot be null if field 2  (ASSET KEY POS) is null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REP.LINE.NARR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates which of the line narratives are to be stored in the output disk file created by the routine RE.RETURN.EXTRACT . </p>
            <p>The RE.STAT.REP.LINE record has three narratives. the value(s) in this field is an indication to the RE.RETURN.EXTRACT routine to store the corresponding narratives in the output disk file. </p>
            <p>Example:   a value of 1 would result in description 2.1.1 from            RE.STAT.REP.LINE record of the report line to be            stored in the output file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>One numeric character with the values either 1 or 2 or 3. Multi valued field. (Optional input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INC.CONSOL.DETAIL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the balance fields LOCAL.BALANCE and FOREIGN.BALANCE should be populated for transaction level records.</p>
            <p>Transaction level records are created when the CONTRACT.DETAILS field is set to YES. If this is set two types of extract record will be produced:</p>
            <p />
            <p>Consolidated records identified by a numeric only key</p>
            <p />
            <p>These records contain the Consolidated Balance for the asset type from the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB file. The fields LOCAL.BALANCE and FOREIGN.BALANCE contain the consolidated balance.</p>
            <p>For profit and loss records the total from the CONSOLIDATE.PRFT.LOSS file is held in the fields LOCAL.BALANCE and FOREIGN.BALANCE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Transaction or P&amp;L consolidated records identified by a key containing the deal number and application separated by a '*'</p>
            <p />
            <p>For a deal the DEAL.BALANCE and DEAL.LCY.BALANCE will be populated. If this field is set to YES the LOCAL.BALANCE and FOREIGN.BALANCE will also be populated.</p>
            <p>For a P&amp;L level consolidated record fields DEAL.BALANCE and DEAL.LCY.BALANCE will be populated, if this field is set to YES the LOCAL.BALANCE and FOREIGN.BALANCE will also be populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p>Possible values YES, NO or null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CRB.FILE.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines at which level the CRB flat files are generated. It has 2 options FIN and FRP and the default option is FRP.</p>
            <p> A value of "FRP" will generate the CRB flat files at Branch(Book) level while running either with online service or as part COB.</p>
            <p> A value of "FIN" will generate the CRB flat files at lead company level including the branch(Book) details while running either with the online service or as part of COB</p>
            <p> And Defaults to "FRP" when this field is left blank</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CSV.FILE.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field enables to generate CRB report information as sequential file (CSV) and this is used only in case of DW.EXPORT application configured at the company level for Insight product. </p>
            <p> A value of "Y" will generate the CRB report as sequential file instead of generating in normal flat files</p>
            <p> Allowed input as "Y" only when CRB.FILE.LEVEL has the value of "FIN"</p>
            <p> Defaults to null </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the name of the CRF report to which the details present are applicable. </p>
            <p>The details in this file record are associated with the report specified in the key. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 21 type A (Alphanumeric) characters. (Mandatory input.)</p>
            <p>Must be a key to a record in the RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the closing balance or the day's movements are to be stored in the output file. </p>
            <p>The amount to be output in the disk file is mentioned here. If this field has a value of CLOSING then the closing balance of each consolidation key is stored. In case the value is MOVEMENT, net of the day's movements is stored in the output file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 8 type A (alphanumeric) characters.   Allowed values are CLOSING or MOVEMENT. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.KEY.POS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field gives details of asset consolidation key components that have to be output to the disk file. </p>
            <p>The asset consolidation key is made of 4 fixed and up to 12 variable components. This field defines which of the variable components are to be stored and in the order in which they are to be stored. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 numeric characters in the range between 1 &amp; 12. Multi valued field associated with Field 3 (PROFIT KEY POS). (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>The component should be defined in CONSOLIDATE.COND file - ASSET&amp;LIAB record.</p>
            <p>In case there are more than one value, then this field cannot be null if field 3  (PROFIT KEY POS) is null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.KEY.IN.REC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the consolidation key is to be stored in the output disk file or not. </p>
            <p>A value of YES in this field results in the consolidation key being output to the disk file created by RE.RETURN.EXTRACT. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 type A (alphanumeric) characters.   Allowed values are YES or NO. (Mandatory input.)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.DETAILS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether records created should contain details from Consolidated files in the CRB base, or should contain individual contract balances and details relevant to the CRB line definition. </p>
            <p>A value of NO will result in records containing the balance details from the CONSOLIDATE.ASST.LIAB / PRFT.LOSS files only. In this case the extract records will be keyed by sequence number only. </p>
            <p>A value of YES will result in individual contract balances for the relevant asset type of contracts being output. Additional information output when YES is used is:    ID :  Sequence * Contract Id * Asset Type    CUSTOMER id    Deal Balance in deal currency    Deal Balance in local currency    Interest / Exchange Rate    Value Date    Maturity Date    Initial Term in Days    Reamaining Term in days These fields are appended to the end of the exisiting record. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.DATE.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field gives the maturity splits required. </p>
            <p>The output file stores split balances. The split required is to be specified here. The balances are then split according to the remaining maturity and stored. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 type A (alphanumeric) characters.   Format is 1 or 2 numeric characters followed by either D, M or Y. Multi value field. (Optional input.)</p>
            <p>The ranges are to be specified as number of days (nnD) or number of months (nnM) or number of years (nnY).</p>
            <p>The ranges have to be specified in ascending sequence only.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY.FORMAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRT.ZERO.SUPP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether the CRF flat file (RE.CRF.<REPORT.NAME>) needs to be updated for the accounts/ contracts when the balances are zero</p>
            <p>A value of YES will not write the CRF extract file with the account/contract records with zero balances</p>
            <p>A value of NO will update the CRF flat file even if the contracts' balances are zero </p>
            <p>Defaults to YES</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

