<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>RE</product>
<table>RE.STAT.REP.LINE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>OVERVIEW CONSOLIDATION/REPORTING - REPORT LINE</p>
            <p>This file contains the definition of the content of a report line. It also holds the details for line narratives, sub headings, totalling for each report and control of spacing (empty lines) before and after lines and totals.</p>
            <p>Details are entered by line number. Missing line numbers (gaps) will be allowed so that extra lines may be inserted at a later time.  Before any details can be loaded to this file, the file RE.STAT.REPORT. HEAD must have been set up.  This one specifies the report name which is part of the key of this file.</p>
            <p>The content definitions may consist fully or partly of groups defined in the file RE.STAT.NAME with additional definitions of other groups or single  definitions.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ASSET4</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.LINE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field together with the previous one ('MAT DATE TO') allows the user to report in different lines of a report time based Assets and/or Liabilities products. The selection will be performed according to the REMAINING time and this multivalue field indicates in which line(s) the various time periods defined will be reported.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters representing the line number or "NOPRINT". Multivalue field. Mandatory input when previous field entered except on 1st multivalue which refers to the line number being entered.</p>
            <p>The value in the first multivalue (9.1) must be blank or "NOPRINT".  The consolidate records meeting the criteria defined in this first multivalue field will automatically go in the line being created, if NOPRINT is specified this line will not be printed.</p>
            <p>Input in this field will only be allowed for Assets and Liability Lines type i.e. where fields 21.1 to 38.1 are used to define the details of the line.</p>
            <p>When this field is used, input of 'MAT' will be mandatory in at least one multivalue of the field 'ASSET.EXT.DUP' (Field 38.1).</p>
            <p>Duplicate line numbers are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field togethr with PP.OPP.LINE allows the user to report in different lines the result of a profit and loss line definition according to the period (current month or year to date or both).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values in this field are: Cm, Ytd or All Mandatory input when Profit details are specified.</p>
            <p>Input in this field is mandatory for Profit and Loss Lines type i.e. where fields 39.1 to 51.1 are used to define the details of the line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET6.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 63.1.1 and 65.1.1 to 71.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 63.1.1 and 65.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT4.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 42.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 76.1.1 and 78.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 76.1.1 and 78.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Narrative to be printed as description for the specified line.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Up to 30 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field and subvalued to cater for the printing of narrative in several languages. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Up to 3 values allowed.</p>
            <p>All 3 values for a particular language cannot be null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAT.POS.TYP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the position type to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1. to 56.1.1 and 58.1.1 to 72.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 56.1.1 and 58.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET12</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET5</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDPT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether Profit and Loss transactions are aggregated into local currency or into a foreign currency or a number of foreign currencies.</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 characters type "CCY". Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 85.1.1 and 87.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 85.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUPRESSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicator to suppress or print a line with zero values.</p>
            <p>If suppression of 'Y' is asked on a Heading line, then the heading line is only printed if a DETAIL, LINK, or TOTAL line is to be printed before the next heading line is encountered.</p>
            <p>If suppression is numeric and if it matches with one of the group specified in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD, then the line is suppressed for zero values.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 2 type A (alphanumeric) and 9 type N (numeric) characters (with the following values: Y    =   To suppress lines with zero values. N(o) =   Do not suppress the lines with zero values. 1 to 9 Optional input.  If left blank then the No option is assumed at printing time.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies an alternative easy means of referencing the RE.STAT.REP.LINE.</p>
            <p>Any value can be entered in this field with the exception that the first character must be alpha.</p>
            <p>Like the ID (Field 0) the Mnemonic must be unique across T24</p>
            <p>Note:      For each re.stat.rep.line, the System will automatically update            the internal file "RE.MNEMONIC.LINE" which allows            the User to display the RE.STAT.REP.LINE codes in mnemonic            sequence instead.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3-10 type MNE (Uppercase alpha or numeric, first character alpha, or ".") characters.  (Optional input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT7.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 40.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 79.1.1 and 81.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 79.1.1 and 81.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET10</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT9</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT11</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET7.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 64.1.1 and 66.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 64.1.1 and 66.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT11.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 83.1.1 and 85.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 83.1.1 and 85.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET2.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 72.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 59.1.1 and 61.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 59.1.1 and 61.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET8.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 65.1.1 and 67.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 65.1.1 and 67.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field TYPE will classify a Line as a Heading, Detail or Total Line.</p>
            <p> HEADING = A Descriptive title given in a line without any finance value.</p>
            <p> DETAIL  = Returns a financial value for the selected criteria. </p>
            <p> LINK    = Used to do maturity splits in the same line, they are same as Detail.</p>
            <p> TOTAL   = Used to define Total or Sub totals for the Detail Line. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT10.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 82.1.1 and 84.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 82.1.1 and 84.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAT.APPLIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the application to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 15.1 to 31.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  Subvalue field, associated with fields 56.1.1 to 72.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 and 56.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT8.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 80.1.1 and 82.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 80.1.1 and 82.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET9.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 66.1.1 and 68.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 66.1.1 and 68.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET7</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAT.DATE.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field together with the next one ('MAT LINE NO') allows the user to report in different lines of a report time based Assets and/or Liabilities products.  The selection will be performed according to the REMAINING time which can be specified in DAYS, Business Days, Months and/or Years.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 numeric characters followed by 'D' for Days, 'B' for Business Days, 'M' for Months or 'Y' for years.  The last period is indicated by the literal 'REST'. When the "B" option is used only "1B" can be specified. This allows all deals maturign before the next working day to be reported separately. Multivalue field. Optional input; Default Value = None</p>
            <p>The time periods must be defined in chronological order i.e. from the smaller time period to 'REST' which has to be the last one.</p>
            <p>Days, Months and Years definitions cannot be mixed up i.e. time periods based on days must be defined together then the time periods based on months and finally the time periods based on years.</p>
            <p>'REST' must be the last time period defined.</p>
            <p>Input in this field will only be allowed for Asset &amp; Liability Lines type i.e. where fields 21.1 to 38.1 are used to define the details of the line.</p>
            <p>When this field is used, input of 'MAT' will be mandatory in at least one multivalue of the field 'ASSET.EXT.DUP' (Field 38.1).</p>
            <p>When this field is used, a minimum of 2 values must be specified, the last one being 'REST'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the types of Assets and Liabilities that are to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type A (alphanumric) characters. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 70.1.1 and 72.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 70.1.1 and 72.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 and 75.1.1 to 87.1.1. Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 73.1.1 and 75.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT2.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 74.1.1 and 76.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 74.1.1 and 76.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FX.REP.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Is used to specify that the original exchange rates are to be of the FX contracts are to be reported.</p>
            <p>When this field is set to historic for a closing line. The            amounts local cuurency equivalents are not taken from            the CRF base but taken directly from the Forex            contracts.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values in this field are : HISTORIC or NULL</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.OPP.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field together with 'PROFIT TYPE' and 'PROFIT SIGN' allows the user to report in different lines the result of a Profit and Loss line definition according to the sign (debit or credit) of the total line or the various consolidate records which are included in the definition of the line.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters representing the line number. Mandatory field when 'PROFIT TYPE' entered; otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p>Input in this field is only allowed for Profit and Loss Lines type i.e. where fields 39.1 to 53.1 are used to define the details of the line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDPT.APPLIC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the application (source) to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type A (alphanumeric) characters with the value for 'PL'. Subvalue field, associated with fields 74.1.1 to 87.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 72.1.1 and 74.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPACE.BEFORE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicator of number of lines to be left blank before printing of the specified line.</p>
            <p>This spacing is only performed if the line is actually printed and is in addition to whatever was asked for as SPACE AFTER (Field 7) in the previous line.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 type A (alphanumeric) characters with the following values: . N  =   Number of lines to be left blank. . NEW=   Print line on new page. Optional input.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are 0 - 9 or NEW.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET1.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 72.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 58.1.1 and 60.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 58.1.1 and 60.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFT.EXT.DUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether Default details apply,  Duplicate requests are allowed, or on which consolidate record(s) the sign defined in fields PROFIT TYPE and PROFIT SIGN applies.</p>
            <p>If fields 39.1 to 52.1 inclusive are all 'Nil', and this report line is to be the default (catch all) line for Profit and Loss not printed else where, then DEF is to be entered here.</p>
            <p>A CRF record will normally only appear once on any one report. Where it is requested that the details are to appear on two or more lines, the 'Y' is to be entered in this field to indicate that duplication is allowed.  For a CRF record to appear twice in a report, the details specified in fields 39.1 to 52.1 must be duplicated in either 39.1 to 52.1 or in 73.1 to 86.1.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 type A (alphanumeric) characters with the values: .    Y       =   Duplication allowed .    DEF     =   Default details .    REC     =   Record on which the sign applies. DAL =  Used for only default non-contingent balances. DOF  =  Used for only default contingent balances. Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 52.1. Optional input. </p>
            <p>If 'Y' is entered and no duplication is found, the entry will be treated as an error.</p>
            <p>When 'Record' has been defined in the field 10 'PROFIT TYPE' input of REC in at least one multivalue of this field will be mandatory.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET8</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINE.BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether line balances are to be recorded for this report. 'DETAIL' - denotes that details of individual movements behind the line are to be recorded by default. 'SUMMARY' - denotes that only line level movements and balances are to be recorded by default. No Value indicates that no balances will be recorded.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid values are 'DETAIL' &amp; 'SUMMARY'</p>
            <p>Input Optional</p>
            <p>A value is only allowed for the main report i.e. when there is no '.' in the key.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SPACE.AFTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicator of number of lines to be left blank after printing of the specified line.</p>
            <p>This spacing is only performed if the line is actually printed and is in addition to whatever was asked for as SPACE BEFORE (Field 6) on the next line.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 type A (alphanumeric) characters with the following values: . N  =   Number of lines to be left blank. . NEW=   Skip to new page for next line. Optional input.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are 0 - 9 or NEW.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT6.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 78.1.1 and 80.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 78.1.1 and 80.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT12.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 72.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 84.1.1 and 86.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 84.1.1 and 86.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET3</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT5</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET4.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 61.1.1 and 63.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 61.1.1 and 63.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAT.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alphabetic characters type "CCY". Subvalue field associated with 55.1.1 to 57.1.1 and 59.1.1 to 72.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 57.1.1 and 59.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.POS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the position type to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>The variables in Fields 21.1, 22.1, 23.1 and 24.1 constitute the fixed part of any Asset and Liability consolidation key.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example:   When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field.  A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed.</p>
            <p>Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included.  This match is done by a priority basis.  The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category  Sector   Type  Currency PosType  CCY  Applic                                                     Mkt.  ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004    1000      100    CREDIT   GBP                   AC SOC.005    1000      100    CREDIT                         AC SOC.007    1000                      GBP                   AC SOC.008    1000      100             USD                   AC SOC.009    1000      100                                   AC SOC.010    1000             DEBIT                          AC SOC.011    1000                      FRF                   AC SOC.012              100                                   AC SOC.013                     CREDIT                         AC SOC.014                              BEF                   AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic.  CCY.  POS  CCY   CAT   SECT   TYPE        LINE.NO. ID       MKT   TYP</p>
            <p>AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  100    CREDIT      SOC004 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  100    CREDIT      SOC005 AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  200    CREDIT      SOC007 AC       1     TR   GBP   2000  200    CREDIT      SOC013 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  100    DEBIT       SOC008 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  100    DEBIT       SOC009 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  200    CREDIT      SOC011 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  100    CREDIT      SOC012 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  200    CREDIT      SOC013 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  200    DEBIT       SOC014 AC       1     TR   FRF   2000  200    DEBIT       not reported                                                    as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type A (alphanumeric) characters corresponding to a valid Position Type. Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 and 22.1 and 24.1 to 38.1. Optional input.</p>
            <p>The input value must be a valid code on the POSITION.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field then ASSET.APPLIC ID (Field 21.1) must not be null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT5.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 77.1.1 and 80.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 77.1.1 and 79.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET5.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 62.1.1 and 64.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 62.1.1 and 64.1.1 to 88.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT4</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Key to a set of consolidation report groups on the file RE.STAT.NAME.</p>
            <p>Input to CONSOL NAME (Field 54.1) enhances the definitions in Fields 21.1 to 38.1 and 39.1 to 53.1 respectively with a definition from the file RE.STAT.NAME which consists of the same variables but are held in that file for their multiple usage in different reports. The details from that file are loaded into fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 for Asset and Liability and 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 for Profit and Loss.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Multivalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 87.1.1. Optional input.</p>
            <p>Input must be a valid key (Field 0) in the file RE.STAT.NAME.</p>
            <p>Duplications of the same key on the file RE.STAT.NAME are not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT3</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REP.NAME.LINE.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the name (ID) of the report name and line number for which details are specified in the following fields.</p>
            <p>The ID is split into a report name and the line number part separated by a full stop.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 14 type A (alphanumeric) characters consisting of a report name followed by a dot '.' and a valid line number. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>The component "report name" of the ID must be an existing ID of the file RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD.</p>
            <p>The line number must be in range 1-9999.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFT.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether Profit and Loss transactions are aggregated into local currency or into a foreign currency or a number of foreign currencies.</p>
            <p>Example:   When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field.  A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included.  This match is done by a priority basis.  The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL  PRODUCT      APPLICATION            CATEGORY CATEGORY  CURRENCY    ID</p>
            <p>SOC104     510001000          GBP    PL SOC105     510001000              PL SOC107     51000    GBP           PL SOC108     510001000          USD    PL SOC110     51000                  PL SOC111     51000    FRF           PL SOC112          1000              PL SOC114              BEF           PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC        PLPRODUCT   ID       CATEGORY CATEGORY  CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL         510001000          GBPSOC104 PL         510001000          USDSOC108 PL         510002000          GBPSOC107 PL         510001000          FRFSOC105 PL         510002000          FRFSOC111 PL         510001000          BEFSOC105 PL         510002000          BEFSOC110 PL         510001000          GBPSOC102 PL         510002000          BEFSOC114 PL         510002000          FRFnot reported                               as no match</p>
            <p>Note:      Where a standard set of instructions are to be set up,            but a line is to contain the local currency amounts            and the local currency is to vary according to the            company begin run.  A record can be set up on the            RE.STAT.RANGE file, with a start of range value of            'LCY'.  This record is then linked to this field using            the * (asterisk) option.  As required the value of            'LCY' will be substituted with the true local            currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 characters type "CCY". Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 51.1 and 53.1. Optional input.</p>
            <p>The input value must be either a possible valid code on the CURRENCY file or an * (asterisk) followed by the key of the record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL FIELD (Field 3) on that file must have a value of PROFT.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field then PROFT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1) must not be null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PP.OPP.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field togethr with PROFIT PERIOD allows the user to report in different lines the result of a profit and loss line definition according to the period (current month or year to date).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters representing the line number.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if PROFIT.PERIOD is current month or year to date.  But override is allowed if the PROFIT.PERIOD is current month or year to date.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid report line for that report.</p>
            <p>Not allowed if PROFIT.PERIOD is all.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAT.EXT.DUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether duplicate requests are allowed.</p>
            <p>A CRF record will normally only appear once on any one report.  Where it is requested that the details are to appear on two or more lines, the 'Y' is to be entered in this field to indicate that duplication is allowed.  for a CRF record to appear twice in a report, the details specified in fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 must be duplicated in either 21.1 to 37.1 or in 55.1.1 to 71.1.1.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 type A (alphanumeric) characters with the values: Y  =  Duplication allowed. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 71.1.1 and 73.1.1 to 87.1.1. Optional Input.</p>
            <p>If 'Y' is entered and no duplication is found, the entry will be treated as an error.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT6</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFT.APPLIC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the application (source) to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>'PL', 'CP', 'CB', 'IA', 'IB', 'IP', 'PLIF', 'CBIF' or 'CPIF'.</p>
            <p>The variable in Field 39.1 constitutes the fixed part of any Profit and Loss consolidation key.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example:   When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 53.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field.  A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed.</p>
            <p>Each consolidation record and currency is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF detail are to be included.  This match is done by a priority basis.  The priority basis is:- Variable 1,  Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Currency, Applic.ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL Category   Product    Currency      Applic ID                          Category</p>
            <p>SOC104       51000        1000        GBP             PL SOC105       51000        1000                        PL SOC107       51000                    GBP             PL SOC108       51000        1000        USD             PL SOC110       51000                                    PL SOC111       51000                    FRF             PL SOC112                    1000                        PL SOC114                                BEF             PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Records exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC       PL CATEGORY   PRODUCT      CCY      LINE NO ID                         CATEGORY PL             51000        1000        GBP      SOC104 PL             51000        1000        USD      SOC108 PL             51000        2000        GBP      SOC107 PL             51000        1000        FRF      SOC105 PL             51000        2000        FRF      SOC111 PL             51000        1000        BEF      SOC105 PL             51000        2000        BEF      SOC110 PL             50000        1000        GBP      SOC112 PL             50000        2000        BEF      SOC114 PL             50000        2000        FRF      not reported                                                  as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>4 type A (alphanumeric) characters with the value of 'PL". Multivalue field associated with fields 40.1 to 53.1. Optional input.</p>
            <p>Values accepted 'PL', 'CP', 'CB', 'IA', 'IB', 'IP', 'PLIF', 'CBIF' or 'CPIF'.</p>
            <p>If any data is to be entered in fields 40.1 to 52.1 then this field must be present.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET12.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 69.1.1 and 71.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 69.1.1 and 71.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains all the Override messages which the user agreed to during input.</p>
            <p>During the validation stage of a new line, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly, for instance, that no details are present in a line type 'DETAIL' (Field 1).</p>
            <p>In the event that the user confirms the Override, the full text of the actual Override Message will be stored, for reference purposes only, in this multivalue filed.</p>
            <p>For example, if the user inserts a new line type 'DETAIL' and no are entered, then when the line is validated a warning bell will sound and a message will appear, at the foot of the screen, which reads:</p>
            <p>'NO DETAILS PRESENT'</p>
            <p>This will draw the user's attention to the line entered, which may be a mistake and can then be corrected, or, on the other hand, it may be correct input and so the user confirms that his line definition is really intended. If, subsequently, the line record is either fully displayed or printed, then all override messages will be present.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Internal field. Multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDAT.CCY.MKT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency market to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character. Subvalue field; associated with field 55.1.1 and 57.1.1 to 72.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1. to 55.1.1 and 57.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET10.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 67.1.1 and 70.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 67.1.1 and 70.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.ACCUM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identity of TOTAL (accumulator) to be updated with all values on lines identified as type DETAIL, LINK and TOTAL.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>One numeric character. Multivalue field to accumulate lines into more than one accumulator. Optional input when TYPE (Field 1) is equal to 'DETAIL', 'LINK' or TOTAL; otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p>Input is only allowed if TYPE (Field 1) is equal to 'DETAIL', or 'LINK' or TOTAL.</p>
            <p>The Accumulator number can not be duplicated within one line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT9.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 81.1.1 and 83.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 81.1.1 and 83.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field together with 'PROFIT.SIGN' and 'PROFIT.OPP.LINE' allows the user to report in different lines the result of a Profit and Loss line definition according to the sign (debit or credit) of the total line or the various consolidate records which are included in the definition of the line.</p>
            <p>he two values have the following meaning:</p>
            <p>.          Line:    When the condition defined for the sign                     applies to the total line result.</p>
            <p>.          Record:  When the condition defined for the sign                     applies to the individual consolidation                     records contained in the line being created</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values in this field are: Line or Record/ Optional Input. Default = Nil.</p>
            <p>Input in this field is only allowed for Profit and Loss Lines type i.e. where fields 39.1 to 53.1 are used to define the details of the line.</p>
            <p>When 'Record' has been input in this field, input of 'REC' will be mandatory in at least one multivalue of the field 'PROFIT.EXT.DUP' (Field 53.1).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT8</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET9</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET11.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 68.1.1 and 70.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 68.1.1 and 70.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT10</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the types(s) of Asset and Liabilities that are to be included in this line. See below for details.</p>
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 36.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed.</p>
            <p>Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used. The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p />
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td />
                    <td>Category</td>
                    <td>Sector</td>
                    <td>Type</td>
                    <td>Currency</td>
                    <td>PosType</td>
                    <td>CCY Mkt.</td>
                    <td>Applic ID</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.004</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td>GBP</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.005</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.006</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>GBP</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.007</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td />
                    <td>USD</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.008</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.009</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td />
                    <td>DEBIT</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.010</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>FRF</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.011</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.012</td>
                    <td />
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.013</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>SOC.014</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>BEF</td>
                    <td />
                    <td />
                    <td>AC</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>The following CRF records exist: </p>
            <p />
            <table>
                <tr>
                    <td>APPLIC</td>
                    <td>CCY. MKT</td>
                    <td>POS TYP</td>
                    <td>CCY</td>
                    <td>CAT</td>
                    <td>SECT</td>
                    <td>TYPE</td>
                    <td>LINE.NO</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>GBP</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td>SOC004</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>USD</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td>SOC005</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>GBP</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>200</td>
                    <td>DEBIT</td>
                    <td>SOC010</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>GBP</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>200</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td>SOC007</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>GBP</td>
                    <td>2000</td>
                    <td>200</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td>SOC013</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>USD</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td>DEBIT</td>
                    <td>SOC008</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>USD</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>200</td>
                    <td>DEBIT</td>
                    <td>SOC010</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>FRF</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td>DEBIT</td>
                    <td>SOC009</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>FRF</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>200</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td>SOC011</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>FRF</td>
                    <td>1000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td>DEBIT</td>
                    <td>SOC010</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>BEF</td>
                    <td>2000</td>
                    <td>100</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td>SOC012</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>BEF</td>
                    <td>2000</td>
                    <td>200</td>
                    <td>CREDIT</td>
                    <td>SOC013</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>BEF</td>
                    <td>2000</td>
                    <td>200</td>
                    <td>DEBIT</td>
                    <td>SOC014</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>AC</td>
                    <td>1</td>
                    <td>TR</td>
                    <td>FRF</td>
                    <td>2000</td>
                    <td>200</td>
                    <td>DEBIT</td>
                    <td>not reported as no match.</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 36.1 and 38.1.</p>
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an *, then input         must consist of one of the following: .</p>
            <p>LIVECR Live credit .</p>
            <p>LIVEDB Live debit .</p>
            <p>LIVECMT Live Commitment-Loan Facility .</p>
            <p>FORWARDCR Forward credit .</p>
            <p>FORWARDDB Forward debit .</p>
            <p>FORWARDCMT Forward Commitment-</p>
            <p>Loan Facility .</p>
            <p>MMFIDCR Fiduciary Credit (Live) .</p>
            <p>MMFIDDB Fiduciary Debit (Live) .</p>
            <p>OVERDUECR Overdue credit .</p>
            <p>OVERDUEDB Overdue debit .</p>
            <p>NABCR Non accrual basis credit .</p>
            <p>NABDB Non accrual basis debit .</p>
            <p>FXSPOTBUY Spot contingent FX buy .</p>
            <p>FXSPOTSELL Spot contingent FX sell .</p>
            <p>FXFWDBUY Forward contingent FX buy .</p>
            <p>FXFWDSELL Forward contingent FX sell .</p>
            <p>DEBIT Accounts in debit .</p>
            <p>CREDIT Accounts in credit .</p>
            <p>SUSPENS Accounts where interest is suspensed. .</p>
            <p>50000 - 59999 Profit and Loss category code range for assets and liabilities reserve accounts/accumulations .</p>
            <p>SP Followed by 50000 - 59999.  SP (Suspended) followed by category code range  for suspended interest/ commission, etc.</p>
            <p>Furthermore, where the CRF.BY.TYPE field on PD.PARAMETER is flagged to 'Y', OVERDUEDB and NABDB may be replaced by :</p>
            <p>OVERDUEPR Overdue Principal debit</p>
            <p>OVERDUEIN Overdue Interest debit</p>
            <p>OVERDUECH Overdue Charges debit</p>
            <p>OVERDUECO Overdue commission debit</p>
            <p>OVERDUETX Overdue Taxes debit</p>
            <p>OVERDUEA1-A5 Overdue Additional Mortgage payments debit</p>
            <p>NABPR Non Accrual Basis Principal debit</p>
            <p>NABIN Non Accrual Basis Interest debit</p>
            <p>NABCH Non Accrual Basis Charge debit</p>
            <p>NABCO Non Accrual Basis Commission debit</p>
            <p>NABTX Non Accrual Basis Tax debit</p>
            <p>NABA1-A5 Non Accrual Basis Additional Mortgage Payments debit</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the input value entered starts with an '*' (asterisk),         then the value following must be that of a key for a         record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL         FIELD (Field 3) on that file, must have the value of         ASSET.TYPE.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID         (Field 21.1) must not be null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT.SIGN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field together with 'PROFIT TYPE' and 'PROFIT.OPP.LINE' allows the user to report in different lines the result of a Profit and Loss line definition according to the sign (debit or credit) of the total line or the various consolidate records which are included in the definition of the line.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values in this field are: .  Debit or      .  Credit Mandatory input when 'PROFIT TYPE' has been input; otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p>Input in this field is only allowed for Profit and Loss Lines type i.e. where fields 39.1 to 53.1 are used to define the details of the line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.OPP.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field together with "ASSET SIGN" allows the user to report in different lines the result of an asset and liability line definition according to the sign (debit or credit) of the total line.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 4 numeric characters representing the line number. Mandatory field when "PROFIT TYPE" entered; otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p>Input in this field is only allowed for asset and liability lines type i.e. where fields 21.1 to 38.1 are used to define the details of the line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET6</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.SIGN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field together with "ASSET SIGN" allows the user to report in different lines the result of an asset and liability line definition according to the sign (debit or credit) of the total line.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Acceptable values in this field are: . Debit or       . Credit Mandatory input when "ASSET OPP LINE" has been input; otherwise not allowed.</p>
            <p>Input in this field is only allowed for asset and liability lines type i.e. where fields 21.1 to 38.1 are used to define the details of the line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT7</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.PRINT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the line as either a Heading, Total or Detail line.  <p>Validation Rules:</p> Up to 11 type A (alphanumeric) characters allowing for the following values: .    Heading .    Total .    Detail .    Link Mandatory input. The following values only are accepted: HEADING -          Signifies that the line is a section heading line to be printed at the beginning of a section. TOTAL   -          Denotes that the line is one in which totals are to be printed. DETAIL  -          Denotes that the line is one for which data accumulated from the Consolidate ASSET&amp;LIAB and Consolidate PROFIT&amp;LOSS record files are to be printed. LINK    -          Same as DETAIL, but applicable (if required) for MM, LD etc. The information is broken down into Time periods specified in the file RE.REP.STAT.LINK. 'LINK' can only be used for group type of CLOSING. The checking is performed by the RE.REP.STAT.LINK file program.  If, at the time of printing, there is no details on the RE.REP.STAT.LINK file for this line number and report name, then the line is treated as a DETAIL line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>K.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>HEADING - A Descriptive title given in a line without any finance value.</p>
            <p>DETAIL - Returns a financial value for the selected criteria.</p>
            <p>LINK - Used to do maturity splits in the same line, they are same as Detail.</p>
			<p>TOTAL - Used to define Total or Sub totals for the Detail Line.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET3.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 59.1.1 to 70.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (NAME Field 1.1).</p>
            <p>Fields 55.1.1 to 71.1.1 correspond to fields 21.1 to 37.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record. Subvalue field associated with fields 55.1.1 to 60.1.1 and 62.1.1 to 72.1.1.  Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 60.1.1 and 62.1.1 to 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LL.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of  35 characters may be entered.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LDPT.EXT.DUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether duplicate requests are allowed.</p>
            <p>A CRF record will normally only appear once on any one report. Where it is requested that the details are to appear on two or more lines, the 'Y' is to be entered in this field to indicate that duplication is allowed.  For a CRF record to appear twice in a report, the details specified in fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 must be duplicated in either 39.1 to 52.1 or in 73.1.1 to 86.1.1.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 3 type A (alphanumeric) characters with the value: Y  =  Duplication allowed. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1. Multivalue field associated with fields 54.1 to 86.1.1. Optional Input.</p>
            <p>If 'Y' is entered and no duplication is found, the entry will be treated as an error.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT3.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields 74.1.1 to 85.1.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24.  They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line.  The prompts (or components) are moved by the system form the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>Fields 73.1.1 to 86.1.1 correspond to fields 39.1 to 52.1 except that the data cannot be input or amended.  The data is copied from the file RE.STAT.NAME when a key of that file is entered in CONSOL.NAME (Field 54.1).</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record. Subvalue field associated with fields 73.1.1 to 75.1.1 and 77.1.1. to 87.1.1 Multivalue field(s) associated with fields 54.1 to 75.1.1 and 77.1.1 and 87.1.1. System generated field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROFIT12</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 40.1 to 51.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record PROFIT&amp;LOSS (Field 1.X NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the one standard, fixed components as defined in the Field 39.1.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 39.1 - 52.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, APPLIC ID.</p>
            <p>For the purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is PL Category Code, Variable 2 is Product Category Code, and Variables 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following details report lines have been loaded for Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>PL PRODUCT APPLICATION CATEGORY CATEGORY CURRENCY ID</p>
            <p>SOC104 510001000 GBP PL SOC105 510001000 PL SOC107 51000 GBP PL SOC108 510001000 USD PL SOC110 51000 PL SOC111 51000 FRF PL SOC112 1000 PL SOC114 BEF PL</p>
            <p>The following CRF Record exist:</p>
            <p>APPLIC PLPRODUCT ID CATEGORY CATEGORY CCYLINE NO</p>
            <p>PL 510001000 GBPSOC104 PL 510001000 USDSOC108 PL 510002000 GBPSOC107 PL 510001000 FRFSOC105 PL 510002000 FRFSOC111 PL 510001000 BEFSOC105 PL 510002000 BEFSOC110 PL 510001000 GBPSOC102 PL 510002000 BEFSOC114 PL 510002000 FRFnot reported as no match</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond PROFIT &amp; LOSS record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 39.1 to 40.1 and 41.1 to 53.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then PROFIT APPLIC ID (Field 39.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a      default (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "PROFIT&amp;LOSS".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET11</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Fields 25.1 to 36.1 contain the possible maximum of twelve variable fields as part of the composite total consolidation key permissible in T24. They specify conditions to be satisfied for reporting against this line. The prompts (or components) are moved by the system from the consolidation conditions record ASSET&amp;LIAB (Field 1.1 NAME).</p>
            <p>The format code and length is obtained from the original program using file name and field number as specified on the consolidation conditions record. These fields will be part of the first set of multivalue associated fields. The possible maximum of twelve variable fields is in addition to the four standard, fixed components as defined in the Fields 21.1 to 24.1 above.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example: When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field. A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed. Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included. This match is done by a priority basis. The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category Sector Type Currency PosType CCY Applic Mkt. ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004 1000 100 CREDIT GBP AC SOC.005 1000 100 CREDIT AC SOC.007 1000 GBP AC SOC.008 1000 100 USD AC SOC.009 1000 100 AC SOC.010 1000 DEBIT AC SOC.011 1000 FRF AC SOC.012 100 AC SOC.013 CREDIT AC SOC.014 BEF AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic. CCY. POS CCY CAT SECT TYPE LINE.NO. ID MKT TYP</p>
            <p>AC 1 TR GBP 1000 100 CREDIT SOC004 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 CREDIT SOC005 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR GBP 1000 200 CREDIT SOC007 AC 1 TR GBP 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR USD 1000 100 DEBIT SOC008 AC 1 TR USD 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 100 DEBIT SOC009 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 CREDIT SOC011 AC 1 TR FRF 1000 200 DEBIT SOC010 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 100 CREDIT SOC012 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 CREDIT SOC013 AC 1 TR BEF 2000 200 DEBIT SOC014 AC 1 TR FRF 2000 200 DEBIT not reported as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>As for the field specified in the Consolidate Cond ASSET &amp; LIAB record.     Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 24.1 and 26.1 to 38.1.     Optional input.</p>
            <p>If the value entered does not start with an * (asterisk), then it must be     a valid value according to length, type, etc. of the original field.</p>
            <p>If value entered starts with an * (asterisk), the data following the     asterisk must be a key to a record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL field (Field 3) on     that file, must have the same value as the name loaded for this field from     CONSOLIDATE.COND.</p>
            <p>If this variable is not from a General file and has not been specified on     the CONSOLIDATE COND file for Application in ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     then no input is allowed here.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1)     must not be null.</p>
            <p>Input would not be allowed, if the Line is for a  default     (non-company specific) Report  (explained below) and the field     FILE.NAME for the variable  is "NO LOOKUP" in the record with     ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The above referred matching and validation is only for lines defined for  default (non-company specific)  reports i.e. the BRANCH.MODE is not equal to Y in the Report's (specified in the first part of the ID) RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record; For validation, the default consolidation definition in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB" would be used. Further, if  a  CRF key variable has two components separated by "_"  due to redefinition of  the  variable  in Company specific consolidation record (explained below), then the matching of the CRF key would depend on the first component of the variable, before the character "_".</p>
            <p>If the LINE has been  defined for a Company specific Report i.e. BRANCH.MODE=Y in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record, then the matching and validation  would be done as follows:</p>
            <p>1.  The value of the field BRANCH in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD record would determine for which Company the Report needs to be generated. The Report would not be generated for other Companies.</p>
            <p>2.  The company specific consolidation key is first  determined for the Company specified as BRANCH. For the Company with ID "xxxxxxxxx", if  in the COMPANY record,  the  field CONS.KEY.CO is null, then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record  with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.xxxxxxxxx". If on the other hand, if the field CONS.KEY.CO refers  to another Company, say with ID "yyyyyyyyy", then the Company specific consolidation key would be the record with the ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB.yyyyyyyyy".</p>
            <p>3. If  the  variable field had been  redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the second component of the CRF key variable  (followed by the character "_") would be matched. The validation for input would also depend on the definition of the variable, in the Company specific consolidation record.</p>
            <p>4. If the variable had not been redefined in the Company specific consolidation record (as determined above), then the CRF key variable would have only one component, and it would be matched. The validation for input would then depend on the  definition of  the variable  in the record with ID "ASSET&amp;LIAB".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.APPLIC.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the application to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>The presently allowed values (see below) are hard coded and additional applications to be included in the consolidation/reporting process need to be added in form of a program change.</p>
            <p>The variables in Fields 21.1, 22.1, 23.1 and 24.1 constitute the fixed part of any Asset and Liability consolidation key.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example:   When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field.  A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed.</p>
            <p>Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included.  This match is done by a priority basis.  The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used. The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category  Sector   Type  Currency PosType  CCY  Applic                                                     Mkt.  ID SOC.004    1000      100    CREDIT   GBP                   AC SOC.005    1000      100    CREDIT                         AC SOC.007    1000                      GBP                   AC SOC.008    1000      100             USD                   AC SOC.009    1000      100                                   AC SOC.010    1000             DEBIT                          AC SOC.011    1000                      FRF                   AC SOC.012              100                                   AC SOC.013                     CREDIT                         AC SOC.014                              BEF                   AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic.  CCY.  POS  CCY   CAT   SECT   TYPE        LINE.NO. ID       MKT   TYP</p>
            <p>AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  100    CREDIT      SOC004 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  100    CREDIT      SOC005 AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  200    CREDIT      SOC007 AC       1     TR   GBP   2000  200    CREDIT      SOC013 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  100    DEBIT       SOC008 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  100    DEBIT       SOC009 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  200    CREDIT      SOC011 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  100    CREDIT      SOC012 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  200    CREDIT      SOC013 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  200    DEBIT       SOC014 AC       1     TR   FRF   2000  200    DEBIT       not reported                                                    as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>2 type A (alphanumeric) characters corresponding to a valid Application identification. Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 38.1. Optional input.</p>
            <p>The following values only are presently accepted: . AC          =  ACCOUNT . MM          =  MONEY MARKET . FX          =  FOREX . LD          =  LOANS AND DEPOSITS . BD          =  BONDS . AZ          =  ALL IN ONE ACCOUNT . AL          =  ASSET AND LIABILITY POSITION</p>
            <p>BL          =  BILLS PROCESSING. DX          =  DERIVATIVES. FD          =  FIDUCIARY PLACEMENTS. FR          =  FUTURE RATE AGREEMENT. IA          =  INTERNATIONAL ACCOUNT STANDARDS. IC          =  INTEREST AND CHARGES. LC          =  LETTER OF CREDIT. LI          =  LIMITS</p>
            <p>MD          =  MISCELLANEOUS DEALS. MG          =  MORTGAGES. ND         =  NDF - NON-DELIVERY FORWARD. PD          =  PAST DUE. FD          =  FIDUCIARY PLACEMENTS. SC          =  SEC TRANSFER OR POSITION TRANSFER. SL          =  SYNDICATED LOANS . SW          =  SWAPS . Sy          =  STRUCTURED PRODUCTS</p>
            <p>If data is to be entered in fields 21.1 to 37.1, this field must be present.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.CCY.MKT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency market to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>The variables in Fields 21.1, 22.1, 23.1 and 24.1 constitute the fixed part of any Asset and Liability consolidation key. ity consolidation key.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example:   When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field.  A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed.</p>
            <p>Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included.  This match is done by a priority basis.  The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category  Sector   Type  Currency PosType  CCY  Applic                                                     Mkt.  ID</p>
            <p>SOC.004    1000      100    CREDIT   GBP                   AC SOC.005    1000      100    CREDIT                         AC SOC.007    1000                      GBP                   AC SOC.008    1000      100             USD                   AC SOC.009    1000      100                                   AC SOC.010    1000             DEBIT                          AC SOC.011    1000                      FRF                   AC SOC.012              100                                   AC SOC.013                     CREDIT                         AC SOC.014                              BEF                   AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic.  CCY.  POS  CCY   CAT   SECT   TYPE        LINE.NO. ID       MKT   TYP</p>
            <p>AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  100    CREDIT      SOC004 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  100    CREDIT      SOC005 AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  200    CREDIT      SOC007 AC       1     TR   GBP   2000  200    CREDIT      SOC013 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  100    DEBIT       SOC008 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  100    DEBIT       SOC009 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  200    CREDIT      SOC011 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  100    CREDIT      SOC012 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  200    CREDIT      SOC013 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  200    DEBIT       SOC014 AC       1     TR   FRF   2000  200    DEBIT       not reported                                                    as no match.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 numeric character corresponding to a valid Market Type. Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 and 23.1 to 38.1. Optional input.</p>
            <p>The input value must be a valid code on the POSITION.TYPE file.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field then ASSET.APPLIC ID (Field 21.1) must not be null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the currency to be included in this line.</p>
            <p>The variables in Fields 21.1, 22.1, 23.1 and 24.1 constitute the fixed part of any Asset and Liability consolidation key.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Example:   When loading details about the consolidation records to be included in a line, (Fields 21.1 - 37.1), it is not necessary to enter a value in each field.  A null value means that any value for that actual field is allowed.</p>
            <p>Each consolidation record and type is matched against the line details loaded, to determine in which line(s) the CRF details are to be included.  This match is done by a priority basis.  The priority basis is:- Variable 1, Variable 2, Variable 3, Variable 4, Variable 5, Variable 6, Variable 7, Variable 8, Variable 9, Variable 10, Variable 11, Variable 12, Type, Currency, Position Type, Currency Market, Applic. ID.</p>
            <p>For purpose of this example assume Variable 1 is Category Code, Variable 2 is sector Code, and Variable 3-12 inclusive are not used.</p>
            <p>The following detail report lines have been loaded for the Report Statement of Condition ('SOC').</p>
            <p>Category  Sector   Type  Currency PosType  CCY  Applic                                                     Mkt.  ID SOC.004    1000      100    CREDIT   GBP                   AC SOC.005    1000      100    CREDIT                         AC SOC.007    1000                      GBP                   AC SOC.008    1000      100             USD                   AC SOC.009    1000      100                                   AC SOC.010    1000             DEBIT                          AC SOC.011    1000                      FRF                   AC SOC.012              100                                   AC SOC.013                     CREDIT                         AC SOC.014                              BEF                   AC</p>
            <p>The following CRF records exist:</p>
            <p>Applic.  CCY.  POS  CCY   CAT   SECT   TYPE        LINE.NO. ID       MKT   TYP</p>
            <p>AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  100    CREDIT      SOC004 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  100    CREDIT      SOC005 AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   GBP   1000  200    CREDIT      SOC007 AC       1     TR   GBP   2000  200    CREDIT      SOC013 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  100    DEBIT       SOC008 AC       1     TR   USD   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  100    DEBIT       SOC009 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  200    CREDIT      SOC011 AC       1     TR   FRF   1000  200    DEBIT       SOC010 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  100    CREDIT      SOC012 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  200    CREDIT      SOC013 AC       1     TR   BEF   2000  200    DEBIT       SOC014 AC       1     TR   FRF   2000  200    DEBIT       not reported                                                    as no match.</p>
            <p>Note:      Where a standard set of instructions are to be set up,            but a line is to contain the local currency amounts and            the local currency is to vary according to the company            being run.  A record can be set up on the            RE.STAT.RANGE file, with a start of range value of            'LCY'.  This record is then linked to this field using the            * (asterisk) option.  As required the value of 'LCY' will            be substituted with the true local currency.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 alphbetic characters type 'CCY. Multivalue field associated with fields 21.1 to 23.1 and 25.1 to 38.1. Optional input.</p>
            <p>The input value must be eiether a valid code on the CURRENCY file or an * (asterisk) followed by the key of the record on the RE.STAT.RANGE file.</p>
            <p>When linking to the RE.STAT.RANGE file, then the CONSOL FIELD (Field 3) on that file must have a value of ASSET.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p>If a value is entered in this field, then ASSET APPLIC ID (Field 21.1) must not be null.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ASSET.EXT.DUP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates whether Default details apply, Duplicate requests  are allowed or if this consolidate record is to be split by time periods as defined in fields MAT DATE TO (Field 8.1) and MAT LINE TO (Field 9.1).</p>
            <p>If fields 21.1 to 37.1 inclusive are all 'Nil', and this report line is to be the default (catch all) line for Asset and Liability details not printed else where, then DEF is to be entered here.</p>
            <p>A CRF record will normally only appear once on any one report. Where it is requested that the details are to appear on two or more lines, the 'Y' is to be entered in  this field to indicate that duplication is allowed.  For a CRF record to appear twice in a report, the details specified in fields 21.1 to 37.1 must be duplicated in either 21.1 to 37.1 or in 55.1 to 71.1.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p> Up to 3 type A (alphanumeric) characters with the values: .    Y      =    Duplication allowed .    DEF    =    Default details .    MAT    =    Maturity split request. DAL = Used for only default non-contingent balances. DOF = Used for only default contingent balances Multivalue field associated with fields  21.1 to 37.1. Optional input.</p>
            <p> If 'Y' is entered and no duplication is found, the entry will be treated as an error.</p>
            <p>'MAT' will only be allowed when fields 'MAT DATE TO' and 'MAT LINE NO' have been defined.</p>
            <p>'MAT' is mandatory in at least one multivalue when 'MAT DATE TO' and 'MAT LINE NO' have been defined.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

