<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>RE</product>
<table>RE.STAT.BAL.REC</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to print the balance details of the base deals for specified report lines. </p>
            <p>The functions (I)nput, (C)opy, (L)ist, (P)rint, (R)eversal, (S)ee and (V)erify are available. </p>
            <p>The functions (I)nput and (C)opy are used to load the records into the file. </p>
            <p>The (V)erify function is used to print the report lines. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>REPORT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the report for which the lines are to be printed. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>3 - 21 SWIFT characters. Multivalue field associated with fields 3.1 and 4.1. Mandatory input.</p>
            <p>Must be an ID of a header record in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used for notes. </p>
            <p>This field is used for entering notes and is not used anywhere else. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters. Multivalue field. Optional input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the different records in this file. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1-14 SWIFT characters. Mandatory input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINE.NO.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the last line number to be printed. </p>
            <p>Line number 9999 represents the last available line for the report. </p>
            <p>If specific line numbers required then this field should be left blank. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 4 numeric characters. Sub valued field associated with field 3.1.1 and multivalue field associated with field 2.1.</p>
            <p>If not specified as 9999 then must be present in RE.STAT.REP.LINE as part of the report specified in REPORT NAME (Field 2.1).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINE.NO.ST</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the first line number to be printed. </p>
            <p>Line number 0001 represents first available line for the report. </p>
            <p>If specific line numbers required then this field should have the line numbers required while LINE NO END (Field 4.1.1) is left null. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>1 - 4 numeric characters. Mandatory input. Sub valued field associated with field 4.1.1 and multivalue field associated with field 2.1</p>
            <p>If not specified as 0001 then must be present in RE.STAT.REP.LINE as part of the report specified in REPORT NAME (Field 2.1).</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

