<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>RE</product>
<table>RE.STAT.TOTAL.RANGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This file contains definitions of a range of values, or a set of individual values, for report line content definitions; where total lines may be split according to the above values. </p>
            <p>It allows the setting up of "standard", often used or virtual views. For example a country may have convertible and non-convertible currencies defined. A record can be set up containing the list of convertible currencies, which would then allow the report to show the total amount, the convertible total and the non-convertible total. This file is used in conjunction with the report heading file RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD. For more comprehensive details refer to the helptext for fields TOTAL.SPLIT, SPLIT.INC.EXC and NARRATIVE in this file. </p>
            <p>The eventual usage of the defined range(s) are recorded by the system, attempts to reverse those which are still in use is not permitted. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the beginning of a range of values or the first of a discrete set of values to be represented by the MNEMONIC.NAME. </p>
            <p>If a range of values needs to be defined the END.RANGE field will contain the last value of the range. If a number of discrete values are required then this field can be expanded to encompass all the individual values, in this case no END.RANGE can be input. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Note:     Value of LCY will be replaced with local currency code           from company record at time of printing. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters, type 'A'. Multi-value field, associated with field CONSOL.FIELD. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The values entered must be a possible valid value for the key component for which this range is defined.</p>
            <p>The range of allowed values for the special data names in CONSOL.FIELD are as follows: APPLICATION         Any application code ASSET.CURRENCY      Any currency code PROFT.CURRENCY      Any currency code ASSET.TYPE          Any from the list below: LIVECR              Live credit LIVEDB              Live debit LIVECMT             Live Commitment (Loan facility) FORWARDCR           Forward credit FORWARDDB           Forward debit FORWARDCMT          Forward Commitment MMFIDCR             Fiduciary credit (live) MMFIDDB             Fiduciary debit (live) OVERDUECR           Overdue credit OVERDUEDB           Overdue debit NABCR     Non accrual basis credit NABDB     Non accrual basis debit FXSPOTBUY           Spot contingent FX buy FXSPOTSELL          Spot contingent FX sell FXFWDBUY            Forward contingent FX buy FXFWDSELL           Forward contingent FX sell DEBIT     Accounts in debit CREDIT              Accounts in credit SUSPENS             Accounts where interest is suspended 50000-59999         Profit and Loss category code range for assets and liabilities reserve accounts/accumulations. SP50000-SP59999     Profit and Loss category code range prefixed by SP (suspended) for suspended interest/commission etc.</p>
            <p>Multi ranges not allowed, but multiple values are permitted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONSOL.FIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the field name for which the set of values or a range of values are defined. </p>
            <p>The consolidation field must be either a valid (existing) field name in the file CONSOLIDATE.COND, or must be one of the following:           APPLICATION           ASSET.CURRENCY           PROFT.CURRENCY           ASSET.TYPE </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 18 alphanumeric characters, type 'A'. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The mnemonic name (key) must be unique.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Narrative used for enrichment/explanation of the mnemonic name. </p>
            <p>The description will be seen as enrichment against the mnemonic when used in RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD. This description does not appear on the report line, it is solely for clarification of the mnemonic id. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters, type 'A'. Multi-value field to allow multi-language descriptions to be set up. (Mandatory input)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.RANGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the last of the range of values to be represented by the MNEMONIC.NAME. </p>
            <p>If a range of values needs to be defined the END.RANGE field will contain the last value of the range. The first value will be defined in the field START.RANGE. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 alphanumeric characters, type 'A'. Multi-value field. (Optional input)</p>
            <p>Input is only allowed if a value exists in field START.RANGE.</p>
            <p>Value in this field must be greater than the value in START.RANGE.</p>
            <p>The values entered must be a possible value for the key component for which this range is specified.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNEMONIC.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Name/identity to specify a set of discrete values or a range of values in report lines. </p>
            <p>The mnemonic name will be used in the file RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD as a total line content definition for the values or a range of values defined in this table. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 20 alphanumeric characters, type 'A'. (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p>The mnemonic name (key) must be unique.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

