<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>RE</product>
<table>RE.TRANSFER.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This defines the Parameters to be used in the Export and Import of the CRB data between physically separate databases. </p>
            <p>The Export process copies the CRB data and some Control information from the specified database into the Export staging area (which is a Unix directory within the "data account" - UniVerse file F.CRB.EXPORT) from where it can be taken out of this database on to tape or any other media. This is done by a "Verify" function in the Application RE.EXPORT.REQUEST or can be done in the Batch in the Process RE.CRB.EXPORT. </p>
            <p>The Import process copies the Exported "tape" into the Import staging area (which is a Unix directory within the "data account" - UniVerse file F.CRB.IMPORT) and then copies the CRB data from the staging area to the CRB files of the specified "Reporting" Company (field CONSOLIDATION.MARK on the COMPANY record should be "R") within the Multi-Company setup and then will Recalculate the CRB Report. This can only be done during the Online session by a "Verify" function in the Application RE.IMPORT.REQUEST. </p>
            <p>Finally, the Consolidated CRB Reports can be produced using the procedures to produces Consolidated  CRB Reports in a Multi-Company Database. </p>
            <p>Authorisation of the record "SYSTEM" in this file will create the Staging area and the files required to Export and Import the CRB data. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multivalue set associated with field range COMPANY.CODE to RESERVED1.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used when importing data. This setting controls what happens in the event of a data error.</p>
            <table border="3" bgcolor="#FFFFFF">
                <tr>
                    <td><strong>Value</strong>
                    </td>
                    <td><strong>Action taken</strong>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>C</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>Continue to import on data error. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>D</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>Delete/skip import on data error. </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <p>S</p>
                    </td>
                    <td>Skip import on data error. </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <p><strong><p>Validation Rules:</p></strong>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Mandatory field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multivalue set associated with field range COMPANY.CODE to RESERVED1.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REP.NAMES</field>
<desc>
            <p>The names of the Reports that have to be Consolidated from the separate databases. </p>
            <p>The Report names specified here will be used to recalculate the Report lines in the Import database. </p>
            <p>If this field is left blank, the Imported CRB files will not be recalculated and the Consolidated Reports can not be produced. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 21 characters may be entered. </p>
            <p>Must be a valid entry on the RE.STAT.REPORT.HEAD file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MNE.MAPPED.TO</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used for Mnemonic Mapping of the CRB files. </p>
            <p>The 3 alpha characters specified here will be used in the mnemonic mapping of the Export and Import files. </p>
            <p>This is to be used when more than one of the Export or Import databases have been setup with the same Company Mnemonic. </p>
            <p>e.g. - If there are 3 separate T24 databases, all with the same mnemonic "ABC" then the CRB files will get overwritten when they are imported with their original file names (FABC.xxxxx). In such a situation, this field can be setup to say "XYZ" so that the CRB files will be transferred with the file name of FXYZ.xxx instead of FABC.xxx so that the files will not be overwritten in the Import process and data will not be lost. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 digit Alpha characters. </p>
            <p>Multivalue field associated with field range COMPANY.CODE         to RESERVED1. </p>
            <p>Mandatory if COMPANY.CODE has been input. Default value         is the Company Mnemonic for the Company specified in         COMPANY.CODE.</p>
            <p>Can be any valid 3 character Alphanumeric data.</p>
            <p>Default value is the Company Mnemonic specified in         COMPANY.CODE.</p>
            <p>No duplicates are allowed within this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED3</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Multivalue set associated with field range COMPANY.CODE to RESERVED1.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is reserved for future expansion. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.IMPORT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Effective date of the CRB data when it was last Imported is stored in this field. There is no value in this field in an "Export" database. </p>
            <p>The Effective date of the CRB data, the last time the Import process was done, is stored in this field. This date is used to compare with the effective date of the rest of the system when the Consolidated Reports are produced and a Warning messages are printed in the Reports. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System generated Noinput field.</p>
            <p>System maintained. Noinput field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The company code for which the CRB data has to be exported or imported. </p>
            <p>The Companies for which the CRB data has to be transferred (Exported or Imported), have to be specified here. </p>
            <p>The company specified should not be a Consolidation company. </p>
            <p>Since the values specified here are used for both the Export and Import, care must be taken that the CRB data is not Imported into a Processing Company. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>The 9 digit Company code or the 3 digit company mnemonic.     </p>
            <p>Multivalue field associated with field range MNE.MAPPED.TO         to RESERVED1. </p>
            <p>Optional field. If left blank, no Export or Import will         be done.</p>
            <p>Must be a valid Company on the COMPANY file.</p>
            <p>Must be a Processing (non Consolidation) company.</p>
            <p>Company code cannot be duplicated within this field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>A description field to store the details of the settings used in this record. Since this parameter file can be used to activate the export of CRB data as well as the import the text entered here can be beneficial for other users.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 to 35 alphanumeric characters. Multivalued to input         Language dependent description.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DT.LAST.IMPORT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field range COMPANY.CODE to RESERVED1 form a related multi value set. </p>
            <p>Standard T24 date field. </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>A maximum of 11 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>This is a NOINPUT, no copy field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The single record in the file must always be named "SYSTEM". </p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Only the value "SYSTEM" is allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

