<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>SY</product>
<table>SY.PRODUCT.VARIANT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p><strong>SY.PRODUCT.VARIANT is used to define the description, categories and advices that are specific to a particular variant of a Structured Product.  For example, an Accumulator product can have several variants like Accumulators with Gearing, Accumulators with Minimum accrual period etc. If a bank wants to send separate advices for each type of Accumulator or wants to differentiate the Profit or Loss from each variant, they can use this SY.PRODUCT.VARIANT table.</strong>
            </p>

            
            <p>This file is not mandatory. If set and linked to the SY product record, system will take the values from this file while processing the product and raising the entries. The ID should be in the format "SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION_VARIANT". The values from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION get defaulted here. The values can be changed as required and then they become specific to this variant of the product. When an SY contract is input, values will be defaulted from the SY.PRODUCT.VARIANT specified.The fields here are replica of fields in the SY.PRODUCT.DEFINTION and it is suggested that Help text of the field in SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION be referred for additional details. </p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
        <p>A textual description of the varaint</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>VALUATION.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
        <p>If valuation of this variant requires some specific method or formula, then a valuation routine can be attached here. This will override the gerneric valuation routine, if any, that is attached to the parent SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. The Valuation routine must have an associated PGM.FILE record. The routine should have two arguments. First incoming arugument to hold SC.POS.ASSET key and the second argument, which is the outgoing argument should be the SC.POS.ASSET record built by the valuation routine.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>SUPPRESS.UNDERLYING</field>
<desc>
        <p>Allowed values are YES and NO. When set to YES the underlyings are not created i.e the underlying are expected to be interfaced from external system. When set to NO the underlyings are not suppressed and is created from SY contract.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FIXING.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The routine attached here will be used to decide the fixing action on the fixing date - whether to exercise or expire.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1"> Valid subroutine should be attached.</p>
            
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MIN.PERIOD.KOUT</field>
<desc>
        <p>The field is relevant only for SY.ACCUDECU product. Allowed values are YES and NO. When set to YES, the contract is knocked out immediately when set to Knockout. When null or NO, the knockout action will take place only on the protected date.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DX.OPTION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>If the underlying DX.TRADE is to be set as an exotic,  the exotic option type is to be defined here. Must be a valid record in DX.OPTION.TYPE.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Input allowed only when DX product is installed.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>RM.PL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">NOINPUT field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RM.SPREAD.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">NOINPUT field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RM.CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">NOINPUT field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>RM.DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">NOINPUT field</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>MTM.REQUIRED</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field indicates whether the mark to market (unrealised PL) entries need to be raised or not. Allowed values to the field are YES and NO.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MTM.DIFFERENCE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Allowed input is REBOOK or ADJUST. When set to REBOOK mark to market value is reversed and rebooked. When set to AJUST the difference between the previous MTM value and current MTM value is posted.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Input allowed only when MTM.REQUIRED is set to YES.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MTM.PL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>The mark to market PL is posted in this category.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">PL category code between 50000 and 59999.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MTM.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>The internal account category to post the other leg of the MTM entry.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A category code between 10000 to 19999.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>MTM.CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Credit transaction code used for raising mark to market entries.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>MTM.DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Debit transaction code used for raising mark to market entries.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DEPOSIT.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>The deposit category to be used while creating the underlying MM.MONEY.MARKET deposit. The category can be changed at individual SY contract level.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Only applicable for products that have an underlying Money market deposit. Category code ranging between 21000 and 21049 is allowed. </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>DEPOSIT.DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Interest day basis to be defaulted in the underlying money market deposit.This can be changed at individual SY contract level.</p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>LOAN.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>The category to be used while creating the underlying  MM.MONEY.MARKET deposit. The category can be changed at individual SY contract level.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Only applicable for contracts which have an underlying Money Market placement. Category code ranging between 21050 and 21099 is allowed.  </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
	
<t>
<field>LOAN.DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
        <p>The interest day basis to be defaulted in the underlying money market loan. This can be changed at individual SY contract level.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Category code ranging between 21050 and 21099 is allowed. </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FEE.PL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
        <p>The fees, if any, gets posted to this PL category.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A category between 50000 and 59999.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FEE.CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Credit transaction code used to raise Fees entries.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>FEE.DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Debit transaction code used to raise Fees entries.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>PREM.REAL.MAT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field indicates if Premium is to be realised only on Maturity. Allowed values are YES and NO. If set to YES, the premium is initially book to an unrealised PL category and on maturity, the premium is moved to a Realised PL Category. If set to NO, then Premium is directly booked to the PREM.PL category.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>


<t>
<field>PREM.PL</field>
<desc>
        <p>The category in which realized premium entries are posted.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A category between 50000 and 59999.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>PREM.CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Credit transaction code used for raising realized premium entries.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>PREM.DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Debit transaction code used for raising realized premium entries.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>UNREAL.PREM.PL</field>
<desc>
        <p>The category in which unrealized premium entries are posted. When PREM.REAL.MAT is set to YES, then the Premium on the SY Contract is first booked to this category. On maturity is moved to relaised category.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Will only allow input if PREM.REAL.MAT is set to YES. A category between 50000 and 59999.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ULPREM.CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Credit transaction code used for raising unrealized premium entries.Will only allow input if PREM.REAL.MAT is set to YES</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ULPREM.DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Debit transaction code used for raising unrealized premium entries.Will only allow input if PREM.REAL.MAT is set to YES</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>UNWIND.CHG.PL </field>
<desc>
        <p>The unwinding charges collected are posted to this category.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A category between 50000 and 59999.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>UNWIND.CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Credit transaction code used for raising unwinding charge entries.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>UNWIND.DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Debit transaction code used for raising unwinding charge entries.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CA.IMPACT</field>
<desc>
        <p>The field indicates whether Corporate action is applicable or not for this SY Variant. Allowed values are YES and NO.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>APPLICABLE.ELEMENT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field can have any field from the underlying contract, which will be affected by a Corporate action. Eg. A field indicating the stike price or lots. </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>ELEMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field indicates whether the field given in APPICABLE.ELEMENT is a price or quantity field. </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CA.RESERVED.02</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">NOINPUT field</p>
            
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>CA.RESERVED.01</field>
<desc>
        <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">NOINPUT field</p>
            
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>NOTIONAL.ENTRIES</field>
<desc>
        <p>Allowed values are YES and NO. When set to YES the Notional entries gets raised for the product.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>NOTIONAL.DIFF</field>
<desc>
        <p>The allowed values are REBOOK and ADJUST. When NOTIONAL.ENTRIES field is set to YES and this is field set to REBOOK the earlier notional entries are reversed and the new notional entry is rebooked. When set to ADJUST, only the difference between the earlier notional and current notional is posted.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EVENT</field>
<desc>
        <p>This should be the one of the events in the SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION of the variant defined.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>COB.PHASE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Different SY.PRODUCTS and variants normally follow common SY.EVENTs like Accrual, Fixing etc.  The common SY.EVENT.DEFINITION record can be set to either run ONLINE or during COB.  However, for certain specific SY Product variants, a particular activity may need to run Online rather than during COB and vice-versa.  This value in this field takes presendence over value in COB phase of SY.EVENT.DEFINITION.  For example,in the SY.EVENT.DEFINITION, fixing event can be set to run during COB on the fixing date.  However, for a particular variant of Accumulators which is based on US Stocks, the price may be available only the day after the fixing date. Hence the Fixing event should not run during the COB on the fixing date but rather the users would prefer to run this Online after receiving the correct price.  In such situations, a variant can be created for Accumulators on US stocks and this field can be set to ONLINE.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>EB.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
        <p>The activity to be triggered for the event mentioned in EVENT field. This takes precendence over the activity defined in SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. This enables different advices to be sent for different variants of the same SY product.</p>
        
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUB.ASSET.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. The contracts of the variant will be valuated using sub asset type defined in this field.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p> It must be a Valid Record of SUB.ASSET.TYPE</p>            
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCL.SUSP.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Accrual of shares can be suspended for an accumulator/decumulator contract due to an corporate action or due to undeclared stock exchange holiday. This field controls the accrual for suspended days. </p>
            <p>This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is not applicable for the following products DCD, DSP, OTCCRAN, OTCGROI.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values - </p>
            <p>'YES' - when the suspension is reset, accrual would be carried out for the suspended days using the latest availlable price. </p>
            <p>'NO'  - accrual would resume from the reset date, units for the suspended days are not recovered. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field determines the accrual basis for equity accumulator/decumulator contracts. This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is not applicable for the following products DCD, DSP, OTCCRAN, OTCGROI.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values - </p>
            <p>'First' - Accrual on value date , no accrual on the final fixing or maturity date. Accrual for interim fixing date added to next fixing. </p>
            <p>'Last' - No accrual on value date, accrual on the final fixing date. Accrual for the interim fixing date added to the current fixing. </p>
            <p>'Both' - Accrual on value date and the final fixing date. Accrual for the interim fixing date added to the current fixing. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.SETT.PL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>The PL category used for cash settlement of accumulator/decumulator contracts. This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values - </p>
            <p>Valid P and L category </p>            
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Credit transaction code to be used for cash settlement. This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
            <p />
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>                Mandatory if CASH.SETT.PL.CATEG is set to 'YES'. </p>      
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CASH.DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Debit transaction code to be used for cash settlement. This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
            <p />
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>                Mandatory if CASH.SETT.PL.CATEG is set to 'YES'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOVATION.PL.CATEG</field>
<desc>
            <p>PL category used for posting novation fees. This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is not applicable for the following products DCD, DSP, OTCCRAN, OTCGROI.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Allowed values - </p>
            <p>Valid P and L category </p>       
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOV.CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Credit transaction code to be used for Novation Fees entries. This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is not applicable for the following products DCD, DSP, OTCCRAN, OTCGROI.</p>
            <p />
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>                Mandatory if NOVATION.PL.CATEG is set to 'YES'. </p>      
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOV.DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Debit transaction code to be used for Novation Fees entries. This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is not applicable for the following products DCD, DSP, OTCCRAN, OTCGROI.</p>
            <p />
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>                Mandatory if NOVATION.PL.CATEG is set to 'YES'. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCL.VANILLA.OPTION</field>
<desc>        
        <p>This field pertains to SY.FX.FORWARDS contracts (Participating forwards/TARKO). This field will be defaulted from SY.PRODUCT.DEFINITION. </p>
        <p />
        <p>Allowed values - </p>
        <p>Buy - indicates that the Participating forwards contract includes a vanilla option component. The fields related to vanilla option is SY.FX.FORWARDS will become mandatory. </p>                   
    </desc>
</t>
<t><field>VARIANT.ID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>EVENT.RESERVED.02</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>EVENT.RESERVED.01</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>PRODUCT.CATEGORY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
