<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.ARR.ACCOUNTING</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The ACCOUNTING component is used by all products which require accounting. Products serviced through AA use activity-based accounting. This component allows for the definition of the allocation rules to use for each action.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>Each Property can have multiple Actions which require accounting. For each of these actions the user must specify the allocation rule (defined in AC.ALLOCATION.RULE) which will be used each time the action is run.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>The allocation rule may be specified at two levels - either at Property Class level or more specifically at property level. If a property level definition is not defined Property class level definition would be used if available. But either of the definition is required otherwise a validation error is raised at proofing level.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a "-"):</p>
                <p>Arrangement Id</p>
                <p>Property name&gt;</p>
                <p>Effective Date</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOOKING.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the current month for the associated property.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 50,000 to 59,999.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOOKING.PM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the previous month for the associated property.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 50,000 to 59,999.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOOKING.PY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the previous year for the associated property.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 50,000 to 59,999.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOOKING.RESERVED.1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHARGEOFF.CATEGORY</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHGOFF.SPECIAL.INCOME</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONSOL.METHOD</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONSOLIDATION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCRUE.AMORT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Flag to indicate if the associated property needs to be accrued or amortised. If flagged as "AMORT" when the associated Property is made-due (either scheduled or ad-hoc) the due amount is amortised using central EB.ACCRUAL processing outside of AA. The associated transaction codes and PL category are required for either Accrual or Amortisation.</p>
                <p>Currently only applicable for "Charge" property class.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Allowed values:</p>
                <p>1. AMORT - Charges will be amortised from the make-due date until the period specified in ACCRUE.PERIOD.</p>
                <p>2. ACCRUE - This Option is allowed only for scheduled CHARGE property.However,If charge property is of type REBATE.UNAMORTIZED then this option is not allowed.If ACCRUE is set for charge property other than scheduled charge then charge amount would be posted to PL directly instead of handover to EB.ACCRUAL for accrual processing.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEF.MVMT.CR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEF.MVMT.DR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEF.MVMT.RE.CR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEF.MVMT.RE.DR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
                <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCRUE.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the period of Amortisation or Accrual for the associated property. Applicable only for "Charge" property class.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Allowed values:</p>
                <p>1. MATURITY - Applicable when the property is flagged to "AMORTISE". Amortisation end date would be the maturity date of the Arrangement.</p>
                <p>2. PERIOD - Any valid period in the format, Pnnn - where P can be "M" - Month, "D" - Days, "Y" - Year or "W" - Week, and nnn - can be any number between 1 to 999. If a period is defined, the end date would be the date calculated as the amortisation start date(usually the make-due date) plus the period specified in calendar days.</p>
                <p>3. SCHEDULE - To perform accrual until next schedule date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INT.ADJUST.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when adjusting accruals for the current month for the associated property.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INT.BOOKING.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the current month for the associated property.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INT.BOOKING.PM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when adjusting accruals for the previous month for the associated property.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INT.BOOKING.PY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when adjusting accruals for the previous year for the associated property.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INT.WAIVING.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when adjusting accruals for the current month for the associated property.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MVMT.CR.TXN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the credit transaction code used in Statement or PL entries for the associated property.</p>
                <p>Currently applicable only for "Charge" amortisation. The transaction code is updated in EB.ACCRUAL when the associated property is to be amortised.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be a valid entry in TRANSACTION table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MVMT.DR.TXN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the debit transaction code used in Statement or PL entries for the associated property.</p>
                <p>Currently applicable only for "Charge" amortisation. The transaction code is updated in EB.ACCRUAL when the associated property is to be amortised.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be a valid entry in TRANSACTION table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MVMT.RE.CR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCRUE.RESERVED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MVMT.RE.DR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
                <p/>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCT.ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the action for which the rule is defined. A Valid action for the property needs to be stated. System would validate the action stated with the list of actions stated in AA.PROPERTY.CLASS to which the property belongs. It is expected that all ACTIONs which have ACCOUNTING stated as YES should find a rule in this table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>1. This field is part of a sub-value set with PROPERTY and ACCT.RULE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.ACC.RESERVED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.ACCR.AMORT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Flag to indicate if the associated property needs to be accrued or amortised. If flagged as "AMORT" when the associated Property class is made-due (either scheduled or ad-hoc) the due amount is amortised using central EB.ACCRUAL processing outside of AA. The associated transaction codes and PL category are required for either Accrual or Amortisation.</p>
                <p>Currently only applicable for "Charge" property class.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Allowed values:</p>
                <p>1. AMORT - Charges will be amortised from the make-due date until the period specified in ACCRUE.PERIOD.</p>
                <p>2. ACCRUE - This Option is allowed only for scheduled CHARGE property.However,If charge property is of type REBATE.UNAMORTIZED then this option is not allowed.If ACCRUE is set for charge property other than scheduled charge then charge amount would be posted to PL directly instead of handover to EB.ACCRUAL for accrual processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.ACCR.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the period of Amortisation or Accrual for the associated property class. Applicable only for "Charge" property class.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Allowed values:</p>
                <p>1. MATURITY - Applicable when the property class is flagged to "AMORTISE". Amortisation end date would be the maturity date of the Arrangement.</p>
                <p>2. PERIOD - Any valid period in the format, Pnnn - where P can be "M" - Month, "D" - Days, "Y" - Year or "W" - Week, and nnn - can be any number between 1 to 999. If a period is defined, the end date would be the date calculated as the amortisation start date(usually the make-due date) plus the period specified in calendar days.</p>
                <p>3. SCHEDULE - To perform accrual until next schedule date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the action for which the rule is defined. A Valid action for the property class needs to be stated if Property level defintion is not defined. System would validate the action stated with the list of actions stated in AA.PROPERTY.CLASS to which the property belongs. It is expected that all ACTIONs which have ACCOUNTING stated as YES should find a rule in this table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  This field is part of a sub-value set with PROPERTY.CLASS and PC.RULE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.ADJUST.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss category code that is credited/debited when adjusting accruals for the current month for the associated property class.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 50,000 to 59,999.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.AMORT.CATEGORY</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.BOOKING.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the current month for the associated property class.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 50,000 to 59,999.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.BOOKING.PM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the previous month for the associated property class.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 50,000 to 59,999.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.BOOKING.PY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the previous year for the associated property class.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 50,000 to 59,999.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCT.RULE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the accounting rule that is associated with the PROPERTY and ACCT.ACTION within the same multi value set.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  This field is part of a sub-value set with PROPERTY and ACCT.ACTION.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>1. Input must be a valid record from AC.ALLOCATION.RULE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.BOOKING.RESERVED.1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.CHARGEOFF.CATEGORY</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.CHGOFF.SPECIAL.INCOME</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.CONSOL.METHOD</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.CONSOLIDATION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.INT.ADJUST.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the current month for the associated property class.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.INT.BOOKING.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the current month for the associated property class.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.INT.BOOKING.PM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the previous month for the associated property class.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.INT.BOOKING.PY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the previous year for the associated property class.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.INT.WAIVING.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss internal category code that is credited/debited when booking accruals for the current month for the associated property class.</p>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 10000 to 19999</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
                <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.MVMT.CR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the credit transaction code used in Statement or PL entries for the associated property class.</p>
                <p>Currently applicable only for "Charge" amortisation. The transaction code is updated in EB.ACCRUAL when the associated property class is to be amortised.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be a valid entry in TRANSACTION table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.MVMT.DR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the debit transaction code used in Statement or PL entries for the associated property class.</p>
                <p>Currently applicable only for "Charge" amortisation. The transaction code is updated in EB.ACCRUAL when the associated property class is to be amortised.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be a valid entry in TRANSACTION table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.MVMT.RE.CR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.MVMT.RE.DR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.RULE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the accounting rule that is associated with the PROPERTY.CLASS and PC.ACTION within the same sub-value set.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AC.ALLOCATION.RULE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.WAIVING.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>Allowed values are</p>
                <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
                <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
                <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
                <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
                <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the Property to which the following accounting rules apply.</p>
                <p>          Note that properties may be specified that are not used by products linked to this condition. This is to allow the accouting property to be inherited by multiple products.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              This field is part of a multi value set with  ACCT.ACTION and ACCT.RULE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>              Input must be a valid record in AA.PROPERTY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the Property class to which the following accounting rules apply. This field is part of a multi value set with PC.ACTION and PC.RULE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record in AA.PROPERTY.CLASS</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJUST.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Profit and Loss category code that is credited/debited when adjusting accruals for the current month for the associated property.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid entry on the CATEGORY table in the range 50,000 to 59,999.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WAIVING.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This holds the charge that is waived and is booked against the PL category specified.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMORT.CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
