<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.ACCRUAL.FREQUENCY</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p> The file AA.ACCRUAL.FREQUENCY allows the user to define the frequency for interest accruals specific to company or for the whole system.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>        User can set default accrual frequency for local currency and foreign currency. It is also possible to override the default frequency for a particular interest property. Accruals for that interest property of the all the products (using this property) will accrue according to the special frequency and rest of the interest properties will accrue according to the default frequency.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>       It is also possible to define different accrual frequency for a given interest property for a given product. The accruals for such an interest property for that particular product will accrue according to the special frequency. Rest of the interest properties for the above product will accrue either according to default frequency or specific frequency if defined.</p>
            <p/>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the specific interest property for which special accrual frequency is to be set. The frequency can be set for either foreign and (or) local currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>  Should be a valid Property of Interest Class</p>
                <p>  Optional Input </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.FCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the special accrual frequency for a particular interest property (set in the field PROPERTY) in foreign currency. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>    Standard date/frequency format. </p>
                <p>    Optional input</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the special accrual frequency for a particular interest property (set in the field PROPERTY) in Local currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>    Standard date/frequency format. </p>
                <p>    Optional input</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.OL.ACCRUAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to specify if the corresponding property is eligible to do online accruals or not</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCRUAL.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the id of the file AA.ACCRUAL.FREQUENCY. The id can be company code or SYSTEM.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.FCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the default accrual frequency for all interest properties in foreign currency for all the products. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>  Standard date/frequency format. </p>
                <p>  Mandatory input</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the default accrual frequency for all interest properties in local currency for all the products</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>  Standard date/frequency format. </p>
                <p>  Mandatory input</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.OL.ACCRUAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to specify if by default system has to project the accruals for all of the properties belonging to all of the products.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRD.PROP.FCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the special accrual frequency for a particular interest property (Property defined for a Product) in foreign currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>  Standard date/frequency format. </p>
                <p>  Optional input</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRD.PROP.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the special accrual frequency for a particular interest property (Property defined for a Product) in local currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>  Standard date/frequency format. </p>
                <p>  Optional input</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROD.PROP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the specific Property under a given Arrangement Product for which special accrual frequency is needed. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>  Should be a valid ID in AA.PROPERTY</p>
                <p>  Optional Input</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROD.PROP.OL.ACCRUAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to specify if the corresponding property that belong to a product is eligible to do online accruals or not</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the specific Arrangement Product for which special accrual frequency is to be set.  Optionally, you can also set the properties under a Product. The frequency can be set for either foreign and (or) local currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>  Should be a valid Arrangement Product (ID in AA.PRODUCT)</p>
                <p>  Optional Input</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
