<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ARR.TERM.AMOUNT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The TERM AMOUNT Property Class is used by all products which involve an amount of money that is lent or deposited for a specified period of time. This property class controls the commitment made by the bank and the customer.</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>UPDATE.COMMT.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether the commitment amount of the Limit used for the arrangement should be updated and shown on the LIMIT record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CANCEL.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Period after which if full committed deposit amount is not paid by the customer, then system shall trigger cancellation of deposits</p>
            <p>Applicable only for DEPOSITS product line</p>
            <p> Standard PERIOD type of field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINAL.TERM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the date the Final Term of the arrangement. This field is updated when a new arrangement based on the Final maturity date or it can be inputed by the User.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This Field will denote the Actual Term of the Loan.It will be used during Loan Renewal.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This Field will determine the end point for contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Term = 5Y</p>
            <p>Final Term = 25Y</p>
            <p>Final Maturity date will be updated as 30 NOV 2025(Based on the Final Term value).The Contract will be renewed every 5Y(Based on the Term) starting from the Arrangement Date.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TERM</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determines the period of time by which the amount must be repaid (either to the bank in the case of a loan or to the customer in the case of a deposit) During product definition it will be common to default the term (e.g. a 30 year mortgage)</p>
            <p />
            <p>                 The term can be entered as a number of:</p>
            <p>                 Days (D), Weeks(W), Months(M) or Years(Y)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ON.MATURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field is currently not in use and has no functional impact</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for Arrangement Conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALC.MAT.ON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field. </p>
            <p>This Field can be used to specify for which activities the maturity date should be recalculated. This should be a valid AA.ACTIVITY record ID. The activities that can be specified in this field are currently restricted to :</p>
            <p> Renegotiate Arrangement</p>
            <p>  Rollover Arrangement</p>
            <p>  Change Product Arrangement</p>
            <p>  Reset Product Arrangement</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Effective Date of this property condition</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FINAL.MAT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This Field denotes the Final Maturity date of the arrangement. This field is updated while creating a new arrangement based on the Final Term which can be amended by the User.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This Field will be used during any Renewal Activity.This Field will denote the end date of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Say for Example,</p>
            <p>Arrangement Date = 30 NOV 2000</p>
            <p>Term = 5Y</p>
            <p>Final Term = 25Y</p>
            <p>Final Maturity date will be updated as 30 NOV 2025(Based on the Final Term value).The Contract will be renewed every 5Y(Based on the Term) starting from the Arrangement Date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will represent the end of availability for the committed loan amount.</p>
            <p>              This field will contain the date on which the committed loan amount will fully be repaid based on TERM and arrangement start date.</p>
            <p>              This field will be no input field at designer level. When a new arrangement is input maturity date will be calculated for the TERM from arrangement start date and will be defaulted.</p>
            <p>              Maturity date can be changed at the arrangement level. If maturity date is changed then TERM will be calculated in DAYS format.</p>
            <p>              If TERM and maturity date is present and TERM is changed then an internal maturity date will be calculated. If this date is not equal to the existing maturity date then TERM will be recalculated and updated in DAYS format.</p>
            <p>              If TERM is changed and maturity date has to be recalculated then existing maturity date should be cleared.</p>
            <p />
            <p>              Example :</p>
            <p>              Term                                  :  24M </p>
            <p>              Arrangement Start date    :  01st January 2007 </p>
            <p>              Maturity date                     :  01st January 2009 </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>              Standard Date format</p>
            <p>              No input field at designer level</p>
            <p>              Maturity date, if input,  should be greater than today and should be greater than effective date.</p>
            <p>        Call contracts without Maturity date are supported </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REVOLVING</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the revolving term amounts for lending products. The effect of a revolving product is to increase the available amount from which a customer may drawdown as a result of certain payments. The options are:</p>
            <p>                 NO - the available amount will not increase when any payments are made.</p>
            <p>                 PAYMENT - any payment against the outstanding amount(due or not due) will result in the available amount increasing </p>
            <p>                 PREPAYMENT - only repayments agains the outstanding amount (balance not yet due) will result in the available amount increasing</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the name of the property that this arrangement level condition relates to</p>
            <p>Name is defined in AA.PRORERTY table</p>
            <p>System maintained field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>      The original commitment amout can be increased or decreased using INCREASE or DECREASE action. This field represent the amount to increase or decrease on the original amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     For increase action, the input in this field should be greater than zero.</p>
            <p>     For decrease action the input in this field should be less than zero.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Standard T24 amount field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the key to the accounting entries raised by the activity being applied to this arrangement property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the total amount which will be lent or deposited for the term (i.e. the committed amount).</p>
            <p />
            <p>               In English Language text it is possible to use 'T' to indicate the thousands and an 'M' to indicate the millions. </p>
            <p>               e.g. INPUT VALUE</p>
            <p>               1T 1,000.00 </p>
            <p>               2M 2,000,000.00</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>               1-14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a "-"):</p>
            <p>Arrangement Id</p>
            <p>Property name&gt;</p>
            <p>Effective Date</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COOLING.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Determine the period of time during which the amount can be redeemed without making due any accrued interest in the case of pre-closure of an arrangement.  In the case of interest already made due, redeem arrangement activity during cooling period will only stop paying the accrued interest and due interest paid will not be reversed back. </p>
            <p>The Period can be entered as a number of: Days(D), Weeks(W), Months(M) and Years(Y). </p>
            <p>This field is an optional field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
            <field>FULL.COMMITTMENT.ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field when set as YES trigger an activity(given below) when the loan /deposit is fully disbursed / funded. </p>
                <p>•	LENDING-FULL.DISBURSE-ARRANGEMENT</p>
                <p>•	DEPOSITS-FULL.FUND-ARRANGEMENT</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
</menu>
</t24help>

