<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ACCOUNT.MOVEMENT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a system maintained file to store the movement of accounting entries when the activity which triggered it has not been authorised. When the activity is authorised, this file gets deleted since movements can now be retrieved from ACCT.ACTIVITY.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NAU.DR.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a debit accounting entry is generated, this field would be updated. This field is signed.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total net forward movement which includes both Credit and Debit entries.Updated only for Forward dated entries and is signed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The forward value date for which movements are raised. When multiple movements are raised on the same balance, then this field would be sub-valued to store multiple date movements.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAU.CR.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a credit accounting entry is generated, this field would be updated. This field is signed.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAU.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The total net movement which includes both Credit and Debit entries.This field is signed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAU.VALUE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The value date for which movements are raised. When multiple movements are raised on the same balance, then this field would be sub-valued to store multiple date movements.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Account reference for which movements are stored. An Arrangement reference could also be used to view the record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid ACCOUNT identifier.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARR.ACTIVITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Arrangement activity reference which generated the above movement. When both primary and Secondary activities raise balance movement entries, both the references would be stored in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY reference.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>AA Account may have multiple balances associated with it and movements occur between balances. This field stores the actual balance on which movements are raised. This is a multi-value field to store multiple balances. With Soft accounting rules(AC.ALLOCATION.RULE), additional entries may also be raised. All movements are recorded against their respective balance.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Multi-valued field.</p>
            <p>Should be a Valid AC.BALANCE.TYPE identifier.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.CR.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a forward dated credit accounting entry is generated, this field would be updated. Updated only for Forward dated entries and is signed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.DR.MOVEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a forward dated debit accounting entry is generated, this field would be updated. Updated only for Forward dated entries and is signed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>ACT.BAL.TYPE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACT.NAU.MVMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACT.NAU.CR.MVMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACT.NAU.DR.MVMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACT.FWD.MVMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACT.FWD.CR.MVMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACT.FWD.DR.MVMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
