<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.ARR.BALANCE.AVAILABILITY</table>
    </header>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NOTICE.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Specifies the maximum amount which can be withdrawn without notification being required.</p>
                <p>The maximum local currency amount that can be withdrawn in a single transaction without incurring an override message. If this value is exceeded then the override message:</p>
                <p>ACCOUNT &amp; - NOTICE CONDS FOR WITHDRAWAL NOT MET</p>
                <p>will be displayed.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>19 numeric characters"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NOTICE.AVAILABILITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The period for which the funds will be available once notice has been given. This field defines the number of days, months or working days for which funds subject to notice conditions will be available. e.g.  if three months notice is given for withdrawal then the bank can stipulate that the funds will only be available for two weeks after which a further three months notice must be given.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>2-3 alphanumeric characters in the format:     nnD, nnM or nnW.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NOTICE.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the notice, in days or months, which must be given before the amount, specified in NOTICE.AMOUNT can be withdrawn.</p>
                <p>The number of days, months or working days which constitute the period. e.g. 20D, 7W, 3M, etc.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters - nnD, nnM or nnW format.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
                <p/>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will hold two values either DUE or CAPITALISE.This Field denote which application method(DUE or CAPITALISE)should be taken while applying periodic rule charges.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will have to accept a valid T24 period.This Field will denote the application period for current aplication method.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
                <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AVAIL.BAL.UPD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the options available for building the available balance on an account. The unauthorised movement fields will be updated but may not necessarily be used for balance checking. This is to enable a new type of balance check to be made if the parameter settings are changed.It can be set at Arrangement level (AA.ARR.BALANCE.AVAILABILITY) or at the Product Level (AA.PRD.DES.BALANCE.AVAILABILITY) or ACCOUNT.PARAMETER level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Unauthorised debits or Unauthorised credits , or both or none of them</p>
                <p>It will be selected in the following order:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>1. Arrangement (AA.ARR.BALANCE.AVAILABILITY)</p>
                <p>2. ACCOUNT.PARAMETER, if not set at Arrangement level</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>BOTH - Unauthorised debits and credits to be included in the available balance</p>
                <p>NONE - No unauthorised movements to be included in the available balance</p>
                <p>DEBITS - Only unauthorised debits to make up available balance</p>
                <p>CREDITS - Only unauthorised credits to make up available balance</p>
                <p>The default will be No authorised movements to be included in the available balance</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CREDIT.CHECK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies on which balance, overdraft and limit checking should be made. It can be set at Arrangement level (AA.ARR.BALANCE.AVAILABILITY) or at the Product Level (AA.PRD.DES.BALANCE.AVAILABILITY) or ACCOUNT.PARAMETER level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The flag will be selected in the following order:</p>
                <p>1. Arrangement</p>
                <p>2. ACCOUNT.PARAMETER, if not set at Arrangement level</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p>AVAILABLE:</p>
                <p>Credit checking is made using AVAILABLE.BAL</p>
                <p/>
                <p>WORKING:</p>
                <p>Credit checking is made using WORKING.BALANCE</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FORWARD:</p>
                <p>Credit checking is made using WORKING.BALANCE plus today's forward movements.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>AVAILWORK:</p>
                <p>Credit checking is made using AVAILABLE.BAL and WORKING.BALANCE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>AVAILFWD:</p>
                <p>Credit checking is made using AVAILABLE.BAL and WORKING.BALANCE plus today's forward movements.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>BLANK: The default checking is against WORKING.BALANCE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
