<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ACTIVITY.BALANCES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>AA.ACTIVITY.BALANCES is an intermediate temporary file used to store balance details of all non bill related balance types. This is a live file and updates to this would be controlled by the system as and when accounting updations are needed for non bill related balances.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>BILL.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the Bill reference associated with the activity.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.UPDATE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Stores the date time stamp as to when this file was last updated</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the Currency of the Arrangement contract</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPERTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The property to which the amount has been split. This also contains the actual balance type which was affected by this activity(PROPERTY.BALANCETYPE format). When a single activity settles multiple properties or multiple balances of the same property, this field would be sub-valued to store all details. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores to the Activity Date associated with the activity</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the activity name which has updated a record in this file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the unique arrangement activity ID assocaited with the activity.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the arrangement ID, which is the ID for this file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPERTY.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual amount that was settled for the property and the balance stated in the previous field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>DELIN.REPAY.REF</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DELIN.REPAY.AMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>DELIN.TOT.AMT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
