<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ARR.CHANGE.PRODUCT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The CHANGE.PRODUCT Property Class is used by all products which allow for a change of product during their lifecycle. When a new product is applied onto the existing arrangement, the user would lose all his negotiations done as part of the old product. This table allows a list of products to which the old product can change and also define time-scales as to when the event would happen. </p>
            <p />
            <p>         There are some property classes which do not apply onto the arrangement when the change product happens. Currently these are : TERM.AMOUNT, CUSTOMER, ACCOUNT and LIMIT classes. The properties of these classes would continue with their running conditions and would not be affected by change product event.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BUS.DAY.CENTRE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates those countries whose calendars must be checked with regard to holiday validation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>          The default value at the arrangement will be the Country of the currency of the arrangement but the User can input any number of extra codes if required.</p>
            <p />
            <p>          (1) 4 type A (alphanumeric) characters. (Optional input.  Multivalue field.)</p>
            <p>           (2) The code must have a valid entry on the REGION/HOLIDAY table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for Arrangement Conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGE.DATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional fied. Allowed values are - PERIOD, MATURITY</p>
            <p> PERIOD – Product change for the arrangement would take place on the given period. Input in field CHANGE.PERIOD becomes mandatory</p>
            <p> MATURITY – Product would be renewed on Maturity date as defined in TERM.AMOUNT property of the arrangment.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INITIATION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Mandatory Field.</p>
            <p />
            <p> This Field will determine whether the Renewal Activity will triggered Automatically or it will be triggered by the User Manually.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Options - AUTO,MANUAL</p>
            <p />
            <p> AUTO - Any Renewal Activity will be triggered Automatically.</p>
            <p />
            <p> MANUAL - User having the option to trigger the any Renewal Activity Manually. If the User was not triggered the any Renewal Activity within specific days then the system automatically trigger default Activity from DEFAULT.ACTIVITY field. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGE.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The user can define a Product for the arrangement to change to after a period of time (e.g. 6 months) or on a specific date. A period (say 6M, 12M) may be stated in this field. The arrangement start date would be considered as the base date for computing the period. For subsequent</p>
            <p>   change product events, the last change product date is considered as base date and not the arrangement start date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       Validation rule:</p>
            <p />
            <p>       Valid PERIOD field.</p>
            <p>       Maximum of 4 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Effective Date of this property condition</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the date on which the arrangement would change from a existing product to a new product.</p>
            <p>Both date and period are not allowed together. System would ignore the DATE.CONVENTION stated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       Validation rule:</p>
            <p />
            <p>          Must be a valid Date.</p>
            <p>          Maximum of 11 Alphanumeric characters allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.TO.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The product to which the arrangement must switch to on this date or period. The product must be one in the allowed list of products. It should belong to the same group as that of the arrangement product. </p>
            <p />
            <p>       Validation rules:</p>
            <p>       Must be a valid entry in AA.PRODUCT</p>
            <p>       Maximum of 30 Alphanumeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.CONVENTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>During the automatic generation of Change product date, the Date Convention and Business day center settings indicate the action which will be taken if the derived date is a non-working day. There are four Date Convention options:</p>
            <p />
            <p>        • Backward – the change product date will move backward to the previous working day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        • Forward – the change product date will move forward to the next working day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        • Forward Same Month – the change product date will move forward to the next working day provided it is within the same month. If it is not within the same month, it will move backward to the previous working day.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        • Calendar – the change product date will not move even if it is a non-working day.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Input allowed are BACKWARD, FORWARD, FORWARD SAME MONTH or CALENDAR.</p>
            <p>        If nothing is specified at the arrangement, CALENDAR would be defaulted</p>
            <p>        Would be ignored if a specific date is stated in CHANGE.DATE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>This Field will determine the defalut Activity which will be triggered INITIATION.TYPE is equal to MANUAL.</p>
            <p>This Field would become mandatory if INITIATION.TYPE is MANUAL.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This Field which can accept a valid AA.ACTIVITY. </p>
            <p>Currently it can accept only ROLLOVER Activity.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOWED.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The list of products to which the arrangement product can switch to. All the products should belong to the same product group. From a designer perspective, this condition may not also be attached to a product which belongs to a different product group.If this field is left</p>
            <p>   blank, the arrangement product is allowed to switch to all products of the same group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       Validation rule:</p>
            <p />
            <p>          Should be a valid product in AA.PRODUCT table.</p>
            <p>          Maximum of 30 Alpha numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a "-"):</p>
            <p>Arrangement Id</p>
            <p>Property name&gt;</p>
            <p>Effective Date</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the name of the property that this arrangement level condition relates to</p>
            <p>Name is defined in AA.PRORERTY table</p>
            <p>System maintained field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRIOR.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a period or date is stated, the change product event happens on that day. But a value may be stated in this field which would run the event 'n' days prior to the change product so that the user can negotiate the terms on the new product. </p>
            <p />
            <p>        For example, if a change product event is scheduled to run on 01-May and prior days is stated as 5, then the change product event 'runs' on 26-April 'effective' 01-May. When no prior day is stated, then the system 'runs' and 'effects' the product change on 01-May.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Numeric field indicating days.</p>
            <p>        Maximum of 3 characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGE.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>  This Field will determine which Activity will be trigger during Loan Renewal.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory if RENEWAL.DATE is used. Options:</p>
            <p> ROLLOVER</p>
            <p> RESET</p>
            <p> CHANGE.PRODUCT</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the key to the accounting entries raised by the activity being applied to this arrangement property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

