<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ARR.ACTIVITY.PRESENTATION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Activity Presentations class is used for defining various versions to be used for different Property Classes / Properties / Activities during an arrangement entry. The main idea is to display various versions / screen while inputting an arrangement through browser for different Properties of the product.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CLASS.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Version name to be used for a given PROPERTY.CLASS. This field can be multi valued along with the PROPERTY.CLASS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 54 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid VERSION ID. The version name entered should match the PROPERTY.CLASS defined above, that is, if for example, INTEREST is the Property Class defined, then the version should be a INTEREST class routine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPERTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Property under which a version screen to be used. This field can be multi valued to give various version names for different Properties.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 30 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid AA.PROPERTY ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Property.Class under which a version screen to be used. The field can be multi valued to give various version names for different Property classes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 30 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid AA.PROPERTY.CLASS ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.SIM.VER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the Version name to be used for a given PROPERTY ID during SIMULATION. This field can be multi valued along with the PROPERTY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 54 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid VERSION ID. The version name entered should match the CLASS of the Property defined above, that is, if for example, INTEREST is the Property class for a Property, then the version should be a INTEREST class routine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SUPPRESS.SEE.MODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>If the user wants to view only the property and its fields relevant to his activity that he is inputting and suppress all other properties that open up in  SEE mode (non-editable), The user has to set this field to "YES". Default option for this field is NULL. If the field is set to NULL, All properties along with its field values would be shown during input of an activity.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the key to the accounting entries raised by the activity being applied to this arrangement property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for Arrangement Conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CLASS.SIM.VER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the Version name to be used for a given PROPERTY.CLASS during SIMULATION. This field can be multi valued along with the PROPERTY.CLASS.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 54 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid VERSION ID. The version name entered should match the PROPERTY.CLASS defined above, that is, if for example, INTEREST is the Property Class defined, then the version should be a INTEREST class routine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the name of the property that this arrangement level condition relates to</p>
            <p>Name is defined in AA.PRORERTY table</p>
            <p>System maintained field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.PROPERTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Property ID under an ACTIVITY. For a given Activity we can define several Properties under it and the corresponding version routine name, which will be used during Arrangement entry.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 30 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid AA.PROPERTY ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.SIM.VER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the Version name to be used for a given ACTIVITY and PROPERTY IDs during SIMULATION. More than one combination of Property and Version can defined under a given Activity in a Muti value set.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 54 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid VERSION ID. The version name entered should match the CLASS of the Property defined above, that is, if for example, INTEREST is the Property class for a Property, then the version should be a INTEREST class routine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Version name to be used for a given ACTIVITY and PROPERTY IDs. More than one combination of Property and Version can defined under a given Activity in a Muti value set.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 54 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid VERSION ID. The version name entered should match the CLASS of the Property defined above, that is, if for example, INTEREST is the Property class for a Property, then the version should be a INTEREST class routine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the Activity ID. Under a given Activity ID, there can be multiple set of Properties and Version names attached, however, Property should be unique.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 55 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid AA.ACTIVITY ID. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a "-"):</p>
            <p>Arrangement Id</p>
            <p>Property name&gt;</p>
            <p>Effective Date</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROP.VERSION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Version name to be used for a given PROPERTY ID. This field can be multi valued along with the PROPERTY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 54 type A (alphanumeric) characters. Must be a valid VERSION ID. The version name entered should match the CLASS of the Property defined above, that is, if for example, INTEREST is the Property class for a Property, then the version should be a INTEREST class routine.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Effective Date of this property condition</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

