<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ARR.AZ.LOAN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p> This property class represents the LOAN product for the module AZ in T24. This property class is used for classic products.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWDOWN.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines a type of drawdown for this product, which specifies the method of withdrawing the Principal amount, from the loan accounts of this product.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The various types of drawdowns are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1. Full Drawdown:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The entire loan amount has to be withdrawn at a time. No partial withdrawals are allowed</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  2. Partial and No interest:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Partial or full withdrawal of the loan amount is permitted from the loan account. Interest and Principal repayment need not be done during the drawdown period.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  3. Partial and interest:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The drawdown of loan amount can be done in partial or in full. During the drawdown period repayment towards interest has to be made. Otherwise it will be treated as arrears.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If a nominated account is defined, in all the options, the system will automatically transfer the drawdown amount on the drawdown date to the nominated account. If no nominated account is defined and if the drawdown is preferred through the AZ account itself, then a teller default will be created and the amount can be drawn through teller using the teller default feature.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Valid for Loan products only.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid numbers are 1,2,3.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Default is 1 (Full Drawdown)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be 1 for CREDIT CARD type of loans.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ONLY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define whether 'interest only repayment' is allowed for this product or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If Y (Yes) is defined, accounts opened under this product shall be able to have Interest Only repayment facility</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If N (No) is defined, accounts of this product shall not be able to have the Interest Only repayment facility.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  For loan accounts with repayment type 'Non Redemption', no validation will be done with respect to this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The permitted values are 'Y' or 'N'</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid only for Loan products</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Default is 'N'</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GRACE.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the period in number of days, until the expiry of which the loan accounts under this product, shall not be considered to be in arrears.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If the account continues to be in arrears status, even after the expiry of the grace period, penalty interest will be applied on the arrears, as per penalty parameters defined.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Optional field</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-999 numeric</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cannot have negative values.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REDUCE.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to provide a revolving limit functionlity in loan products.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If defined as '' then on the scheduled dates the limit is reduced for P and A schedules and incase of N schedules where there is no interest liquadation account, which provides a non-revolving functionlity.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If defined as 'NO' then on the scheduled dates the limit is not reduced which provides a revolving limit functionlity. In this case the PRINCIPAL in AZ.ACCOUNT is not reduced on schedule dates or when the principal is repaid.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Not allowed for deposits and CREDIT CARD.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  'NO' not allowed for ANNUITY type of loans.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If set to 'NO' then value in DRAWDOWN field cannot be set to 1, i.e., full drawdown.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed values are 'NO' or ''.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the maturity instruction for the deposit accounts opened under this product.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'Automatic Rollover' is specified the deposit will be rolled over with the same terms as that of the original deposit.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'Payment to Nominated Account' is defined here, on date of maturity the maturity amount will be credited to the nominated account specified in the deposit account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Partial Rollovers and rollover with additional amount are handled at account level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Permitted values : 'Automatic Rollover' / 'Payment to Nominated Account'</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed only for FIXED type deposits.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TERM.PRIORITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the Term of the loan has to be prioritised and kept constant or not, in the case of Re scheduling.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In AZ Loan accounts, the term of the loan or repayment amount may change due to certain factors like Principal increase, Principal decrease, change in Rate of interest, change in frequency etc. In such cases, it is possible to retain the original term and the maturity date as constant and change the repayment amount suitably, by specifying the Term Priority as 'Y'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If Term Priority is specified as 'N', then by keeping the repayment amount as constant the term will be changed by altering the maturity date of the loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field has to be opted by the user whenever a Rescheduling of the loan account is to be done. According to the value defined here, Rescheduling will be done and the previous schedule will be written to AZ.SCHEDULES.HIST.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In case of annuity type of loans if the user defined annuity amount is greater than the system generated amount then the contract will be matured earlier than the actual maturity date even though this field is set to 'Y'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In case of OTHERS/NONRED type of loans, TERM.PRIORITY 'N' is not applicable as they may have uneven payments. Hence if AZ contract is of OTHERS/NONRED type of loans, then system shall ignore the value in this field and work as if TERM.PRIORITY is 'Y'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Valid value 'Y' or 'N'</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Repayment type of the All in One Accounts opened under this product. This type determines the way in which the loan / deposit account is to be repaid.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The repayment types available for loan accounts are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1. ANNUITY</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This type of loan has a fixed periodic repayment amount (the 'annuity') consisting of two variable components of principal and interest. The repayment amount is calculated at the start of the contract so that the principal will be fully repaid after the required number of repayments. Initially, repayments consist mostly of interest. However, as the contract progresses, the size of the principal component increases as the accrued interest reduces.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In All in One loan account, for defining a zero repayment at the start of the loan, for a fixed period, Annuity type of repayment can be defined in the schedule with amount as Zero.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  2. LINEAR</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Linear loans also have an interest and a principal component to their periodic repayments. In this case, however, the principal repayment amount remains fixed over the lifetime of the contract. The interest element reduces as the accrued interest on the reducing balance decreases. This leads to a repayment scheme whereby the total periodic repayment reduces over the lifetime of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  3. NONRED</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In NONRED type of loans, there is no regular repayment of principal, but only interest. The redemption of Principal will be done on maturity date of the loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In All in One account loans, the validations relating to Interest Only and Maximum Period interest only will not happen for this type of loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  4. OTHER</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Non structured repayments are handled under this type. Repayment of any amount on any dates are allowed, provided the total repayment amount is equal to principal.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  5.CREDIT CARD</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This type of Loan repayment type was added from G14.0.00. For this repayment type, the schedules are NO. When the repayment type is Credit Card the regular schedules are discarded, sub a/cs are created and new types of schedules like CI, CC are generated automatically.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Repayment types available for Deposit accounts are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  FIXED</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Deposit amount is accepted in a fixed lump sum and repaid as fixed amount either with interest accumulated or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  SAVING PLAN</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Deposit amount is accepted in a periodic basis and the principal is increased in a recurring manner till the end of a fixed term.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1 to 12 Alpha characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input must be either 'ANNUITY', 'LINEAR', 'OTHERS', 'NONRED' or 'CREDIT CARD' for loan products and 'SAVINGS PLAN' or 'FIXED' for Deposit products.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Once defined and record authorised cannot be changed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAN.INT.ADJUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to decide whether interest adjustment is allowed or not in an ANNUITY or CREDIT-CARD type AZ loan account. Interest adjustment is a functionality by which interest payment could be lesser than the accrued interest amount and the remaining amount would be debited from suspense account of class AZINTADJ. The suspense account would be settled during the subsequent repayments. Interest adjustment is allowed only if this field is set to YES.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Validation rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Holds YES or NO</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Input allowed only if ACCT.SYNC field is set to YES.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PD.LINK.TO.AZ</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be input as either 'YES' or 'NO' or ''.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If this field is YES-an, attempt to repay an amount, less than the amount raised by way of schedules after repay date will create, PD. In this case APPLY.PENALTY must be set to 'N'.If PD is not installed, then the funds will be automatically debited from repay account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If this field is NO then, the amount still payable will continue to remain in the account (i.e., the principal will not be reduced) and AZ.OVERDUES will be updated. Allowed only if ACCT.SYNC is set to 'YES'. Not allowed for CREDIT CARD type of loan products.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If this field is '' then, FT on hold will be created for the insufficient funds.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  YES or NO or ''. Value in this field should be same as that of ACCT.SYNC for loans</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Once input the values cannot be changed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Partial payment will raise PD only if repay date is past for credit cards.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the name of the property that this arrangement level condition relates to</p>
            <p>Name is defined in AA.PRORERTY table</p>
            <p>System maintained field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESCHED.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the notice period in days for the corresponding reschedule type, for all the AZ accounts opened under this product.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For a particular type of reschedule, the reschedule notice will be linked and the reschedule event will happen after the expiry of reschedule notice.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The valid types of reschedules are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1. Rate Change 2. Lump sum Repayment 3. Redraw 4. Term Change 5. Frequency Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Note: At present, only Rate Change is supported. If the BASIC.INTEREST is changed today or for a forward date after the contract is input then this change is applied to the az.account after the number of days defined in this field. The BI change is processed during COB.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Multi value field associated with Reschedule Type</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input allowed only if reschedule Type is defined</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-99 numeric character with period D, M or Y (Example: 15D, 01M)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Not applicable for credit card loans</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IRA.PROCESS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a switch for activating the IRA processing in AZ.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.CLOSURE.FEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the charges to be levied for pre-closure of the deposit / loan account or part withdrawal of deposit.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  These charges will be debited only if the pre-closure of the deposit / loan is done by using AZ.ACCOUNT. The withdrawals made through other channels like Teller or ATM, the system will not recognise the differential interest and the charges. In these cases, the pre-closure fee and differential fee are to be debited manually.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Should be a valid charge code defined under FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.INSTL.INT.ONLY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Total period of time that the interest only repayment could be defined for a loan during the life time of a loan account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If input is given in numbers it is treated as number of days.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If input is given prefixing P, it is treated as number of installments.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If input is given as 60, it implies that the total number of Interest Only repayment period cannot exceed 60 days during the life of the loan account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If input is given as P60, it implies that the total number Interest only repayment period cannot exceed 60 installments (of any frequency like daily, monthly) during the life of the loan account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Note: For loan accounts with repayment type 'Non Redemption', no validation will be done with respect to this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Value for this field will be accepted only if 'INT ONLY' field is defined as Y</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid only for Loan Product</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cannot have negative values</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the key to the accounting entries raised by the activity being applied to this arrangement property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SINGLE.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the value that should be set in the SINGLE.LIMIT field in the ACCOUNT that is attached to this APP.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Input can be 'Y', 'N' or ''.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If input as 'Y' then the acct that is attached to the product parameter should also have the field single limit marked as yes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If input as 'N' or '' then the acct that is attached to the product parameter cannot have the field single limit marked as 'Y'. In this case all the AZ.ACCOUNT that are linked to the same limit must have REDUCE.LIMIT set to be the same.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input can be either 'Y', 'N' or ''.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESCHED.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the types of reschedules for all the AZ accounts opened under this product, for the purpose of linking it with the notice of reschedule.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For a particular type of reschedule, the reschedule notice will be linked and the reschedule event will happen after the expiry of reschedule notice.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The valid types of reschedules are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1. Rate Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  2. Lump sum Repayment</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  3. Redraw</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  4. Term Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  5. Frequency Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Note: At present only Rate Change is supported.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Multi value field associated with Reschedule Notice</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ANNUITY.ADJUST</field>
<desc>
            <p>In case of ANNUITY type of loans, this field indicates if the annuity amount can be lesser than the interest amount for the period.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'YES' is defined, then system allows user to define ANNUITY Amount lesser than the interest amount .</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'NO' is defined, then system validates that the ANNUITY amount should be atleast interest.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Valid options are 'YES', 'NO'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Default is 'NO'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a "-"):</p>
            <p>Arrangement Id</p>
            <p>Property name&gt;</p>
            <p>Effective Date</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECALC.CURR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the changes made to the loan account schedule, on account of re-scheduling, are to be effected from the current repayment date or from the next repayment date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'Y' is defined here the effect of re-scheduling will be given from the current repayment date and if 'N' is specified the effect will be from the next repayment date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field will not be considered for future dated or back dated BI rate changes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed values 'Y' or 'N'</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Not applicable for credit card loans</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for Arrangement Conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROLL.MAT.WRK.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates if the rolled over new maturity date should be a working day or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If the field is Yes, during rollover of loans &amp; deposits, if the new maturity date happens to be on a holiday, then the system shall set the new maturity date to the first working day after the rolled over date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Assume that value date of AZ is 10th Aug 2005 &amp; maturity date is 15th Aug 2005 . Then during rollover, the system shall set Value date as 15th Aug &amp; new maturity date as 20th Aug.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the field is YES &amp; 20th Aug happens to be a holiday &amp; first working day after rollover is 22nd Aug , then new maturity date will be set to 22nd Aug.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If the field is NO, then new maturity date will still be 20th Aug only.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed values - YES,NO.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  NO &amp; null are treated the same.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Effective Date of this property condition</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

