<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ARR.ACTIVITY.CHARGES</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>      The property class ACTIVITY.CHARGES defines the charges that needs to be applied when a activity is triggered on the arrangement. </p>
            <p />
            <p>        Charge can be collected when a activity is triggered on a arrangement, for example charge can be collected when the term amount is increased or decreased (LENDING-INCREASE-TERM.AMOUNT, LENDING-DECREASE-TERM.AMOUNT). The charge defined will correspond to the CHARGE property. These properties and their conditions would be defined in the product designer of an product</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>      This field denotes the activity to be generated for the given charge. The fields SCHED.CHARGE and CHG.ACTIVITY are associated. More than one charge activity can be defined for a charge.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Validation</p>
            <p>     Should be valid activity</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field . Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the name of the property that this arrangement level condition relates to</p>
            <p>Name is defined in AA.PRORERTY table</p>
            <p>System maintained field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will have to accept a valid T24 period.</p>
            <p>This Field will denote the application period for current aplication method.</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.SETTLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field aids in turning off automatic settlement from Unallocated Credit balance (UNC balance). If the field is set as YES and if there is a balance in UNC, then the balance is used to settle the activity charge. The activity to be used for settlement is stated in SETTLE.ACTIVITY field. If the user does not want an automatic settlement from the UNC balance, the field could be set to NULL or could be explicitly stated as NO. If the field is left blank, a repayment from UNC balance is not attempted.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>p&gt;Optional field . Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON.RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING . During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON.RESETTING . During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON.RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will hold two values either DUE or CAPITALISE</p>
            <p>This Field denote which application method(DUE or CAPITALISE)should be taken while applying periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SCHED.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>       This field represents the CHARGE property. The charge property defined here should be defined in the product.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field . Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the key to the accounting entries raised by the activity being applied to this arrangement property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for Arrangement Conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
 <t>
            <field>SYS.ACTIVITY.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>An activity that can attract a charge would be updated. System updated field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Associated application method of the associated commission. System updated field. Updated as </p>
                <p>Due if the associated charge is of Debit nature. </p>
                <p>Pay if the associated charge is of Credit nature.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.AUTO.SETTLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Associated auto settle method of the associated commission charge. System updated field. Always updated as Yes.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Associated charge code used to calculate commission on the associated activity. System updated.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
 <t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will have to accept a valid T24 period.This Field will denote the application period for current aplication Method. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLE.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the repayment activity to be triggered when there is unallocated credit. Triggered as secondary activity of Activity charge make due. <p>Validation Rules:</p> Should be a valid record id in AA.ACTIVITY file.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a "-"):</p>
            <p>Arrangement Id</p>
            <p>Property name&gt;</p>
            <p>Effective Date</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>       This field denotes the activity on which the charge would be applied. Should be valid record id in the file AA.ACTIVITY. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This will hold three values either DUE or CAPITALISE or DEFER.This Field denote which application method(DUE or CAPITALISE or DEFER)should be taken while applying activity charges. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>        This field indicates the charge that would be collected when the corresponding activity is triggered. This field is associated with the ACTIVITY.ID field. The charge defined will correspond to the CHARGE property. These properties and their conditions would be defined in the product designer of an product</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Validation rule</p>
            <p>     Should be a valid AA.PROPERTY belonging to the CHARGE property class</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Effective Date of this property condition</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field . not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed .</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>CHARGE.AUTO.SETTLE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
