<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ACTIVITY.CALC.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The purpose of AA.ACTIVITY.CALC.TYPE is to specify a method by which the base amount for charge calculation will be arrived. This is mainly used for getting the base amount for Activity based charges. </p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allows to specify a description for the Activity calculation type record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Can be any valid alphanumeric characters</p>
            <p>   maximum 35 characters</p>
            <p>   Minimum 3 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field stores the override that was generated when the record was commit. No input, system updated field</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.CALC.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID can be any valid alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Validation rules</p>
            <p>      Should be a valid alphanumeric character </p>
            <p>      maximum 30 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the end day of the month that can be used to restrict the period that HIGHEST and LOWEST calculations are performed. </p>
            <p />
            <p>   For example of the highest balance check only up to the 20th of the month this will contain 20</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This is an optional field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Should be between the range 1 to 31</p>
            <p>   Only allowed if CALCULATION = HIGHEST or LOWEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALC.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Start day of the month that can be used to restrict the period that HIGHEST and LOWEST calculations are performed. </p>
            <p />
            <p>   For example of the highest balance check only applies from 10th of the month this will contain 10.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This is an optional field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Should be between the range 1 to 31</p>
            <p>   Only allowed if CALCULATION = HIGHEST or LOWEST</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCULATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies how the activity value for the calculation should be determined. Values available initially are: </p>
            <p />
            <p>      ROUTINE – calculation is based on the API defined in the ROUTINE field</p>
            <p>      CURRENT – the value of the CURRENT activity</p>
            <p>      TURNOVER – the value of the activities since this charge was last applied</p>
            <p>      COUNT – the number of activities since this charge was last applied</p>
            <p />
            <p>    For future releases the additional values should be available:</p>
            <p />
            <p>      AVERAGE – the average value of the activities in the period should be used</p>
            <p>      HIGHEST – the highest value in the period should be used</p>
            <p>      LOWEST – the lowest value in the period should be used</p>
            <p />
            <p>   This field is mandatory</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Validation rules</p>
            <p>    Should be any one of the valid values defined for the field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Routine to calculate the base value for the calculation. </p>
            <p />
            <p>   Mandatory if the CALCULATION  is set to ROUTINE</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Validation rules</p>
            <p>   Should be a valid entry in EB.API</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>