<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ARR.ACTIVITY.MAPPING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>   The ACTIVITY.MAPPING component provides the link between external applications and arrangement activities when performing a debit or credit to an arrangement account. Customer initiated or scheduled debits and credits on an Arrangement are accomplished through T24 applications such as Funds Transfer, Teller, Clearing, etc. In order for the proper allocation rules to be used, each T24 Transaction must result in a specific Activity which would be triggered through AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY application. This mapping could be done in this component.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for Arrangement Conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANSACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field links AA to the other applications. When an external (non-AA) application raises a debit or credit movement to an arrangement account this needs to be translated to an activity on the arrangement. The transaction code of the underlying entry will be checked here and the associated TXN.ACTIVITY will be used. If the transaction code is not specified the DEFAULT.CR.ACTIVITY or DEFAULT.DB.ACTIVITY will be used based on the sign of the movement.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     This field is part of a multi value set with TXN.ACTIVITY.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Input must be a valid record from TRANSACTION.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.CR.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the default AA Activity to be used for AA credit transactions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid record from AA.ACTIVITY and Activity type should be set to ACCOUNTING.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the name of the property that this arrangement level condition relates to</p>
            <p>Name is defined in AA.PRORERTY table</p>
            <p>System maintained field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the Effective Date of this property condition</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
            <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a "-"):</p>
            <p>Arrangement Id</p>
            <p>Property name&gt;</p>
            <p>Effective Date</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the key to the accounting entries raised by the activity being applied to this arrangement property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.DB.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the default AA Activity to be used for AA debit transactions</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid record from AA.ACTIVITY and Activity type should be set to ACCOUNTING.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input not allowed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the activity that will be performed against an arrangement  when a movement with the associated TRANSACTION code is posted from an external application to an Arrangement Account.</p>
            <p>     This field is part of a multi value set with TRANSACTION.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>     Must be a valid record from AA.ACTIVITY</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The underlying AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS must be defined with an ACTIVITY.TYPE of ACCOUNTING</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

