<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.ACTIVITY.HISTORY.SIM</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p/>
            <p/>
            <p/>
            <p>AA.ACTIVITY.HISTORY.SIM logs full history of the activities processed, in their original sequence during SIMULATION.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>       Each Activity performed on an arrangement is effective dated and stored on this file. T24 stores the sequence of activities, links to any financial transactions (e.g. deposits, withdrawals, disbursements, repayments, etc.), when it was performed, how many times was it performed etc. </p>
            <p/>
            <p> Activities with NOLOG attributes are not recorded in this file</p>
            <p/>
            <p>        These details are held for effective arrangement running under simulation mode.</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>AGENT.EVENT.REF</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AGENT.EVENT.STATUS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARC.DATE.TILL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When system archives the Activity history, it stores the last date upto which system has archived in the ARC.ID key. The archiving process is controlled by the commons used in I_AA.ARCHIVE.COMMON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARC.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When system archives the Activity history, it stores the log of references as to where the system has archives the records. The keys to those references are stored in this field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The arrangement reference on which activities are performed.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rule:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Should be a valid AA.ARRANGEMENT id.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.ID</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONTRACT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When external applications credit/debit an arrangement, the details need are stored onto the Arrangement Activity. The field holds the external transaction ID which initiated this AAA. This could be a valid FT, TT IDs etc.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DD.REF.ID</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The effective date on which the below activities have been performed. This field through INITIATION field indicate a subset which store details as per the date on which activities are triggered. The latest date remains on the top. Picked from the EFFECTIVE.DATE of AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rule:</p>
                <p>       Date field- Maximum of 11 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INITIATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates how the activity was triggered. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>      SCHEDULED - The activity was executed as part of a scheduled COB job.(like MAKEDUE)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      TRANSACTION - The activity was triggered by external transactions(like DISBURSE)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      USER - The activity was triggered manually by the user.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      SECONDARY  - The activity was triggered as a secondary activity from a primary activity.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>      Valid values are SCHEDULED, TRANSACTION, USER, SECONDARY</p>
                <p>      Maximum of 30 characters</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AAA.ID</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LAST.EFF.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field reserved for future development</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LAST.HIST.COUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field reserved for future development</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REF.ACTIVITY.REF</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYSTEM.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the System date when the activity was triggered. For example, the EFFECTIVE.DATE of an AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY can be forward dated or back dated. But this field would always indicate system date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation rules:</p>
                <p>      Date field</p>
                <p>      Maximum of 11 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.ACT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The total amount that has been transacted as part of this activity.  This field is different from ACT.AMT (which holds the amount for a single activity). This field holds a cumulative total of all amounts for this activity irrespective of the date on which such transaction occured.  Holds significance only when the activity deals with external payments. Otherwise would default to 0.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation rules:</p>
                <p>      Amount field (AMT) </p>
                <p>      Maximum of 17 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.ACT.CNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The total number of times that this activity has been performed on this arrangement. This field is different from ACT.CNT (which holds the count for an activity for a date). This field holds a cumulative total of all counts for this activity irrespective of the date on which such transaction occured.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation rules:</p>
                <p>      Numeric field</p>
                <p>      Maximum of 3 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANS.REF</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANSACTION.INITIATION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACT.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the amount that was transacted by the above activity on that effective date. Amounts are always in arrangement currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Maximum of 17 characters</p>
                <p>        Amount field</p>
                <p>        Updated only for transactions dealing with external amount(like repayment, deposits etc)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACT.COUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the number of times this activity was performed on a single date. When an activity (say Repayment) is performed more than once, then the ACTIVITY.ID and ACT.DATE remain the same - but the count alone is incremented. Deletion/reversal would decrement the count accordingly.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>        Numeric field to hold count</p>
                <p>        Maximum of 3 characters.</p>
                <p>        Decrements when the activity is deleted/Reversed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The effective date on which this activity was performed on an arrangement. Subvalued to store same activities performed on multiple dates.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Date field storing the EFFECTIVE.DATE on AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACT.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the current state of the activity.</p>
                <p>        UNAUTH - Activity is currently in Unauthorised state.</p>
                <p>        UNAUTH-REV - The Activity has been reversed and yet to be authorised.</p>
                <p>        UNAUTH-CHG - The activity has undergone a change in its unauthorised state</p>
                <p>        AUTH - The activity has been authorised.</p>
                <p>        AUTH-REV - The activity has been reversed and authorised.</p>
                <p>        DELETE-REV - The activity was reversed and later reversal was deleted.</p>
                <p>        DELETE - The activity has currently been deleted.</p>
                <p>        ADJREVERSE-NAU - The activity has undergone a reversal under &apos;reverse/replay&apos; mechanism. But is yet to be authorised.</p>
                <p>       ADJREPLAY-NAU - The activity was replayed under &apos;reverse/replay&apos; mechanism. But the replay is yet to be authorised.</p>
                <p>       ADJREVERSE-AUT - The activity had undergone a reversal and that reversal has been authorised.</p>
                <p>       ADJREPLAY-AUT - The activity had undergone a replay and the replay has been authorised.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that was performed on this EFFECTIVE.DATE.  This is picked from AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY&apos;s ACTIVITY field. Subvalued to record various activities performed on the same date. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Should be a valid record in AA.ACTIVITY.</p>
                <p>       Maximum of 55 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the amount that was transacted by the above activity on that effective date. Amounts are always in arrangement currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Maximum of 17 characters</p>
                <p>        Amount field</p>
                <p>        Updated only for transaction dealing with external amount(like repayment, deposits etc)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that has been performed on this arrangement.  This is picked from AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY&apos;s ACTIVITY field. The field till TOT.ACT.CNT are part of this activity subset. The subset indicates details with respect to activity.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Should be a valid record in AA.ACTIVITY.</p>
                <p>       Maximum of 55 Alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY reference which triggered the activity on this EFFECTIVE.DATE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Should be a valid AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY id(unauthorised/authorised)</p>
                <p>       Maximum of 40 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
