<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.ACTIVITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>An Activity is a business function which can be triggered by a user, the close of business or by another application like Funds Transfer or Teller. An Activity is  property specific named instances of AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS</p>
            <p>             Arrangement property conditions are created and maintained by performing a number of activities on the arrangement during its lifetime, Activities can be performed on user request or automatically according to a schedule.</p>
            <p />
            <p>                The Activities may be created automatically by the system(while authorising AA.PRODUCT.GROUP) or they may be user defined. The user defined activities must be linked to a system activity. The definition of user activities allows the user to setup different charges for the same system activity or different restriction rules.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the product line for which this activity is valid. This field gets updated from the ID of the current record.  For user activities, this defaults to the product line of the LINKED.ACTIVITY</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>        System maintained (NOINPUT) field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides a detailed description of the AA.ACTIVITY.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Mandatory Field.</p>
            <p>                Up to 50 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPERTY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The fields denotes the property on which this activity could be triggered. This field gets updated from the ID of the current record.  For user activities, this defaults to the property of the LINKED.ACTIVITY</p>
            <p />
            <p>        System maintained(NOINPUT) field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROCESS.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the process that would be carried out in the activity. This field gets updated from the ID of the current record. For user activities, this defaults to the process id of the LINKED.ACTIVITY</p>
            <p />
            <p>      System maintained (NOINPUT) field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RELATED.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used ONLY whilst simulating an Arrangement scenario and is used only for LENDING, DEPOSIT product lines at the moment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>For example, when a NEW arrangement is to be simulated for 2 schedules, the schedules could be run only after the arrangement could be disbursed(either fully or partially). But, disbursement is always transaction driven and may not be captured using a AA.SIMULATION.CAPTURE application. To automatically trigger an activity after the current activity(stated in this ID), this field may be utilised. So, a LENDING-NEW-ARRANGEMENT would have LENDING-DISBURSE-COMMITMENT as its RELATED.ACTIVITY. Similarly, automatic repayments on DUEs may be triggered by using this field. The disbursement and repayments generally assume FULL disbursement and payment which may be altered at the AA.SIMULATION.RUNNER to simulate partial disbursements and payments.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Only an activity belonging to the Activity class stated in  its AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS may be stated (RELATED.ACT.CLASS field). User Activities may also be stated here as long as they belong to the core Activity class.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field has NO relevance on activities triggered on Live arrangement.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validations:</p>
            <p>Should be a valid entry in AA.ACTIVITY file.</p>
            <p>Should belong to the Activity class stated in RELATED.ACT.CLASS field of the AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LINKED.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>All user defined activities must be linked to a core system activity. This field defines system activity to which the given user defined activity is linked. This field cannot be input for system activities.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Validation rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Mandatory for User defined activities</p>
            <p>        Input in this field should be a valid id in AA.ACTIVITY file  </p>
            <p>        Maximum of 55 characters</p>
            <p>        Must link to a System activity</p>
            <p>        The value in this field cannot be changed after authorisation of the record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Overrides, if any, generated by this application is stored here</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ID of activity is alpha numeric. System activities always follows the below format</p>
            <p>          &lt;&lt;AA.PRODUCT.LINE&gt;&gt; :&lt;&lt;Activity Name&gt;&gt;: &lt;&lt;AA.PROPERTY or "ARRANGEMENT"&gt;&gt; </p>
            <p />
            <p>But users can create a derivative of their own and the ID is a free text in those instances.</p>
            <p>        Validation rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Any Alphanumeric character</p>
            <p>        Maximum of 55 characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Enquiry selection field. Used to filter out Activities related to the Product of the Arrangement.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Not available for input.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used for classifying the activities. The list of classification can be defined in the EB.LOOKUP file for AA.ACTIVITY.ATTRIBUTE. This gets the value from AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS table. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Validation rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Non Mandatory field.</p>
            <p> Contents should be defined in EB.LOOKUP of AA.ACTIVITY.ATTRIBUTE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field describes the AA.ACTIVITY and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>                This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the description of the AA.ACTIVITY in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                Mandatory Field.</p>
            <p>                Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ACTIVITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the current activity is a system created or a user defined activity. For system created activity, this would default to YES.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        System maintained(NOINPUT) field</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

