<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.ARRANGEMENT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The AA.ARRANGEMENT file records generic information of the arrangement contract, which is common for all product lines.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>                    An AA.ARRANGEMENT record is created whenever a new arrangement is created using "New Arrangement" activity and remains as long as the contract is closed (or matured based on the product line). When the contract is closed the record is moved to AA.ARRANGEMENT.HIST and the record is deleted.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>                    It records basic information like customer, currency, property and product of the arrangement. It also tracks product changes during the life of the arrangement.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CLOSURE.REASON</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the reason for closing the account</p>
                <p>This field is linked to the virtual table EB.LOOKUP. </p>
                <p>All values must have an existing code in the EB.LOOKUP table with ID as CLOSURE.REASON. </p>
                <p>EB.LOOKUP will be used to provide a general description of the closure code and same will be displayed on screen as an enrichment to the closure reason code.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CO.CODE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the currency of the Arrangement contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               Arrangement contract can be in both local currency or foreign currency. This field is used to specify in which currency the asset/liability is held.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               3 character length, standard currency field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field denotes the customer of the Arrangement. Customer is always the primary owner of the arrangement.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER.ROLE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ELIGIBILITY.REVIEW</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LAST.REVIEW.DATE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINK.ARRANGEMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether this arrangement provides any bundle linkage. The following are the options:</p>
                <p>Imagine Bundle arrangement B1 links M1(a Mortgage) and A1(Savings Accounts) to form a Offset mortgage bundle.</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of B1, this field would hold both M1 and A1 respectively as subvalues in this field</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of M1, this field would hold a value of B1</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of A1, this field would hold a value of B1</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINK.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date from which this arrangement has been included as part of a Bundle. Populated only if the Arrangement is a participant in a bundle and would not be updated for standalone arrangements. When the arrangement is removed from a bundle or added to a bundle, a new multi-value would be created with that effective date</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINK.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether this arrangement provides any bundle linkage. The following are the options:</p>
                <p>Imagine Bundle arrangement B1 links M1(a Mortgage) and A1(Savings Accounts) to form a Offset mortgage bundle.</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of B1, this field would hold the recipient Interest property of M1 and the Donor interest property of A1 respectively as subvalues in this field</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of M1, this field would NOT hold any value</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of A1, this field would NOT hold any value</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AGENT.ARR.ID</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINK.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether this arrangement provides any bundle linkage. The following are the options:</p>
                <p>Imagine Bundle arrangement B1 links M1(a Mortgage) and A1(Savings Accounts) to form a Offset mortgage bundle.</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of B1, this field would hold both RECIPIENT and DONOR with M1 and A1 respectively in LINK.ARRANGEMENT</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of M1, this field would hold a value of BUNDLE with B1 as LINK.ARRANGEMENT</p>
                <p>On AA.ARRANGEMENT record of A1, this field would hold a value of BUNDLE with B1 as LINK.ARRANGEMENT</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.APPL</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field denotes the T24 application linked to the Arrangement contract. It is possible to identify the Arrangement contract by the ID of the linked application.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              Lending (AA.PRODUCT.LINE) products are linked to ACCOUNT application, so for all lending product LINKED.APPL is updated as ACCOUNT.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              Associated with LINKED.APPL.ID</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              Internet.Services (AA.PRODUCT.LINE) products are linked to CUSTOMER application.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.APPL.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the T24 application id linked to the Arrangement contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              Associated with LINKED.APPL</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.BALANCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A user can optionally specifiy one or more Balances being donated by the donor.</p>
                <p>Sub Valued field to allow multiple balance types to be donated.</p>
                <p>Specify the actual Balance type that needs to be taken for compensation.</p>
                <p>If this field is left blank, then it means that donor is not donating any balance.</p>
                <p>This may prove useful when a participant, by just being part of a package, there is a need to suppress their Interest (say, a Penalty Interest) which would otherwise accrue based on unauthorised overdraft balances</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.MAX.OFFSET</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The maximum % of the recipient balance that can be offset by the Donation.</p>
                <p>For ex, in an Offset mortgage, if the Principal is -85,000 and if the Donor balances amount to credit +100,000 then specifying Max Offset as 100% would mean only 85,000 of the credit balances are offset against the Recipient’s debit balance.</p>
                <p>There is no additional benefit for the surplus 15,000 in the Donor Balances 80% in Max Offset would mean only 68,000 (80% of 85,000) of the credit balance can be offset against the recipient’s debit balance In the case of Interest Compensation, this will be set to “” to indicate that there is no “Offset’ percentage but only a consolidation of Donor and Recipient balances to calculate interest on</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Credit/Debit specification at the bundle contradicts with the Source Calc type of the Interest property Sub Value field associated with Donor Balance Type Input is allowed only if Donor Balance Type is input Because the Donor Balance type can have Credit or Debit balances on a given day, there would be a flag to specify which balances of the balance type should be used for Offset</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIG.CONTRACT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>  This field represents the original contract date of the arrangement taken over from the legacy system. This value in this field can less than today but it should not be greater than the effective date or the start date of the arrangement in T24</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation rule</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Standard date format</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PLAN.SELECT.METHOD</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROD.EFF.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the effective date of product change for the arrangement contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Associated with PRODUCT.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Standard date field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field denotes product of the arrangement contract. The characteristics of the arrangement is derived from the Product to which it is linked to.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              An arrangement product and arrangement contract is a series of properties (AA.PROPERTY) relating to different components (AA.PROPERTY.CLASS). Each product has a set of mandatory components and optional components.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              It is possible to change the product of the arrangement during its life-cycle subject to certain restrictions. For each product change this field is updated along with the effective date of change.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AGENT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The agent arrangement linked to the Arrangement</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indentifies the Product Group (AA.PRODUCT.GROUP) of the arrangement contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              It is not possible to change the product group of the arrangement after the contract is authorised (or active).</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.LINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Product Line (AA.PRODUCT.LINE) of the arrangement contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              It is not possible to change the product line of the arrangement after it is active.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the status of the product. Three options are available.</p>
                <p>A) Current - Currently active product for the arrangement.</p>
                <p>B) Processed - Old products for the arrangement carry this status.</p>
                <p>C) Scheduled - A product that is scheduled for future is updated with this status.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field maintains the list of properties linked to the product of the arrangement contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            It is not possible to change the product of the arrangement which does not contain any of the properties linked to the old product.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RELATIONSHIP.ARR</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RELATIONSHIP.DATE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RELATIONSHIP.PLAN</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REWARDS.ARR.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Hold the Rewards’s arrangement ID, based on which rewards have to be calculated. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>START.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the creation or start date of the arrangement contract. Date on which the arrangement or service arrangement becomes active.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Standard date field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VALUE.DATE.BAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The  fields from BALANCE.TYPE to VALUE.DATE.BAL are used for enquiries in AA. The field VALUE.DATE.BAL represents the balance available for the balance type on a given value date for a given property in the arrangement</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARR.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the status of the Arrangement during the life cycle of the contract. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                The status can be standard statuses like, </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                UNAUTH - The arrangement has been input and not Authorised yet.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                AUTH - The arrangement has been Authorised and LIVE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                AUTH-FWD (Forward) - At this stage the Arrangement is not active and will be active on a future date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                CURRENT - The arrangement has begun disbursement. Even if partial disbursement happens, this field would hold the same value.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                MATURED - Arrangement contract has matured and ALL DUES on this arrangement has been cleared.</p>
                <p>                EXPIRED - Arrangement contract has gone past its final payment date. But it still has some dues left unsettled. But no-more disbursement can happen after status has reached MATURED or EXPIRED.</p>
                <p>                REVERSED - The arrangement contract has been reversed.</p>
                <p>                 CANCELLED - Arrangement contract has been Cancelled(Only for Deposits)</p>
                <p>                CLOSE - Arrangement contract has been Closed</p>
                <p>PENDING.CLOSURE - Arrangement contract is ready for closure.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VARIATION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VARIATION.EFF.DATE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique identification number for the arrangement contract. The format of the ID is as follows</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               AAYYDDDXXXXX</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               where: AA - Arrangement Architecture module identifier, YYDDD - Year and date of input in julian date format, XXXXX - is a random string generated by the system. </p>
                <p>          If an arrangement is linked to ACCOUNT, then the account number and the arrangement id can be used inter-changeably.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the role played by the arrangement in a bundle scenario. For example, Imagine Bundle arrangement B1 links M1(a Mortgage) and A1(Savings Accounts) to form a Offset mortgage bundle.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>1. On B1 record, this field would hold BUNDLE -which indicates it is the Bundle arrangement which links the various participants.</p>
                <p>2. On M1, this field would hold RECIPIENT - which indicates this is the recipient arrangement in the bundle</p>
                <p>3. On A1, this field would hold DONOR - which indicates this arrangement donates its balances as part of the bundle.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BALANCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>    The  fields from BALANCE.TYPE to VALUE.DATE.BAL are used for enquiries in AA. The field BALANCE.TYPE represents the balance type for a given property in the arrangement</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BOOK.DATE.BAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p> The  fields from BALANCE.TYPE to VALUE.DATE.BAL are used for enquiries in AA. The field BOOK.DATE.BAL represents the balance available for the balance type on a given booking date for a given property in the arrangement.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANNEL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the network through which the Arrangement contract was requested for input or created.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CLOSURE.NOTES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the additional notes for closing the account.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
