<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.CHARGE.DETAILS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This is a central file used to maintain activity or rule based charge details for an arrangement. This file has two purposes.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>     1. Maintains history of charges applied for an arrangement.</p>
            <p>     2. Gives information needed for the system to raise charge bills.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ARR.ACTIVITY.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the arrangement activity ID of the Activity which raised this charge for the arrangement. This is used as a link for raising charge bills.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARR.CHARGE.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The ID of CHARGE.DETAILS is made up of the Arrangement.ID-Charge.ID. Here Charge.ID is the charge property ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Bill amount to be raised in arrangement currency. This amount is updated when charge is calculated for an activity or when a rule is broken. This will be used to update the bill when it is issued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Bill amount to be raised in local currency. This amount is updated when charge is calculated for an activity or when a rule is broken. This will be used to update the bill in local currency amount when it is issued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the charge bill ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the type of the bill to be raised. This can be either Activity based charges (ACT.CHARGE) or periodic rule based charge (PR.CHARGE).</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the charge amount calculated at tier level</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHARGE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the periodic charge property type. If periodic property evaluation results into a credit then this field would be updated as CREDIT. Otherwise it would be null. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHG.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the charge amount after considering FREE.AMT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHG.CALC.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether the charge is fixed or calculated. It can have either FIXED or CALCULATED</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the arrangement activity ID of the Activity which raised this charge for the arrangement. This is used as a link for raising charge bills.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEF.BILL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Calculated charge amount for the activity charge property. It is associated to ARR.ACTIVITY.ID and BILL.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEF.BILL.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Calculated charge amount in local currency for the activity charge property. It is associated to ARR.ACTIVITY.ID and BILL.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use to hold default charge.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.AMT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For future use to hold default charge in local currency.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FINAL.CHG.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the charge amount after applying MIN.CHG.AMT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FREE.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the amount to be deducted from the calculated charge amount</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MIN.CHG.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the minimum charge for the total charge amount computed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAY.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the bill due date. This will be same as issue date when Due period is null.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the base balance used for charge calculation</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJ.AMT.TOTAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the total of adjusted amounts and this is an associated sub-value set of BILL.ID</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the balance applied to tier calculation</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.CALC.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the charge amount calculated at tier level after considering the minium and maximum definition</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.CALC.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the Rate/Amount/Units used for the calculation</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.MAX.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the maximum charge amount applicable for the tier</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.MIN.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defined the minimum charge amount applicable for the tier</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.TIER.CALC.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the sum of tier charge amount</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WAIVE.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge waive amount (for future use)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WAIVE.AMOUNT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge waive amount  in local currency (for future use)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WAIVE.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the waived amount</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WAIVE.REASON</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the reason for waiving the charge.</p>
                <p> This is an associated sub-value set for BILL.ID set of attributes.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJ.AMT.TOTAL.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Local currency equivalent of total adjusted amounts and this is an associated sub-value set of BILL.ID</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJUST.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the adjusted charge amount as part of Charge Override Routine attached in the charge condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Charge adjustment may happen in either way INCREASE/DECREASE from the actual system calculated/Fixed charge amount.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJUST.REASON</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will hold the text message if anything returned from the charge adjustment routine(Local routine) as part of the adjustment process.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> Bill amount in arrangement currency.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMOUNT.LCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Bill amount in local currency.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denote which application method should be taken while applying charges.The allowed values are DUE or CAPITALISE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifes the period for the charge bill to be made due or capitalise. Period can be in days, weeks, months or years.Standard T24 period field.</p>
                <p>If charge is made due/cap on the date of issue then this field should be updated as zero.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
