<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.DEBUG.LOG.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>When an activity/action is processed or any update is done in AA, it is it is possible to save certain information about the activity, action, API, and the variable values (in the subroutines) during processing which may be of use in tracking down the cause of any problem or just to report that the API routines has completed without any errors. This file records all these details when debug log is turned on.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      It records variable names, variable contents when the log was updated. The API routines defined in API can also pass the debug information to be updated. The action routines are configured to log some critical variables and variable contents.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field represents the name of the routine from which debug update was requested.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.UPDATED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the date on which the log was last updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBUG.LOG.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>Unique key by which the debug log details can be identified. It is generated by the system based on the application and transaction reference of the application (application ID).</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The format of the id is as follows - Property application name followed by application id (arrangement activity number) delimited by hyphen</p>
            <p>   Eg : AA.ARR.ACCOUNT-AAACT0033500002</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the variable name or watch variable in the API which is logged.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Associated with the field KEY.VALUE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>KEY.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the value of the variable defined in KEY.NAME when the log was updated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Associated with the field KEY.VALUE.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RECORD.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the ID of the originating application. </p>
            <p />
            <p>     In some cases both the Application id in the id of the record (AA.DEBUG.LOG.DETAILS id) and this field can contain the same value. </p>
            <p>     However in most cases since activity is triggered from AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY always DEBUG.LOG.ID contains the ID of Arrangement activity record id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

