<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.INTEREST.DETAILS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The file AA.INTEREST.ACCRUALS holds the interest accrual information for an arrangement for a given interest property.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>This live file stores the interest rate, number of days, principal balance, basis used for a given period and the accrual amount. The fields showing the above information are associated. A new set of multivalues is formed for every change interest rate, basis, balance and period. If there is no change in any of the above said parameters, a new set is shown for every month.</p>
            <p />
            <p>These details would be updated during simulation for enquiry purposes.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>COMPOUND.YIELD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the payment date for the corresponding property.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the start date of the current interest period. This field also represents the date when there was a change in the balance/principal of the contract. Hence whenever there is balance movement a new set of fields are added.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the start date of a interest period. This field is associated with PERIOD.END Period start date and end date of previous and current interest periods are stored in multivalue sets.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.SUSP.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the total suspended amount till the accrued date for the current period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field will get updated when interest is accrued after arrangement is suspended. </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field will also get updated when SUSPEND activity is run and SUSPEND.OVERDUE is set for the interest property.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The interest accrued from last payment date till suspend activity run date will be updated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the number of days for which accruals have been made for the current interest period. Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the spread or the margin that was used in the calculation of interest in current set of accrual fields.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the end date of the current interest period.Hence whenever there is balance movement a new set of fields are added.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPERTY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the id of the file. The id has two parts - arrangement number and the property name separated by hyphen.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.ARCHIVE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represent the date when the record was last archived.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.ACCR.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the total accrued amount till the accrue date for the current period. This field forms part of the set PERIOD.START.DATE and PERIOD.END.DATE. For every new interest periods, this field will also be multivalued and the accrued amount till date would be stored.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPOUND.FQU</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the frequency of interest getting compounded</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the interest rate that was used in the calculation of interest for the current set of interest multivalue fields.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the end date of a interest period. This field is associated with PERIOD.START. Period start date and end date of previous and current interest periods are stored in multivalue sets.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCRUAL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the amount of interest accrued for the given period rounded to the number of decimals defined for the currency</p>
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACT.ACC.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>The ACT.ACCT.AMT contains the amount of interest accrued for the given period rounded to six decimal places.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BALANCE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field BALANCE represents the balance amount or principal effective for the accrual period. </p>
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represent the calculation basis for the accrual amount. The basis mentioned in the interest property condition of the arrangement is considered. For futher information check helptext for INTEREST.BASIS</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

