<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.INTEREST.ACCRUAL.HIST</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p> The file AA.INTEREST.ACCRUALS.HIST holds the historical information of interest accrual for an arrangement for a given interest property.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>             This live file stores the interest rate, number of days, principal balance, basis used for a given period and the accrual amount. The fields showing the above information are associated. A new set of multivalues is formed for every change interest rate, basis, balance and period. If there is no change in any of the above said parameters, a new set is shown for every month. </p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>COMPOUND.YIELD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DAYS</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represents the number of days for which accruals have been made for the current interest period. Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                 The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the date from which the Profit Rate is applicable for this Interest method. Arranged in descending order, it will store the related rate on which Interest will be accrued, the corresponding profit amount &amp; the activity reference that resulted in this update.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FINAL.SCHEDULE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the final occurrence of the Fixed Interest Method. On this final date, any rounding differences between the agreed profit amount and accrued amounts so far will be posted.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FIXED.INT.AMT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FLOATING.INDEX</field>
            <desc>
                <p>BASIC.INTEREST key associated with the INT.EFF.DATE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FROM.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>         This field represents the start date of the current interest period. This field also represents the date when there was a change in the balance/principal of the contract. Hence whenever there is balance movement a new set of fields are added.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules</p>
                <p>        Standard date format of 11 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.ACCRUAL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>           This field contains the amount of interest accrued for the given period rounded to the number of decimals defined for the currency</p>
                <p>          The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. This is just an information fields, no entries will be raised based on this.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.ACT.ACC.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> The ACT.ACCT.AMT contains the amount of interest accrued for the given period rounded to six decimal places.</p>
                <p>           The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. This is just an information fields, no entries will be raised based on this.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>          The field BALANCE represents the balance amount or principal effective for the accrual period. </p>
                <p>           The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCRUAL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>           This field contains the amount of interest accrued for the given period rounded to the number of decimals defined for the currency</p>
                <p>          The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.BASIS</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represent the calculation basis for the accrual amount. The basis mentioned in the interest property condition of the arrangement is considered. For futher information check helptext for INTEREST.BASIS</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>       1 - 2 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.COMPOUND.FQU</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represents the frequency of interest getting compounded</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.COMPOUND.YIELD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.DAYS</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represents the number of days for which accruals have been made for the current interest period. Accruals are split into current month, previous month and previous year.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                 The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.FROM.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>         This field represents the start date of the current interest period. This field also represents the date when there was a change in the balance/principal of the contract. Hence whenever there is balance movement a new set of fields are added.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules</p>
                <p>        Standard date format of 11 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.MARGIN</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represents the spread or the margin that was used in the calculation of interest in current set of accrual fields.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rules</p>
                <p>       Standard rate format</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.PERIOD.END</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>      This field denotes the end date of a interest period. This field is associated with PERIOD.START. Period start date and end date of previous and current  interest periods are stored in multivalue sets.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.PERIOD.START</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the start date of a interest period. This field is associated with PERIOD.END Period start date and end date of previous and current  interest periods are stored in multivalue sets.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>         This field represents the interest rate that was used in the calculation of interest for the current set of interest multivalue fields.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate </p>
                <p>        changes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules</p>
                <p>        Standard rate format</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.TO.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>           This field represents the end date of the current interest period.Hence whenever there is balance movement a new set of fields are added.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                 The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules</p>
                <p>        Standard date format of 11 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACT.ACC.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> The ACT.ACCT.AMT contains the amount of interest accrued for the given period rounded to six decimal places.</p>
                <p>           The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.TOT.ACCR.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represents the total accrued amount till the accrue date for the current period. This field forms part of the set PERIOD.START.DATE and PERIOD.END.DATE. For every new interest periods, this field will also be multivalued and the accrued amount till date would be stored.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This is just an information fields, no entries will be raised based on this.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INT.EFF.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Associated with FLOATING.INDEX or PERIODIC.INDEX. Stores the dates when there is a change in BASIC.INTEREST or PERIODIC.INTEREST index.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.ACCRUAL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the rounded accrued  amount for the current multi value set. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.ACT.ACC.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the unrounded accrued amount for the current multi value set. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the balance on which accrual was computed. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.BASIS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the interest basis used for the accrual calculation. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.COMPOUND.FQU</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the frequency of interest getting compounded. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.COMPOUND.YIELD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the compounding method</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.DAYS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the number of days for which accrual has been calculated. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.FROM.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the start date of the interest period. It also represents the date when there was a change in the principal/rate of the contract. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the activity reference that has resulted in the update of the above said details. This will be used to remove all related information when the activity is reversed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.MARGIN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the margin value used for the accrual calculation. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.PERIOD.END</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the end date of the interest period. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.PERIOD.START</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the start date of the interest period. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the rate used for the accrual calculation. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.TO.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the end date of the interest period. It also represents the date when there was a change in the principal/rate of the contract. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IPROJ.TOT.ACCR.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the total accrued amount for the period. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LAST.ARCHIVE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>       This field represent the date when the record was last archived. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINK.EFF.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.ARRANGEMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.BALANCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A user can optionally specifiy one or more Balances being donated by the donor.</p>
                <p>Sub Valued field to allow multiple balance types to be donated.</p>
                <p>Specify the actual Balance type that needs to be taken for compensation.</p>
                <p>If this field is left blank, then it means that donor is not donating any balance.</p>
                <p>This may prove useful when a participant, by just being part of a package, there is a need to suppress their Interest (say, a Penalty Interest) which would otherwise accrue based on unauthorised overdraft balances</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJUST.INT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.INT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field describes when link rate is changed. It's associated with LINK.INT.RATE field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.INT.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field describes the link rate on a particular date. It's associated with LINK.INT.DATE field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.RATE.CHANGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the list of link rate change dates. It'll be cleared once change interest is processed for the child arrangements in COB.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Credit/Debit specification at the bundle contradicts with the Source Calc type of the Interest property Sub Value field associated with Donor Balance Type Input is allowed only if Donor Balance Type is input Because the Donor Balance type can have Credit or Debit balances on a given day, there would be a flag to specify which balances of the balance type should be used for Offset</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MARGIN</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represents the spread or the margin that was used in the calculation of interest in current set of accrual fields.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rules</p>
                <p>       Standard rate format</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MAX.OFF.SET</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The maximum % of the recipient balance that can be offset by the Donation.</p>
                <p>For ex, in an Offset mortgage, if the Principal is -85,000 and if the Donor balances amount to credit +100,000 then specifying Max Offset as 100% would mean only 85,000 of the credit balances are offset against the Recipient’s debit balance.</p>
                <p>There is no additional benefit for the surplus 15,000 in the Donor Balances 80% in Max Offset would mean only 68,000 (80% of 85,000) of the credit balance can be offset against the recipient’s debit balance In the case of Interest Compensation, this will be set to “” to indicate that there is no “Offset’ percentage but only a consolidation of Donor and Recipient balances to calculate interest on</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.MODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether the calculated interest has to be billed at the start of the period or not, This will hold only one value "ADVANCE". If it is set then the TOT.DUE.AMT will be updated at start of the period.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIOD.END</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>      This field denotes the end date of a interest period. This field is associated with PERIOD.START. Period start date and end date of previous and current  interest periods are stored in multivalue sets.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIOD.START</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the start date of a interest period. This field is associated with PERIOD.END Period start date and end date of previous and current  interest periods are stored in multivalue sets.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ALTERNATE.INTEREST</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIODIC.INDEX</field>
            <desc>
                <p>PERIODIC.INTEREST key associated with the INT.EFF.DATE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROFIT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the profit amount applicable for this property for the life of the contract.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROFIT.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the Rate applicable for accrual of Fixed Interest Method. Applicable only for Fixed type of Interest. It is updated along with an effective date from which this rate is applicable and the corresponding activity reference.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.ACCRUAL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the rounded accrued  amount for the current multi value set. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.ACT.ACC.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the unrounded accrued amount for the current multi value set. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.ADJUST.INT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the balance on which accrual was computed. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.BASIS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the interest basis used for the accrual calculation. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.COMPOUND.FQU</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the frequency of interest getting compounded. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.COMPOUND.YIELD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the compounding method</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>          The field BALANCE represents the balance amount or principal effective for the accrual period. </p>
                <p>           The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.DAYS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the number of days for which accrual has been calculated. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.FROM.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the start date of the interest period. It also represents the date when there was a change in the principal/rate of the contract. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.INT.ACC.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the current month accrual amount. An accrual accounting will be raised during cob for this amount. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.INT.ACC.PM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the previous month accrual amount. An accrual accounting will be raised during cob for this amount. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.INT.ACC.PY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the previous year accrual amount. An accrual accounting will be raised during cob for this amount. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.INT.SUSP.CM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the current month suspended accrual amount. An accrual accounting will be raised during cob for this amount. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.INT.SUSP.PM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the previous month suspended accrual amount. An accrual accounting will be raised during cob for this amount. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.INT.SUSP.PY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the previous year suspended accrual amount. An accrual accounting will be raised during cob for this amount. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.MARGIN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the margin value used for the accrual calculation. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.PERIOD.END</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the end date of the interest period. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BASIS</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represent the calculation basis for the accrual amount. The basis mentioned in the interest property condition of the arrangement is considered. For futher information check helptext for INTEREST.BASIS</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes. A new subvalue sets (BALANCE - ACT.ACC.AMT) within a mutlivalue set is created if the calculation type is either BAND or LEVEL. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>       1 - 2 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.PERIOD.START</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the start date of the interest period. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the rate used for the accrual calculation. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.TO.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the end date of the interest period. It also represents the date when there was a change in the principal/rate of the contract. The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.TOT.ACCR.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the total accrued amount for the period. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.TOT.DUE.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the total accrued amount that has been made due for that period</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.TOT.RES.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the difference of total accrued amount and total due amounts for corresponding periods. This would get update when property type is set to RESIDUAL.ACCRUAL in AA.PROPERTY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.TOT.RPY.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the total accrued amount repaid for the interset periods as in PERIOD.START and PERIOD.END.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJ.TOT.SUSP.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This filed represents the total suspended accrued amount for the period. This field will get updated during online accrual projection.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>         This field represents the id of the file. The id has two parts - arrangement number and the property name separated by hyphen. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>         This field represents the interest rate that was used in the calculation of interest for the current set of interest multivalue fields.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate </p>
                <p>        changes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules</p>
                <p>        Standard rate format</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.PROFIT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Stores the system calculated profit amount if any for the Fixed Interest method. This will happen for Flat Rate/Reducing Rate option when the user defined profit amount does not exist.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TO.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>           This field represents the end date of the current interest period.Hence whenever there is balance movement a new set of fields are added.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                 The fields FROM.DATE to ACT.ACC.AMT form an association containing interest accrual data. A new multivalue is created each time a month end is passed or the principal or interest rate changes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules</p>
                <p>        Standard date format of 11 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.ACCR.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represents the total accrued amount till the accrue date for the current period. This field forms part of the set PERIOD.START.DATE and PERIOD.END.DATE. For every new interest periods, this field will also be multivalued and the accrued amount till date would be stored.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.DUE.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the total amount made as due for the interest periods as in PERIOD.START and PERIOD.END. This may be different from the TOT.ACCR.AMT when a bill is issued before the due date and subsequently a change in interest, basis, principal changes the accrued amount, in this case due amount would be based on the bill issued, i.e. the billed amount.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.RES.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the difference of total accrued amount and total due amounts for corresponding periods. This would get update when property type is set to RESIDUAL.ACCRUAL in AA.PROPERTY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.RPY.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the total accrued amount repaid for the interset periods as in PERIOD.START and PERIOD.END.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.SUSP.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the total suspended amount till the accrued date for the current period.</p>
                <p>This field will get updated when interest is accrued after arrangement is suspended. </p>
                <p>This field will also get updated when SUSPEND activity is run and SUSPEND.OVERDUE is set for the interest property.</p>
                <p>The interest accrued from last payment date till suspend activity run date will be updated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         Standard T24 amount field of upto 19 characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPOUND.FQU</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field represents the frequency of interest getting compounded</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
