<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.MARKETING.CATALOGUE.DESIGNER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>Marketing Catalogue Designer allows to define the fields and its mapping details from AA tables that describes the product features. It describes the definition of product catalogue for marketing/sales purposes. The id of marketing catalogue is Product group along with date. So for all the products under the product group their respective product conditions would be extracted using the marketing definition defined for the product group.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.FIELD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Source property field from where the data must be extracted. Should be a valid field in STANDARD.SELECTION table of AA.PRD.CAT.XXX where XXX is the property class of the property defined.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.NULL.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field describes Data to be defaulted when the extracted value from AA Table is NULL</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the name of the source property from where data must be extracted. It will be AA.PRD.CAT.XXXX  (XXXX – Source Property name).</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Pre-defined special type of data that needs to be extracted from Interest or Charge property tables, for example if INTEREST is chosen, standard interest related fields would be automatically included for extraction, and similarly CHARGE. The standard set of fields are defined in the table AA.STANDARD.FIELD.TYPE for both INTEREST and CHARGE.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>In case the information is not present in any AA table, such information could still be defined here to be included in the marketing catalog.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SRC.FLD.LOOKUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved For future </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SRC.FLD.RULE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User can define the marketing catalogue for Negotiation Rules or Periodic rules by using this field.</p>
                <p>Negotiation rule type for SOURCE.FIELD defined in AA.PRD.CAT.XXX table that needs to be extracted.</p>
                <p>Periodic rule type for SOURCE.FIELD defined in AA.PRD.CAT.XXX table that needs to be extracted.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SRC.FLD.RULE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates any rule associated with the actual field name. Options – Negotiation or Periodic or activity restriction rules.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It will accepts only one option PUBLISH. In order to maintain a separate design and run-time, when the marketing catalogue definition is ready for production, using the action within the Table AA.MARKETING.CATALOGUE.DESIGNER the record can be moved to AA.MARKETING.CATALOGUE  with PUBLISH action </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standrad multi-language description type field to update description for the record</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FIELD.DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard full description field where a detailed notes on the purpose of the record could be updated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FIELD.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User defined field name which represents a data that needs to be extracted from AA Tables. It is mandatory field. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard full description field where a detailed notes on the purpose of the record could be updated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MARKET.CAT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is valid record from AA.PRODUCT.GROUP application. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Records the overrides generated during processing marketing catalogue created. </p>
                <p>Standard override field, Multi-valued.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.API</field>
            <desc>
                <p>In case the information is not present in any AA table, but can only be produced via a routine specify the name of the routine which would be called when the marketing catalogue information is presented.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.DATA.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It describes the Data type of the Source Field or Negotiation Field.  It will be defaulted by the system if Source Field OR Negotiation field defined.  It Should be input by the user if no SOURCE.FIELD is input, in which case it is assumed that the field value would be input by the user or would be returned by an API defined.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
