<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.OVERDUE.STATS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This is a central table used to store statistical data of various overdue statuses that an arrangement is going through during its lifecycle. This is a live table and it is maintained by the system internally.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Broadly, this table is updated on two occassions:</p>
            <p>1. Whenever there is a change to arrangement overdue status.</p>
            <p>2. Whenever there is a movement of amount, either credit or debit but, the overall arrangement overdue status still remains the same.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In the first case, the arrangement overdue status undergoes a change and hence recording this overdue status movement would be necessary for maintaining the statistics. This change in overdue status can happen either because an AGE activity has moved certain bills to next overdue status and hence the arrangement overdue status has changed or there could be a repayment which has moved back the overdue status of unpaid bills to a lower overdue status and hence the arrangement overdue status has undergone a change. In either case, the statistics table would to updated with suitable information to reflect this change in status.</p>
            <p />
            <p>In the second case, even though the overdue status of the arrangement has not changed, still the amount movement within the current arrangement overdue status has to be recorded so that it would be useful in the calculation of average amount for the overdue status. Again, here the amount movement can happen either due to AGE activity or due to repayment activity. In the case of AGE activity, the overall arrangement overdue status can be in a particular overdue status, when a bill is aged but to a lower overdue status and thus not changing the overall arrangement overdue status. However, the amount movement has to maintained still. Similarly, a partial repayment would not have changed the overall overdue status of the arrangement, but the amount movement has to maintained still.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MVMT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the date of either debit or credit amount movement into a overdue status.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATUS.COUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field gives the total number of times the arrangement has visited a overdue status during the life of the arrangement.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OD.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the overdue status that the arrangement has moved into during its life cycle.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOT.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field gives the total number of days the arrangement has stayed in a overdue status during the life of the arrangement.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVMT.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the debit movement of amount for a overdue status on the movement date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field signifies the start date of a period for a overdue status.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRD.AVG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the period average amount for a overdue status. This average amount is calculated as a daily balance average within a given period for a overdue status.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARR.ID.OD.PROP.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>ID for this table is a combination of arrangementID-OverduePropertyID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the overdue status average amount. This is calculated as sum of all the period averages for the overdue status divided by the total count for this overdue status.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the period end date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MVMT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the credit movement of amount for an overdue status on the movement date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

