<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRODUCT.TRACKER.PROOF</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The base file where any changes to product conditions are updated and tracked after a product has been proofed. After publishing these changes would be picked by a generic service process - AA.ARR.PRODUCT.TRACKER - which would apply these changes onto the relevant arrangements so that the changes to the product are effected on the arrangement records using them. Would be automatically updated as part of the proofing mechanism.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The product on which certain conditions have been amended,</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRACK.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>   This field represents the id of the product tracker</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPERTY.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The Property and currency combination to indicate the currency condition for the property has been amended. When a property is a noncurrency property, then this field would only hold the property id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESIGNER.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The AA.PRD.DES.XXX (where XXX is the class) which has undergone a change. This gets updated even when the designer condition is reversed out.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual effective date on which the condition have been changed. This date would indicate on which date would the change be effected on the arrangement property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EFF.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>The effective period condition which has undergone a change. For example, when a Interest property follows a FIXED.INTEREST for first 6 months and switches to a FLOATING rate after that, then any amendments to FLOATING rate condition would update this field to 6M. This is an indication to the system not to apply this change onto arrangements which have not crossed this period yet.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

