<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PAYMENT.DATES</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This application stores the history of processed payment dates.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>SCHEDULE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the payment type of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTUAL.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represent the actual payment date. The payments dates will be calendar days, if the payment date happens to be a holiday. Standard T24 date field</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field identifies the main Arrangement Contract number.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FINANCIAL.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the financial date of the payment. This field represents the value date of the accounting entries raised during the payment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This date can be cycled forward or backward to the next working day if the payment date falls on a holiday. This depends on the fields DATE.CONVENTION and DATE.ADJUSTMENT in the PAYMENT.SCHEDULE property. Standard T24 date field</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>HOL.PAYMENT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the payment type for which payment holiday dates are maintained in HOLIDAY.DATE field. This is captured from the field HOL.PAYMENT.TYPE of Payment Schedule condition.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>HOL.START.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the holiday start date for which payment holiday dates are maintained in HOLIDAY.DATE field. This is captured from the field HOL.START.DATE of Payment Schedule condition.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>HOLIDAY.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the list of holiday payment dates that are to be skipped as given in the payment holiday definition of Payment Schedule condition.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INTERIM.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the last interim capitalisation date. Standard T24 date field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NUM.PAYMENTS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field identifies the number of times the associated payment has been processed, i.e. crossed payment date / made due. It is used in relation with NUM.PAYMENTS in Payment Schedule property class to identify number of remaining payments to be processed in future for the payment type.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the payment date. Standard T24 date field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
