<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRODUCT.LINE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The Product Line provides a high level definition of the business components (Property Classes) that may be required to construct a product belonging to that line.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>  For example the LENDING Product Line will enable users to design and service term loan products such as:</p>
            <p>        Loans (personal, small business, etc.)</p>
            <p>        Mortgages</p>
            <p>        Lines of Credit</p>
            <p/>
            <p> The Product Lines are defined by Temenos and cannot be created by the User. A Product Line is described by the Property Classes which constitute it.  The financial institution may then use these “building blocks” of functionality to construct the individual products which are available for sale to its customers.</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ST.PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the property class where the properties of this class could be shown as stacked in ProductBuilder</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STACKED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When flagged to YES, the properties of the type above class would be shown as stacked in ProductBuilder</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUB.BATCH.PRIORITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field assumes significance only when BUNDLE product line is procured. If BUNDLE is procured, even within a single line, the Donors would have to get processed before the Recipients are processed so that the results are consistent during every COB. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validations:</p>
                <p>DONOR, RECIPIENT - One of the 2 options.</p>
                <p>No Significance if BUNDLE line is not licensed by the bank</p>
                <p>System maintained and cannot be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BATCH.PRIORITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When multiple Product line licenses are procured, this field indicates which processes run first and which run next. For example, by default the DEPOSITS schedule get processed before the LENDING schedules and ACCOUNTS run last. The field is system maintained and cannot be modified.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validations:</p>
                <p>Stores a number which indicates the priority of schedule processing</p>
                <p>System maintained and cannot be modified.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the AA.PRODUCT.LINE and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the AA.PRODUCT.LINE  in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>    Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Provides a more detailed description of the AA.PRODUCT.LINE</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>    Up to 50 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the group name that is used to group the property classes together</p>
                <p>Grouping of property classes would allow to setup specific group level settings in ProductBuilder</p>
                <p>Associated multi-value with GROUP.CLASS</p>
                <p>Standard text type field, should be a unique value from EB.LOOKUP table for the key starting with AA.PC.GROUP"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GROUP.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Holds the property classes that are associated with the Group</p>
                <p>Associated multi-value with GROUP"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINE.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field indicates the characteristic of this line. Some lines may have a financial angle to it(dealing with amounts, currencies etc) like LENDING and some may not share that characteristic(like INTERNET.SERVICES). Currently to state that the products of this line deal with amounts, this field may be stated as CCY. </p>
                <p>A new option SINGLE is added along with the  existing options CCY and REPLAY.</p>
                <p>The option SINGLE would indicate that there can be only one unique arrangement for each customer for products belonging to this line. For example, a customer may take as many LENDING products that he may require – but there can be only one RELATIONSHIP.PRICING arrangement for a customer.</p>
                <p>Validations would be added based on this field whilst taking NEW arrangement to throw error when multiple arrangements are taken under a single product.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Maximum of 35 Alphanumeric characters. Accepts CCY or NULL Non-mandatory field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MANDATORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies whether inclusion of a Property a Class in the associated multi value field PROPERTY.CLASS is mandatory when creating a new product in AA.PRODUCT.GROUP and subsequently, AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.LINE.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These records are released by Temenos and cannot be created.</p>
                <p>       Currently, the available option is LENDING, INTERNET.SERVICES and PROXY.SERVICES. </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Property Classes that may be included when defining an AA.PRODUCT.GROUP. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Mandatory Input. Input must be a valid AA.PROPERTY.CLASS ID. Multi value field associated with MANDATORY field. A new property class PAYOUT is released in Lending Product line as “OPTIONAL”.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
