<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRD.DES.AC.ACCT.GROUP.CONDN</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application replaces the pre G8 file SAVINGS.COND that was used to to implement parameters used by savings accounts on the system. Even though the file takes on the parameters set up inside the old SAVINGS.COND file it does not restrict itself to just that and can be used more generically to set up parameters for other types of accounts.</p>
            <p>Validation Rules</p>
            <p>Changes to some parameters which are used in the update processing of the ACCT.AVAILABILITY file is controlled and can be only made in a record that has a date appended to the id. This date specifies day on which the new parameters are transferred into the active record (ID without a date appended to it). The change made will be effected in the end of day process and will obviously also rebuild the ACCT.AVAILABILITY file.</p>
            <p>A record must be created for each group and currency combination in order to allow the underlying accounts in the combination to use the parameter set up</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.PENDING.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the category code to be used when forming a suspense account to which the tax amount calculated on interest &amp; or charges on an account needs to be posted to in case either the field DEFER.CHARGE.DAYS or the field DEFER.DB.INT.DAYS has been specified. The amount posted into this suspense account will reversed after the notification period has been served.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be input if the either of DEFER.DB.INT.DAYS or DEFER.CHARGE.DAYS has been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If input must be a valid category code set up on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If input must be in the range 10000-19999.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WDL.PRD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the type of WDL.PERIOD entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'CALENDAR' or 'VARIABLE'. Any number of the first characters may be entered, e.g. 'C' or 'CA' will suffice for CALENDAR and will also be expanded to CALENDAR on the screen.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field is mandatory only if the corresponding WDL.PERIOD is entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.RESTRICT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to restrict the accounts that belong to this group and currency from making debit transactions if set to 'Y'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>'Yes' or 'No'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>THRESHOLD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the threshold for each transaction code or group in the field</p>
            <p>TXN.CODE.GRP</p>
            <p>WAIVE.CREDIT.INT</p>
            <p>NO.VIOLATION</p>
            <p>This threshold applies to each statement period.</p>
            <p>The associated</p>
            <p>TXN.CODE.GRP</p>
            <p>Fields</p>
            <p>THRESHOLD</p>
            <p>NO.VIOLATION</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 2 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 numeric field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.AMOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the maximum amount which can be withdrawn without notification being required.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The maxmimum local currency amount that can be withdrawn in a single transaction without incurring an override message. If this value is exceeded then the override message:</p>
            <p />
            <p>ACCOUNT &amp; - NOTICE CONDS FOR WITHDRAWAL NOT MET</p>
            <p />
            <p>will be displayed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFER.CHARGE.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to allow the system to defer the charge posting to the account on which they are due in order to facilitate a means of notifying the customer of the details in advance. The number of days specified here will equal to the number of days in the notification period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be input if the field CHARGE.PENDING.CAT has been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>3 alphanumeric characters - nnD or nnW format.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If nnC entered, the number of days is taken to be calendar days.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If nnW entered, the number of days is taken to be business days.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREDIT.CHECK</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies on which balance, overdraft and limit checking should be made. It can be set at ACCOUNT level or at the ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION or ACCOUNT.PARAMETER level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The flag will be selected in the following order:</p>
            <p />
            <p>1. ACCOUNT</p>
            <p />
            <p>2. ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION, if not set at ACCOUNT level</p>
            <p />
            <p>3. ACCOUNT.PARAMETER, if not set at ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION level</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>AVAILABLE: Credit checking is made using AVAILABLE.BAL</p>
            <p />
            <p>WORKING: Credit checking is made using WORKING.BALANCE</p>
            <p />
            <p>FORWARD: Credit checking is made using WORKING.BALANCE plus today's forward movements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>AVAILWORK: Credit checking is made using AVAILABLE.BAL and WORKING.BALANCE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>AVAILFWD: Credit checking is made using AVAILABLE.BAL and WORKING.BALANCE plus today's forward movements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>BLANK: The default checking is using WORKING.BALANCE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RETENTION.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines how long transactions remain on the live account violations file (</p>
            <p />
            <p>Additionally, this field will also be used to determine when transactions will be deleted from the history file (</p>
            <p />
            <p>For example, if '12M' is entered in this field, a violation record will remain on the live file for 12 months before being transferred to the history file. The record will then remain on the history file for a further 24 months before being deleted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 4 characters may be entered. The first 3 characters define the length of the period and the final character defines the type of period i.e. :- D = Days W = Weeks M = Months Y = Years e.g. 30D (30 days), 8W (8 weeks), 12M (12 months), 2Y (2 years)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.DEPOSIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the maximum deposit allowable in the specified period above.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is used in validating against the sum of all the deposits within the specified period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field is optional, but input is only allowed if and only if the DEPOSIT.PERIOD is populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are</p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
            <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
            <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge property</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSIT.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates a deposit period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Duplicate entries are not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is associated with field range DEP.PERIOD.TYPE to MAX.DEP.INC.</p>
            <p />
            <p>3-4 alphanumeric characters - nnnD, nnW or nnM format.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PREMIUM.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the premium type associated with this file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input must exist on the SAVINGS.PREMIUM file. (Optional Input)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.DEP.INC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the maximum increase allowable in the specified period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is used in validating against the increase in balance within the specified period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field is optional, but input is only allowed if and only if the DEPOSIT.PERIOD is populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>11 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NOTICE.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the notice, in days or months, which must be given before the amount, specified in NOTICE.AMOUNT can be withdrawn.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The number of days, months or working days which constitute the period. e.g. 20D, 7W, 3M, etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>3 alphanumeric characters - nnD, nnM or nnW format.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.WDL.AMT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the maximum withdrawal amount in the period defined above for the corresponding transaction code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field is optional, but must not be input if the corresponding WDL.TXN.CODE has not been populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>11 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
            <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
            <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.PENDING.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the category code to be used when forming a suspense account to which the charge settling on an account will be posted to when the field DEFER.CHARGE.DAYS has been specified. The amount posted into this suspense account will reversed after the notification period has been served.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be input if the field DEFER.CHARGE.DAYS has been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If input must be a valid category code set up on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If input must be in the range 10000-19999.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
            <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
            <p>Condition id</p>
            <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
            <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
            <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
            <p />
            <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
            <p />
            <p>OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
            <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MANDATORY</p>
            <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A list of all valid credit transaction codes that may be used by this group of accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>A default transaction code may be defined as 'DEFAULT'. This will be used for any transaction code used that is not found in this list.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid transaction code. Duplicate entries are not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SETTLE.ACCT.CLOSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is a flag specifying whether a settlement account is required at the time of closing an account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>1-2 alphabetic character field . (Mandatory input)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.CODE.GRP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to define the transaction code or codes within which a threshold has been set in the field</p>
            <p />
            <p>TXN.THRESHOLD</p>
            <p />
            <p>e.g.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>36.1 TXN.THRESHOLD.. 6</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>37.1.1 TXN.CODE.GRP 15</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>36.2 TXN.THRESHOLD.. 3</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>37.2.1 TXN.CODE.GRP 99</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>36.3 TXN.THRESHOLD.. 5</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>37.3.1 TXN.CODE.GRP 135</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>or</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>36.1 TXN.THRESHOLD.. 6</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>37.1.1 TXN.CODE.GRP 15</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>37.1.2 TXN.CODE.GRP 99</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>36.2 TXN.THRESHOLD.. 5</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>37.2.1 TXN.CODE.GRP 135</p>
            <p />
            <p>Fields</p>
            <p />
            <p>TXN.THRESHOLD</p>
            <p />
            <p>NO.VIOLATION</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>A maximum of 7 characters may be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be the key to a valid entry on the</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PENALTY.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the penalty code that may be applied to the account whenever penalty is due.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field is optional, but must not be input if the corresponding transaction code has not been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Only valid 'CHARGE' or 'COMMISSION' types can be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>11 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.DEPOSIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the minimum amount that can be deposited into the account in any one transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTRICTED.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>When the Field DEBIT.RESTRICT is set to YES, then this field is used to specify the OVERRIDE message, at the time of committing debit entries in the account belonging to this group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This is a text field and any user defined override message can be given in this field</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Text Field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Value can be inputted only when the field DEBIT.RESTRICT is set to YES. Otherwise this is a NOINPUT field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the maximum balance that the account is supposed to maintain.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If a deposit transaction will make the account go above this balance then an override message will be required.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MINIMUM.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the minimum balance that the account is supposed to maintain.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If a withdrawal transaction is going to make the account go below this balance then an override will be required.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>19 Numeric characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WDL.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines a withdrawal period for the transaction code associated to this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is associated with field range WDL.PRD.TYPE to MAX.NO.WDLS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field is optional, but must not be entered if the corresponding transaction is not entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>3-4 alphanumeric characters - nnnD, nnW or nnM.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>If this field is set to YES then no credit interest will be paid for the next interest cycle on any account breaking the conditions of the transaction threshold group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The details of the qualifying transactions are stored on the</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid values are &amp;#145;YES&amp;#146; or &amp;#145;NO&amp;#146;</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.NO.WDLS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the maximum number of withdrawals allowable within the specified period defined above for the corresponding transaction code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field is optional, but must not be input if the corresponding WDL.TXN.CODE has not been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>2 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WDL.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This multivalued field will contain a list of all valid withdrawal transaction codes that may be used by this group of accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>A default transaction code may be defined as 'DEFAULT'. This will be used of any debit transaction code used that is not found in this list.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>This field is associated with field range MAXIMUM.PER.WDL to PENALTY.CODE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Duplicate entries are not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid debit transaction code</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SINGLE.LIMIT.DEFLT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Single limit default field can be set to Y/N. The value set here will be defaulted to single limit field in account, for the new account opened with the group condition. If single limit field in account is defaulted to "Y" then only one account is allowed to utilize the limit. If set to "N" then multiple accounts can utilize the same limit.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Optional Input</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input can be Y/N/Blank</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NO.VIOLATION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field allows the related transaction threshold set, not to be used for calculating account violations. This means that transactions in this group will be recorded on the</p>
            <p />
            <p>TXN.STATUS</p>
            <p />
            <p>VIOLATION.STATUS</p>
            <p />
            <p>This is to allow a transaction threshold set to be used for specifying the conditions for the waiving of credit interest without affecting</p>
            <p />
            <p>VIOLATION.STATUS</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input of NO or null, results in the transaction threshold set being used for violation processing.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Allowed inputs are YES, NO or null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.PERIOD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the type of the DEPOSIT.PERIOD entered above. Effective from G14.1, a user defined routine can be attached to this field with a prefix of @</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>'CALENDAR' or 'VARIABLE'. Any number of the first characters may be entered, e.g. 'C' or 'CA' will suffice for CALENDAR and will also be expanded to CALENDAR on the screen.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Input will be mandatory if and only if DEPOSIT.PERIOD has been populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.MATURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will define a period after which the deposit amount of the associated transaction code becomes available for withdrawal without incurring a penalty fee.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>3-4 alphanumeric characters - nnnD, nnW or nnM format.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Cannot input into this field if the corresponding DEPOSIT.TXN.CODE has not been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.NO.DEPOSITS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will contain the maximum number of deposits allowable on the account before which an override will be required.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>2 numeric characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WITHDRAWAL.UNIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the denomination in which a withdrawal can be made.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p>RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSIT.UNIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the denomination in which a deposit can be made.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>19 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.INCREASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the maxmimum annual balance increase allowed for this category of account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>The maximum amount an account balance can be increased by per year. The calculation is based on the start of year opening balance (START.YEAR.BAL) in the account record and the current online cleared balance (ONLINE.CLEARED.BAL).</p>
            <p />
            <p>e.g. If an account balance can only be increased by 10,000.00 per annum, from a start of year balance of 50,000.00 and with a current online balance of 43,000.00 then the maximum increase which will be allowed is 17,000.00.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Similarly if the online balance is 58,000.00 then the maximum increase will be 2,000.00.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If this amount is exceeded then the override message:</p>
            <p />
            <p>MAXIMUM ALLOWED DEPOSIT = &amp; is displayed. Thereafter the message:</p>
            <p />
            <p>MAXIMUM INCREASE ALREADY EXCEEDED will be displayed for all further deposits.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>19 numeric characters - local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAXIMUM.PER.WDL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the maximum amount allowable per withdrawal for the transaction code associated to this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Input to this field is optional, but must not be entered if the corresponding WDL.TXN.CODE is not entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>11 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
            <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INC.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ALLOW.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be entered to have a list of valid debit transaction codes to which debit transactions done for accounts belonging to this group will be restricted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If entered must be a valid debit transaction code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AUTO.SETTLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the system must automatically raise the accounting transactions to move the IC P&amp;L to xxxxxSP when an account is suspended and then move the xxxxxSP to P&amp;L when the suspense is removed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>If the indicator on ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION is not set, then the indicator on ACCOUNT.ACCRUAL is checked.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Option : 'YES', 'NO' or Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAILABILITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>The period for which the funds will be available once notice has been given.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field defines the number of days, months or working days for which funds subject to notice conditions will be available. e.g. if three months notice is given for withdrawal then the bank can stipulate that the funds will only be available for two weeks afterwhich a further three months notice must be given.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>2-3 alphanumeric characters in the format: nnD, nnM or nnW.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAILABLE.BAL.UPD</field>
<desc>
            <p>It identifies whether</p>
            <p />
            <p>1.</p>
            <p />
            <p>2.</p>
            <p />
            <p>3.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>For example if nothing is set at ACCOUNT level then the ACCT.GROUP.CONDITION is checked and if still nothing is set at this level, the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER is checked.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
