<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRD.DES.CHANNEL.ACCESS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Property Class that defines through product which channel is allowed.</p>
            <p>This Property Class is used by all products which are channel based. </p>
            <p>Channels can be replaced or given additional channels at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p>Also allows to subscription, de-subscription, and block and unblocks the subscription for a specific period.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MV.RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RESERVED.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Time to which this Channel will be de-subscribed on the end date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 15 type T (valid time format)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
            <p />
            <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
            <p />
            <p>OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
            <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MANDATORY</p>
            <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
            <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
            <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge property</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date to start the subscription for this specific Channel.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Mandatory</p>
            <p>Up to 11 type D (valid date format)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
            <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date to which this Channel will be de-subscribed.</p>
            <p>If date is not mentioned then it subscribes always</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type D (valid date format)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MV.RESERVED.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
            <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
            <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>START.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Time from which this Channel will be subscribed on the start date</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 15 type T (valid time format)</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EB.CHANNEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies what type of channel to be use. Must be a valid channel on EB.CHANNEL.</p>
            <p>For MOBILE.SERVICES product line, only EB.CHANNEL records classified as MOBILE in the CHANNEL.TYPE field will be allowed. </p>
            <p>An equivalent mapping of these Mobile records has to define in the properties file for successful Java calls. </p>
            <p>Please refer to the ARC Mobile User Guide for more details.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            <p>Multivalue field.</p>
            <p>The code must have a valid entry on the EB.CHANNEL table.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SV.RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>NOINPUT field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
            <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date to unblock the blocked Subscription of this channel.</p>
            <p>Date should be between the channel subscription period if end date is mentioned.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type D (valid date format)</p>
            <p>This field is multi value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.END.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Time to unblock the blocked Subscription on the block end date of this channel.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 15 type T (valid time format)</p>
            <p>This field is multi value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Date to block the subscription to this channel for a specific period.</p>
            <p>Date should be greater than Channel start date.</p>
            <p>If multivalued then it should be greater than previous block end date.</p>
            <p>Every block periods should be in sequence.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 11 type D (valid date format)</p>
            <p>This field is multi value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BLOCK.START.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>Start time to block the Subscription on the block start date of this channel.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 15 type T (valid time format)</p>
            <p>This field is multi value.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
