<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRODUCT.GROUP</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This definition would group the discrete properties and give a basic shape to the product. The product group provides a structure to the product whilst also defining constraints to any products derived from the group. The actual conditions of the property would be stated at AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER level.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>  This application may also be utilised to build AA.ACTIVITY records when new properties/Groups are introduced. While authorizing the product group if the field REBUILD.ACTIVITIES is set to YES, system will create instances of the activity class records.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>PL.PC.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the property classes which are yet to be assigned with property name in AA.PRODUCT.GROUP record. When a property is assigned in the field PROPERTY for the property class, it is is removed from this field, so, at any point of time, this will only hold the unassigned property classes, and is updated by the system at run-time when the record is ""viewed""</p>
                <p>System maintained field"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PORTFOLIOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The id of the product group.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         Any Alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>         Maximum of 30 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.LINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When defining a product group, it is mandatory that the group fall into one of the Product lines released by Temenos. When properties are stated in this table, it is mandatory that they should belong to one of the classes defined on the Product line. Product line is the highest level in designing a product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         Should be a valid AA.PRODUCT.LINE id.</p>
                <p>         Maximum of 20 characters</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Properties that may be included when defining a new product in AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER. It is possible to have more than one Property belonging to a Property Class and one or all of these can be Mandatory.</p>
                <p>         Multi value set of fields associated with AA.PROPERTY and MANDATORY. This field is also part of a sub value set with MANDATORY.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Input must be a valid AA.PROPERTY id.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Property Classes that may be included when defining a new product in  AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER.</p>
                <p>         Multi value set of fields associated with AA.PROPERTY and MANDATORY.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Input must be a valid AA.PROPERTY.CLASS id.</p>
                <p>        All mandatory classes in the associated product line record should be defined here. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REBUILD.ACTIVITIES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field is used to rebuild AA.ACTIVITY records from AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS. AA.ACTIVITY is an instance of AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS and records would be created on AA.ACTIVITY for all instances(properties) of class(property class) during authorisation stage. This can also be used to rebuild activities when a new property is introduced into the group.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation rule:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Accepts YES and NULL.</p>
                <p>      Rebuilds only when the field is stated as YES</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYSTEM.GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Certain product groups are released by Temenos to perform mapping to existing parameter tables from Product designer conditions. These groups would have YES on these fields.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>         Valid input must be either YES or null. </p>
                <p>         This is system updated field and cannot be edited</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADDITIONAL.CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field can be used for classifying the groups. The list of classification can be defined in the EB.LOOKUP file for AA.PRODUCT.GROUP.ATTRIBUTE. For example, a product group may cater to RETAIL banking, whilst another product may cater for PRIVATE banking. These classifications may be done using this field.Since the classification is 'soft', it is left to the discretion of the financial institution as to how they would want to group their products.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Non Mandatory field.</p>
                <p>   Contents should be defined in EB.LOOKUP of AA.PRODUCT.GROUP.ATTRIBUTE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CATEGORY.FROM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CATEGORY.TO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the AA.PRODUCT.GROUP and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the AA.PRODUCT.GROUP in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXCLUDED.CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Provides a more detailed description of the GROUP being defined</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GROUP.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Valid options are INTERNAL and EXTERNAL</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         INTERNAL - This means that the group being defined is the own Bank's product. Hence only products which are specified as INTERNAL are available for sale to customers.</p>
                <p>         EXTERNAL - There may be a necessity for Banks to do comparison between its own product(INTERNAL) and one by its competitor. Those groups may be defined as EXTERNAL. These products may then be used for comparitive analysis to show the superiority of Bank's own product. Products of this type are not available for sale to own customers.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MANDATORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies whether the defined property is mandatory while designing new product in AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER. When a property is defined as Mandatory and no condition is specified for that in AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER, those products would not pass the Publishing process.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      When a class is defined as mandatory in the AA.PRODUCT.LINE, then atleast one property belonging to that class needs to be defined as mandatory here.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         Multi value set of fields associated with PROPERTY and PROPERTY.CLASS. This field is also part of a sub value set with PROPERTY.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Valid options are NO and YES. Default value is NO.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
