<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRD.PRF.BALANCE.MAINTENANCE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p/>
            <p>               This property class allows to capture bills, balances and adjust the balances of the bill for those contracts which has been taken over from existing legacy system or existing T24 lending modue into T24 AA module. </p>
            <p>               The action routines CAPTURE.BILL, ADJUST.BILL etc help in capturing the bill and its balances into the new system.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.ADJ.NARR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field gives the user to specify narration specific to bill adjustment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Upto 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>              This field represents the bill creation date. If null, the payment date would be defaulted. The bill date cannot be greater than the payment date and prior to original contract date. The original contract date is defined while taking over the contracts (arrangements)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             Validation rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             Standard T24 date field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the bill id of the bill that is captured or whose balance that needs to be adjusted. If the bill is captured for the first time, value in this field should be new. New bill id is generated by action CAPTURE.BILL</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             Should be NEW or valid bill details id</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Bill Type would be picked from EB.LOOKUP instead of the hard-coded values of PAYMENT, EXPECTED, PR.CHARGE, ACT.CHARGE, INFO</p>
                <p>Note: DEF.CHARGE would also be available</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validations:</p>
                <p>•Standard lookup field</p>
                <p>•Maximum number of characters is restricted to 15</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFER.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The date on which customer will see this bill in his statement. This will be normally ‘X’ days after the original cycled date of the Bill. On this date, the actual Make due/Capitalise activity is going to happen for the bill. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEL.BILL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>  This field represents the delinquent outstanding amount that needs to be captured or adjusted for the bill.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Standard T24 amount field</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJ.BAL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field is used to specify the adjusted balance amount for the corresponding balance type. This is a signed field, that is, sign given here indicate a debit or credit entry to be passed based on the balance type and the product line of the product. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Example:</p>
                <p>      We have captured a penalty interest, say a debit balance of 100, from legacy system for a lending product. Subsequently, when the balance is to be adjusted such that the new balance amount is say 500, then a value -400 has to be given here.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Standard t24 signed amount field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
                <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NET.ADJUST.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The net adjustment for non-contingent balance types would be calculated and stored in this field by the system during Balance Adjustment, Write off activities of Balance maintenance.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Example:</p>
                <p>   Say we have adjusted the following non contingent balances captured from the legacy system,</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Penalty interest accruals increased = -1000</p>
                <p>   Current loan account decreased = 10000</p>
                <p>   This field would be updated with the net amount of 9000.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Valid rule</p>
                <p>           System maintained field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.BAL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field is used to specify the new balance amount for the corresponding balance type when we capture new balance type or when we adjust an existing balance type. This is a signed field. Sign given here will be corresponding to the Product Line of the underlying product.  For write off activities, system will default zero in this field. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Example:</p>
                <p>      When we want to capture a penalty interest, say a debit balance of 100, from legacy system for a lending product, the value given here would be -100. Subsequently, when the balance is to be adjusted such that the new balance amount is say 500, then a value -500 has to be given here.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Standard t24 amount field</p>
                <p>           can be signed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.BANK.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the BANK’s new bill amount for the given property. For the amount defined here would be issued and made due during capture bill activity. This field can also be used to give a BANK’s new bill property amount when we adjust existing bills. For write off activities, system will default zero in this field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rules</p>
                <p>           Standard t24 amount field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJ.BAL.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For each capture or adjusted property, the corresponding balance type is specified in this field. The balance given here should be non-bill related balance type that are not currently linked to the arrangement (Prefixes that are not AGE or DUE).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Should be a valid record in AC.BALANCE.TYPE</p>
                <p>           cannot be a bill related balance type</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.BILL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the new bill amount. This amount would be the sum of all the properties amount for all the payment types.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>          Validation rule</p>
                <p>          Standard T24 amount field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.PROP.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the new bill amout for the given property. For the amount defined here would be issued and made due during capture bill activity. This field can also be used to give a new bill property amount when we adjust existing bills. For write off activities, system will default zero in this field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rules</p>
                <p>           Standard t24 amount field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEW.SUS.PROP.AMT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
                <p/>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJ.BANK.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the bill adjustment for BANK amount  for the given property. This can be signed. Sign given here signifies if we are decreasing or increasing the bill property amount.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>    Example:</p>
                <p>    A bill for loan product, which has constant payments, is captured with a monthly repayment amount of 10000, in which the principal part is say 3000 and interest part is 7000. Suppose, the interest amount is to be increased by say 500, then a value of -500 has to be given here, which would increase the Interest amount to 7500.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rules</p>
                <p>           Standard t24 signed amount field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OR.BANK.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the BANK original amount of a given property for a payment type.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Standard T24 amount field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OR.BILL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the total original bill amount. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Standard T24 amount field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OR.PROP.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the original amount of a given property for a payment type.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Standard T24 amount field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIG.BAL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the original balance amount for each balance type given. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Valiadtion rule</p>
                <p>           Standard T24 amount field. </p>
                <p>           System maintaine field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OS.BANK.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>             This field represents the BANK outstanding bill  amount of a given property for a payment type.</p>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             Standard T24 amount field</p>
                <p>             System maintained field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OS.BILL.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>              This field represents the outstanding bill amount of  the bill</p>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             Standard T24 amount field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OS.PROP.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>             This field represents the outstanding bill  amount of a given property for a payment type.</p>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             Standard T24 amount field</p>
                <p>             System maintaine field. </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OS.SUS.PROP.AMT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJ.PROP.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the bill adjustment amout for the given property. This can be signed. Sign given here signifies if we are decreasing or increasing the bill property amount.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>    Example:</p>
                <p>    A bill for loan product, which has constant payments, is captured with a monthly repayment amount of 10000, in which the principal part is say 3000 and interest part is 7000. Suppose, the interest amount is to be increased by say 500, then a value of -500 has to be given here, which would increase the Interest amount to 7500.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rules</p>
                <p>           Standard t24 signed amount field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>              This field represents the total payment amount for a given payment type in the bill. The sum of NEW.PROP.AMT for the list of properties under the payment type should be equal to the PAYMENT.AMOUNT</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             Standard T24 amount field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>              This field denotes the payment date of the bill. The payment date should not be less than the original contract date defined during takeover of the contracts (arrangement) from legacy system. It cannot be less than the Bill date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             Standard T24 date field         </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>              Once the Payment Type has been specified, the user can specify whether the amount will be Due (to or from the customer) or Capitalised. Currenty only option allowed is DUE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>              T24 provides a mechanism (AA.PAYMENT.TYPE) by which users can define that standard payment types that can be used by a product.  A payment type is required for every payment schedule definition</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             1) Should be a valid record id in the file AA.PAYMENT.TYPE</p>
                <p>             2) Should only be the payment types defined in the payment schedule property of the arrangement taken  </p>
                <p>                  over.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>Allowed values are</p>
                <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
                <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
                <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
                <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJ.SUS.PROP.AMT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
                <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
                <p>Condition id</p>
                <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
                <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>              For each Payment definition the user must specify the Properties with amounts to be paid. The properties defined here should be only those defined in payment schedule property of the arrangement taken over. All the mandatory and allowed properties of the payment types need to be defined</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             Should be a valid record id of the file AA.PROPERTY.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESTRICT.PROP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denote for which Properties system should not allow the user to adjust property amount.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Cannot be duplicated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Should be valid record in AA.PROPERTY file.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESTRICT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denote for which Balance Types system should not allow the user to adjust Balance amount.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Cannot be duplicated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Should be valid record in AA.PROPERTY file.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJUST.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field describes overall reason for the adjustment entry being passed.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Upto 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WOF.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field allows to do partial write off a balance amount. It indicates that the corresponding balance needs to be written off partially. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rules</p>
                <p>           Standard t24 amount field</p>
                <p>           Write Off Amount should not be greater than the original balance amount.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WOF.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes for which property Write Off Activity can be triggered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Cannot be duplicated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Should be valid record in AA.PROPERTY file.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WRITE.OFF</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This fields speficies whether to write off a balance amount. Currently when a value of YES is given in this field, it indicates that the corresponding balance needs to be written off. In future this field will be changed to give descriptive meaning for various types of write off.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rule</p>
                <p>        Upto 15 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJUST.DIFF.ACC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This Field denotes Account number which are used while adjusting Balance Amount.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Validation rule</p>
                <p> Should be valid record in ACCOUNT file.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WRITE.OFF.BILL</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This fields speficies whether to write off an entire bill amount. Currently when a value of YES is given in this field, it indicates that the entire bill will be written off. In future this field will be changed to give descriptive meaning for various types of write off.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule</p>
                <p>           Upto 15 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJUST.PROP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the properties for which balances are to captured or adjusted. Cannot be duplicated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>           Should be valid record in AA.PROPERTY file.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BANK.PAYMENT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>              This field represents the total BANK payment amount for a given payment type in the bill. The sum of NEW.BANK.AMT for the list of properties under the payment type should be equal to the PAYMENT.AMOUNT</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             Validation rule</p>
                <p>             Standard T24 amount field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    <t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
