<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRD.PRF.AC.GENERAL.CHARGE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This table is used to specify for groups of Accounts which charges are to</p>
            <p>     be levied. </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Charges fall into 2 types, those that are levied at the same time as debit</p>
            <p>     interest is applied (Interest Related Charges) and those which are</p>
            <p>     considered to be fees for maintenance of an Account (Ledger Fee Charges).</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If the Account has maintained a higher balance than that specified,</p>
            <p>     calculated charges can be waived.  Separate sets of balance level details</p>
            <p>     are specified for Interest Related Charges and for Ledger Fee Charges.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Interest Related Charges</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Interest Related Charges include DEBIT.INT.ADDON, GOVERNMENT.MARGIN,</p>
            <p>     HIGHEST.DEBIT Charge and INTEREST.STATEMENT Charge.  DEBIT.INT.ADDON,</p>
            <p>     GOVERNMENT.MARGIN and HIGHEST.DEBIT are charged when debit one interest is</p>
            <p>     applied.  Either DEBIT.INT.ADDON or HIGHEST.DEBIT may be charged but not</p>
            <p>     both.  INTEREST.STATEMENT Charge is levied each time debit one interest</p>
            <p>     is applied.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     In each case the rates applicable are those ruling on the date of debit</p>
            <p>     one interest capitalisation.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Ledger Fee Charges</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Ledger Fee Charges may be applied monthly, quarterly or half yearly as</p>
            <p>     specified in the Company record, always at the end of a calendar month.</p>
            <p>     The charges can be based on Balance Requirement, Number of Credits, Number</p>
            <p>     of Debits, Turnover of Credits, Turnover of Debits and non immediate</p>
            <p>     Transaction charges depending on the Transaction Codes.  Either the number</p>
            <p>     of credits and debits or the turnover figures can be charged, but not</p>
            <p>     both.  It is possible to combine all these charges into one charge.  A</p>
            <p>     notional amount of credit interest may be calculated and deducted from the</p>
            <p>     charge amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     In each case the charges effective on the date of the charges</p>
            <p>     capitalisation are applicable for the whold of the capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     A waive marker may be set in Account records to indicate that charges</p>
            <p>     should be calculated but not applied.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     No Ledger Fee Charges are calculated on balances and activity in the</p>
            <p>     month in which an Account is opened or closed, (unless the Account Closure date is the last day of the month).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
            <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Profit and Loss entries</p>
            <p>     generated for combined Charges.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p> (1) 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OF.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge per</p>
            <p>     chargeable debit entry.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If 'Y' is specified in COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT, the numbers of debit and credit</p>
            <p>     entries are combined and one charge is calculated using the details in the</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.CREDIT record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table</p>
            <p>     corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in the TURNOVER.CHARGE</p>
            <p>     field.  Reversal entries are subtracted.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.OF.FCY.ACCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether the charges defined in BAL.REQUIREMENT,</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.CREDIT,</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE</p>
            <p>     apply to all Accounts, or only to Accounts in local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     'Y' means the charges apply to all Currencies.  'N' or 'NO' means they</p>
            <p>     apply only to local currency Accounts.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 'Y', 'N' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating</p>
            <p>     Highest Debit charges.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Highest Debit is a flat percentage charge calculated on</p>
            <p>     the Highest Debit balance during each Capitalisation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     This charge is similar to DEBIT.INTEREST.ADDON. They cannot both be</p>
            <p>     specified.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 0-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Day Basis for calculating notional credit</p>
            <p>     interest for offsetting charges, for Accounts in the</p>
            <p>     Currency specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL,</p>
            <p>     DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE is used</p>
            <p>     to specify details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for</p>
            <p>     Accounts in specific Currencies.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in</p>
            <p>     DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and</p>
            <p>     DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in</p>
            <p>     OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is defined, the Average or Minimum</p>
            <p>     Balance for the application period is determined (depending on OFFSET.BAL.TYPE) and the notional credit interest is calculated using the</p>
            <p>      PERCT.FOR.OFFSET as the rate and the Day Basis defined in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      If A (360/360) or F (360/360) is specified each month will be treated</p>
            <p>      as having 30 days.  In months with 31 days, the 30th is ignored, and</p>
            <p>      in February the last day is counted as 3 days, or 2 in a leap year.</p>
            <p>      __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>         (1) 'A 360/360', 'B 366/360', 'E 366/365' or 'F 360/365' or</p>
            <p>             'A', 'B', 'E' or 'F'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOW.AMT.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the smallest amount of charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT,</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and</p>
            <p>     STATEMENT.CHARGE, which will be booked, for Accounts in the Currency</p>
            <p>     specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY.  If calculated charges are</p>
            <p>     less than this amount they will be waived.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL,</p>
            <p>     DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used to specify details</p>
            <p>     for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific</p>
            <p>     Currencies.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in</p>
            <p>     DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and</p>
            <p>     DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies for which there is</p>
            <p>     no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and</p>
            <p>     LOW.AMT.CHARGE.</p>
            <p>     Depending on CHARGE CODE LEVEL, individual or combined charge amounts</p>
            <p>     calculated.  If the result is less than the amount specified in this</p>
            <p>     field, the charge is waived.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CHRG.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Currency of the Balance in the associated INT.CHARGE.BAL. For Accounts in Currencies with no input in this field, the Default Balance in local currency, INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL is used. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    INT.CHARGE.CCY and INT.CHARGE.BAL are used to define the required Balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges on Accounts in specific Currencies. For any Accounts in Currencies not specified in this field, the Default (Local Currency Equivalent) Balance specified in INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL is used. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    (1) 3 type SSS (SWIFT) characters Currency Code or (2) 1-3 numeric characters (will be converted to Currency code). Multivalue field associated with INT.CHARGE.BAL. (Optional input). It must be a valid code on the CURRENCY table (Ref: General Tables).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
            <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
            <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CHRG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the required Balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges for Accounts in the Currency specified in the associated INT.CHARGE.CCY. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    INT.CHARGE.BAL and INT.CHARGE.CCY are used to define the required Balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges in specific Currencies. The Default Balance (in local currency) in INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL is used if there are no details in INT.CHARGE.BAL and INT.CHARGE.CCY for the Currency of the Account. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Depending on INT.CHRG.BAL.TYPE, the Minimum or Average balance for the interest Capitalisation period is calculated. If this is not less than the required Balance, Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges are waived. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. Multivalue field associated with INT.CHARGE.CCY. (Mandatory input if INT.CHARGE.CCY is input, otherwise not allowed). The number of decimals allowed depends on the Currency in the associated INT.CHARGE.CCY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERCT.FOR.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies a rate for calculating notional credit interest for offsetting</p>
            <p>     against Charges specified BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT,</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Notional credit interest for offsetting charges is calculated using the</p>
            <p>     credit balances during the application period, the balance type (Average</p>
            <p>     or Minimum) specified in OFFSET.BAL.TYPE and the Percentage rate specified</p>
            <p>     in PERCT.FOR.OFFSET.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The Day Basis (360/360, 366/365 etc.) and Minimum Balance for calculating</p>
            <p>     offset can be defined for specific Currencies in the multivalue associated</p>
            <p>     group of Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.OFFSET and</p>
            <p>     LOW.AMT.CHARGE.  For Accounts in Currencies with no details in these</p>
            <p>     fields, the DEFAULT DAY BASIS and DEF BAL NO OFFSET are used.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       (1) Up to 10 numeric characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the balance (in local currency equivalent) required before offset interest is calculated for Accounts in Currencies with no details in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies may be specified in the multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    The Average or Minimum Balance for the application period is determined (depending on OFFSET.BAL.TYPE) and converted to local currency. If the result is less than the value specified in this field, no offsetting credit interest is calculated. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input if PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is defined, otherwise not allowed.) The number of decimals allowed depends on local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
            <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
            <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge property</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>GOVERNMENT.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating</p>
            <p>     Government Margin charges.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Government Margin is a supplementary flat percentage</p>
            <p>     charge on debit balances calculated by the system on Debit Interest</p>
            <p>     Capitalisation date and collected on behalf of the Government.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 0-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STATEMENT.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge for the</p>
            <p>     issue of account statements.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Specifies which ACCT.STATEMENT.CHARGE record is to be used to determinne</p>
            <p>     the charges for the issuing of account statements.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRANS.CODE.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether charges per entry should be calculated using the charge</p>
            <p>     records applicable to each Transaction code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables) specifies the</p>
            <p>     TRANSACTION.CHARGE record applicable to each Transaction code.  No charge</p>
            <p>     is calculated unless the IMMEDIATE.CHARGE field on the Transaction record</p>
            <p>     is 'NO'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If there is an entry in COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE, the charges are accumulated</p>
            <p>     into one charge amount and the Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts in the</p>
            <p>     record specified in COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE are used.  Otherwise the charges</p>
            <p>     for each Transaction Code are processed separately using the Free, Minimum</p>
            <p>     and Maximum amounts in the individual Transaction Charge records.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 'Y', 'N' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Can accept the following types:</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Key  Days/Denominator  </p>
            <p>    A  360/360  </p>
            <p>    B  366/360  </p>
            <p>    C  366/366  </p>
            <p>    D  360/366  </p>
            <p>    E  366/365  </p>
            <p>    F  360/365  </p>
            <p />
            <p>    For illustrations of all supported </p>
            <p />
            <p>    INTEREST.BASIS</p>
            <p />
            <p>    Specifies the Day Basis for calculating notional credit interest for offsetting charges of Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies may be specified in the multivalue group of associated OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    If PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is defined, the Average or Minimum Balance for the application period is determined (depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE) and the notional credit interest is calculated using the PERCT.FOR.OFFSET as the rate and the Day Basis defined in this field. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>    Valid input is A, B, C, D, E, or F.</p>
            <p />
            <p>    (Mandatory input if PERCT.FOR.OFFSET is input, otherwise not allowed).</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TURNOVER.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge</p>
            <p>     depending on the total value of chargeable credit entries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The charge is calculated as a percentage of the total value of chargeable</p>
            <p>     entries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If 'Y' is specified in COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT the total value of chargeable</p>
            <p>     debit and credit entries is charged using the details in the</p>
            <p>     TURNOVER.CREDIT record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table (Ref:</p>
            <p>     General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in</p>
            <p>     TURNOVER CHARGE field.  Reversal entries are subtracted.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TR.CODE.DR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Transaction Code to be assigned to Account entries</p>
            <p>     generated for combined Charges.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p> (1) 1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. </p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFSET.CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the Currency of Accounts for which the details in MIN.AV.BAL,</p>
            <p>     DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for waiving charges</p>
            <p>     and calculating offsets.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The multivalue group of associated Fields MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS,</p>
            <p>     BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used to specify details for waiving</p>
            <p>     charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     For Accounts in Currencies with no details specified in OFFSET.CURRENCY,</p>
            <p>     MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE, the default</p>
            <p>     values (in local currency equivalent) specified in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL,</p>
            <p>     DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) characters Currency Code or 1-3</p>
            <p>            numeric characters Numeric Currency Code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NUMBER.OF.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge per</p>
            <p>     chargeable credit entry.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If 'Y' is specified in COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT), the number of debit and credit</p>
            <p>     entries are combined and one charge is calculated using the details in the</p>
            <p>     Number of Credit record specified.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table (Ref:</p>
            <p>     General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in</p>
            <p>     TURNOVER.CHARGE.  Reversal entries are subtracted.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TURNOVER.DEBIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating a charge</p>
            <p>     depending on the total value of chargeable debit entries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The charge is calculated as a percentage of the total value of chargeable</p>
            <p>     entries.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If 'Y' is specified in COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT the total value of chargeable</p>
            <p>     debit and credit entries is charged using the details in the</p>
            <p>     TURNOVER.CREDIT record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table (Ref:</p>
            <p>     General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in the</p>
            <p>     TURNOVER.CHARGE field.  Reversal entries are subtracted.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 1-2 numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the local currency equivalent of the balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement charges for Accounts in Currencies with no Balance specified in Fields INT.CHARGE.CCY and INT.CHARGE.BAL. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Depending on Field INT.CHRG.BAL.TYPE, the Minimum or Average balance for the interest Capitalisation period is calculated. If there is an entry in Field INT.CHARGE.CCY for the Currency of the Account, the result is compared with the balance in the corresponding INT.CHARGE.BAL. Otherwise, the result is converted to local currency and compared with the Default Balance in this field. If it is not less, any Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit or Interest statement charge is waived. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. [Optional input. Not allowed unless INT.CHRG.BAL. TYPE is specified. Default is no waiver.] The number of decimals allowed depends on local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
            <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HIGHEST.DEBIT.CHG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating the Highest Debit charge to be applied on the charge frequency. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Highest Debit is a flat percentage charge that is calculated based on the Highest Debit balance on the account. The balance used depends on the way the COMPANY record has specified the CALCULATION.METHOD. If this field has been set up with monthly calculation, then the balance of each month is used for calculating the charge and so on. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    This is an optional field. If entered the field must point to a valid HIGHEST.DEBIT record.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEBIT.INT.ADDON</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating</p>
            <p>     Debit Interest Addon charges.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Debit Interest Addon is a supplementary flat</p>
            <p>     percentage charge which is applied to the overdraft interest amount</p>
            <p>     calculated by the System on Capitalisation date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Note:      Debit Interest Addon is not applicable to the 2nd type</p>
            <p>                of Debit Interest defined in fields prefixed 'DR2' in</p>
            <p>                Group and Account Debit Interest records.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     This charge is similar to HIGHEST.DEBIT. They cannot both be specified</p>
            <p>     for the same Account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     (1) 0-2 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
            <p />
            <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
            <p />
            <p>OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
            <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MANDATORY</p>
            <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMB.DEBIT.CREDIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether charges for debit and credit entries specified in</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT and TURNOVER.DEBIT</p>
            <p>     should be calculated separately or combined.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If 'NO' is specified, debit and credit charges are calculated separately,</p>
            <p>     otherwise a combined charge is calculated using the credit charge details</p>
            <p>     specified in NUMBER.OF.CREDIT or TURNOVER.CREDIT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     An entry is chargeable if the record on the TRANSACTION table (Ref:</p>
            <p>     General Tables) corresponding to the Transaction Code contains 'Y' in the</p>
            <p>     TURNOVER.CHARGE field.  Reversal entries are subtracted.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If there is any input in NUMBER.OF.DEBIT or TURNOVER.DEBIT, 'NO' must be</p>
            <p>     specified.</p>
            <p>      (1) 'Y', 'N' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether charges (BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT,</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE)</p>
            <p>     should be added together into one total before checking against balances,</p>
            <p>     smallest charge etc. or whether each charge should be checked and applied</p>
            <p>     individually.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If 'IND' is specified, the details specified in each of the tables</p>
            <p>     relating to the charges listed above are used to calculate the charges,</p>
            <p>     make adjustments for Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts, calcualte tax</p>
            <p>     where applicable and generate separate transactions for each charge.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If 'COM' is specified, the details defined in each of the tables are used</p>
            <p>     to calculate the amount of each charge, but the results are added together</p>
            <p>     to generate one transaction for the total charge, using details in</p>
            <p>     CATEGORY, TR.CODE.CR, TR.CODE.DR and COMBINED.TAX.CODE to determine</p>
            <p>     Transaction Codes and profit and loss Category and to Calculate Tax on the total charge if appropriate.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      Offset amounts, minimum charge, etc. are applied to each transaction</p>
            <p>      generated.</p>
            <p>      __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>         (1) 'COM', 'IND' or an abbreviation thereof.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
            <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
            <p>Condition id</p>
            <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
            <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMBINED.TAX.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the Tax record containing details of Tax applicable to the combined Charge. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Note: If combined charges are specified (CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL = 'COM'), any Tax codes in the tables relating to the charges in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT are ignored. Only the Tax Code specified in this field is applicable. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Up to 2 numeric character Tax code. (Optional input if CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL is 'COM', otherwise not allowed.) There must be an existing record for this code on the TAX table (Ref: General Tables), with effective date less than or equal to the effective date of this record. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>WAIVE.CHRG.NEG.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies that all charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT,</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE</p>
            <p>     should be waived if the Account has a negative Balance at any time during</p>
            <p>     the calculation period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If this field contains Y, all charges specified in the fields listed above</p>
            <p>     are waived if the Balance is negative at any time during the calculation</p>
            <p>     period (even if it is only negative for one day).</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If CALCU STEP PERIOD specifies that charges are calculated in monthly</p>
            <p>     steps (M), the Balances are checked for each month separately and charges</p>
            <p>     waived for any month in which the Balance is ever negative.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If CALCU STEP PERIOD specifies that charges are calculated in one step for</p>
            <p>     the whole period (P) as specified in the Company record, all charges are</p>
            <p>     waived if the Balance is negative at any time during the whole period.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 'Y', 'N' or 'NO'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.AV.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the required Balance for waiving charges for Accounts in the</p>
            <p>     Currency specified in the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY.  The required</p>
            <p>     Balance may be the Minimum or Average Balance during the application</p>
            <p>     period, depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL,</p>
            <p>     DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used to specify details</p>
            <p>     for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific</p>
            <p>     Currencies.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in</p>
            <p>     DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and</p>
            <p>     DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in</p>
            <p>     OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The Average or Minimum balance for the application period is calculated(depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE).  If the result is not less than the</p>
            <p>     MIN.AV.BAL all charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT,</p>
            <p>     NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT,  TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE are</p>
            <p>     waived.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OFFSET.BAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies whether Average or Minimum balance should be used for</p>
            <p>     calculating notional credit interest for offsetting against charges or for</p>
            <p>     determining the required balance for waiving charges.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The Average or Minimum balance during the application period is used to</p>
            <p>     determine whether charges should be waived and whether notional credit</p>
            <p>     interest should be calculated to offset charges.  If notional credit</p>
            <p>     interest is calculated, the Average or Minimum balance is used in the</p>
            <p>     calculation.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 'AVERAGE' or 'MINIMUM' or any abbreviation thereof.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for processing Transaction Code</p>
            <p>     Charges accumulated under one charge.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The TRANSACTION table (Ref: General Tables) specifies the</p>
            <p>     TRANSACTION.CHARGE record applicable to each Transaction code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If there is an entry in COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE, the charges are accumulated</p>
            <p>     into one charge amount and the Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts in the</p>
            <p>     record specified in COMB.TRNS.CHRG.CDE are used.  Otherwise the charges</p>
            <p>     for each Transaction code are processed separately using Free, Minimum and</p>
            <p>     Maximum amounts in the individual Transaction Charge records.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 1-3 numeric characters Transaction Charge code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CHRG.BAL.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Used in conjunction with Fields INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL, INT.CHARGE.CCY and INT.CHARGE.BAL to specify a balance for waiving Debit Interest Addon, Highest Debit and Interest Statement Charges. This field specifies whether a Minimum or Average balance is required. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Depending on this field, the Minimum or Average balance for the interest Capitalisation period is calculated. If this is not less than the appropriate balance specified in Fields INT.CHARGE.DEF.BAL, INT.CHARGE.CCY and INT.CHARGE.BAL then any DEBIT.INTEREST ADDON, HIGHEST.DEBIT or INTEREST.STATEMENT charge is waived. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    'MINIMUM' or 'AVERAGE' or any abbreviation thereof. (Optional input, if any input in DEBIT.INT.ADDON, GOVERNMENT.MARGIN, HIGHEST.DEBIT or INTEREST.STATEMENT. Otherwise not allowed.)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the required Balance (in local currency equivalent) for waiving charges for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. The required Balance may be the Minimum or Average Balance during the application period, depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts, in specific Currencies may be specified in the multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    The Average or Minimum balance for the application period is calculated (depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE) and converted to local currency equivalent. If the result is not less than the DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BALl all charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE are waived. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input if OFFSET.BAL.TYPE is input, otherwise not allowed. Default is no waiver.) The number of decimals allowed depends on local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the smallest amount (in local currency equivalent) which will be booked for charges specified in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT, NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE. If calculated charges are less than this amount they will be waived. The information in this field is only used when processing Accounts in Currencies for which no defaults are specified in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Details for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific Currencies may be specified in the multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies for which there is no input in OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE. </p>
            <p />
            <p>    Depending on CHARGE.CODE.LEVEL, individual or combined charge amounts are converted to local currency equivalent. If the result is less than the amount specified in this field, the charge is waived. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>    0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point. (Optional input. Default is no waiver.) The number of decimals allowed depends on local currency.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.STATEMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating Interest</p>
            <p>     Statement charges.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Some customers require a detailed Interest Statement each time interest is</p>
            <p>     applied.  The Interest Statement charge is a fixed amount which may be</p>
            <p>     applied each time debit interest is applied.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 0-2 numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.NO.OFFSET</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies the balance required for calculating notional credit interest</p>
            <p>     for offsetting against charges, for Accounts in the Currency specified in</p>
            <p>     the corresponding OFFSET.CURRENCY.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The multivalue group of associated Fields OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL,</p>
            <p>     DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used to specify details</p>
            <p>     for waiving charges and calculating offsets for Accounts in specific</p>
            <p>     Currencies.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Default values (in local currency equivalent) defined in</p>
            <p>     DEFAULT.MIN.AV.BAL, DEFAULT.DAY.BASIS, DEF.BAL.NO.OFFSET and</p>
            <p>     DEF.LOW.AMT.CHARGE are used for Accounts in Currencies with no input in</p>
            <p>     OFFSET.CURRENCY, MIN.AV.BAL, DAY.BASIS, BAL.NO.CREDIT and LOW.AMT.CHARGE.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The Average or Minimum Balance for the application period is determined</p>
            <p>     (depending on the OFFSET.BAL.TYPE).  If the result is less than the valuespecified in this field, no offsetting credit interest is calculated.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 0-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.REQUIREMENT</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the record containing details for calculating</p>
            <p>     a maintenance charge depending on the balance in the</p>
            <p>     Account.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 1-2 numeric characters</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CALCUL.STEP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>  Specifies whether charges in BAL.REQUIREMENT, NUMBER.OF.CREDIT,</p>
            <p>       NUMBER.OF.DEBIT, TURNOVER.CREDIT, TURNOVER.DEBIT and STATEMENT.CHARGE</p>
            <p>       should be calculated once to cover the full charge period, as specified in</p>
            <p>       the Company record, or in monthly steps.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       If 'MONTHLY' is specified, Free, Minimum and Maximum amounts apply to</p>
            <p>       charges calculated for each month, otherwise the Free, Minimum and Maximum</p>
            <p>       amounts are only applied to the total charges for the period.</p>
            <p>       __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>          (1) 'MONTHLY', 'PERIOD' or any abbreviation thereof.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Category code to be assigned to Profit</p>
            <p>     and Loss entries generated for combined Charges.</p>
            <p>     __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>        (1) 4 or 5 numeric character Category code.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
