<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRD.PRF.AZ.DEPOSIT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This property class represents the DEPOSIT product for the module AZ in T24. This property class is used for classic products.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
            <p />
            <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
            <p />
            <p>OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
            <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MANDATORY</p>
            <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROLL.MAT.WRK.DAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates if the rolled over new maturity date should be a working day or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If the field is Yes, during rollover of loans &amp; deposits, if the new maturity date happens to be on a holiday, then the system shall set the new maturity date to the first working day after the rolled over date.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Assume that value date of AZ is 10th Aug 2005 &amp; maturity date is 15th Aug 2005 . Then during rollover, the system shall set Value date as 15th Aug &amp; new maturity date as 20th Aug.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the field is YES &amp; 20th Aug happens to be a holiday &amp; first working day after rollover is 22nd Aug , then new maturity date will be set to 22nd Aug.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If the field is NO, then new maturity date will still be 20th Aug only.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed values - YES,NO.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  NO &amp; null are treated the same.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESCHED.NOTICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the notice period in days for the corresponding reschedule type, for all the AZ accounts opened under this product.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For a particular type of reschedule, the reschedule notice will be linked and the reschedule event will happen after the expiry of reschedule notice.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The valid types of reschedules are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1. Rate Change 2. Lump sum Repayment 3. Redraw 4. Term Change 5. Frequency Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Note: At present, only Rate Change is supported. If the BASIC.INTEREST is changed today or for a forward date after the contract is input then this change is applied to the az.account after the number of days defined in this field. The BI change is processed during COB.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Multi value field associated with Reschedule Type</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input allowed only if reschedule Type is defined</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1-99 numeric character with period D, M or Y (Example: 15D, 01M)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Not applicable for credit card loans</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
            <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
            <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESCHED.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the types of reschedules for all the AZ accounts opened under this product, for the purpose of linking it with the notice of reschedule.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For a particular type of reschedule, the reschedule notice will be linked and the reschedule event will happen after the expiry of reschedule notice.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The valid types of reschedules are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1. Rate Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  2. Lump sum Repayment</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  3. Redraw</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  4. Term Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  5. Frequency Change</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Note: At present only Rate Change is supported.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Multi value field associated with Reschedule Notice</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
            <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EARLY.RED.MARGIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the margin rate of interest that has to be deducted from the eligible rate arrived for early redemption of deposit amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For example if margin is defined as 2, and for early redemption of a deposit the eligible interest was arrived as 9% after referring the interest table, then the final interest paid for this early redemption will be 7%</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Numeric Value.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OD.CATEGORY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the category code to which the account needs to be changed, if the deposit is matured based on certain conditions,</p>
            <p />
            <p>  like,</p>
            <p />
            <p>  1. MATURITY.INSTR and nominated account are not defined.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  2. MATURITY.INSTR is not defined but nominated account is defined and FINAL.MATURITY in AZ.ACCOUNT is not defined.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Should be a valid category defined in the CATEGORY table.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Range allowed: 1 to 9999</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.CLOSURE.FEE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the charges to be levied for pre-closure of the deposit / loan account or part withdrawal of deposit.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  These charges will be debited only if the pre-closure of the deposit / loan is done by using AZ.ACCOUNT. The withdrawals made through other channels like Teller or ATM, the system will not recognise the differential interest and the charges. In these cases, the pre-closure fee and differential fee are to be debited manually.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Should be a valid charge code defined under FT.CHARGE.TYPE or FT.COMMISSION.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PART.REDEMPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether a portion of the funds available in the fixed Deposit can be allowed for redemption, before the maturity date of the deposit.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'Y' is defined the accounts opened under this deposit product will have the facility of part redemption. If 'N' is defined, part redemption facility will not be available for deposit accounts opened under this product</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed only form FIXED deposit products.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROLLOVER.ACCTNG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies if accounting entries over the AZ.ACCOUNT need to be raised during rollover. This could be useful for passbook printing purposes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  For example,</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Let us assume that the deposit is for 5000.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the MATURITY.INSTR is 'AUTOMATIC ROLLOVER' then during rollover the following entries will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  A. Nominated account is given,</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Case 1. Rollover amount - 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr AZ.ACCOUNT 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cr Nominated a/c 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Cr AZ.ACCOUNT 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr Nominated a/c 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Case 2. Rollover amount - 6000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr AZ.ACCOUNT 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cr Nominated a/c 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Cr AZ.ACCOUNT 6000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr Nominated a/c 6000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Case 3. Rollover amount - 4000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr AZ.ACCOUNT 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cr Nominated a/c 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Cr AZ.ACCOUNT 4000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr Nominated a/c 4000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  B. No nominated account given,</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Case 1. Rollover amount - 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr AZ.ACCOUNT 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cr Internal a/c 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Cr AZ.ACCOUNT 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr Internal a/c 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Case 2. Rollover amount - 6000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr AZ.ACCOUNT 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cr Internal a/c 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Cr AZ.ACCOUNT 6000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr Internal a/c 6000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Create a TELLER.DEFAULT crediting AZ.ACCOUNT for 1000.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Case 3. Rollover amount - 4000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr AZ.ACCOUNT 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cr Internal a/c 5000</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Cr AZ.ACCOUNT 4000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Dr Internal a/c 4000</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Create a TELLER.DEFAULT debiting Internal account for 1000.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  MATURITY.DR txn code will be used on the debit side and ROLLOVER.CR txn code will be used on the credit side entries to AZ.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If nominated account is not provided then an internal account will be used. The category of the internal account need to be defined in ACCOUNT.CLASS application for 'AZROLLOVER' id.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed only if ACCT.SYNC is set to 'Y'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed only for FIXED type deposits.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PI.TABLE.TO.USE</field>
<desc>
            <p>In the case of early redemption of a deposit, either partial or full, the eligible interest rate will be based on the period for which the redeemed amount was in force. To find this eligible interest rate, the system has to refer either the current periodic interest table or the periodic interest table that corresponds to the opening date of the deposit or the lowest of these two rates or trigger a routine to get the interest rate.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed input are 'CURRENT' / 'OPENING' / 'LOWEST' / 'OTHERS'</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.CREDIT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the minimum credit balance that has to be held in accounts of this product, at any time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Amount field</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Negative value not permitted</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Applicable for credit balance type of accounts</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
            <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
            <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge property</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CREATE.TD.FOR.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to create TELLER.DEFAULT or not for the interest amount during part withdrawal(through TELLER) /Pre closure when till account is used as credit side account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  .</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If this value is YES then a TELLER.DEFAULT record will be created when a TELLER transaction is processed debiting an AZ.ACCOUNT Fixed Deposit. This will only be created when no nominated/interest liquidation is specified on the AZ.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If the field CREATE.TD.FOR.INT is NULL the interest will be credited to the credit side account irrespective of it being the till account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Validation rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Value of YES is permitted only for Deposits &amp; with Teller product installed in the company</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REPAYMENT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Repayment type of the All in One Accounts opened under this product. This type determines the way in which the loan / deposit account is to be repaid.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The repayment types available for loan accounts are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1. ANNUITY</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This type of loan has a fixed periodic repayment amount (the 'annuity') consisting of two variable components of principal and interest. The repayment amount is calculated at the start of the contract so that the principal will be fully repaid after the required number of repayments. Initially, repayments consist mostly of interest. However, as the contract progresses, the size of the principal component increases as the accrued interest reduces.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In All in One loan account, for defining a zero repayment at the start of the loan, for a fixed period, Annuity type of repayment can be defined in the schedule with amount as Zero.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  2. LINEAR</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Linear loans also have an interest and a principal component to their periodic repayments. In this case, however, the principal repayment amount remains fixed over the lifetime of the contract. The interest element reduces as the accrued interest on the reducing balance decreases. This leads to a repayment scheme whereby the total periodic repayment reduces over the lifetime of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  3. NONRED</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In NONRED type of loans, there is no regular repayment of principal, but only interest. The redemption of Principal will be done on maturity date of the loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In All in One account loans, the validations relating to Interest Only and Maximum Period interest only will not happen for this type of loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  4. OTHER</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Non structured repayments are handled under this type. Repayment of any amount on any dates are allowed, provided the total repayment amount is equal to principal.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  5.CREDIT CARD</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This type of Loan repayment type was added from G14.0.00. For this repayment type, the schedules are NO. When the repayment type is Credit Card the regular schedules are discarded, sub a/cs are created and new types of schedules like CI, CC are generated automatically.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Repayment types available for Deposit accounts are:</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  FIXED</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Deposit amount is accepted in a fixed lump sum and repaid as fixed amount either with interest accumulated or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  SAVING PLAN</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Deposit amount is accepted in a periodic basis and the principal is increased in a recurring manner till the end of a fixed term.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  1 to 12 Alpha characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input must be either 'ANNUITY', 'LINEAR', 'OTHERS', 'NONRED' or 'CREDIT CARD' for loan products and 'SAVINGS PLAN' or 'FIXED' for Deposit products.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Once defined and record authorised cannot be changed</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MULTI</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents whether multiple deposits are allowed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PAY.INT.AT.MAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is used to decide whether accrued interest has to be paid out or rolled over during rollover of a fixed deposit. Allowed values are YES or NO</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'YES' is defined, then during rollover, the accrued interest before rollover will be paid out .When final maturity is reached or maturity instruction is Payment to Nominated account, then interest will be paid to Nominated account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'NO' is defined, then interest will be rolled over along with the principal deposit amount by default. The amount of rolled over deposit can anyway be overridden by the rollover amount definition at AZ.ACCOUNT level</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
            <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
            <p>Condition id</p>
            <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
            <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.INSTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the maturity instruction for the deposit accounts opened under this product.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'Automatic Rollover' is specified the deposit will be rolled over with the same terms as that of the original deposit.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'Payment to Nominated Account' is defined here, on date of maturity the maturity amount will be credited to the nominated account specified in the deposit account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Partial Rollovers and rollover with additional amount are handled at account level.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Permitted values : 'Automatic Rollover' / 'Payment to Nominated Account'</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed only for FIXED type deposits</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PASSBOOK.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the id of TELLER.PASSBOOK that need to be used while printing passbooks for this product.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field provides a facility to define different passbook layouts for different products.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The id must be a valid id in TELLER.PASSBOOK.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If not defined then the id SYSTEM in TELLER.PASSBOOK will be used by default while printing passbooks.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRE.CLOSE.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A local routine with a valid PGM.FILE entry with PGM.TYPE set to 'S' can be attached in this field. This routine will be triggered when a part withdrawal or preclose of a deposit happens. If it is a multi deposit then this routine will be triggered for every sub account during preclosure / part withdrawal.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field is allowed only if PI.TABLE.TO.USE is set to OTHERS.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  The routine to be triggered will have to be input as 'LOCAL.ROUTINE(INTEREST.RATE)'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Where INTEREST.RATE is the rate that is returned from the routine. This rate will be used instead of EARLY.RED.MARGIN if any given.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SINGLE.LIMIT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field specifies the value that should be set in the SINGLE.LIMIT field in the ACCOUNT that is attached to this APP.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Input can be 'Y', 'N' or ''.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If input as 'Y' then the acct that is attached to the product parameter should also have the field single limit marked as yes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If input as 'N' or '' then the acct that is attached to the product parameter cannot have the field single limit marked as 'Y'. In this case all the AZ.ACCOUNT that are linked to the same limit must have REDUCE.LIMIT set to be the same.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Input can be either 'Y', 'N' or ''.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
            <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.DEP.FQU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the frequency of further credits to the deposit account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  In the case of deposits like Savings Plan, Recurring Deposit, this field is use for defining the frequency of future credits expected.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  For example, if M01 is defined here, regular monthly credits to the account are expected.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Type of input allowed are: D&lt;nn&gt;,W&lt;nn&gt;, M&lt;nn&gt;.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field and grace period field should have a rationale input i.e. Grace can't be Month. End while the deposit frequency is daily. This validation is valid from 14.2.00 with the introduction of period. end option in Grace period field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.INT.FQU</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the frequency for interest credit, for all deposit accounts opened under this product.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Example</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If 'M01' is defined here, this frequency will be defaulted to the deposit account of this product and interest will be credited / capitalised every month from the start date. This is acheived by defaulting the 'I' schedule into the az.account during creation.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If a liquidation account is defined in ACCOUNT then interest will be credited to that account as per this frequency. Otherwise the interest will be capitalised in the Deposit account itself</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'NM01' is defined here, then the interest will be paid out to the nominated account after capitalising it every month from the start date. This is acheived by defaulting the 'IN' schedule into the az.account during creation.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This field is also used during deposit rollover. Based on the setup done here either a 'I' or 'IN' schedule will be created during rollover. If this is not defined then the 'IN' schedule will be created on maturity after rollover.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Type of input allowed are: Dnn,Wnn, Mnn</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.INT.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the type by which the credit interest frequency will be processed for the deposit accounts opened under this product.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  This field is associated with CR.INT.FQU ( frequency for interest credit)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Allowed types are: ANNIVERSARY / PERIOD.END</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If ANNIVERSARY is defined then the credit interest frequency will be based on the opening date.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If PERIOD.END is defined then the credit interest will be based on the calendar end like month end.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
