<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This is the master table for designing any product which the financial Institution may wish to introduce. This is the table where users link the desired Properties (from AA.PROPERTY) to the appropriate conditions. The user may define Products conditionally available by specifying allowed currencies and through user-defined rules. </p>
            <p/>
            <p>                As economic conditions change over time, the characteristics of products are likely to change.  These changes will be entered as updated Defined Property records with new effective dates.  This method allows a change to be scheduled for a future date.  Additionally, back-dated changes can also be entered in the same fashion</p>
            <p/>
            <p>                In addition to dated changes of a single Defined Property, the Product Builder also allows a Product to be defined with “timed” changes of its conditions.  These timed changes are handled as either “product changes” (i.e.  an introductory product is set for a given period after which the arrangement will revert to a standard product) or as “condition changes” (i.e. a standard product property is linked to one Defined Property and after a period of time switches to a different Defined Property.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>                A key feature of the Product Builder is Product inheritance.  This allows for the creation of product families where derivatives of a generic product or sub-product can be quickly created by simply defining the delta (in terms of product conditions) between the new and existing product.  This means that where a Defined Property is not specifically defined it will be inherited from the parent product, grandparent product, etc. </p>
            <p/>
            <p>                Once a Product has been defined through the Product Builder it must be published to be made available for sale.  To publish a Product, T24 will effectively work its way down the Product hierarchy populating all the conditions on each characteristic according to the principal of inheritance described above.  These characteristics will then be recorded in the published catalogue.  If a change is then made to a higher-level product it will not be reflected in any derived products until the product catalogue is republished. Product management is handled by a different table - AA.PRODUCT.MANAGER.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ELIGIBILITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the eligibility of customers who can avail this product. Some products may be reserved/targeted at a specific level of customers. NOINPUT field. For use in future.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field provides a more detailed description of the Product being designed. TEXT field to allow multiple lines of description.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.ARR.LINK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.CALC.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.EFF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.EFF.BASE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PC.PRD.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the description of the condition defined in AA.PRODUCT.CONDITION for the property and condition combination</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PR.SOURCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the parent product that contains the condition for the associated calculation source property in IN.CALC.PR</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PR.VAR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PRD.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADVANCE.RATEFIX.PERIOD</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the parent product that contains the condition for the associated property in IN.PROPERTY</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.SR.BAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.SR.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.SR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INHERITANCE.ONLY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>T24 product builder follows a structured way of defining products. In addition to this structural hierarchy, the Product Builder enables the definition of “families” of products th</p>
                <p>            rough Product Inheritance.  This allows for a derivative of a product to be defined by simply specifying a “parent” product and any different conditions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Inheritance Only products do not undergo full proofing validations nor are they available for sale on their own. They are only abstract definition of a product which should be derived down the hierarchy to define the product in its entirety. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Validation Rule:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Accepts a value of YES/NO.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field stores the override raised while commiting the record . No input, system maintained field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PARENT.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A key feature of the Product Builder is Product inheritance.  This allows for the creation of product families where derivatives of a generic product or sub-product can be quickly created by simply defining the delta (in terms of product conditions) between the new and existing product.  This means that where a Defined Property is not specifically defined it will be inherited from the parent product, grandparent product, etc. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>            When a product is a derivative of another product, its immediate product may be stated in this field. The resolving of hierarchy would only happen during Proofing process and the resultant published record would have the full product structure of both the parent and the current conditions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Validation rule:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Should be a valid id in AA.PRODUCT.</p>
                <p>            The field cannot be changed for subsequent dated records.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.PRD.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the description of the condition defined in AA.PRODUCT.CONDITION for the property and condition combination</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRD.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field acts as a pointer to a defined set of conditions for the Property. While defining, it must be made sure that there exists a valid condition (AA.PRD.DES.XXX where XXX is the property class of the given property) on the date of this product record to avoid errors during product publishing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARR.LINK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field allows the user to define the link between the product designer and the arrangement.</p>
                <p>              The Product Builder supports 3 options in terms of how each arrangement will be affected by changes to its Product definition.  </p>
                <p>                      NON.TRACKING – Once the arrangement has been opened, all conditions for a specific Property will be set for the duration of the arrangement.  Subsequent changes to the “NON.TRACKING” product conditions will not affect the arrangement.</p>
                <p>                  TRACKING – The Product Conditions of a Property will contain values for all mandatory parameters.  At the arrangement level the user cannot change any of the conditions of the Property.  Throughout the duration of an arrangement any product level changes to a “tracking” property will be reflected in the arrangement.  </p>
                <p>                  CUSTOM.TRACKING – This type of arrangement property behaves in a similar way to “tracking” properties except that individual conditions can be input (within negotiation limits) at the arrangement level.  Any attributes, which have been input, will effectively become fixed for the duration of the arrangement.  All other attributes will track changes at the product property.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                  This field is Mandatory.</p>
                <p>                  This field is part of a multi value set of fields with PROPERTY,PRD.PROPERTY and EFFECTIVE. It is also part of a sub value group within this set with  PRD.PROPERTY and EFFECTIVE.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the name of the product which is being defined.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               NOINPUT, System maintained field. Used for Indexing on the product record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.DESIGNER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the id of the file AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER.  </p>
                <p/>
                <p>      The id is made up of two parts seperated by hypen. The first part can be alpha numeric character representing the name of the product and the second part defines the date from which the current definition of the product would be effective.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Today would be defaulted to the product name.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates which product group the current product belongs to. Product group defines a higher level of product definition which groups the classes and its properties whilst also deciding on the mandatory properties of the group.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               To create a new product, the user must specify either the PRODUCT.GROUP when defining a top-level product or the PARENT.PRODUCT when defining a sub-product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rule:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Maximum of 30 Alphanumeric characters</p>
                <p>           Must contain a valid entry in AA.PRODUCT.GROUP.</p>
                <p>           NOCHANGE field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents a property which forms part of this product. If a property is defined as Mandatory in its product group, it is mandatory that the property is defined on the product using the group or atleast should have been inherited from its parent.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               Valid AA.PROPERTY id.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.VARIATION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the balance on which calculation is based. SOURCE.BALANCE and SOURCE.PROPERTY are mutually exclusive fields. Either of the fields may be defined.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               Valid only if corresponding AA.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE in the field SOURCE.TYPE is BALANCE</p>
                <p>               Valid AC.BALANCE.TYPE id.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field represents the property on which calculation is based. SOURCE.BALANCE and SOURCE.PROPERTY are mutually exclusive fields. Either of the fields may be defined. Publishing process will ensure that the property defined here is also part of the product definition as a whole.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Currently not used and reserved for future.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               Valid only if SOURCE.TYPE is PROPERTY</p>
                <p>               Valid AA.PROPERTY id.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p> Key to the AA.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE application and used for calculating base balance for associated CALC.PROPERTY    </p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Should be a Valid record in AA.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE</p>
                <p>           When CALC.PROPERTY is stated, this field is mandatory.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VARIATION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VARIATION.DEFAULT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Some properties require calculations for them. For example, a Current Interest property may have to accrue interest at a specific rate on a specified amount. The base amount on which such calculations should happen is stated here. The field is associated with SOURCE.TYPE, SOURCE.BALANCE and SOURCE.PROPERTY fields.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           The property stated here would be validated in the proofing stage to verify if they actually belong to this product.</p>
                <p>           Must be a valid AA.PROPERTY id.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field Indicates the currency(ies) that are possible within this product. The input must be a valid record from the CURRENCY table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                 This is a multi value field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               Input in this field is mandatory only for financial products (Those products whose PRODUCT.LINE has LINE.ATTIB set as CCY eg: LENDING)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used only when the financial institution uses ELIGIBILITY property. For example, in ELIGIBILITY condition, there is an option to move to a default product if certain eligibility rules are not met. It is mandatory that such default products do not have any Eligibility checks themselves. So, when a product is flagged as DEFAULT.PRODUCT, it is mandatory that the product should NOT have any ELIGIBILITY property defined under it. This is checked when the product is proofed/published.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Options :</p>
                <p>YES - indicates this product could be used as a Default product for Eligibility rule failure.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field describes the product record and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                  This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                  This field is Mandatory.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the effective period after which the new property condition comes into effect.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              In addition to dated changes of a single Defined Property, the Product designer also allows a Product to be defined with “timed” changes of its conditions.  These timed changes may be defined as “condition changes” (i.e. a standard product property is linked to one Defined Property and after a period of time switches to a different Defined Property. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Valid Period field. </p>
                <p>           Valid Suffixes are W- Week, M-Month, Y- Year and D-Days</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE.BASE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represent the effective base of the new property condition. It will accept two values.</p>
                <p>1.	START</p>
                <p>2.	ANNIVERSARY</p>
                <p>START – Forward condition effective date is calculated by considering base date as value date of arrangement. In case disbursement has happens different date than new arrangement creation date then all existing START type conditions will be deleted and new conditions created based on disbursement date of the arrangement</p>
                <p>ANNIVERSARY – Forward condition effective date is calculated by considering base date as anniversary date which is exist in account property field ANNIVERSARY.  In case anniversary date has changed in life of the loan then all anniversary conditions will be deleted and new conditions created based on new anniversary date. </p>
                <p>ARRANGEMENT – It is default value of this field.  If user doesn’t select any one of above options then system will treat those are ARRANGEMENT type conditions.  Forward condition effective date is calculated by considering START.DATE of the arrangement. It will not be changed any of the time. </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the effective date from which these product conditions come into force.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               Noinput -System maintained field.</p>
                <p>               Valid date field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
