<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PROPERTY.CLASS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>A Product Line is described by the Property Classes which constitute it and those which do not.  </p>
            <p>                The “Lending” line and “Account” line will have a number of common classes such as “Interest” and “Charge” and at least one distinguishing class, which in the case of “Lending” could be an “Overdue” or “Credit Limit” class.  </p>
            <p/>
            <p>                The Property Classes and Product Lines which are available are defined by Temenos.  The financial institution uses these “building blocks” of functionality to construct the individual products which are available for sale to its customers.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>            The PROPERTY.CLASS definitions are released by Temenos and cannot be amended with the exception of the description fields.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>BALANCE.PREFIX</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A property class can hold related financial balances that are updated by the different activities allowed for that class. The system will derive the name of the associated balance based on the property name and a prefix representing the balance lifecyle stage.</p>
                <p> Field is associated with Product line This field holds the allowed prefixes for use in the balance type and should reflect the possible stages in the lifecycle. Values should be 3 alphanumeric. </p>
                <p>A value of AGE here denotes that the balance can move through multiple stages based on the OVERDUE property definitions. </p>
                <p>Possible values are: </p>
                <p>AVL - The available balance;CUR - The current or live value of the property balance;ACC - The current accrued balance for the property;DUE - The due balance for property;AGE - An aged balance where the prefix will be determined by the overdue status For example the a property called LOANINT would have an accrued balance (CURLOANINT) which then becomes due (DUELOANINT) and ages through stages ODA and ODB giving the balances ODALOANINT and ODBLOANINT. Input only allowed by Temenos.</p>
                <p>PAY – A new PAY&lt;Charge&gt; is available for lending product line. It indicates payable charge to customer.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CLASS.GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>  This field can be used for grouping of products. The list of groups available can be defined in the EB.LOOKUP file for AA.PC.GROUP. Used for enquiry and display purposes for filtering out the required classes.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEL.INFO.REQD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>    This field denotes whether delivery information is required for the property class. If this field is set to Y then delivery processing is done for the property class</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the AA.PROPERTY.CLASS and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the AA.PROPERTY.CLASS  in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>              Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Provides a detailed description of the AA.PROPERTY.CLASS</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>              Up to 50 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.LINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the Product line for which BALANCE.PREFIX is associated and accounting can be set as required or not in AA.PROPERTY.CLASS.ACTION</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These records are released by Temenos and cannot be created. These are the basic building blocks(components) of a product and Arrangement.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This multi-valued field controls attributes that a property of this class may or may not have.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            Valid options for this field are:</p>
                <p>                  CCY – The property conditions for the same product will vary by currency (e.g. interest and principal conditions). The product property condition definition (AA.PRD.DES.xxxxx) will contain the currency in the key. If CCY is not defined then the property will NOT be based on currency.</p>
                <p>                  DATED – The property conditions can vary by date and the relevant dated property definition should be used when performing processing. The product property condition (AA.PRD.DES.xxxxx) will contain an effective date in the record key. If DATED is not specified the record will not contain a date.</p>
                <p>                  MULTIPLE – Allows more than one property of that class to be defined for a single product. If MULTIPLE is not specified only one property of this class can be linked to an aa product.</p>
                <p>                  TRACKING – Certain property classes require that a property can or must be defined at the arrangement level. Other types of property (e.g. interest conditions) may be defined at the product level and the arrangements of that product simly 'track' the product definition and do not require any definition at the arrangement level. If TRACKING is not specified then a property of this class cannot be defined as a tracking property in the product definition.</p>
                <p>                 NON.TRACKING - Indicates that the properties belonging to this class should only have fixed link behaviour. In other words, these properties may not have CUSTOM.TRACKING or TRACKING link to the arrangement. </p>
                <p>                 OPT.CCY - Indicates that the properties may or may not have Currency component in them. But it needs to have a default non currency condition and when a explicit currency condition is not stated, it picks the default condition for processing. For example , CHARGE property supports OPT.CCY option.</p>
                <p>                TRACKING.ONLY - Indicates that the properties of this class can ONLY have tracking behaviour. Also, the properties of this class should be stated as PRODUCT.ONLY in AA.PROPERTY. Currently, ACTIVITY.PRESENTATION, ACTIVITY.API and ACCOUNTING are TRACKING.ONLY classes.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>ARRANGEMENT - This component has to be added to the product level but there are no specific attribute values at product condition/arrangement condition level. It can be triggered at the arrangement level only through activities.</p>
                <p>For example, BALANCE.MAINTENANCE.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    <t><field>K.TYPE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
