<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRD.PRF.ELIGIBILITY</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>ELIGIBILITY property class is currently used for ACCOUNTS, LENDING and DEPOSITS product line. </p>
            <p>This property class is used to evaluate eligibility of a customer for the product based on the rules defined. </p>
            <p>The eligibility evaluation will be triggered at a given frequency or when there is a static change for the customer. </p>
            <p>Upon any failure of a rule during eligibility review process, the arrangement will be moved from the current product to a default product as per the setup.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>Defining rules for Eligibility:</p>
            <p/>
            <p>1. EB.CONTEXT must have an entry for each T24 application, whose field values are used to evaluate a condition. </p>
            <p>2. Toolbox can be used as an external interface to create rules and save it to T24 so that XML format of the rules will be automatically downloaded to the applications EB.RULES.VERSION and EB.RULES in T24. </p>
            <p>3. Technically to communicate to T24 we need an entry in EB.RULE.GATEWAY for each rule(shouldn’t define more than one rule). ELIGIBILITY property class uses the id of EB.RULE.GATEWAY as a key to trigger rule engine.</p>
            <p/>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>FAILURE.RULE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a no input field. This field will be updated by the system with the rule id which failed on evaluation.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FAILURE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>During online while validating an arrangement, any rule failure can be reported through the two failure type options ERROR or OVERRIDE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It Contains the name of the product belongs to current proofed condition. It will be extracted from the first component of the record Key. It is system updated field. Input is not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It contains the name of the property belongs to current proofed condition. It will be extracted from the second component of the record key. It is system updated field. Input is not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It contains the currency of the current proofed condition.  Currency is optional one. It will be extracted from the third position of the record key. It is system updated field. Input is not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It contains the variation of the current proofed condition. It will be extracted from the fourth position of the record key. It is system updated field. Input is not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It contains the effective period from which this condition would effects on the arrangement.  It will be extracted from the fifth position of the record key. It is system updated field. Input is not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It contains the effective date of the proofed condition. It will be extracted from the sixth position of the record key. It is system updated field. Input is not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LAST.RUN.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a no input field. This field will be updated by the system with the date when rule evaluation last triggered.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGE.ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A valid input from AA.ACTIVITY only. If an activity is specified here, then this activity will be triggered instead of CHANGE.PRODUCT activity, on any rule failure during cob.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
                <p/>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIODIC.REVIEW</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether rules should be evaluated on a periodic basis. If set to YES, then REVIEW.FREQUENCY needs to be input. Allowed values are YES and NULL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will hold two values either DUE or CAPITALISE.This Field denote which application method(DUE or CAPITALISE)should be taken while applying periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will have to accept a valid T24 period.This Field will denote the application period for current application method.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
                <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation ules</p>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUST.STATIC.REVIEW</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether rules should be evaluated when there is any static change to the customer record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRD.CHANGE.REQUIRED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a no input field. This field will be updated by the system during rule evaluation as “YES” if CHANGE.PRODUCT has to be triggered.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REVIEW.FREQUENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the frequency at which rule evaluation process should be triggered.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ROLE.FAILURE.ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Associated with CUSTOMER.ROLE field, this indicates the system’s behaviour for a role specific rule failure during cob. The rule evaluation process will be triggered during cob based on the frequency or any static change to the customer record associated with the role.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ROLE.FAILURE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Associated with CUSTOMER.ROLE field, during online while validating an arrangement, any role specific rule failure can be reported through the two failure type options ERROR or OVERRIDE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ROLE.RULE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Role specific evaluation rule, associated with the CUSTOMER.ROLE field. Rule will be evaluated against the customers who belong to the role specified in associated CUSTOMER.ROLE field. </p>
                <p>Valid input from EB.RULE.GATEWAY only.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RULE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A Rule id must have a valid entry in EB.RULE.GATEWAY. This is an associated multi value field with FAILURE.TYPE and FAILURE.ACTION</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RULE.RESULT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is a no input field. This field will be updated by the system with the result of rule evaluation. The RULE.RESULT can be CHANGE.PRODUCT or IGNORE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER.ROLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is an associated multi-value field, the associated fields are ROLE.RULE, ROLE.FAILURE.TYPE and ROLE.FAILURE.ACTION. Apart from the default rule(s), Role specific rules can be defined. If an arrangement’s customer role finds a match with this role then the corresponding rule, failure.type and failure.action will be considered.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property classes</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ELIGIBILE.DEFAULT.PRD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The default product to which the arrangement has to be moved on rule failure during cob.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FAILURE.ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the system’s behavior for a rule failure during cob. The rule evaluation process will be triggered during cob based on the frequency or any static change to the customer. Valid options are CHANGE.PRODUCT and IGNORE. If CHANGE.PRODUCT is set, then during cob on rule failure, the arrangement will move to the default product specified.</p>
                <p>If IGNORE is set, then during cob on rule failure, arrangement will still remain under the current product only.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    <t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
