<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRD.PRF.AC.GROUP.INTEREST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The Group Interest  allows the specification of a calculation method of debit/credit interest for groups of accounts and provides the link to the GENERAL.CHARGE table where the charges applicable to the same groups of Accounts are specified. Account groups are determined automatically on the basis of Customer and Account details such as Residence, Sector, Account Category and Currency. At the time of Account input, reference is made to ACCT.GEN.CONDITION and CONDITION PRIORITY (Ref: General Tables) tables.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  - Interest can be calculated on a Daily, Average, or Highest balance basis using value dated balances.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  - Rates can be fixed or linked to Basic Rates plus or minus a Margin.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  - Different rates can be specified for different balance levels and may be linked to the same or different basic rates. The rates may apply to the whole of the balance or to the part between two balance levels.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>CR.INTEREST.TAX.MIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the amount of interest which can be earned tax free.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If the amount of credit interest earned in a capitalisation period is greater than this amount then tax, if defined, will be deducted. Note the interest minimum will be applied for CR and CR2 individually not for the sum of the two.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Debit interest can be used to offset the tax - see NET.TAX field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     19 numeric characters. (Optional)</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.OFFSET.ONLY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies that credit interest is to be calculated only for offset against</p>
            <p>        debit interest and not for crediting the Customer's Account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Input to this field has no effect unless the debit and credit</p>
            <p>        capitalisation dates are the same.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Note : Only the second type of Credit Interest (specified in the CR2</p>
            <p>               fields) may be used to offset the second type of Debit Interest</p>
            <p>               (DR2).</p>
            <p>        __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>           (1) 'Y'     -for offset only.</p>
            <p>               or blank -for application to the Account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RATE.CHANGE.ADVICE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field decides whether or not to produce advices for those accounts in the above group.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     YES Produce advices according to the value in</p>
            <p />
            <p>     ADVICE.TYPE</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     If no value is specified in the field</p>
            <p />
            <p>     ADVICE.TYPE,</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.MIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum debit interest value that will be posted to an account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>      Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) numeric characters</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.ACCR.OPEN.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field denotes whether the Account should receive any interest for the</p>
            <p>         month, if the account was opened within the dates specified for Minimum</p>
            <p>         balance type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>         If set to NO, then no interest will be applied if the account was opened</p>
            <p>         after the start date and before the end date. Setting the field to Yes</p>
            <p>         will allow the Account to receive interest according to the minimum</p>
            <p>         balance criteria.</p>
            <p>         __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>            (1) Optional input. Yes or No.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
            <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
            <p>Condition id</p>
            <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
            <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.ZERO.INT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates that credit interest will not be paid for the entire capitalisation period if the balance of the account falls below this value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>       Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p>       1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point and commas</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
            <p />
            <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
            <p />
            <p>OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
            <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MANDATORY</p>
            <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.NET.TAX</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether debit interest should be netted against the credit interest prior to calculating tax.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If this is set to Y (yes) then the debit interest due in the capitalisation period will be offset against the credit interest when tax is calculated. Note CR will be netted with DR and CR2 with DR2 and tax calculated individualy. Also the debit interest capitalisation frequency must match the credit in order for the netting to take place.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     1 Alpha - Y or N.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.MIN.WAIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A setting of Yes indicates that debit interest amounts below the minimum value, specified in DR.MIN.VALUE, are to be waived.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       If this field is set to No or Null, the minimum value, DR.MIN.VALUE, should be posted to the account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>        YES, NO or NULL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.INT.CALC.RND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of rounding to apply to individual credit interest calcualtions, i.e. the amount stored in the CR.INT.AMT field of either INFO.ACCT.CR, ACCR.ACCT.CR or STMT.ACCT.CR (or ...CR2).</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The default is to perform natural rounding relevant to the currency of the interest amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     NONE indicates that no rounding is to be applied to the caclculated interest amount. In this case the total interest will be the sum of the unrounded amounts, and then the total interest will be rounded. </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Any other value should be the key to an EB.ROUNDING.RULE record. This record will determine the type of rounding to be applied to the calculated interest amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Take the example of a currency with 2 decimal places, where the interest amounts are unrounded and the total is naturally rounded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt1 = 1.333 </p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt2 = 2.333</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt3 = 3.333</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The total interest will be 6.999 which will be naturally rounded to 7.00.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Now perform the same calculation with the interest amounts naturally rounded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt1 = 1.33</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt2 = 2.33</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt3 = 3.33</p>
            <p />
            <p>     total interest will be 6.99.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Alphanumeric field, can be:-</p>
            <p />
            <p>     blank = default natural rounding</p>
            <p />
            <p>     NONE = interest amount not rounded</p>
            <p />
            <p>     key to EB.ROUNDING.RULE to determine the type of rounding to apply.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.ZERO.INT.BAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates that credit interest 2 will not be paid for the entire calculation period if the balance of the account falls below this value.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p>     1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point and commas</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.LEGAL.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Maximum Legal Rate for this group.</p>
            <p>        __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>           (1) 1-10 type R (standard rate format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.MIN.WAIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A setting of Yes indicates that second credit interest amounts below the second minimum value, specified in CR2.MIN.VALUE, are to be waived.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      If this field is set to No or Null, the second minimum value, CR2.MIN.VALUE, should be posted to the account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>      YES, NO or NULL.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.OFFSET.ONLY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Specifies that credit interest is to be calculated only for offset against</p>
            <p>        the second debit interest (DR2) and not for crediting the Customer's</p>
            <p>        Account.  (CR2 fields specify a second interest which may be calculated.)</p>
            <p />
            <p>        Input to this Field has no effect unless the second debit (DR2) and second</p>
            <p>        credit (CR2) capitalisation dates are the same.</p>
            <p>        __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>           (1) 'Y'      - for offset only.</p>
            <p />
            <p>               or</p>
            <p />
            <p>               blank    - for application to the Account.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
            <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.DEBIT.CHG.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the maximum charge percentage of the first debit interest</p>
            <p>        amount. (e.g. 50%)</p>
            <p>        __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>           (1) 1-10 type R (standard rate format) characters plus a decimal point.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFER.DB.INT.DAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to allow the system to defer the debit interest posting to the account on which they are due in order to facilitate a means of notifying the customer of the details in advance. The number of days specified here will equal to the number of days in the notification period.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Must be input if the field DB.INT.PENDING.CAT has been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     3 alphanumeric characters - nnD or nnW format.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If nnC entered, then number of days is taken to be calendar days.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If nnW entered, then number of days is taken to be business days.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.ACCR.CLOSE.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes whether the Account should receive any interest for the</p>
            <p>        month, if the account was closed before the specified start date for the</p>
            <p>        MINIMUM balance type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        If set to NO, then no interest will be applied if the account was closed</p>
            <p>        before the start date. Setting the field to Yes will allow the Account to</p>
            <p>        receive interest up to the closure date according to the minimum balance</p>
            <p>        criteria, effectively making the closure date the end date for the minimum</p>
            <p>        balance requirements.</p>
            <p>        __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>           (1) Optional input. Yes or No.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.TAX.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies either a Tax record (defined in TAX table) or Tax.Type.Condition record with a "*" symbol prefixed to a valid tax.type.condition which specifies the calculation and processing of tax, applicable to debit interest. If tax rate is given then tax is calculated on the associated group of accounts. If a Tax Type Condition Identifier is specified, the system will derive the applicable TAX.CODE from the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION based on the customer grouping. (tax.type.condition allows to define different tax rates for different tax.gen.condition records). Input of tax.type.condition helps in deducting different rates of tax for different group of customers in the associated group of accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>      1-2 numeric characters. (Optional input. Not allowed if INTEREST.DAY.BASIS contains 'NONE'.) There must be an existing record for this code on the TAX table (Ref: General Tables) with an effective date not later than the effective date of this record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      For computation of tax JOINT HOLDER wise for an account based on their tax status, only a valid TAX.TYPE.CONDITION ID has to be specified along with a local routine in CALC.ROUTINE field. eg. *CGT has to be specified.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.ZERO.INT.OC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input into this field will determine whether any accounts opened or closed during the capitalisation period will have interest 2 paid. No or Null input will result in no interest being paid. Yes input will result in interest 2 being paid, obviously dependent upon the value in CR2.ZERO.INT.BAL.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Input only allowed if CR2.ZERO.INT.BAL is populated</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     3 alphabetic YES, NO or Null</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
            <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
            <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
            <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
            <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge property</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR2.MIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum second credit interest value that will be posted to an account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>       Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) numeric characters.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.INT.PENDING.CAT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field defines the category code to be used when forming a suspense account to which the debit interest settling on an account will be posted to when the field DEFER.DB.INT.DAYS has been specified. The amount posted into this suspense account will reversed after the notification period has been served.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Optional input.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Must be input if the field DEFER.DB.INT.DAYS has been entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If input must be a valid category code set up on the CATEGORY file.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If input must be in the range 10000-19999.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CORR.AT.CAP.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will determine if the correction processing on debit interest needs to be performed only on the capitalisation date of the account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     'YES' or 'NO'.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The field must be set to 'YES' when the deferred processing has been turned on.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.ZERO.INT.OC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Input into this field will determine whether any accounts opened or closed during the capitalisation period will have interest paid. No or Null input will result in no interest being paid. Yes input will result in interest being paid, obviously dependent upon the value in CR.ZERO.INT.BAL.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       Input only allowed if CR.ZERO.INT.BAL is populated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>       3 alphabetic YES, NO or Null</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
            <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.INT.TOT.RND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of rounding to apply to the total amount of debit interest, i.e. the amount stored in the TOTAL.INTEREST field of either INFO.ACCT.DR, ACCR.ACCT.DR or STMT.ACCT.DR. (Or ...DR2 )</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The default is to perform natural rounding relevant to the currency of the interest amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Any value entered should be the key to an EB.ROUNDING.RULE record. This record will determine the type of rounding to be applied to the calculated interest amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Take the example of a currency with 0 decimal places, where the interest amounts are unrounded and the total is rounded down.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt1 = 1.666 </p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt2 = 2.666</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt3 = 3.666</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The total interest will be 7.998 which will be rounded down to 7.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Now perform the same calculation with the interest amounts naturally rounded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt1 = 1</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt2 = 2</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt3 = 3</p>
            <p />
            <p>     total interest will be 6.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Alphanumeric field, can be:-</p>
            <p />
            <p>     blank = default natural rounding</p>
            <p />
            <p>     key to EB.ROUNDING.RULE to determine the type of rounding to apply.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.MIN.WAIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A setting of Yes indicates that credit interest amounts below the minimum value, specified in CR.MIN.VALUE, are to be waived.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       If this field is set to No or Null, the minimum value, CR.MIN.VALUE, should be posted to the account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>       YES, NO or NULL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.INT.TOT.RND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of rounding to apply to the total amount of credit interest, i.e. the amount stored in the TOTAL.INTEREST field of either INFO.ACCT.CR, ACCR.ACCT.CR or STMT.ACCT.CR. (Or ...CR2 )</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The default is to perform natural rounding relevant to the currency of the interest amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Any value entered should be the key to an EB.ROUNDING.RULE record. This record will determine the type of rounding to be applied to the calculated interest amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Take the example of a currency with 0 decimal places, where the interest amounts are unrounded and the total is rounded down.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt1 = 1.666 </p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt2 = 2.666</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt3 = 3.666</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The total interest will be 7.998 which will be rounded down to 7.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Now perform the same calculation with the interest amounts naturally rounded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt1 = 1</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt2 = 2</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt3 = 3</p>
            <p />
            <p>     total interest will be 6.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Alphanumeric field, can be:-</p>
            <p />
            <p>     blank = default natural rounding</p>
            <p />
            <p>     key to EB.ROUNDING.RULE to determine the type of rounding to apply.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.MIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum second debit interest value that will be posted to an account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>      Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DB.INT.CALC.RND</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the type of rounding to apply to individual credit interest calcualtions, i.e. the amount stored in the CR.INT.AMT field of either INFO.ACCT.CR, ACCR.ACCT.CR or STMT.ACCT.CR.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The default is to perform natural rounding relevant to the currency of the interest amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     NONE indicates that no rounding is to be applied to the caclculated interest amount. In this case the total interest will be the sum of the unrounded amounts, and then the total interest will be rounded. </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Any other value should be the key to an EB.ROUNDING.RULE record. This record will determine the type of rounding to be applied to the calculated interest amount.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Take the example of a currency with 2 decimal places, where the interest amounts are unrounded and the total is naturally rounded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt1 = 1.333 </p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt2 = 2.333</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt3 = 3.333</p>
            <p />
            <p>     The total interest will be 6.999 which will be naturally rounded to 7.00.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Now perform the same calculation with the interest amounts naturally rounded.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt1 = 1.33</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt2 = 2.33</p>
            <p />
            <p>     amt3 = 3.33</p>
            <p />
            <p>     total interest will be 6.99.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     Alphanumeric field, can be:-</p>
            <p />
            <p>     blank = default natural rounding</p>
            <p />
            <p>     NONE = interest amount not rounded</p>
            <p />
            <p>     key to EB.ROUNDING.RULE to determine the type of rounding to apply.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.TAX.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies either a Tax record (defined in TAX table) or Tax.Type.Condition record with a "*" symbol prefixed to a valid tax.type.condition which specifies the calculation and processing of tax, applicable to credit interest. If tax rate is given then tax is calculated on the associated group of accounts. If a Tax Type Condition Identifier is specified, the system will derive the applicable TAX.CODE from the TAX.TYPE.CONDITION based on the customer grouping. (tax.type.condition allows to define different tax rates for different tax.gen.condition records). Input of tax.type.condition helps in deducting different rates of tax for different group of customers in the associated group of accounts.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>      1-2 numeric characters. (Optional input. Not allowed if INTEREST.DAY.BASIS contains 'NONE'.) There must be an existing record for this code on the TAX table (Ref: General Tables) with an effective date not later than the effective date of this record.</p>
            <p />
            <p>      For computation of tax JOINT HOLDER wise for an account based on their tax status, only a valid TAX.TYPE.CONDITION ID has to be specified along with a local routine in CALC.ROUTINE field. eg. *CGT has to be specified.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.MIN.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The minimum credit interest value that will be posted to an account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     Up to 14 type AMT (standard amount format) numeric characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.ACCR.OPEN.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field denotes whether the Account should receive any interest for the</p>
            <p>         month, if the account was opened within the dates specified for Minimum</p>
            <p>         balance type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>         If set to NO, then no interest will be applied if the account was opened</p>
            <p>         after the start date and before the end date. Setting the field to Yes</p>
            <p>         will allow the Account to receive interest according to the minimum</p>
            <p>         balance criteria.</p>
            <p>         __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>            (1) Optional input. Yes or No.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.ACCR.CLOSE.AC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes whether the Account should receive any interest for the</p>
            <p>        month, if the account was closed before the specified start date for the</p>
            <p>        MINIMUM balance type.</p>
            <p />
            <p>        If set to NO, then no interest will be applied if the account was closed</p>
            <p>        before the start date. Setting the field to Yes will allow the Account to</p>
            <p>        receive interest up to the closure date according to the minimum balance</p>
            <p>        criteria, effectively making the closure date the end date for the minimum</p>
            <p>        balance requirements.</p>
            <p>        __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>           (1) Optional input. Yes or No.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.BALANCE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field represents the balance type for the credit interest. Should be a valid record in AC.BALANCE.TYPE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR2.MIN.WAIVE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A setting of Yes indicates that second debit interest amounts below the minimum second value, specified in DR2.MIN.VALUE, are to be waived.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       If this field is set to No or Null, the minimum second value, DR2.MIN.VALUE, should be posted to the account.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>       YES, NO or NULL.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.POST.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field can be used to define the interest posting period. Input in</p>
            <p />
            <p>     LAST.DAY.INCLUSVIE</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p>     Optional input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>     S Semi-annually</p>
            <p />
            <p>     A Annual</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ADVICE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field decides the type of advice produced for those accounts in the above group,</p>
            <p />
            <p>     provided the field</p>
            <p />
            <p>     RATE.CHANGE.ADVICE</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>APR.REQUIRED</field>
<desc>
            <p>This allows the user to specify whether the APR (TEG) calculation is</p>
            <p>        required.</p>
            <p>        __________________________________________________</p>
            <p />
            <p>           (1) 1-2 alpha characters.</p>
            <p />
            <p>               Valid values are "Y" and "NO".</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BAL.CALC.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p> A routine can be attached to calculated the balance on which the interest would be calculated. This field represents the routine name. Should be a valid record in EB.API file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
