<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PROPERTY.CLASS.ACTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Application to describe the Actions allowed for Property classes and specify if Accounting is valid for a product line or not.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PROP.CLASS.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p> Key to the application. Should be a Valid Property class and Action separated by 'Hyphen' .For eg - TERM.AMOUNT-INCREASE</p>
            <p> New records can be released only by Temenos</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p> Contains the Property class of ID component </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SHORT.DESC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Provides a short description of the AA.PROPERTY.CLASS.ACTION</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.LINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates to which product line is this action relevant. Certain actions may be exclusive only to certain lines. For example, ISSUE.PAYOFF would not exist for DEPOSITS/ACCOUNTS product lines since it is relevant only to Loans.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCOUNTING</field>
<desc>
            <p>When an ACTION is defined it may or may not generate an accounting event. This field indicates that the action could generate accounting movements for the associated Product Line</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Valid options are NULL, YES and NO. NULL and NO are same .</p>
            <p> If YES, then BALANCE.PREFIX must be present for Associated Product line in AA.PROPERTY.CLASS for the property class in ID.Component</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>An Action is performed on a property of the specified class as part of a business Activity. The actions that comprise an activity will depend upon the property, product line and type of business event being processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Examples of ACTIONS are ACCRUE, CALCULATE, CHANGE, DECREASE, DISBURSE, DRAW, INCREASE and UPDATE. The actions available will depend on the property class and its behaviour.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the AA.PROPERTY.CLASS.ACTION  and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>                This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the AA.PROPERTY.CLASS.ACTION  in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>              TEXT field. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

