<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRODUCT</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p />
            <p>     This is a live file built for every product. This file holds details of the proofed and published properties of the product on the latest date. At any given time one could view the list of properties proofed and cataloged for the product.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>PRF.PROPERTY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    This field denotes the successfully cataloged properties belonging to the product. This is a multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes the AA.PRODUCT record and is used for enrichment. This field is populated from AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER</p>
            <p>     This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     This field is Mandatory.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MB.ELIGIBLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>      This field represents the id of the file AA.PRODUCT. The id is the name of the product without its other attributes like currency and date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>     This field denotes the name of product group to which the product belongs to.Should be a valid product group id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRF.EXPIRY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>  This field denotes the expiry date when the product was last proofed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.PUBLISHED</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>     This field denotes the date when the record was last published.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ELIGIBILITY.FILTER</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRF.AVAILABLE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    This field denotes the available date when the product was last proofed</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.STATUS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>      This field denotes the current status of the product. If the product was proofed lately it will hold the value "PROOFED", similarly if the product was published lately it will hold the value "PUBLISHED"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CUSTOMER.NO</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVE.PRODUCTS</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p> Active products are defined </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.AVAILABLE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>  This field denotes the available date when the product was last cataloged.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.EXPIRY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>     This field denotes the expiry date when the product was last cataloged.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAT.PROPERTY</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>     This field denotes the successfully cataloged properties belonging to the product. This is a multivalue field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>PRODUCT.INTEGRITY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>PRODUCT.ERROR</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>REMEDY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
