<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRODUCT.PROOF</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>Once the product designed in AA.PRODUCT.DESIGNER has been proofed, the proofed record will be written to this file - AA.PRODUCT.PROOF. This file is read only.</p>
            <p>  Prior to proofing all records for this product will be removed.Product records are identified with a key of:</p>
            <p>  PRODUCT – Effective  Date</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ELIGIBILITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the eligibility of customers who can avail this product. Some products may be reserved/targeted at a specific level of customers. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>  For future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field provides a more detailed description of the Product being designed. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.ARR.LINK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.CALC.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.EFF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.EFF.BASE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PC.PRD.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the description of the condition defined in AA.PRODUCT.CONDITION for the property and condition combination</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PR.SOURCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the parent product that contains the condition for the associated calculation source property in IN.CALC.PR</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PR.VAR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PRD.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADVANCE.RATEFIX.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the parent product that contains the condition for the associated property in IN.PROPERTY</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.SR.BAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.SR.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.SR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"The fields starting with IN.PROPERTY to IN.SR.PR are used to show the conditions that are defined in the parent product. These fields will allow the user to see the conditions that are derived from the parent products during product design stage.</p>
                <p>Please refer to the corresponding fields helptext from PROPERTY to SOURCE.PROPERTY for more specific information"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INHERITANCE.ONLY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field determines whether the product is defined for inheritance purposes only and will not be available for sale.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PARENT.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the product will inherit properties from a parent product. If a product is selected in this field, the new product will inherit all properties that have not been specifially defined within it.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PC.PRD.PR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the description of the condition defined in AA.PRODUCT.CONDITION for the property and condition combination</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRD.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field acts as a pointer to a defined set of conditions for the Property. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARR.LINK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field defines the link between the product designer and the arrangement.</p>
                <p>  The Product Builder supports a number of options in terms of how each arrangement will be affected by changes to its Product definition. </p>
                <p>  To provide the highest level of flexibility, each set of Product Conditions on a Product are defined as fixed, tracking, or negotiable.</p>
                <p>  Fixed – Once the arrangement has been opened, all conditions for a specific Property will be set for the duration of the arrangement. Subsequent changes to the “fixed” product conditions will not affect the arrangement.</p>
                <p>  Tracking – The Product Conditions of a Property will contain values for all mandatory parameters. At the arrangement level the user cannot change any of the conditions of the Property. Throughout the duration of an arrangement any product level changes to a “tracking” property will be reflected in the arrangement. </p>
                <p>  Negotiable – This type of arrangement property behaves in a similar way to “tracking” properties except that individual conditions can be input (within negotiation limits) at the arrangement level. Any attributes, which have been input, will effectively become fixed for the duration of the arrangement. All other attributes will track changes at the product property.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  This field is part of a multi value set of fields with PROPERTY,PRD.PROPERTY and EFFECTIVE. It is also part of a sub value group within this set with PRD.PROPERTY and EFFECTIVE.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the name of the product which is being defined.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.DESIGNER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the id of the file AA.PRODUCT.CATALOG. The id should be a valid product. This file would be built after succesfull proofing of products</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates which product group the current product belongs to. Product group defines a higher level of product definition which groups the classes and its properties whilst also deciding on the mandatory properties of the group.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the property which forms part of this product. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.VARIATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the balance on which calculation is based.SOURCE.BALANCE and SOURCE.PROPERTY are mutually exclusive fields. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field represents the property on which calculation is based. SOURCE.BALANCE and SOURCE.PROPERTY are mutually exclusive fields. Either of the fields may be defined. Publishing process will ensure that the property defined here is also part of the product definition as a whole.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p> Key to the AA.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE application and used for calculating base balance for associated CALC.PROPERTY    </p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           Should be a Valid record in AA.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE</p>
                <p>           When CALC.PROPERTY is stated, this field is mandatory.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VARIATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VARIATION.DEFAULT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>All properties which require calculations on them are stated here. For example, a Current Interest property may have to accrue interest at a specific rate.</p>
                <p>  The field is associated with SOURCE.TYPE, SOURCE.BALANCE and SOURCE.PROPERTY fields.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field Indicates the currency(ies) that are possible within this product. The input must be a valid record from the CURRENCY table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  This is a multi value field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field describes the AA.PRODUCT.PROOF record and is used for enrichment. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the effective period after which the new property condition comes into effect.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  In addition to dated changes of a single Defined Property, the Product designer also allows a Product to be defined with “timed” changes of its conditions. These timed changes may be defined as “condition changes” (i.e. a standard product property is linked to one Defined Property and after a period of time switches to a different Defined Property. </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE.BASE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represent the effective base of the new property condition. It will accept two values.</p>
                <p>1.	START</p>
                <p>2.	ANNIVERSARY</p>
                <p>START – Forward condition effective date is calculated by considering base date as value date of arrangement. In case disbursement has happens different date than new arrangement creation date then all existing START type conditions will be deleted and new conditions created based on disbursement date of the arrangement</p>
                <p>ANNIVERSARY – Forward condition effective date is calculated by considering base date as anniversary date which is exist in account property field ANNIVERSARY.  In case anniversary date has changed in life of the loan then all anniversary conditions will be deleted and new conditions created based on new anniversary date. </p>
                <p>ARRANGEMENT – It is default value of this field.  If user doesn’t select any one of above options then system will treat those are ARRANGEMENT type conditions.  Forward condition effective date is calculated by considering START.DATE of the arrangement. It will not be changed any of the time. </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the effective date from which the product change comes into force.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
