<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRD.DES.TERM.AMOUNT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The TERM AMOUNT Property Class is used by all products which involve an amount of money that is lent or deposited for a specified period of time. This property class controls the commitment made by the bank and the customer.</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
                <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MATURITY.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will represent the end of availability for the committed loan amount.</p>
                <p>              This field will contain the date on which the committed loan amount will fully be repaid based on TERM and arrangement start date.</p>
                <p>              This field will be no input field at designer level. When a new arrangement is input maturity date will be calculated for the TERM from arrangement start date and will be defaulted.</p>
                <p>              Maturity date can be changed at the arrangement level. If maturity date is changed then TERM will be calculated in DAYS format.</p>
                <p>              If TERM and maturity date is present and TERM is changed then an internal maturity date will be calculated. If this date is not equal to the existing maturity date then TERM will be recalculated and updated in DAYS format.</p>
                <p>              If TERM is changed and maturity date has to be recalculated then existing maturity date should be cleared.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              Example :</p>
                <p>              Term                                  :  24M </p>
                <p>              Arrangement Start date    :  01st January 2007 </p>
                <p>              Maturity date                     :  01st January 2009 </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>              Standard Date format</p>
                <p>              No input field at designer level</p>
                <p>              Maturity date should be greater than today and should be greater than effective date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the total amount which will be lent or deposited for the term (i.e. the committed amount).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               In English Language text it is possible to use 'T' to indicate the thousands and an 'M' to indicate the millions. </p>
                <p>               e.g. INPUT VALUE</p>
                <p>               1T 1,000.00 </p>
                <p>               2M 2,000,000.00</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>               1-14 type AMT (standard amount format) characters plus a decimal point. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
                <p/>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ON.MATURITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>    This field is currently not in use and has no  functional impact   </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>Allowed values are</p>
                <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
                <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
                <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CANCEL.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Period after which if full committed deposit amount is not paid by the customer, then system shall trigger cancellation of deposits</p>
                <p>Applicable only for DEPOSITS product line</p>
                <p> Standard PERIOD type of field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
                <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
                <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
                <p>Condition id</p>
                <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
                <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REVOLVING</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the revolving term amounts for lending products. The effect of a revolving product is to increase the available amount from which a customer may drawdown as a result of certain payments. The options are:</p>
                <p>                 NO - the available amount will not increase when any payments are made.</p>
                <p>                 PAYMENT - any payment against the outstanding amount(due or not due) will result in the available amount increasing </p>
                <p>                 PREPAYMENT - only repayments agains the outstanding amount (balance not yet due) will result in the available amount increasing</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGE.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>      The original commitment amout can be increased or decreased using INCREASE or DECREASE action. This field represent the amount to increase or decrease on the original amount.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>     For increase action, the input in this field should be greater than zero.</p>
                <p>     For decrease action the input in this field should be less than zero.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>     Standard T24 amount field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TERM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Determines the period of time by which the amount must be repaid (either to the bank in the case of a loan or to the customer in the case of a deposit) During product definition it will be common to default the term (e.g. a 30 year mortgage)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                 The term can be entered as a number of:</p>
                <p>                 Days (D), Weeks(W), Months(M) or Years(Y)</p>
                <p>                 This field is mandatory input at arrangement level</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UPDATE.COMMT.LIMIT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether the commitment amount of the Limit used for the arrangement should be updated and shown on the LIMIT record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COOLING.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.COMMITTMENT.ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field when set as YES trigger an activity(given below) when the loan /deposit is fully disbursed / funded. </p>
                <p>•	LENDING-FULL.DISBURSE-ARRANGEMENT</p>
                <p>•	DEPOSITS-FULL.FUND-ARRANGEMENT</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    <t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
