<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRD.DES.LD.OTH.COND</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The LD.OTH.COND Property Class is used by all products which are mapped to LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION.  This property class is primarily used for defining the various properties that are needed in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   Although property classes have negotiation rules and other attributes defined, this class does not need any rules to be defined as they will be used  for doing direct field level mapping .</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SETTLEMENT.MARKET</field>
<desc>
            <p>This indicates the CURRENCY.MARKET of the currency in which a LD deal is made.  </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   2 numeric characters. Code must be in the range 1-99.</p>
            <p>   Must be a valid value on the CURENCY.MARKET table.</p>
            <p />
            <p>   For detailed description on SETTLEMENT.MARKET, help text on LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file can be referred.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.PR.PER.TOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tolerance in percentage formats on the SYSTEM calculated amount when MAT.AMOUNT is input in LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> This field has specific significance to Certificate of deposit type of product, where the user inputs the final maturity amount. Where a card rate is available, the user may input the initial investment (AMOUNT field in LD) as well as the final maturity amount (MAT.AMOUNT in LD). If the user input value in the AMOUNT field is different from the amount calculated by the SYSTEM an override is provided. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> In order to protect typographical errors in such input, maximum tolerance in percentage formats may be specified in this field. If the system calculated amount plus the tolerance in this field is less than the value input by the user in the AMOUNT field an error will be displayed and the deal cannot be put through. Such comparison is done and error shown only if MAT.AMOUNT is input in the LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> For a standard loan or deposit (where no input is made in MAT.AMOUNT) the tolerance is this field is added to the MAX.INIT.AMT to decide the maximum AMOUNT that can be drawn down in the LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 percentage field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Cannot be greater than 100. Negative values not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input. Input allowed only if MAX.INIT.AMT is input. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Either set of fields MAX.PR.AMT.TOL &amp; MIN.PR.AMT.TOL or set of fields MAX.PR.PER.TOL &amp; MIN.PR.PER.TOL may be input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Either MAX.PR.PER.TOL or MIN.PR.PER.TOL can alone be input if so required</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.PR.AMT.TOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tolerance in absolute amount on the SYSTEM calculated amount when MAT.AMOUNT is input in LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> This field has specific significance to Certificate of deposit type of product, where the user inputs the final maturity amount. Where a card rate is available, the user may input the initial investment (AMOUNT field in LD) as well as the final maturity amount (MAT.AMOUNT in LD). If the user-input value in the AMOUNT field is different from the amount calculated by the SYSTEM an override is provided. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> In order to protect typographical errors in such input, maximum tolerance in absolute amount may be specified in this field. If the system calculated amount plus the tolerance in this field is less than the value input by the user in the AMOUNT field an error will be displayed and the deal cannot be put through. Such comparison is done and error shown only if MAT.AMOUNT is input in the LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> For a standard loan or deposit (where no input is made in MAT.AMOUNT) the tolerance is this field is added to the MAX.INIT.AMT to decide the maximum AMOUNT that can be drawn down in the LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 Amount format </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Value must be greater than zero</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input. Input allowed only if MAX.INIT.AMT is input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Either set of fields MAX.PR.AMT.TOL &amp; MIN.PR.AMT.TOL or set of fields MAX.PR.PER.TOL &amp; MIN.PR.PER.TOL may be input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Either MAX.PR.AMT.TOL or MIN.PR.AMT.TOL can alone be defined if so required</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
            <p />
            <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
            <p />
            <p>OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
            <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MANDATORY</p>
            <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONVERSION.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The conversion type, BUY, SELL or MID that is to be used.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>  4 character alpha character. Allowed values are only BUY, SELL or MID</p>
            <p />
            <p>  For detailed description on CONVERSION.TYPE, help text on LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file can be referred.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
            <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FWD.BWD.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the method which will be followed for the generation of interest and commission schedules. The value input here is defaulted to the FWD.BWD.KEY field in LD records (at input stage) for categories that have records in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> The following provides an explanation of the various input values for this field: </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> If the derived day is a non working day the system response will be: </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> FWD = forward The system will go forward to the next working day. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> BWD = backward The system will go backward to the last working day. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> FSM = forward same month The system will go forward to the next working day provided it is within the same month. If it is not within the same month the system will go backward to the last working day. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> CAL = Calendar The system will use the same date irrespective of whether dates cycled are working days or not. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
            <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
            <p>Condition id</p>
            <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
            <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUNDING.RULE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold Product level rounding rule for interest, commission, charge and fee calculations. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Should be a valid EB.ROUNDING.RULE id. </p>
            <p />
            <p>   For detailed options on different rounding options, help text on LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file can be referred.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
            <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
            <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge property</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.PR.AMT.TOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tolerance in absolute amount on the SYSTEM calculated amount when MAT.AMOUNT is input in LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> This field has specific significance to Certificate of deposit type of product, where the user inputs the final maturity amount. Where a card rate is available, the user may input the initial investment (AMOUNT field in LD) as well as the final maturity amount (MAT.AMOUNT in LD). If the user-input value in the AMOUNT field is different from the amount calculated by the SYSTEM an override is provided. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> In order to protect typographical errors in such input, minimum tolerance in absolute amount may be specified in this field. If the system calculated amount less the tolerance in this field is more than the value input by the user in the AMOUNT field an error will be displayed and the deal cannot be put through. Such comparison is done and error shown only if MAT.AMOUNT is input in the LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> For a standard loan or deposit (where no input is made in MAT.AMOUNT) the tolerance is this field is reduced from the MAX.INIT.AMT to decide the minimum AMOUNT that can be drawn down in the LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 Amount format </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-14 numeric characters plus a decimal point</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Value must be greater than zero</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> MIN.PR.AMT.TOL cannot be greater than MIN.INIT.AMT</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input. Input allowed only if MIN.INIT.AMT is input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Either set of fields MAX.PR.AMT.TOL &amp; MIN.PR.AMT.TOL or set of fields MAX.PR.PER.TOL &amp; MIN.PR.PER.TOL may be input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Either MAX.PR.AMT.TOL or MIN.PR.AMT.TOL can alone be defined if so required</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MIN.PR.PER.TOL</field>
<desc>
            <p>Tolerance in absolute amount on the SYSTEM calculated amount when MAT.AMOUNT is input in LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> This field has specific significance to Certificate of deposit type of product, where the user inputs the final maturity amount. Where a card rate is available, the user may input the initial investment (AMOUNT field in LD) as well as the final maturity amount (MAT.AMOUNT in LD). If the user input value in the AMOUNT field is different from the amount calculated by the SYSTEM an override is provided. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> In order to protect typographical errors in such input, minimum tolerance in percentage formats may be specified in this field. If the system calculated amount less the tolerance in this field is more than the value input by the user in the AMOUNT field an error will be displayed and the deal cannot be put through. Such comparison is done and error shown only if MAT.AMOUNT is input in the LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> For a standard loan or deposit (where no input is made in MAT.AMOUNT) the tolerance is this field is added to the MAX.INIT.AMT to decide the maximum AMOUNT that can be drawn down in the LD.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Standard T24 percentage field</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Cannot be greater than 100. Negative values not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input. Input allowed only if MIN.INIT.AMT is input. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Either set of fields MAX.PR.AMT.TOL &amp; MIN.PR.AMT.TOL or set of fields MAX.PR.PER.TOL &amp; MIN.PR.PER.TOL may be input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Either MAX.PR.PER.TOL or MIN.PR.PER.TOL can alone be input if so required</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INTEREST.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates the interest frequency for generation of interest schedules. The value input here will be defaulted to the INTEREST.DUE.DATE field in LD contracts (at input stage) for categories that have records in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION.</p>
            <p />
            <p> The values that will be accepted by this field are:</p>
            <p />
            <p> D/DAILY: to specify daily schedules. In the LD contract this would be defaulted to show a daily frequency starting from the day after the value date of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Wn / WEEKn : to specify weekly schedules starting n weeks from the value date of the contract. For example if the input is W1, for a contract dated February 14, 2002, the interest frequency would be on a weekly basis beginning February 21, 2002.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Mxxnn: to specify monthly schedules every xx months on nn date of the month. For example if the input is M0315, for a contract value dated February 14, 2002, the first schedule generated would be on February 15,2002, the next schedule on May 15, 2002 and so on. It is also possible to simply specify the no. of months in the frequency without specifying the date component. In the above example, if the input was M03, the first interest schedule will start 3 months from the value date of the contract on the anniversary of the value date of the contract. For example, for a contract input on February 14, 2002, the next interest due date will be on May 14, 2002.</p>
            <p />
            <p> BSNSS : this will generate interest schedules on every business day.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Apart from the above, the records specified in EB.FREQUENCY application can also be input in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
            <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
            <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CURRENCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the currency for which the set of rules is defined. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Different set of rules can be defined for different currencies, by multi-valuing this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Mandatory input if any rules under it are defined.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 3 alpha currency mnemonic or 1-3 numeric currency code.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> The currency code or the mnemonic must exist on the currency table</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURE.AT.SOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>Flag for maturing a LD contract during Start of Day </p>
            <p />
            <p>    If set to YES, maturity entries would be raised during Start of Day process.</p>
            <p>    If not set to YES, maturity entries would be generated during End of Day process.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>    Optional Input field</p>
            <p />
            <p>  For detailed description on MATURE.AT.SOD, help text on LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file can be referred.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
            <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BASE.DATE.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field provides the user with the option to specify the basis under which subsequent event dates will be derived for interest and commission schedules.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>   Input allowed should be either BASE or PREV</p>
            <p />
            <p>   For detailed description on BASE.DATE.KEY, help text on LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION file can be referred.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHG.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Represents a reference on the LMM.CHARGE.CONDITIONS table that holds the P&amp;L category code where the charge amount will be taken. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Multi-value set in order to default as many charge codes as desired</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Optional Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> 1-3 numeric characters. Optional Input</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Must be a valid code on the LMM.CHARGE.CONDITIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMISSION.FREQ</field>
<desc>
            <p>Field indicates the commission frequency for generation of commission schedules. The value input here will be defaulted to the COMM.DUE.DATE field in LD contracts (at input stage) for categories that have records in LD.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Validation rules:</p>
            <p />
            <p> The values that will be accepted by this field are:</p>
            <p />
            <p> 1. D/DAILY: to specify daily schedules. In the LD contract this would be defaulted to show a daily frequency starting from the day after the value date of the contract. </p>
            <p />
            <p> 2. Wn / WEEKn : to specify weekly schedules starting n weeks from the value date of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p> 3. Mxxnn: to specify monthly schedules every xx months on nn date of the month. </p>
            <p />
            <p> 4. BSNSS : this will generate interest schedules on every business day.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
