<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRD.PRF.ACCOUNT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The ACCOUNT Property Class is used by all products which are account based.  This property class primarily controls the description of the account.  Each T24 product defined and processed in AA can have a single ACCOUNT Property defined.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>                 Although account names are typically account specific, generic titles can be defaulted from the product and can be replaced or given additional detail at the arrangement level.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in  Negotiated.Fields  and only newly negotiated fields will appear on  Changed.Fields </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Currency of the Account.</p>
                <p>            All entries passed to the Account must be in this Currency.</p>
                <p>            once the Account record has been authorised, the Currency cannot be amended.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            3 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character or 1-3 numeric character Currency code. Cannot be changed after record has been authorised. (Mandatory Input)</p>
                <p>            It must be an existing code on the CURRENCY Table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CURRENCY.MARKET</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Currency Market for exchange rate information for this Account, in countries where different rates are quoted for the same Currency.</p>
                <p>            The use of this field is only applicable in countries where the exchange market defines different rates for the same Currency, according to rules determined by the local authorities or central bank.</p>
                <p>            A typical example would be Belgium, where foreign currencies are quoted on the Regular Market and also on the Free Market.  Different sets of exchange rates exist for these two markets.</p>
                <p>            The Currency Market flag may also be used to denote notional markets, i.e. where the User would like to define different sets of exchange rates according to the type of product handled.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            1 numeric character Currency Market code. (Optional Input.  Default is 1.) Cannot be changed.</p>
                <p>            It must be an existing code on the CURRENCY.MARKET table.</p>
                <p>            Details for the Currency Market specified must be included in the CURRENCY record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A customer specified reference can be specified for an account arrangement.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                Up to 16 type S (alpha) characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DATE.ADJUSTMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> Input allowed for all date conventions except for Calendar, Date Adjustment is used to specify whether the new date will represent an adjustment of the ‘Value’ date of the entries (Actual payment date does not get adjusted) or an adjust of the ‘Period’ (Actual payment date gets cycled).</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input allowed should be either PERIOD or VALUE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DATE.CONVENTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>During the automatic generation of payment schedules, the Date Convention and Date Adjustment settings indicate the action which will be taken if the derived date is a non-working day. There are four Date Convention options:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>• Backward – the payment date will move backward to the previous working day.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>• Forward – the payment date will move forward to the next working day.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>• Forward Same Month – the payment date will move forward to the next working day provided it is within the same month. If it is not within the same month, the payment date will move backward to the previous working day.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>• Calendar – the payment date will not move regardless of whether it is on a working day.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The base date that would be used for application of next payment date would be the previous unadjusted payment date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input allowed should be either BACKWARD, FORWARD, FORWARD SAME MONTH or CALENDAR.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNT.REFERENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The field holds the reference of the underlying ACCOUNT application. If this field is populated, system would use the reference stated here to create the ACCOUNT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
                <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INACTIVE.MONTHS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the Number of months without customer activity before an Arrangement Account is declared as Inactive. Based on this value only the Arrangement Accounts are marked as Inactive.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid numeric value in the range 1-99</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MANDATE.APPL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates for which application these mandate settings apply. Must be a record on MANDATE.PARAMETER.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid ID in MANDATE.PARAMETER</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Optional Field</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MANDATE.RECORD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When the MANDATE.APPL and MANDATE.REG is used for triggering mandate requirement, this is the MANDATE that is checked against to ensure that the correct numbers of signatories etc are available.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid record in EB.MANDATE</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MANDATE.REG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the rule that must be passed to ensure the mandate checking is triggered. Not a mandatory field, if null then the mandate checking would be triggered by default.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be a valid record in EB.RULE.GATEWAY</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MNEMONIC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A mnemonic is an alternate key which can be defined by a user to reference the account</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNT.TITLE.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The title lines are used to describe the specific account in multiple languages.  </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                 Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields  Nr.Negotiable  through to  Nr.Message </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
                <p/>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in  Nr.Attribute . If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field  Nr.Type </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIGINATION.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is for information purposes only. This field may find use to store the external reference identifier which initiated this arrangement - like a Loan Origination's reference.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      This is a standard T24 NOCHANGE Field of 35 characters in length and holds any character.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNT.TITLE.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The title lines are used to describe the specific account in multiple languages.  </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PASSBOOK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Determines if the arrangement has a passbook.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>ACCOUNT.CLASS validations on categories allowed would be honored. If set to "Y" all account statements would be suppressed. Maps to the underlying ACCOUNT application to the same field</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Y or NO.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PORTFOLIO.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>An arrangement could be linked to customer's portfolio reference(SEC.ACC.MASTER id) using this field. When the portfolio is linked, the arrangement would also be taken into consideration during portfolio valuation for the customer. Not relevant for product conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>The portfolio reference should belong to the customer of the Arrangement(Optional input) </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POSITION.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the Type of Foreign Exchange Position which will be updated as a result of movements over this account.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>           2 type SSS (uppercase alpha) character Position Type code. (Optional Input. Default is TR.) Cannot be changed.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           It must be an existing code on the Position Type Table (FX.POS.TYPE in General Tables).</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POSTING.RESTRICT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>At the arrangement level, a posting restriction code (defined in POSTING.RESTRICT) can be used to restrict the following:</p>
                <p>                  • All Debits</p>
                <p>                  • All Credits</p>
                <p>                  • All Transactions</p>
                <p>                  An override will be required to accept any entry which meets the conditions of a Posting Restriction. </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will hold two values either DUE or CAPITALISE.This Field denote which application method(DUE or CAPITALISE)should be taken while applying periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will have to accept a valid T24 period.This Field will denote the application period for current aplication method.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
                <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ALT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Alternate System IDs are typically used for accounts that have been taken over from a different system or bank.  Each of these previous account systems are specified in T24 and for accounts which have been taken over, the alternate account ID specific to the previous system will be specified at the arrangement level. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                 Up to 16 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
                <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
                <p>Condition id</p>
                <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
                <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REFERAL.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the conditions under which Account details or details of entries over the Account are to be included in an end of day report for referral to the Account Officer responsible.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Referral conditions can be defined depending on transaction such as transaction code, amount and sign, or the balance of the Account.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>1-6 numeric character Referral code. Multivalue field. (Optional input. No default value.)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>It must be an existing code on the REFERAL Table (Referral).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Duplicate codes are not allowed.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SHADOW.ACCOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the value YES or NULL.</p>
                <p>While inputting new arrangement for account creation, system updates this field based on the value specified in the product condition of Account property class.</p>
                <p>If this field has value 'YES' then the balance details of this account is not maintained within T24 and it will be held by an external DDA system. Within T24, only static information of this account would be maintained.</p>
                <p>If this field has NULL value, then it is like a normal T24 account, so the balances would be maintained by T24 for this type of accounts.</p>
                <p> VALIDATION RULES </p>
                <p> Should be either YES or NULL only. Default value is Null. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SHORT.TITLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The short title is typically an abbreviation of the account title and is used throughout T24 as enrichment. It is a multi-lingual field. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ALT.ID.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>In this application any alternate account systems defined in the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER application will be defaulted to allow maintenance of the alternate account system.</p>
                <p>            When alternate account systems are defined in the ALT.ACT.PARAMETER application and entered in the ACCOUNT.PARAMETER ALTERNATE.ID field, their system identifiers will be displayed here, allowing maintenance of the alternate account identifiers in the following field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>            No amendments are allowed.</p>
                <p>            Multivalue field.</p>
                <p>            This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ANNIVERSARY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field stores the Anniversary Date of the arrangement in the format 'MMDD'. This is user inputtable field which will be used to get the start and end date of periodic rules if Rule Start is set to 'Anniversary' in the periodic attribute.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BASE.DATE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>  This nochange field at the arrangement level indicates if the Anniversary field should be from the agreement date or from the first disbursement date(start).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         If Start is selected, then system will maintain the MMDD of the arrangement start date in Anniversary until the first disbursement happens and then overwrites Anniversary with the MMDD of first disbursed date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BUS.DAY.CENTRES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates those countries whose calendars must be checked with regard to holiday validation. User can input multiple Country codes if required. System will default the Country of the arrangement currency in case user left this field value null.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>4 type A (alphanumeric) characters.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is multi value.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The code must have a valid entry on the REGION/HOLIDAY table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CATEGORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Historically, the CATEGORY of an account has been used in T24 as both a product definition and as a characteristic which is used to segregate and produce balance sheets.  In an AA Product, the Product code is used to distinguish products.  The Category of the account is used for reporting (i.e. balance sheet) purposes only.  The Category of an account should be defined at the product level.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    <t><field>GENERATE.IBAN</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACCOUNTING.COMPANY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>BASE.DATE.KEY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
