<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRD.CAT.INTEREST</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The INTEREST Property Class is used for all interest definition and processing in AA.  A T24 product defined and processed in AA can have multiple interest properties defined (e.g. principal interest, penalty interest, commission, etc.).  The number of interest properties is determined by the users defining the products.</p>
            <p>   The different condition ids of interest property can be attached to the different types of interest properties at product level</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates at which rate is the arrangement currently running on for the date on the Id. This shows the actual rate even if it is running on a Periodic and would include the margin rate calculations as well.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             System maintained(NOINPUT) field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FIXED.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Three basic types of interest are supported by T24; Fixed, Floating, and Periodic.  Each of these interest types can include one or more margins and can be specified in a tiered structure.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                  A fixed rate is directly entered by the user specifying the Defined Property and is not defined by an index table.  Fixed rates are entered as positive numbers unless a negative rate is allowed. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                This field is part of a multi value set of fields including FIXED.RATE, FLOATING.INDEX, PERIODIC.INDEX, PERIODIC.PERIOD, PERIODIC.BASE, MARGIN.TYPE, MARGIN.OPER, MARGIN.RATE, TIER.MIN.RATE, TIER.MAX.RATE, TIER.AMOUNT,TIER.PERCENT. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FLOATING.INDEX</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Three basic types of interest are supported by T24; Fixed, Floating, and Periodic.  Each of these interest types can include one or more margins and can be specified in a tiered structure.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                  A floating interest rate is tied to a variable base rate (i.e. BASIC.INTEREST).  During interest calculation, T24 will use the currency specific rate applicable for the calculation date (i.e. the rate used for the calculation will change whenever the base rate is changed).  </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FLOATING.NOTICE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is reserved for future development</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FT.TXN.TYPE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCOUNTING.MODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies how the accounting entries will be raised. Whether it needs to work like discounted or fixed type of interest.</p>
                <p>Advance: This is nothing but discounted interest, interest amount will be collected inadvance before the interest periods.</p>
                <p>Upfront Profit: Interest amount will be collected at the beginning of the contract.</p>
                <p>None: Denotes conventional interest bearing contract.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
                <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.MODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether the interest property can be schceduled upfront(calculated interest would be billed at the start of the period,) or not. Available option is “ADVANCE”.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If this field is set to ADVANCE then the payment type with this interest property (which is there in the payment schedule definition) should also have the PAYMENT.MODE set to ADVANCE. Allowed payment methods are DUE/PAY, CAPITALISE will not be allowed for this type of interest.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>        
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INTEREST.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether interest method is fixed life of the contract or not.</p>
                <p>FIXED – Fix the total profit amount regardless of any change to loan parameters. This field is specify whether total interest amount need to fixed or not.</p>
                <p>Null – Will be treated as a normal interest bearing property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INTERNAL.BOOKING</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Income / expense will be posted to internal account category specified in Accounting condition instead of PL categories.</p>
                <p>This will accept YES or NULL</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.ARRANGEMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Where at least one tier is set to be ‘Linked Rate’, the Arrangement to be linked for calculating the Interest Rate, must be specified here (or automatically defaulted by the system, where a Limit is attached) </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will be used to specify the Interest Property of the Linked Arrangement that should be referred to, for getting the Interest Rate. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Where at least one tier is set to be ‘Linked Rate’, this must be specified. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It would be possible to specify that the rate for a given tier be ‘Linked’, by setting the field Linked Rate to Yes. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>This can be mixed with normal rate calculations as well. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Where the Linked Rate is set to Yes, system would expect that an Arrangement reference in given in the ‘Linked Arrangement’ field along with the Interest property to be linked to. </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACCRUAL.RULE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When accruing interest, T24 must determine which amounts to include in each day’s balance, the actual days to include in the period (e.g. first day, last day) and how to round any calculations.</p>
                <p>                    T24 allows users to define the calculation method to use, by specifying an accrual rule in EB.ACCRUAL.PARAM.  Users can define the following:</p>
                <p>                    • First Day Inclusive (Yes/No)</p>
                <p>                    • Last Day Inclusive (Yes/No)</p>
                <p>                    • Rounding Rule (Natural, Down, Up, Currency, None) </p>
                <p>                    • Intermediate Calculation Rounding (Yes/No)</p>
                <p>                    • Credit value date adjustment</p>
                <p>                    • Debit value date adjustment</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MARGIN.OPER</field>
            <desc>
                <p> The options are ADD or SUB. This indicates whether the MARGIN.RATE should be added or subtracted from the Floating or Periodic Rate.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE. It is also part of a sub value set with MARGIN.TYPE and MARGIN.RATE and input is only allowed if a rate is entered in MARGIN.RATE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MARGIN.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A margin rate can be used to adjust the specified rate of interest and to appropriately reflect any rate profit realized.  The result is the nominal rate of interest.  T24 allows for the following margin configuration:</p>
                <p>              • Single or Multiple Margins (Field MARGIN.TYPE)</p>
                <p>              • Rate Adjustment Method (Field MARGIN.OPER)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE. It is also part of a sub value set with MARGIN.TYPE and MARGIN.OPER.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MARGIN.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies whether there are single or multiple margins</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE. It is also part of a sub value set with MARGIN.OPER and MARGIN.RATE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MIN.INT.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the minimum interest amount to be posted for an arrangement/account. </p>
                <p>If the calculated interest amount is less than the amount specified in this field, system will waive the interest amount or adjust the interest amount based on the option set in the field MIN.INT.WAIVE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MIN.INT.WAIVE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates if the calculated interest amount has to be waived or adjusted.</p>
                <p>If the field is set to YES, then the system will waive the interest amount if it is less than the MIN.INT.AMOUNT specified.</p>
                <p>If NULL value is set and if the calculated interest amount is less than the MIN.INT.AMOUNT specified, then system will post the minimum interest amount.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGATIVE.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to set negative interest rates on accounts in credit. To do this, the NEGATIVE.RATE field must be set to “Yes”. If the field is set as either “No” or left unpopulated, then when interest rates fall below 0, zero interest will be accrued.  Negative interest rates may occur either as a result of a negative rate being specified or as the result of the rate minus any margin which is specified. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
                <p/>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTUAL.PROFIT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User can defined Total interest / profit amount for the contract. </p>
                <p>Mandatory input if RATE.TYPE is ‘Flat Amount’. </p>
                <p>Value in CALC.PROFIT.AMT will be populated in this field which the user can override.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OFFSET.DETAILS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ON.ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When the periodic interest rate needs to be recalculated for certain activities, this field in combination with RECALCULATE may be used to setup the activity for which interest needs to be recalculated</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>1. Applicable only for Periodic interest rate recalculation</p>
                <p>2. Must be a valid activity in AA.ACTIVITY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIG.PROFIT.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field is used to define the profit amount realised in the Legacy system. Assuming the total profit amount for the contract is 10,000  and remaining profit amount to be realized during migration is 3,000, one will give the difference (7,000) in this attribute. And 3,000 will be input in the Actual Profit Amount that has to be realized in T24. If someone wants the total profit amount, they can simply add these 2 to get them. Once authorised, the value cannot be changed.</p>
                <p>Validation:</p>
                <p>•	Applicable for Fixed Interest Method</p>
                <p>•	Input enabled during migration of the contract(through take-over activity)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIODIC.INDEX</field>
            <desc>
                <p>A periodic rate is tied to an index (e.g. LIBOR) which is dependent on a period of time (e.g. term) and possibly an amount.  Once the arrangement is active, the rate is fixed until it is reset.  Periodic rates can be reset at a pre-determined frequency.</p>
                <p>                  To define a periodic rate, the user specifies:</p>
                <p>                  • PERIODIC.INTEREST index to use</p>
                <p>                  • Period (this will default to TERM if a Term Amount Property exists)</p>
                <p>                  • Interest selection method if the term is not found on the index. The option currently available is INTERPOLATE.</p>
                <p>                  • Rate Reset period</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ADJUST.OPTION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIODIC.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If system does not find a interest rate in the correct bucket of PERIODIC.INTEREST table, it automatically applies a method to arrive at a rate chosen by this method.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>          Valid method is:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>          INTERPOLATE - System automatically interpolates the rate. This is the DEFAULT option as well.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIODIC.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the interest period to be used when linking to PERIODIC.INTEREST.(This will default to TERM if a Term Amount Property exists),. When a period is stated in Years or Weeks, they would be converted to Months and Days respectively and then located on the PI table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIODIC.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the rate on which the index runs on the date stated in the key. When a periodic index is used and the field is left blank, then system computes the rate from PERIODIC.INTEREST and defaults it here. When a rate is already present(say, the user changes the system computed rate), then system does not compute the new rate.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        Validation rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>        System defaulted and modifiable.</p>
                <p>        Standard Rate field.</p>
                <p>        Valid only if Periodic index is stated.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIODIC.RESET</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This indicates the reset period of the index stated. System would automatically reset the PERIODIC.RATE at the frequency stated in this field. Applicable only at Arrangement level. Periodic index may still be used without this field meaning, it never resets the computed rate</p>
                <p/>
                <p>          Validation rule:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>          Valid PERIOD field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will hold two values either DUE or CAPITALISE.This Field denote which application method(DUE or CAPITALISE)should be taken while applying periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will have to accept a valid T24 period.This Field will denote the application period for current aplication method.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
                <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.THRESHOLD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The user can specify that interest will only be calculated if a balance threshold is surpassed. For credit interest, the user can specify the minimum balance which must be maintained. For debit interest, the user can specify the maximum debit balance for which interest will not be calculated.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
                <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
                <p>Condition id</p>
                <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
                <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RATE.TIER.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>T24 allows for the definition of tiers of interest rates.  Each tier is specified by defining the amount up to which the interest rate applies.  Additionally, each tier can be of a different interest rate type (i.e. fixed, floating, or periodic).  There are three type of tiers; Single, Level, and Banded.  </p>
                <p>                  Single Rate</p>
                <p>                  When a single rate tier type is specified a single nominal interest rate will apply for the entire balance amount.</p>
                <p>                  Rate Levels</p>
                <p>                  By specifying level tiers a product can be defined which will calculate interest at different rates depending on the balance amount.  A single rate of interest will be selected and applied based upon the balance amount.  For example for a deposit a single product can have a higher rate of interest for accounts which maintain higher credit balances.  Conversely for a loan product a higher rate of interest can be charged for accounts with higher debit balances.  </p>
                <p>                  For example, aassuming a credit balance of 15,000 and level interest which specifies an applicable rate of 10 per cent up to 10,000 and 15 per cent above 10,000.  A single rate of 15 per cent will be applied to the entire amount of 15,000.</p>
                <p>                  Banded Rates</p>
                <p>                  Banded tier interest will typically result in a “blended” interest rate.   This is similar to Level tiers, but allows for the interest rate of each tier to be applied to the portion of the balance that falls within the tier.</p>
                <p>              For example, assuming a credit balance of 15,000 and banded interest which specifies an applicable rate of 10 per cent up to 10,000 and 15 per cent above 10,000.  Two calculations will be performed (i.e. 10 per cent on 10,000 and 15 per cent on 5,000)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>              This field is Mandatory.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RATE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether Interest definition is based on a rate or amount and in case of rate what type of rate. </p>
                <p>Reducing Rate: Rate defined in Interest rate related fields will be considered as Reducing or Diminishing Rate for Interest calculation.</p>
                <p>Flat Rate: Rate defined in interest rate related fields will be considered as a Flat Rate.</p>
                <p>Flat Amount: Amount defined in the ACTUAL.PROFIT.AMT will be considered as the total interest amount for the interest property.</p>
                <p>This will be allowed only when INTEREST.METHOD is FIEXED</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RECALCULATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Related to ON.ACTIVITY activity, when flagged to RATE, system will recalculate Periodic rate when the activity setup in ON.ACTIVITY is processed. When the value is NOTHING periodic rate would not be recalculated when the activity setup in ON.ACTIVITY is processed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory when ON.ACTIVITY is setup</p>
                <p>The fields ON.ACTIVITY and RECALCULATE in interest property class will be enhanced to allow user to define when to recalculate ‘Profit Amount’. </p>
                <p>All activities which could result in payment schedule recalculation can be configured to recalculate ‘Profit Amount’ i.e., activities with payment schedule calculate and update action</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>REFER.LIMIT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For an arrangement under ACCOUNTS Product Line, it is possible link the first tier amount of debit interest to the LIMIT record attached.</p>
                <p>It can be achieved by setting the field REFER.LIMIT in INTEREST property condition as ‘YES’. This functionality can be enabled only if the LIMIT is managed by AA.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RELATIONSHIP.MARGIN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RELATIONSHIP.OPERAND</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RELATIONSHIP.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RELATIONSHIP.VARIATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUPPRESS.ACCRUAL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Field accepts the options 'YES' or 'ALTERNATE'.</p>
                <p>Indicates whether accruals needs to be Suppressed or Accrual should be done for the Alternate Interest Property.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>For Example:</p>
                <p>                      It will be set as YES by the system if the DONOR.ACCRUAL field is set as SUPPRESS for any product / arrangement in INTEREST.COMPENSTION property of a Bundle arrangement.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If it is set as 'ALTERNATE' for a property then the Accrual will be suppressed for the property for which it is set and Accrual will happen for the Alternate property which is set in Activity Restriction.</p>
                <p>                      Blank value in this field denotes that there is no suppression of accrual</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This is a Non Mandatory field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPOUND.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>T24 supports the compounding of both debit and credit interest.  </p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Compounding interest applies a factor to the compound interest calculation based upon the  number of compounding periods in the year. This field defines the number of compounding periods to be applied.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       Note that the compounding type provides a factor in the calculation only  and does not actually cause the base principal amount to be actually increased by the calculated interest amount.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>       The following compound frequencies are supported:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      DAILY </p>
                <p>      – Interest is compounded 360/5/6 times a year (from days in year in INTEREST.BASIS) </p>
                <p/>
                <p>      WEEKn </p>
                <p>      – Interest is compounded 52/n times per year based on a number of WEEKS</p>
                <p>      -- Bi-weekly compounding should be defined as WEEK2 and will result in 26 periods</p>
                <p>      -- Four-Weekly compounding should be defined as WEEK4 and results in 13 periods </p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Mnn </p>
                <p>      – Interest is compounded 12/n times a year based on a numberof months</p>
                <p>      --  Monthly compounding should be defined as M01 and will result in 12 periods</p>
                <p>      --  Bi-Monthly should be defined as M02 and will result in 6 periods</p>
                <p>      --  Quarterly should be defined as M03 and will result in 4 periods</p>
                <p>      --  Semi-Annual should be defined as M06 and will result in 6 periods</p>
                <p>      --  Annual should be defined as M12 and will result in 1 period</p>
                <p>      --  Bi-Annual should be defined as M24 and will result in 0.5 periods</p>
                <p>      --  Any number of months up to 99 may be defined and results in 12/n periods</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      TWMTH</p>
                <p>       – Interest is compounded twice a month resulting in 24 periods as opposed to WEEK2</p>
                <p>      which results in 26 periods</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Nnnn</p>
                <p>       - Compounding takes place nnn times per year.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The tier amount relates to the field RATE.TIER.TYPE and amounts can be entered if either BAND or LEVEL are selected.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.MAX.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For each tier defined, a user can specify a minimum and/or maximum rate for the tier.  This is applicable for variable and periodic rates and allows the tier rate to be controlled.  </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.MIN.RATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For each tier defined, a user can specify a minimum and/or maximum rate for the tier.  This is applicable for variable and periodic rates and allows the tier rate to be controlled.  </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TIER.PERCENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The tier percent relates to the field RATE.TIER.TYPE and percentages can be entered if BAND is selected.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set of fields listed in the helptext for FIXED.RATE. Either TIER.PERCENT or TIER.AMOUNT can be entered by not both. If TIER.PERCENT is defined, then the Sum of Tier percentage should be 100% </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPOUND.YIELD.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DAY.BASIS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>T24 can calculate interest based upon several different day basis types.  Each T24 Interest Day Basis type is represented as a numerator and denominator.</p>
                <p>                  • Numerator (interest days)</p>
                <p>                  o 360 – Each month is considered to have 30 days </p>
                <p>                  o 366 – The exact number of days will be used</p>
                <p>                  • Denominator (days in the year)</p>
                <p>                  o 360 – Each year is considered to have 360 days</p>
                <p>                  o 365 – Each year is considered to have 365 days</p>
                <p>                  o 366 – The exact number of days in the year will be used (365 or 366)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                  T24 allows the following interest day basis types:</p>
                <p>                  Type        Notes</p>
                <p>                  A (360/360)     A1 and A2 are variations which alter the method of treating a month as 30 days.</p>
                <p>                  B (366/360) </p>
                <p>                  C (366/366) </p>
                <p>                  D (360/366) </p>
                <p>                  E (366/365) </p>
                <p>                  F (360/365)     F1 and F2 are variations which alter the method of treating a month as 30 days.</p>
                <p>                  S (special)      Allows for actual interest amounts to be entered by the user.  The amounts in the     schedule must be within a tolerance of 5% when compared with the product of amount * rate * period.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                  This is a Mandatory field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    <t><field>LINKED.EFFECTIVE.RATE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
