<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PAYMENT.TYPE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This applciation enables users to define the standard payment types that can be used by a product.  A payment type is required for every payment schedule definition.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>TERM.TOLERANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether the payment type is ‘Calculated’ or ‘Manual’.  </p>
                <p>             The majority of the defined payment types will be defined as ‘Calculated’.  During the setup of each arrangement it may be possible for the user to negotiate a different payment amount than the one determined by T24.</p>
                <p>             For arrangements with ad-hoc payment schedules a financial institution can create a ‘Manual’ payment type which indicates that the payment amounts will be entered manually and not be calculated by T24.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             This field is Mandatory.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>          Input allowed is CALCULATED or MANUAL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.ROUTINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This application enables the user to define a routine to calculate the payment amount.</p>
                <p>         Input in this field is allowed when the field CALC.TYPE is equal to OTHER</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This fields denotes different types of calculated payments that could be applied.</p>
                <p>         T24 supports five types of calculated payments:</p>
                <p>             • Constant – results in equal repayments.  This is used for ‘Annuity’ arrangements and requires both a Term Amount and Interest property to be specified. </p>
                <p>             • Linear – the Term Amount repayment remains fixed over the lifetime of the arrangement. Optional properties such as Interest, Charge, and Tax may be included.  The actual amounts calculated by these properties will be added to the fixed Term Amount repayment.  </p>
                <p>             • Actual – is used for repayment of calculated property classes (i.e. Interest, Charge, and Tax) and will be determined on each payment schedule date.</p>
                <p>             • Progressive – On choosing this type, a progressive percentage should be defined in the field PROG.PAY.PERC. System will calculate an amount which will be progressing by the rate specified in PROG.PAY.PERC. Exactly same as CONSTANT type when PROG.PAY.PERC is defined as 0. Optionally user routine could be attached for this type.</p>
                <p>             • Other – indicates that a user routine will calculate the repayment amounts.  </p>
                <p>             • Accelerated - In this calculation type payment amount would be calculated using Monthly frequency (e0Y e1M e0W e0D e0F) even if user has given the payment frequency as weekly or Bi-weekly.             Then the amount calculated for monthly will then be factored to the payment frequency defined in payment schedule to arrive at the final payment amount for each period i.e. divided by 2 or 4 based on whether frequency is Bi-weekly or weekly.    </p>
                <p/>
                <p>             This field is Mandatory.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>          Options are CONSTANT, LINEAR, ACTUAL, PROGRESSIVE, ACCELERATE or OTHER.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field describes the AA.PAYMENT.TYPE and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>           This is a Mandatory field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXTEND.CYCLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p> Indicates whether the property class needs to be extended beyond the payment end date. For example, if a scheduled ACTUAL payment type used for collecting specific charge needs to be collected even after the payment end date, the charge needs to be stated in this field</p>
                <p> Interest by default gets extended even after payment end date </p>
                <p> No cycling would happen for CONSTANT payment type even beyond payment end date though.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MAND.PROP.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the mandatory property classes that would be necessary for the payments.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>         The property classes entered in this field will be validated against the property field in payment schedule for a given payment type.Depending on the Calculation Type there may be rules as to the Property Classes specified:</p>
                <p>             • Constant – both Account and Interest properties are required. </p>
                <p>             • Linear – Account property is required</p>
                <p>             • Actual – Account property cannot be specified. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>             This is a multi value field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>          Input must be a valid record from AA.PROPERTY.CLASS.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.MODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will allow a user to collect the Interest amount upfront (at the start of the interest period)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>To achieve the above case, this field should be set to ADVANCE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Input in this field is allowed only when the CALC.TYPE is set to ACTUAL and MAND.PROP.CLASS is equal to INTEREST</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAYMENT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Any alphanumeric characters can be used to define the name of the payment type.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>             Up to 30 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SCHEDULE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will decide whether the payment type should follow any special schedule processing.</p>
                <p>Currently will support ONLINE option only.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>ONLINE - This will decide whether the payment type should have to process immediately whenever the start date has given as current system date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYSTEM.PAYMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> This field denotes whether the payment type is a user defined payment type or system defined. for the system defined payment types this field is set to yes.  All fields except description is noinput if the field SYSTEM.PAYMENT is set to YES</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TAX.INCLUSIVE</field>
        </t>
    <t><field>K.TYPE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
