<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.PRODUCT.CONDITION</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table allows to add description and group the product conditions</p>
            <p>The product condition can be per currency, date or variation, and since these are in multiple records the common description could be updated in this Table, and system will use this description for all the variations</p>
            <p>It also possible to associated a context for the conditions by ProductLine or ProductGroup so that the system filters out the conditions that are applicable for a ProductLine or ProductGroup which should useful when assigning the conditions for the Product</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CONDITION.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the second part of the record key o this Table, AA.PRODUCT.CONDITION, may be used for selecting the records from this table by "Conditon name"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONTEXT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes either ProductLine or ProductGroup key based on CONTEXT.TYPE</p>
                <p>Required when CONTEXT.TYPE is set"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CONTEXT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the context type for the condition, allowed values are,</p>
                <p>LINE - Conditions to be used for ProductLine</p>
                <p>GROUP - Conditions to be used for ProductGroup</p>
                <p>Option field, if not set, the condition will not be filtered"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the condition and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRD.COND.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the ID of the record, should be in the format "PropertyClass" * "ConditionName"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
        </t>
    <t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
