<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p> This file contains the Period level definition. This file allows the user to create records which has specific period definition in them.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>COMPARISON.TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Single value field. </p>
            <p value="2">Value to this field can be entered as one of the value defined in AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS file of the same field.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TYPE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field represents the TYPE that can be defined in AA.PRD.DES.XXX record.</p>
        <p>Input must be one of the TYPE defined in corresponding AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>Possible Values are :</p>
        <p>CAP - The rule value to be used as CAP if rule is broken</p>
        <p>FLOOR - The rule value to be used as FLOOR if rule is broken</p>
        <p>BALANCE.TYPE - The rule value to be used as BALANCE.TYPE if rule is broken</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RESTRICTION.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This provides another layer for restriction to the Rule. By default, the rule is applicable over the specified period. Optionally the user could input this field to restrict the period further by defining a start period &amp; end period within the period(defined in PERIOD) between which the Rule is applied.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>             Input must be like nnnT-mmmT, where</p>
            <p>         nnnT &amp; mmmT should be a valid Period Type with the exception of allowing 0.</p>
            <p />
            <p>         E.g: 0D-1D, 0M-1M; 1M-12M;</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Arrangement Start - 20070601</p>
            <p>            RULE.START        - ARRANGEMENT</p>
            <p>            PERIOD            - 12M</p>
            <p>            PERIOD.TYPE     - REPEATING</p>
            <p>            RESTRICTION.PERIOD- 0M-1M</p>
            <p>            DATE.TYPE         - NULL</p>
            <p />
            <p>         The rule is applied only for 1M from 01-June every year.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field represents the exact period the user wants to define for the Rule.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> : </p>
            <p />
            <p>                   No input if </p>
            <p>                     1) the PERIOD.TYPE is INITIAL or</p>
            <p>                     2) RULE.START is ANNIVERSARY</p>
            <p />
            <p>                   Mandatory input otherwise. If DATE.TYPE is set to Calendar, then this field should be in 'Y'(years) or  'M' (months).</p>
            <p />
            <p>                   Accepted values are :</p>
            <p>                    nnM or nnY or nnD or nnW (For Example : 01D, 12M )</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.ERR.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>  This field represents error message that needs to be raised when the rule is broken.</p>
            <p />
            <p>                   Should be a valid record id of the file EB.ERROR.</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If not specified, the default error specifed in the EB.COMPARISON.TYPE will be raised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.END.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the end period until when the rule is applicable.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validations</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard period field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Accepted values are : nnM or nnY or nnD or nnW (For Example : 01D, 12M )</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.START.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the start period from when the rule is applicable. The actual start date is calculated based on RULE.START definition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Validations</p>
            <p />
            <p>Standard period field</p>
            <p />
            <p>Accepted values are : nnM or nnY or nnD or nnW (For Example : 01D, 12M )</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PERIOD.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the rule that needs to be applied on a specific period or life time of the contract.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Options are:</p>
            <p />
            <p>LIFE – Restriction applies for the entire life of an arrangement or arrangement life as a certain product.</p>
            <p />
            <p>INITIAL – Restriction applies for an initial period only of an arrangement during its life time or the initial period of an arrangement as a certain product.</p>
            <p />
            <p>REPEATING – Restriction applies for a fixed repeating period during either the life of the arrangement or the life of an arrangement as a certain product. For example the restriction may be based on a 12 a month calendar period (i.e. Jan to Dec) or a 3 month period starting on the anniversary of the loan,</p>
            <p />
            <p>ROLLING – Restriction applies for a rolling period that ends at the date of a transaction. For example the maximum repayment in the last three months.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTR.CLASS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Identifies the Periodic Attribute Class to which the Periodic Rule belongs to. </p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>                   Mandatory Input. Input must be a valid AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS ID.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.OVE.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p> This field represents override message that needs to be raised when the rule is broken.</p>
            <p />
            <p>                   Should be valid record id of the file OVERRIDE</p>
            <p />
            <p>     If not specified, the default override specifed in the EB.COMPARISON.TYPE will be raised.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.END</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTTRIBUTE.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>                    This field represents the id of the file AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.START</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the base date which is to be taken for computing the periods.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       Mandatory Input field.</p>
            <p />
            <p>       Allowed Inputs:</p>
            <p>       1) AGREEMENT - takes the current Product's Effective date as the base date.</p>
            <p>       2) ANNIVERSARY - takes the date and month from the field anniversary in the property corresponding to ACCOUNT property class.</p>
            <p>          This is not a valid input for the PERIOD.TYPE - LIFE.</p>
            <p>       3) ARRANGEMENT - takes the start date of the Arrangement</p>
            <p>       4) START       - takes the first disbursement date as the base date. If not disbursed, then the arrangement start date will be taken till it is disbursed.</p>
            <p>       5) COOLING.PERIOD - takes the cooling date as the base date for calculating the periodic restriction (Eg. If the cooling period ends on 31st Dec. 2010, periodic restriction is set For AMOUNT.INCREASE and the period is set to 1 year when RULE.START is set to COOLING.PERIOD, then periodic restriction will apply from the end date of cooling period and not from the date of arrangement). </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field describes the Periodic Attribute and is used for enrichment. </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>                   This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>                   Mandatory Input</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.END.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field is reserved for future use. They were meant to specify the exact end date between which a rule could exist.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.START.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The field is reserved for future use. They were meant to specify the exact start dates between which a rule could exist.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DATE.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This denotes if the rule is applicable for Calendar period or not. When set to Calendar, Rule Start will be applied from the calendar start date of the month or year as specified.</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Other set up to support Calendar type are:</p>
            <p>            1) PERIOD - should be in 'Y', or in 'M'</p>
            <p>            2) PERIOD.TYPE - should be either INITIAL or REPEATING.</p>
            <p />
            <p>            E.g.</p>
            <p>            Arrangement Start - 20070601</p>
            <p>            RULE.START        - ARRANGEMENT</p>
            <p>            PERIOD            - 12M</p>
            <p>            PERIOD.TYPE     - REPEATING</p>
            <p />
            <p>            Then the Start &amp; End dates of the Rule when the Effective Date is 20071001 is</p>
            <p>              Start Date : 20070601(Actually it should be 20070101 - since arrangement start date falls later, this date is taken)</p>
            <p>              End Date   : 20071231 (ends on calendar end date)</p>
            <p />
            <p>            and when Effective Date is 20080201,</p>
            <p />
            <p>              Start Date : 20080101</p>
            <p>              End Date   : 20081231 (ends on calendar end date)</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>K.TYPE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
