<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRD.DES.AZ.ACCOUNTING</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>All in One Account module enables the Banks to define Account based Loan and Deposit products. The loan/ deposit accounts opened under this module, based on a pre defined All in One Products, are different from the Contract based Loans and Deposits, in view of flexibility in operations, like a normal account. The repayment schedules defined under this module are for the purpose of reference with the account balance, for arriving at the arrears or allowing redraw facilities, on the scheduled dates.</p>
            <p />
            <p> AZ.ACCOUNTING  describes the parameter details of All in One Account Products.</p>
            <p />
            <p> By using this file, Banks can define various types of Loan / Deposit Products under All In One Module (AZ Module) like Education Loan, Housing Loan, Car loan etc., with different features unique to each type of Product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> The AZ accounts opened under a particular All in One product, inherits the default features of the product like penal rate, Repayment type, Maximum Interest only period, etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p> However, at AZ account level also, changes are accepted to override the defaulted values.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Certain validations like minimum term, maximum term, allowed category, maximum back date, minimum and maximum amount (in the case of deposit) are done at the AZ account, with respect to the values defined under the corresponding AZ Product.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CORR.IMMED</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the way system should collect interest correction amount .</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Value NEXT is allowed only for Annuity contracts &amp; with ANNUITY.ADJUST as YES .</p>
            <p />
            <p>  When correction entries are raised due to back-dated drawdown or repayment, then the system collects the correction amount from AZINTADJ Suspense account immediately . Only during NEXT repayment( online/cob), the system shall collect above correction amount from repayment account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Default value is CURRENT and in this case, correction amount is collected immediately from the repayment account .</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Values - CURRENT,NEXT</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ON.CHG.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to identify the entries that are raised due to the tax on charge collected as late payment fee.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Debit transction code defined in the TAX file.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAX.BACK.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the maximum number of days, earlier than the current business date, up to which the value date of the accounts, defined under this product, can go back.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  However, the maximum back value date defined under DATES table of T24, will override the maximum back date arrived by the number of days defined here.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1-3 digit Numeric value</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Cannot have negative values</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROLLOVER.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used when raising the credit entry during rollover of deposits.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CORR.RTN</field>
<desc>
            <p>A local hook routine triggered when interest correction entry is raised for Annuity contracts with Annuity adjustment as YES. It takes precedence over INT.CORR.IMMED.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  It should be called with the following arguments (ACC.ID,'',INT.CORR.IMMED)</p>
            <p />
            <p>  where</p>
            <p />
            <p>  ACC.ID is input argument &amp; holds the AZ Account ID currently being processed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Y.INT.CORR.IMMED is output returned from this subroutine &amp; should hold the values of CURRENT, NEXT only.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OD.CHARGE.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a credit entry and a overdue charge repayment to a loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Not allowed for CREDIT CARD type of products.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Debit transaction code not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
            <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
            <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CORR.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan/deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a interest correction entry. Interest correction can be for various reason like preclosure or part withdrawal in deposits etc</p>
            <p />
            <p>VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p>TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p>Both debit / credit transaction code allowed.</p>
            <p>Refer to INT.CR.CAP for transaction codes that need to be setup.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
            <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Transaction Code to be used on the Debit entry generated by AZ.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The Transaction Code of the entry is used to determine the references and narratives to be printed on statements.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The Debit/Credit indicators within the Transaction Code table are not used to verify this input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The transaction code defined here should be used or duplicated in any other field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If the ACCT.SYNC field is "Y" -then the transaction code defined here might be used as a default for the other leg of the transaction that it not affecting the loan / deposit when the transaction is triggered from AZ.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  To exemplify,</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In Credit Card type of loan, if the loan repayment takes place. Dr. will be to the internal/customer/nominated a/c and credit to the loan a/c. As debit side of the transaction is not affecting the loan (debit to a customer a/c)- the transaction code will be one inscribed in this field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be an existing code in Transaction Table.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.DR.MATURITY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to when raising the debit entry during normal deposit maturity.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAN.PRECLOSE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Loan Preclose implies closing down of the loan a/c well before the ORIGINAL maturity date- where Credit will be to the Loan a/c and Debit will be to the Repay a/c.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  When entered the system automatically identifies the transaction code as an EVENT of Loan Preclose.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The SYSTEM record must be defined in AZ.SETTLEMENT.PRIORITY file.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.ON.INT.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan/deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a tax on interest entry when the TAX.KEY is defined in AZ.ACCOUNT.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Both debit / credit transaction code allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Debit/Credit transaction code should be the same as the transaction code defined in TAX table.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  For instance, if TAX.KEY is defined as 10 in AZ.ACCOUNT, in the respective Tax table, the Credit/debit transaction code is defined as 243/244, then the same codes should be defined here.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOAN.REPAY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Loan Repay txn implies repayment of loan installment - where Credit will be to the Loan a/c and Debit will be to the Repay a/c.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  When this txn code is used it repays the loan based on the rules defined in AZ.SETTLEMENT.PRIORITY.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  When entered the system automatically identifies the transaction code as an EVENT of Loan Repay. Whenever repayment of loan is made through AZ.ACCOUNT, this transaction is used to identify the event, if ACCT.SYNC.is set to 'YES'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "id" in transaction application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
            <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
            <p>Condition id</p>
            <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
            <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.ADJ.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan/deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a interest adjustment entry.This is applicable only for Annuity contracts and if this entry is encountered, then the system shall debit AZINTADJ Suspense account instead of the underlying AZ Account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Only debit transaction code allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Value date in the entry should be same as the bank date(TODAY).</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Applicable only for ANNUITY contracts with Reduce limit as 'NO'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.SUS.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan/deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  It is applicable only for Annuity contracts . If ANNUITY.ADJUST is Yes at the AZ contract level and the ANNUITY amount defined is lesser than the interest for the period, then the system shall use this transaction code to debit AZINTADJ Suspense account &amp; credit AZ Account.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Only debit transaction code allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Applicable only for ANNUITY contracts .</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
            <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
            <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge property</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MATURITY.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Maturity txn implies complete and full closure of loan a/c- where Credit will be to the Loan a/c and Debit will be to the Repayment a/c.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  When entered the system automatically identifies the transaction code as an EVENT of Loan Maturity. When the loan is normally closed as per schedule of repayment then this TXN code is used on the credit side of the transaction.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.DR.CAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan / deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Interest Dr. Cap implies the Capitalization of interest to the loan a/c- where Debit will be to the loan a/c and Credit to the Interest Receivable category.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  When entered the system automatically identifies the transaction code as an EVENT of Interest Dr. Cap. When the interest is capitalized, this CODE is used on the Debit side of the Transaction for identifying the event.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In case of a loan during I schedule the system would raise an entry to debit the az.account with 392/391 as the txn code. During N schedule the system would raise an entry to credit the az account with the value defined in the first multi value of INT.CR.CAP.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In case of a deposit during I schedule the system would raise an entry to credit the az.account with 382/381 as the txn code. During N schedule the system would raise an entry to debit the az account with the value defined in the first multi value of INT.DR.CAP.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  When interest is to be paid manually then these fields could be multivalued and different txn codes can be defined if needed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in Transaction application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCOUNT. SYNC is set to 'Y'</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The following table gives the txn codes that have to be defined in addition to any other txn codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Field Name Interest liq acct Loan Deposit</p>
            <p />
            <p>  INT.CR.CAP Yes 392 382</p>
            <p />
            <p>  No 391 381</p>
            <p />
            <p>  INT.DR.CAP Yes 392 382</p>
            <p />
            <p>  No 391 381</p>
            <p />
            <p>  INT.CORR.TXN Yes 396 386</p>
            <p />
            <p>  No 395 385</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OD.INTEREST.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a credit entry and a overdue interest repayment to a loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Not allowed for CREDIT CARD type of products.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Debit transaction code not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.DR.PART</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a part withdrawal of a deposit.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEP.DR.PRE.CLOSURE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is due to preclosure of a deposit.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
            <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CR.CAP</field>
<desc>
            <p>This pertains to AZ deposits where on Capitalisation date interest is capitalized to the credit of the deposit acct using this TXN code.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This txn code is used capitalization of interest to the deposit acct, where Credit will be to the deposit acct and debit to the interest payable category.</p>
            <p />
            <p>When TXN code is entered the system will automatically identify the transaction code as event of Interest Credit Cap.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>Must be a valid 'ID' in Transaction application</p>
            <p>TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT</p>
            <p>Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to 'Y'</p>
            <p>Refer to INT.DR.CAP on the specific transaction codes that need to defined. This is not applicable for ANNUITY / CREDIT CARDS.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the Transaction Code to be used on the Credit entry generated by AZ.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The Transaction Code of the entry is used to determine the references and narratives to be printed on statements.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The Debit/Credit indicators within the Transaction Code table are not used to verify this input.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If the ACCT.SYNC field is "Y" -then the transaction code defined here might be used as a default for the other leg of the transaction that it not affecting the loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  The transaction code defined here should be used or duplicated in any other field.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  See example in DR.TXN.CODE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  1-10(Max Value) numeric characters Transaction Code. (Mandatory Input)</p>
            <p>  The Maximum value is specified in EB.OBJECT for TRANSACTION. </p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be an existing code in Transaction Table.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DRAWDOWN.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  Draw down Txn implies making a draw down on the loan a/c- where Debit will be to the Loan a/c and Credit will be to the Nominated a/c.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  When entered the system automatically identifies the transaction code as an EVENT of Draw down. Whenever, loan is drawn this TXN code is used to identify the event, if ACCT.SYNC.is set to 'Y'.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid id in transaction application.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e loan repay, Draw down etc</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRINCIPAL.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a credit entry and a principal repayment to a loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Not allowed for CREDIT CARD type of products.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Debit transaction codes not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
            <p />
            <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
            <p />
            <p>OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
            <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MANDATORY</p>
            <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OD.PRINCIPAL.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the loan side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a credit entry and a overdue principal repayment to a loan.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Not allowed for CREDIT CARD type of products.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Debit transaction codes not allowed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEPOSIT.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to signify that the entry is a deposit credit entry. If MULTI is set as 'Y' then a sub account is created else a principle increase is made.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  In case of clearing credits the transction code for collection, the txn code defined in CQ.PARAMETER / ACCOUNT.PARAMETER that is used when the cheque is marked as CLEARED, has to be defined here.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.SYNC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Allowed values are 'YES' and ''.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  If 'YES' then the working balance in a/c and the principal in AZ.ACCOUNT created will be in sync. This can be achieved by using specific transaction codes for specific AZ related events. (For more details on transaction codes and events, refer the help text for various fields like DRAWDOWN.TXN). If the input is 'NULL', the two balances might not be in harmony.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  If 'YES', then an entry over the AZ.ACCOUNT should contain a valid txn code (apart from DR.TXN.CODE and CR.TXN.CODE) defined in its APP so that it knows how to process the entry within AZ.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Permitted values either 'YES' or ''.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Once input the values cannot be changed.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BONUS.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used while raising the bonus entry in SAVINGS PLAN type of deposit.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHARGE.DR.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>Valid Transaction code should be entered. Txn codes that affect the deposit side (Debit or Credit) are identified and categorized as TXN codes.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  This txn code is used to identify the entries that are raised while charging the late payment fee.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>  VALIDATIONS</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Must be a valid "ID" in transaction application</p>
            <p />
            <p>  TXN codes are input to identify the EVENT i.e. loan repay, Draw down etc.</p>
            <p />
            <p>  Mandatory input if the ACCT. SYNC is set to "Y".</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
