<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.PRD.PRF.UI.BEHAVIOUR</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Defines the behaviour and context flow.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>STMT.NOS</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ENQUIRY.ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Attributes to enable / disable the enquiry features: </p>
            <p />
            <p>  NO.SELECTION -  restricts  enquiry selection screen embeeded on enquiry response window. </p>
            <p>  ALL.DATA   - to display all the selected records. </p>
            <p>  NO.COLUMN.HEADER –  restricts the column header being displayed on the enquiry results.window. </p>
            <p>  NO.TOOLBAR – to disable the enquiry toolbar display. </p>
            <p>  ZERORECORD.DISPLAY – blank screen will be displayed when no records are selected.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOLBAR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Indicates the pre-defined list of toolbar types.</p>
            <p>  • APPLICATION</p>
            <p>  • ENQUIRY</p>
            <p>  • ENQUIRY.SELECTION</p>
            <p>  • CONTRACT</p>
            <p>  • SIGN.OFF</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
            <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.6</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
            <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
            <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOOLBAR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Browser toolbar to be associated with toolbar types. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
            <p />
            <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
            <p>These are called classic products</p>
            <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOW.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A generic value field specifying what to display at this point in the workflow.  This should either be a EB.COMPOSITE.SCREEN record Id or a URL to a static page.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.3</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
            <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.4</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
<desc>
            <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
            <p />
            <p>Error block further processing</p>
            <p>Override Give an override</p>
            <p>Information  Record details only</p>
            <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
            <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
            <p />
            <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
            <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
            <p />
            <p>OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
            <p />
            <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
            <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
            <p />
            <p>MANDATORY</p>
            <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.VALUE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
<desc>
            <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field represents the key to the product level conditions of a property class</p>
            <p>This field basically has three components seperated by a hyphen</p>
            <p>Condition id</p>
            <p>Currency - if the property class is currency based. By default takes up local currency</p>
            <p>Effective date - if the property class is dated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
            <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
<desc>
            <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.1</field>
<desc>
            <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.2</field>
<desc>
            <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
            <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYSTEM.ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Attributes to turn off the system level features:</p>
            <p>  NO.AUTOCOMPLETE  - disable the IE’s auto complete feature. </p>
            <p>  SIMPLE.INTERFACE - turns off all the above mentioned contract and enquiry features.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>Allowed values are</p>
            <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
            <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
            <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
            <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
<desc>
            <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Describes this condition record and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p>This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the Description of the property condition in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
<desc>
            <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ID.COMP.5</field>
<desc>
            <p>Reserved for future use</p>
            <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
            <p>System field no input allowed</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FLOW.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>A generic type field specifying the type of flow being defined.  Values allowed are :-</p>
            <p>  “FIRST.LOGIN” - action to be performed when a new user logs in for the very first time.</p>
            <p>  “EVERY.LOGIN” – action to be performed when a user logs in.</p>
            <p>  “INITIAL.SCREEN” – initial composite screen to be displayed after a user logs in. </p>
            <p>  “POST.COMMIT” – action to be performed following a successful commit.</p>
            <p>  “LOGOUT” - action to be performed when a user logs out.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
            <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
            <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
            <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
            <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
            <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
            <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p>Valid charge property</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
<desc>
            <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
            <p />
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMMIT.ACTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Multi-value defining the actions to be performed when committing a record.  Valid values are :-</p>
            <p>  Blank – normal commit processing.</p>
            <p>  “CONFIRM” – General override to be raised confirming committal of the contract whilst displaying the contract in See mode (using either the same VERSION or an alternative VERSION record).</p>
            <p>  “PASSWORD” – User’s password must be supplied for successful committal.</p>
            <p>  “ONE.TIME.PASSWORD” – A one-time password must be supplied for successful committal.</p>
            <p>  “MEMORABLE.DATA” - User’s memorable data must be supplied for successful committal.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CONTRACT.ATTRIBUTES</field>
<desc>
            <p>Attributes to enable / disable the contract features:</p>
            <p>  MULTI.VERSION.HEADERS – enables version multi-line version headers to be displayed. </p>
            <p>  NO.AUTO.LAUNCHES – restricts auto launch of enquiries. </p>
            <p>  NO.CALENDAR  -  Hides the calendar icon for date type fields. </p>
            <p>  NO.CHECKFILE.ENRICHMENT – turns off the check file enrichment feature. </p>
            <p>  NO.CONTEXT.ENQUIRIES – disables the context enquiries.</p>
            <p>  NO.DROPDOWNS – disable the dropdown feature. </p>
            <p>  NO.HEADER.TAB  -  won’t display the contract header. </p>
            <p>  NO.HOT.FIELDS – disable the hot fields functionality. </p>
            <p>  NO.WEB.VALIDATION.FIELDS – disable the web validation.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
            <p />
            <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
            <p />
            <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
