<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.SIM.CHARGE.OVERRIDE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The charge override property class is used to waive or negotiate any adhoc charges triggered for an activity. i.e When an activity collects a activity charges or periodic charges this property class is automatically added to the properties tab so that user can negotiate the charge amount collected by the system.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the name of the property that this arrangement level condition relates to</p>
                <p>Name is defined in AA.PRORERTY table</p>
                <p>System maintained field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the Effective Date of this property condition</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
                <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Not used for Arrangement Conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input not allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will hold two values either DUE or CAPITALISE</p>
                <p>This Field denote which application method(DUE or CAPITALISE)should be taken while applying periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will have to accept a valid T24 period.</p>
                <p>This Field will denote the application period for current aplication method.</p>
                <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
                <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When this arrangement condition is triggered, It is possible to include any charge property that is not even triggered or configured in the product by a manually adding it</p>
                <p>To validate if the property is available in the arrangement.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the key to the accounting entries raised by the activity being applied to this arrangement property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a "-"):</p>
                <p>Arrangement Id</p>
                <p>Property name&gt;</p>
                <p>Effective Date</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.ACT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Total of negotiated charge collected.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.DEF.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the total charge computed by the system.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHG.ACT.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The waived charge amount which is to be collected.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Eg:</p>
                <p>Consider an activity 'LENDING-INCREASE-TERMAMOUNT' when triggered collects an charge of 500 USD.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Being a privilege customer to the bank, the bank decides to waive the charge amount of 500 USD to 250 USD. This 250 USD is specified in this field so that Bills and accounting entries are raised for this charge amount.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHG.AMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The actual charge amount which is computed by the system. It is not necessary that the user should input this field. This is automatically populated when an activity charge or periodic charge is calculated by the system.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Eg:</p>
                <p>Consider an activity 'LENDING-INCREASE-TERMAMOUNT' when triggered collects an charge of 500 USD.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This 500 USD is defined in this field. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHG.DESC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Description about why the charge has been negotiated when triggering the activity.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHG.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies what type of charge is being collected. This is also automatically populated by the system depending upon the charge calculated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>It can accept 2 values 'ACT.CHARGE' - Activity Charge; 'PR.CHARGE' - Periodic Charge.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>p&gt;Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
