<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <title>AA.SIM.CHARGEOFF</title>
        <table>AA.SIM.CHARGEOFF</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>"For a variety of reasons, a Bank may be required to ‘charge-off’ the principal balance of a loan.  This may be determined by the Bank, or can occur after bank examiners determine a borrower to be high risk (loan repayment has been deemed ‘doubtful’) and/or the loan is considered under collateralized.  This can be a partial charge-off, a series of partial charge-off transactions, or a total charge-off.  The loan may or may not be in non-accrual status when processing a partial charge-off.  Also, the customer is unaware, the customer’s loan record remains intact and payments are processed accordingly (further described below under Shadow Accounting).</p>
            <p>The following features are achieved through Charge-off:</p>
            <p>• A full charge off or multiple partial charge-off transactions should be allowed. </p>
            <p>• Interest on the Charge-off balance should accrue but is not passed to income (similar to NAB).</p>
            <p>• Allow reversal of Charge-off transactions</p>
            <p>• Enable the removal from Charge-off or partial removal from Charge-off (i.e. a lessening of the Charge Off amount).</p>
            <p>• Dual Accounting – i.e. having two sets of books; the Customer Record vs. the Bank Record and applying payments “independently” to the two records."</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>FINANCIAL.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Provides a feature to specify different credit allocation based on arrangement's Financial Status i.e. based on arrangement being suspended or not.</p>
                <p>This will accept three options</p>
                <p>Both - Only one credit allocation irrespective of arrangement being  suspended or Not. If ""Both"" selected then no other option can be specified.</p>
                <p>Performing - Specifies credit allocation to be applied on the arrangement when it is not suspended. Both is not alllowed and system would insist to define Suspend if not defined.</p>
                <p>Suspended - Specifies credit allocation to be applied on the arrangement when it is suspended. Both is not allowed and system would insist to define Performing if not defined."</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APPLICATION.ORDER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"This field is used to specify in which order credit allocation should be applied on the bills. This is similar to the field APPLICATION.ORDER in PAYMENT.RULES. Options are</p>
                <p>OLDEST.FIRST - Credit allocation will start from oldest bills and move towards latest bill.</p>
                <p>NEWEST.FIRST - Credit allocation will start from latest bill and move towards oldest bill."</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APPLICATION.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"This field is used to specify how credit allocation should be applied on the arrangement during repayment. This is similar to the field APPLICATION.TYPE in PAYMENT.RULES. Options are</p>
                <p>BILL.PROPERTY - Credit allocation will be on bills and property wise</p>
                <p>BILL.DATE - Credit allocation will be on bills and bill payment date wise</p>
                <p>CURRENT - Credit allocation will be on current balances."</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRODUCT.KEY</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BALANCE.PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will specify the property for which credit allocation to be applied and the sequence will be the order in which properties are specified. Only Account and Interest properties are allowed.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BALANCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"This field will specify the order of credit allocation on the balance types and the sequence will be the order in which balance types are repaid. Three options available are</p>
                <p>BILLED - All of the due/overdue balances are to be setttled</p>
                <p>CURRENT - Current bank balances are to be setted</p>
                <p>CHARGEOFF - Charged off balances are to be settled"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHARGE.OFF.ORDER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"When arrangement is charged-off this attribute will specify in which order should the arrangement be charged off. This will accept two values.</p>
                <p>OLDEST.FIRST - Due/Overdue balances will be charged off first and then Current balances</p>
                <p>NEWEST.FIRST - Current balances will be charged off first and then Due/Overdue balances "</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
        </t>
    <t><field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACTIVITY</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>ACTION</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>WRITEOFF.ORDER</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
