<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.SIMULATION.RUNNER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>After the basic information for simulation has been captured, the next step is to actually run the simulation.AA.SIMULATION.RUNNER application is used to run the simulation from a given start date to end date.By using this application we can find the status of the Arrangement for particular period.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>RUN.T.ACT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes if a transaction activity has to be simulated or not. This field is associated with SIM.T.DATE.</p>
                <p>      Options YES or NO.</p>
                <p>      YES - Denotes transaction activity has to be simulated</p>
                <p>      NO - Denotes transaction activity need not be simulated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RUN.U.ACT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes if a user activity has to be simulated or not. This field is associated with SIM.U.DATE.</p>
                <p>      Options - YES or NO.</p>
                <p>      YES - Denotes user activity has to be simulated</p>
                <p>      NO - Denotes user activity is not required to be simulated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>S.ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes that a schedule activity has been simulated as on SIM.S.DATE</p>
                <p>      This field is system updated field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>S.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the amount that has been processed for the corresponding S.ACTIVITY</p>
                <p>      This field is system updated field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>S.RUN.STAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes that the corresponding activity is a scheduled activity. This field will be get updated as SCHEDULED</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SIM.CAPTURE.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the reference of the simulation capture for which the runner is associated with.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SIM.CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defaults the base currency for this arrangement. NOINPUT field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SIM.END.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes date upto which Simulation needs to run. It left as NULL would run upto the Matuity date of the arrangement.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SIM.RUN.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Date on which this simulation is run. Usually defaults to TODAY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SIM.S.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This denotes the date on which a schedule activity has been simulated.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.REF</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the arrangement reference which can be an existing arrangement or a simulated arrangement.</p>
                <p>      If this field is input with an existing arrangement reference then it represents that existing arrangement is simulated.</p>
                <p>      If this field is input with a simulated arrangement reference then it represents that  arrangement is virtual</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SIM.T.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This denotes the date on which a transaction activity has been simulated.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SIM.U.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This denotes the date on which a user activity has been simulated.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This denotes the status of the simulation runner.</p>
                <p>      COMPLETED - SUCCESSFULLY -&gt; This denotes that runner has been executed successfully</p>
                <p>      COMPLETED - ERROR -&gt; This denotes that runner is completed but has got errors while executing</p>
                <p>      Processing -&gt; This denotes that runner is getting executed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>T.ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field can be input to simulate transaction activities like repayment, disbursement.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>T.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is updated during simulation when a relative activity is simulated by the system with the transaction amount used for the activity.</p>
                <p>This amount may be override using T.OVR.AMOUNT field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>System maintained field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>T.OVR.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field can be input with a transaction amount which the corresponding transaction can use for simulation. This amount overrides the system calculated amount in T.AMOUNT.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validations</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Standard amount field.</p>
                <p>Cannot be negative.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>T.RUN.STAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes that the corresponding activity is transaction activity. This field will be updated as TRANSACTION</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>U.ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field can be input to simulate a user activity like change interest, update charge</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>U.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field can be input with a user amount for the corresponding user activity</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>U.RUN.STAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes that the corresponding activity is user activity. This field will be updated as USER</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field allows the user to provide description for the simulation run</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ERR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This Field are used to trap error mesages in Simulation.</p>
                <p>  ERR.SOURCE and ERR.MESSAGE which are both associated MV sets.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  ERR.MESSAGE will show the actual returned error message</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ERR.SOURCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>   ERR.SOURCE will denote to the name of the property (like COMMITMENT) </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXECUTE.SIMULATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field allows the user to decide whehther the simulation can be executed to live arrangement. YES can be set if simulation status is simulation is successfull</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to provide information to the customer based on which customer can take appropriate actions. This field is primarily used during account closure where when during request closure simulation (CALCULATE-PAYOFF activity) this field will populate the details of where the account is being linked to. This information will help the customer to remove appropriate links and then proceed further. This field is for information purpose only.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INFO.SOURCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This will denote the name of the property for which corresponding messages are displayed Ex: PAYOFF</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RUN.S.ACT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes if the schedule activity has to be simulated or not. This field is associated with SIM.S.DATE</p>
                <p>      This field is system updated field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
