<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>AA.SCHEDULED.ACTIVITY</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>The file stores the list of activities that have been scheduled to run for this arrangement. It only stores the next run date of the activity and would update the subsequent date after that event.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>NEXT.RUN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This is the nearest date on which a activity is scheduled to run for this arrangement. This is the lowest date among the NEXT.DATE fields.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NEXT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date on which this activity is scheduled to run next.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTIVITY.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>The actual activity which needs to be triggered for the date. It has to be a valid entry in AA.ACTIVITY file</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ARRANGEMENT.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>The id to the scheduled activity file is a valid arrangement id.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EVENT.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p />
            <p>    This field denotes the actual event date of the activity. </p>
            <p> . The field PRIOR.DAYS in the CHANGE.PRODUCT class may be used for triggering this activity, a specific number of days prior to the actual event taking effect. For example, if a product is scheduled to change on 01-Apr, then the bank may trigger the CHANGE.PRODUCT 10 days prior to the actual event(say on 20-Mar) so that the user may negotiate on the new terms and a window is provided. In other words, even though the CHANGE.PRODUCT event ‘runs’ on the 20-Mar COB, it actually has a forward effective date of 01-Apr in its AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY so that the conditions are created for the forward date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>The date when this activity last ran. For the activity which is scheduled for the first time, this field would be null. But would be updated after the activity has run successfully.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

