<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.SIM.REPORTING</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The Property class is used by all products. This property class is used for reporting IFRS cash flows and also data to Position Management applicable for the Arrangement.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.POS.CLASS.CAT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies a category to build the default settlement account if the liquidation account is not defined in settlement condition for the property class/property</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Allowed values from 10000 to 19999</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXCLUDE.EIR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EXPECTED.TERM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the values in terms of period such as XXD(Days), XXW(Weeks), XXM(Months) and XXY(Year) where XX denotes any number.</p>
                <p>When the expected term is beyond the maturity date, maturity is considered as expected end date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IAS.CLASSIFICATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the classification of contract based on IFRS standard.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IAS.SUBTYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Sub type  for the corresponding classification defined in IAS.CLASSIFICATION field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be a valid sub type for the corresponding classification defined in IAS.CLASSIFICATION file.</p>
                <p>The field cannot be amended at arrangement level</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The action that was triggered on the arrangement property</p>
                <p>The action is taken from ACTIVITY.CLASS record of the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the effective date of the property condition</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
                <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>Not applicable at product level</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INCLUDE.FORWARD.RATES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether interest events are to be projected into   the future.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   The next interest movement will always be shown in the   Position Management system. Subsequent events will not be included unless    this field is defined. It may contain the following values:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      BOTH     - Show fixed and variable rate contract future payments</p>
                <p>      VARIABLE - Show only future payments for variable interest contracts</p>
                <p>      FIXED    - Show only future interest and commission payments for fixed</p>
                <p>                 rate contracts.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   A fixed rate contract is a contract where only FIXED.RATE is present in the Interest Property.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Can take any of the following values, FIXED VARIABLE BOTH or null</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MARGIN.OPERAND</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Margin Operand to be used while arriving rate using MARKET.MARGIN</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Allowed values - ADD,SUB</p>
                <p>Input is optional</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MARKET.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Market rate to calculate the NPV based on future cashflow information.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The field can either be a Fixed rate or PERIODIC.INTEREST key with prefix P</p>
                <p>Input is mandatory if IAS.CLASSIFICATION field is entered.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MARKET.MARGIN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Margin to calculate the NPV based on future cashflow information</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input is optional</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained.</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines which individual attribute (field) has the negotiation rules defined in fields "Nr.Negotiable" through to "Nr.Message"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Must be a valid field name within this property</p>
                <p>This field is part of a multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether to raise error or override message when rule is broken</p>
                <p>Allows only two values ERROR or OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>ERROR error message is raised</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE Override message is generated</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines named values to indicate if an option applies to the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE. More than one option can be associated with the NR.ATTRIBUTE, with certain restrictions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid Inputs are NEGOTIABLE, NON-NEGOTIABLE, OVERRIDE, FIX-VALUE, MANDATORY as described below: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE can be negotiated at the arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>NON-NEGOTIABLE</p>
                <p>The value of NON-NEGOTIABLE will indicate that the associated NR.ATTRIBUTE cannot be negotiated at the arrangement level. Both NEGOTIABLE and NON-NEGOTIABLE cannot be defined together</p>
                <p/>
                <p>OVERRIDE</p>
                <p>Specifies if a default override message should be generated if the default attribute is amended at the arrangement level. If OVERRIDE is not specified, no override will be generated.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>FIX-VALUE</p>
                <p>Specified if the field value is to be fixed at the arrangement level. If FIX-VALUE is not specified the field value will vary with the changes to the underlying product condition.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>MANDATORY</p>
                <p>Specifies if the attribute is mandatory for this product condition. Can only be specified where the attribute is not defined as mandatory in the property class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
                <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is possible to define negotiation rules in EB.COMPARISON.TYPE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.STANDARD.COMPARISON</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the negotiation rule that is linked to the field defined in "Nr.Attribute". If an attribute has a negotiation rule linked to it (in associated fields NR.TYPE, NR.VALUE and NR.MESSAGE) the attribute must be defined as negotiable.</p>
                <p>It is possible to define more than one negotiation rule for an attribute</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</p>
                <p>This is a multi value set of fields</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the value that links to the rule in field "Nr.Type"</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.CAPITALISE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Where  a Charge payable/Charge receivable and Interest Payable/receivable is capitalised, the Position class corresponding to the nature of item i.e. charge or interest, a position class is defined here. For example, in case of Charge, it can be AAPMC and in case of interest it can be AAPMN.</p>
                <p>To show expected movements for these capitalisation events in case of undisbursed/unfunded contracts the 4th Character will be replaced by “E”, i.e AAPEC or AAPEN.</p>
                <p>Validation:</p>
                <p>Must exist on the table PM.POSN.CLASS and mandatory for Property class/Property other the Principal Property class/Property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.DECREASE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>PM Position class for Principal Decrease event under GAP is specified here. From the Position class defined here, the Position class for Principal Decrease event under CAS is derived by replacing the 3rd and 4th characters with those of the Position class defined for the category code of the settlement Account in PM.AC.PARAM.</p>
                <p>Where the timing for Disbursal or funding event is not certain, the Position classes built will have the 4th Character as “E” .</p>
                <p>For example, the User has defined AAPMD for GAP event, the CAS position class is derived as AAXXD, where XX are taken from PM.AC.PARAM corresponding to the category code of the settlement Account. The Position class for expected event is then built as AAPED for GAP and AAXED for CAS ( X is from PM.AC.PARAM)</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must exist in PM.POSN.CLASS and mandatory for Principal Property class/Property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.FX</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Position Class used to show the currency Position in FXP Position reference if the transaction gives raise to currency Position. The Currency Position so shown is real FX position and not Forward FX Position.</p>
                <p>Validation Rule:</p>
                <p>Must exist on the table PM.POSN.CLASS.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.INCREASE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>PM Position class for Principal Increase event for GAP is specified here. From the Position class defined here, the Position class for Principal Increase event for CAS is derived by replacing the 3rd and 4th characters with those of the Position class defined for the category code of the settlement Account in PM.AC.PARAM.</p>
                <p>Where the timing for Disbursal or funding event is not certain, the Position classes built will have the 4th Character as “E” .</p>
                <p>For example, the User has defined AAPMI for GAP event, the CAS position class is derived as AAXXI,  where XX are taken from PM.AC.PARAM corresponding to the category code of the settlement Account. The Position class for expected event is then built as AAPEI for GAP and AAXEI for CAS ( X is from PM.AC.PARAM)</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must exist in PM.POSN.CLASS and mandatory for Principal Property class/Property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.MATURITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>PM Position class for Principal Maturity event for GAP is specified here. From the Position class defined here, the Position class for Start event for CAS is derived by replacing the 3rd and 4th characters with those of the Position class defined for the category code of the settlement Account in PM.AC.PARAM.</p>
                <p>Where the timing for Disbursal or funding event is not certain, the Position classes built for maturity will have the 4th Character as “E”.</p>
                <p>For example, the User has defined AAPMM for GAP Start event, the CAS position class is derived as AAXXM, where XX are taken from PM.AC.PARAM corresponding to the category code of the settlement Account. The Position class for expected event is then built as AAPEM for GAP and AAXEM for CAS ( X is from PM.AC.PARAM)</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must exist in PM.POSN.CLASS and mandatory for Principal Property class/Property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>All the ACTIVITIES with related AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS containing activity type as CASHFLOW shall trigger cash flow event by default . But if  any activity need not trigger a cash flow then the Activity name to be input in this field and the associated field CASH.FLOW to be set as 'NO'</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input is optional</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.NEW.ROLLOVER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the rollover maturity event for the deal. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS' and mandatory for principal property class/property is defined</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.OLD.ROLLOVER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the position class to which the User wants to relate the Previous Maturity movement for the deal.</p>
                <p>Validation Rule:</p>
                <p>Must exist on the table “PM.POSN.CLASS” and is mandatory for Principal Property class/Property is defiend.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.OVERDUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Position class defined here represents the Overdue amount receivable either in a loan or a savings plan instalment in CAS report under CAL line.</p>
                <p>Validation rule:</p>
                <p>Must exist on the table “PM.POSN.CLASS” and is mandatory if Overdue balances are opted to be shown in CAS report.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.REPAYMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Position class to which the User wants to relate the Principal Instalment Payment event ( a loan instalment or a savings plan instalment). If AAPMR is the position class defined for GAP, then the Position class for CAS is derived as AAXXR (XX is taken from the position class defined in PM.AC.PARAM for the category code of the settlement Account). </p>
                <p>To show expected movements for Undisbursed/unfunded contracts without any schedule the 4th character will be replaced by “E” i.e it wil be AAXER ( X is taken from PM.AC.PARAM)</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must exist on the table PM.POSN.CLASS and mandatory for all property class/property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.ROLLOVER.START</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Position Class to which the user wants to relate the rollover start movement for the deal. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS' and mandatory for principal property class/property is defined</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.START</field>
            <desc>
                <p>PM Position class for Principal Start event for GAP is specified here. From the Position class defined here, the Position class for Start event for CAS is derived by replacing the 3rd and 4th characters with those of the Position class defined for the category code of the settlement Account in PM.AC.PARAM.</p>
                <p>Where the timing for Disbursal or funding event is not certain, the Position classes built will have the 4th Character as “E” .</p>
                <p>For example, the User has defined AAPMS for GAP Start event, the CAS position class is derived as AAXXS, where XX are taken from PM.AC.PARAM corresponding to the category code of the settlement Account. The Position class for expected event is then built as AAPES for GAP and AAXES for CAS ( X is from PM.AC.PARAM)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Must exist in PM.POSN.CLASS and mandatory for Principal Property class/Property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>POS.CLASS.UNALLOCATED</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Position class to build the Balances in UNC ( Unallocated Credit Balance) if the same are opted to be included in the CAS report under CAL line.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Exist on the table 'PM.POSN.CLASS' and mandatory for principal property class/property is defined</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>Allowed values are</p>
                <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
                <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
                <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The key to the arrangement property condition.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge can be collected when the periodic rule is broken</p>
                <p>This field denotes the charge property. The property and its condition is</p>
                <p>defined the product designer and validated during publishing</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Valid charge property</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>All the properies of the  Activity for which CASH.FLOW is not 'NO' shall be included in cash flow .But if  Property  need not be included in cash flow calculations, then the  Property name to be input in  field PROPERTY and the associated field EXCLUDE.EIR to be set as 'YES'. for eg, Penalty interest property of Interest property class need not be included in EIR calculations.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input is optional</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.CLASS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User can specify the Property Class to which the Position Classes have to be associated with. This gives the flexibility to the User to define the relevant Position Classes for each of the Property classes</p>
                <p/>
                <p>For example, user can configure different set of position classes for interest and principal. If the property class is defined then properties related to this property class will not be allowed in PROPERTY.ID.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Should be a valid record in AA.PROPERTY.CLASS</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROPERTY.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the property to which the user wants to relate the position class. This definition allows users to configure different combination of position class for each property. </p>
                <p>For example, user can configure different set of position class for adminfee and processingfee.If the property is defined then property class of this property is not  allowed in PROPERTY.CLASS field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Should be a valid record in AA.PROPERTY</p>
                <p>If Property class relating to this property should not have been defined in the field Property Class.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CASH.FLOW</field>
            <desc>
                <p>All the ACTIVITIES with related AA.ACTIVITY.CLASS containing activity type as CASHFLOW shall trigger cash flow event by default . But if  any activity need not trigger a cash flow then the Activity name to be input in  field ACTIVITY.NAME and the associated field CASH.FLOW to be set as 'NO'</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Values - YES , null shall trigger cash flow and NO shall not trigger cashflow.</p>
                <p>Input is optional</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for property conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UPDATE.OVERDUE.POS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether the user want to include the overdue movements for the contract     balances in CAS report.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Allowed values are Y or null</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field - lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEALER.DESK</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If provided by the User, the same gets defaulted to the reporting property attached to an Arrangement. Else, it is defaulted to "00"</p>
                <p>Validation Rules : </p>
                <p>Alpha or Numeric or combination of both as allowed in DEALER.DESK table. Must be an existing ID on the DEALER.DESK table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines whether all attributes (fields) can be negotiable or not.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>This field is Mandatory</p>
                <p>Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
