<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <title>AA.SIM.CONSTRAINT</title>
        <table>AA.SIM.CONSTRAINT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The constraint property class is used by all the products to restrict backdated activities. Allowed restriction types are  1. INTEREST.PERIOD, 2. STATEMENT.PERIOD, 3. RENEWAL, 4. PERIOD, DATE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>INITIAL.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates a hard date prior to which backdating would be restricted. This could be used along with relative types like INTEREST.PERIOD, STATEMENT.PERIOD, PERIOD and RENEWAL options. If a date is stated along with the above types, system would first validate the relative dates and compare them against this date and take this date if it is greater than the computed date. The field may be used when the user wants to restrict backdating from a specific date – but still wants to honor the relative options going forward on those arrangements.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation: </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Optional field.</p>
                <p>Should be a Valid date.</p>
                <p>Not allowed with DATE option.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the option chosen is OVERRIDE on RESULT field, a user defined OVERRIDE message may be stated here. This is only to differentiate one override from other when different options are chosen. If no message is stated, a default generic override message would be used.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Optional field.  If no message is stated, system would use the default override message -  AA-CONSTRAINT.VIOLATED</p>
                <p>Should be a valid entry in OVERRIDE application</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the actual period of constraint. The various options of the field are:</p>
                <p>If TYPE is stated as STATEMENT.PERIOD, RENEWAL - no input to this field would be allowed. </p>
                <p>If TYPE is stated as INTEREST.PERIOD -  Allows a numeric value in this field (for example, no backdating prior to 3 interest periods). If nothing is stated, system would not allow any backdating prior to current interest period by default</p>
                <p>If TYPE is stated as PERIOD – A valid IN2PERIOD value should be stated in this field. The field is mandatory with this option</p>
                <p>If TYPE is stated as DATE – A Valid date value should be stated in this field. The field is mandatory with this option</p>
                <p>Cannot be stated if no option is chosen in TYPE field.</p>
                <p>Validation:</p>
                <p>Optional field</p>
                <p>Cannot be stated if TYPE field is not set.</p>
                <p>Valid Numerical value, Period or date allowed based on the TYPE stated</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RESULT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the outcome of the restriction.</p>
                <p>The field is mandatory when TYPE field is chosen. Otherwise, could be left blank.</p>
                <p>ERROR – Any violation of constraint would result in a Error and would stop the activity</p>
                <p>OVERRIDE – Any violation of constraint would result in Override and would require approval to proceed with the activity. The override could be converted to an error if need be in OVERRIDE application</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the constraint type. The options allowed are:</p>
                <p>INTEREST.PERIOD – Activity would be restricted and governed by the Interest period of the arrangement. For example, to restrict any activity past the billing period, this option may be used.</p>
                <p>STATEMENT.PERIOD – Constraint would be based on when the statement was last generated for this account. When multiple statements are generated(including special ones), the latest statement date them would be taken and any date prior to that would be restricted.</p>
                <p>RENEWAL – When this option is chosen, any activity prior to the last renewal date would be restricted</p>
                <p>PERIOD – User could state a specific period(say 1M, 6M etc) to indicate specific periods before which the activity would be restricted</p>
                <p>DATE – Indicates a date prior to which back dating would be restricted</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Non Mandatory field.</p>
                <p>Valid options are INTEREST.PERIOD, STATEMENT.PERIOD, RENEWAL, PERIOD and DATE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DETAIL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates further details to support the TYPE stated in the TYPE field.</p>
                <p>If INTEREST.PERIOD is stated in the TYPE field, Valid Interest property whose billing consideration needs to be stated here. If the PROPERTY.TYPE is set as “Accrue by Bills” for  Penalty  Interest property, then the interest property should not allowed in DETAIL field. The field is mandatory when TYPE is INTEREST.PERIOD.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Optional field</p>
                <p>Mandatory if TYPE is stated as INTEREST.PERIOD</p>
                <p>Not allowed for other TYPE options.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ERROR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the option chosen is ERROR on RESULT field, a user defined EB.ERROR may be stated here. This is only to differentiate one error from other when different options are chosen. If no message is stated, a default generic error message would be used.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>Optional field. If no message is stated, system would use the default error message -  AA-CONSTRAINT.VIOLATED</p>
                <p>Should be a valid entry in EB.ERROR</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
        </t>
    <t><field>K.TYPE</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
