<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.SIM.OVERDUE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>After a bill is made due, the bills are subject to aging process as per the OVERDUE property setting for the arrangement. A number of options are required to define the aging periods, statuses and accounting treatment of the outstanding balance.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>                             The system can apply penalty interest and charges based on overdue and current balances. The AA module allows this to be configured in a flexible manner when creating products.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Bill Type would be picked from EB.LOOKUP instead of the hard-coded values of PAYMENT, EXPECTED</p>
                <p>However all the options would not be available for this field within PAYMENT.SCHEDULE</p>
                <p>The following values would not be available,</p>
                <p>1.INFO</p>
                <p>2.PR.CHARGE</p>
                <p>3.ACT.CHARGE</p>
                <p>4.DEF.CHARGE</p>
                <p>Other user defined values may be given which then can be used in Overdue PC to define different aging rules for the BillType</p>
                <p>When a user defined value is captured it would be assumed as PAYMENT type Bill, and not “Expected” type bill</p>
                <p>Validations:</p>
                <p>•Standard lookup field</p>
                <p>•Maximum number of characters is restricted to 15</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CHANGED.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field lists all fields that have been negotiated for each dated version of the property. For a subsequently dated property, the attributes listed in this field will appear in "Negotiated.Fields" and only newly negotiated fields will appear on "Changed.Fields"</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.ATTR.OPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field - Allowed Values are RESETTING and NON-RESETTING.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities (for eg : change.product, rollover or reset) the property conditions will be reset from the product.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> NON-RESETTING - During any Renewal Activities property conditions will be maintained from the Arrangement level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Not used in Arrangement/Sim level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p> Leaving the field blank sets NON-RESETTING as the default option.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.NEGOTIABLE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EFFECTIVE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>                             This field indicates the method of finding the value date for the accounting entries as a result of ageing status movement. The allowed values are DUE, STATUS or can be Blank. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>             DUE    - The value date will be the bill due date. </p>
                <p>             STATUS - The value date will be the ageing status effective date.</p>
                <p>             Blank  - The value date will be the bill's financial date.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               Example:</p>
                <p>               Suppose a bill has been made DUE on 30th November and its Finanacial date is say on 02 December. Subsequently when the bill moves to GRA (Grace) overdue status , say after 5 days from the due date, that is, on 5th December. The accounting value date for various values in this field would be: -</p>
                <p/>
                <p>               DUE            - 30th November</p>
                <p>               STATUS         - 5th Decemeber</p>
                <p>               When blank     - 2nd December</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the arrangement number, extracted from the first component of the id</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the name of the property that this arrangement level condition relates to</p>
                <p>Name is defined in AA.PRORERTY table</p>
                <p>System maintained field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the Effective Date of this property condition</p>
                <p>System updated field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
                <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID.COMP.6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>System field no input allowed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MANUAL.CHANGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Reserved for future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MOVE.BALANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>                            This field denotes if accounting entries are to raised for the overdue status movement. The field when set to YES would mean accounting entries are needed for status movement and the current status would be debited and previous status which has move balance set to YES or DUE balance type would be credited.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>             Valid options are YES and NO</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NEGOTIATED.FLDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No input and multi value field that lists the attributes on the arrangement property record that have been fixed and/or negotiated. These are stored when the arrangement level record is committed. When the arrangement level record is next used all items in the NEGOTIATED.FIELDS list will be maintained</p>
                <p>Once an attribute has been fixed or negotiated it will remain in negotiated field list on all subsequent dated versions of the property.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NOTICE.DAYS</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>                            This field represents the calendar days post to a aging status that a chaser advice to be sent.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                           Validation rules</p>
                <p>                           Accepts any number</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NOTICE.FREQ</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>                            The field represents a frequency in which the advice to be sent for the aging status. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                Both Notice days and frequency can be given, in which case, the system would produce advice after the notice days and thereon based on the frequency set, advices would be sent. If Notice days are not given, system would cycle the notice dates with the base as ageing status date. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                Validation rules</p>
                <p>                Should be a valid T24 freqeuncy</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.MESSAGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.OPTIONS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTIVITY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The activity that caused this arrangement property to be updated.</p>
                <p>The activity is taken from the underlying AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY request that caused the record to be modified</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.RESERVED2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Field - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.STD.COMP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Not used for Arrangement Conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input not allowed</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - not used for arrangement conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>System Field NoINPUT allowed -</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERDUE.STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>                             This field denotes the overdue or aging status of the arrangement. The list of values allowed is equal to the list defined in EB.LOOKUP file with the ID like AA.OVERDUE.STATUS*&lt;odStatus&gt;. For example, if PDO is an overdue status, then a record in EB.LOOKUP.FILE should be defined as AA.OVERDUE.STATUS*PDO.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard Override field containing override messages generated by amendments to this property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PAY.TOLERANCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field represents the tolerance percentage that needs to be applied on the bill's original amount.  The tolerance percentage is applied on the bill amount that was issued. It is then compared with the current outstanding amount in bill.  If the outstanding amount is within the tolerance then the bill is either not aged as specified in the field TOL.ACTION.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application method that needs to be applied to the periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>Allowed values are</p>
                <p>Due - The periodic rule charges are made due</p>
                <p>Capitalise - The periodic rule charges are capitalised</p>
                <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.APP.PERIOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the application period for the given periodic rule charges.</p>
                <p>The periodic rule charges will be applied at the end of the period. If the value defined is zero, then the charges are applied immediately.</p>
                <p>Standard T24 period field.</p>
                <p>Not inputtable at arrangement level</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.ATTRIBUTE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>These are set of Attributes which define the names of the rule, which will be applied on certain attributes of property classes over a period of time</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid record from AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AGE.ALL.BILLS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is set to indicate that all bills under the arrangement should be aged to this status. Usually this field is set to YES for a higher overdue status. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                             This is an optional field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                             Can take either YES or NO only.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.CHARGE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Not used for arrangement level conditions</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.MSG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Based on the PR.BRK.RES option selected, this will hold either an OVERRIDE or EB.ERROR id. By default the ids will be picked from the associated EB.COMPARISON.TYPE record. If CAP or FLOOR values are given, then the underlying AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS should have this type defined in it</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid OVERRIDE ID or EB.ERROR ID</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.BRK.RES</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When a rule is broken what action needs to be taken is defined here. Currently, the various options available are </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Error block further processing</p>
                <p>Override Give an override</p>
                <p>Information  Record details only</p>
                <p>CAP the rule value is to be used as a CAP if the rule is broken</p>
                <p>FLOOR the rule value is to be used as a FLOOR if the rule is broken</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be one of the above valid options</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.RESERVED.3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PR.VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the actual rule value, which will be applied on certain attributes of the property classes over a period of time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Input must be a valid data type defined in the corresponding</p>
                <p>AA.PERIODIC.ATTRIBUTE.CLASS record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STATUS.MVMT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is reserved for future use</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the key to the accounting entries raised by the activity being applied to this arrangement property</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUSPEND</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>                           This field represents whether the arrangement needs to be suspended when the current aging status is reached. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AGE.BILLS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>  This field denotes whether to consider the current bill for further aging when the bill is deemed to be settled (that is Delin.os.amt in the bill is zero and Aging.status is settled)</p>
                <p>              Validation rules</p>
                <p>              Valid options are BILL.STATUS or SETTLE.STATUS</p>
                <p>              BILL.STATUS allowed only BILL.SETTLEMENT has value BILL.TOTAL</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE4</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE5</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE6</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SYS.RESERVE7</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System field - reserved for future use</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TARGET.PRODUCT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the target classic product of the given property class</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The already existing T24 products are mapped using AA infrastructure</p>
                <p>These are called classic products</p>
                <p>These products are mapped to different property clases</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOL.ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the action to be taken when bill amount is within the tolerance set.  If it is set to REMAIN and if the bill amount is within the tolerance, the overdue status will not be changed and will remain in the same status.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOL.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>          This field represents the tolerance amount that can be set for the bill's outstanding amount. If the currency defined in bill matches the TOL.CCY, then the tolerance amount is taken from this field. If the outstanding amount is within the tolerance, then bill is either not aged or will be considered as repaid based on the setting in the field TOL.ACTION.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                        Validation rule</p>
                <p>                        Standard T24 amount field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AGEING</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field tells when the bill is to be moved to the specified aging status. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>                             There are two types of aging, one is by days and ther other by bills. When bills are to be aged by days, give the number of days (numeric value)  from the make due date and if it is by bills given the number followed by 'B' character. In both cases, the number defined should be in ascending order. An overdue definition should either be fully based on days or by bills, i.e., it is not possible to define a overdue status based on days and another status by bills.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                  A value of zero in this field indicates that the bill will move the overdue status on the same day the bill was made due.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                             This is a mandatory field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                             Can be either numeric value or numeric value suffixed with character 'B'. A value of zero cannot be set to more than one overdue status.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOL.CCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>                          This field denotes the tolerance currency. If the currency defined in bill matches the TOL.CCY, then the tolerance amount is taken from the field TOL.AMOUNT</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>                        Validation rule</p>
                <p>                        Standard T24 currency field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AGEING.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>                            This file denotes whether the aging should be based on days or by bills. This field is associated multivalue field starting from OVERDUE.STATUS  to EFFECTIVE.DATE</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                            Allowed inputs are DAYS and BILLS.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>                            If days, the value in the field AGEING denotes number of days.</p>
                <p>                            If bills,  the value in the field AGEING denotes number of bills</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARR.BILL.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Optional field to indicate which of the BillType aging rules determines overall arrangement aging status, and the resolved status would be updated in ARR.AGING.STATUS in AA.ACCOUNT.DETAILS</p>
                <p>As part of conversion this field would be updated as “PAYMENT” as only the bills that have BillType as “PAYMENT” were picked up for aging</p>
                <p>Validations:</p>
                <p>•Standard lookup field</p>
                <p>•Maximum number of characters is restricted to 15</p>
                <p>•INFO option not applicable for this field although it is part of the lookup values</p>
                <p>•No duplicate definition is possible</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ARRANGEMENT.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The key to the arrangement property condition. The key is comprised of the following components (delimited by a -):</p>
                <p>Arrangement Id</p>
                <p>Property name&gt;</p>
                <p>Effective Date</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BILL.SETTLEMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p/>
                <p>             This field represents whether the settlement is against the total bill oustanding that is bill is considered for delinquency processing. </p>
                <p>             Only the values BILL.TOTAL and null are allowed at present.  </p>
                <p>             If the value is BILL.TOTAL, the original repayment amount is compared with the total outstanding amount of the selected bill and if it happens to be greater than or equal to total outstanding amount, the bill is deemed to be settled.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
