<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>AA.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>For property classes which require Source balance amount for calculation, AA.SOURCE.CALC.TYPE record can be used to specify how the balance amount can be determined. </p>
            <p/>
            <p>Balance amount can be daily, average, highest, lowest, current or a routine may return the balance amount for a balance type. It is also possible to define credit or debit balance amount is required for calculations.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Base amount for calculation will be based on either a BALANCE, ACTIVITY or PROPERTY.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>BALANCE - Base amount of a property</p>
                <p>ACTIVITY - Transaction amount in AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY</p>
                <p>PROPERTY - Currently not supported</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>1. Mandatory Field.</p>
                <p>2. Valid Inputs are BALANCE, PROPERTY and ACTIVITY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BALANCE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will determine if Debit balance amomt is required or Credit balance amount is required for calculation or both are required. It will accept only  values -DEBIT,CREDIT,BOTH</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.END.DAY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.ROUTINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If CALCULATION is defined ROUTINE then a valid routine can be attached which will return the balance amount that can be used for calculations. Routine attached should be a valid record in EB.API.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>If CALC.TYPE is ROUTINE then this field is mandatory</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.START.DAY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CALC.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The following balance amounts can be determined on top of which calculations can be carried out.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>DAILY - Calculated on Daily balances</p>
                <p>AVERAGE - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>HIGHEST - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>LOWEST - Reserved for future use</p>
                <p>COUNT - Reserved for future use </p>
                <p>TXN.AMOUNT - Calculated on AA.ARRANGEMENT.ACTIVITY Amount( can be used for activity charges) </p>
                <p>ROUTINE - If Calculation type is routine then a valid routine should be attached in ROUTINE field of BALANCE.CALC.TYPE record</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field describes the activity in generic terms and is used for enrichment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>             This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the description of the ACTIVITY in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>1. Mandatory Field.</p>
                <p>2. Multi-language field</p>
                <p>3. Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MID.ACCOUNT.CLOSE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes whether the interest needs to be calculated for the month, if the arrangement was closed on or before the specified Calculation End Day.</p>
                <p>If set to NO, then no interest will be applied if the account was closed on or before the Calculation End Day. Setting the field to BLANK will allow the interest according to the minimum balance criteria. Here interest will not be paid even if closure happened on the Calc End Day becaue the End of day balance will become 0.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Optional input. BLANK or NO.</p>
                <p>Can only be set to NO if the BALANCE.TYPE is set to MINIMUM and for Monthly calculation</p>
                <p>Default = BLANK</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MID.ACCOUNT.OPEN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes whether the interest needs to be calculated for the month, if the arrangement was opened after the specified Calculation Start Day for the MINIMUM interest type.</p>
                <p>If set to NO, then no interest will be applied if the account was opened after the Calculation Start Day. Setting the field to BLANK will allow the interest according to the minimum balance criteria</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Optional input. BLANK or NO.</p>
                <p>Can only be set to NO if the BALANCE.TYPE is set to MINIMUM and for Monthly calculation</p>
                <p>Default = BLANK</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SOURCE.CALC.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the id of the  record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
