<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>AA</product>
<table>EB.COMPARISON.TYPE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>Comparison type defines rule that determines the acceptable difference in the arrangement attribute value when compared to the product default value. Rules can also be defined to restrict values being input dont exceed the desired limit.</p>
            <p />
            <p> Temenos will release the comparison type records. The definition of comparison type will contain the following information</p>
            <p />
            <p> • The types of data field that can use the comparison type. The use of comparison types can be restricted to fields of a specific data type to ensure that meaningful rules are defined, for example a tolerance check would make no sense defined against an alphanumeric field and would only be useful with rate and amount fields.</p>
            <p> • The name of the routine used to perform the comparison. E.g. the routine that will compare the arrangement value against the product default value and the rule tolerance.</p>
            <p> • The name of the routine used to perform the input validation in the product property definition</p>
            <p />
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>VALID.DATA.TYPE</field>
<desc>
            <p>List of system data types allowed to use this rule. I.e. values allowed in T(Z)&lt;1&gt;. No value specified implies that the comparison rule is suitable for all data types. </p>
            <p />
            <p> The data type defined in this field should match the data type of the field that is used for comparison.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.NAME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field denotes the ID of comparison type record.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPARISON.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is mandatory.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> The name of the subroutine used to validate the entered value for an arrangement against the defined default value in the product property definition. Also returns the value to be stored in the arrangement.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DESCRIPTION</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field describes the activity in generic terms and is used for enrichment.</p>
            <p />
            <p> This field can be expanded to allow the User to enter the description of the ACTIVITY in various languages. Each expansion of the field will correspond to a new Language as defined in the LANGUAGE table (Ref: GENERAL TABLES), and will indicate to the User the Language in which the Description must be entered.</p>
            <p />
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p> 1. Mandatory Field.</p>
            <p> 2. Multi-language field</p>
            <p> 3. Up to 35 type A (alphanumeric) characters.  </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.DEF.ROUTINE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is mandatory.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> The name of subroutine used to validate that the definition of the rule values in the property or standard comparison rule are correct.</p>
            <p />
            <p> The following are the routines that are used.</p>
            <p />
            <p> AA.SINGLE.VALUE.RULE.VAL - Validation of single values for single value rules such as Min, Max etc.</p>
            <p> AA.LIST.VALUE.RULE.VAL - Validates a list of values supplied for list or range checks.</p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.ERR.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is mandatory.</p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> The key to the EB.ERROR table to be used to generate an error message if the rule is broken. </p>
            <p />
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>RULE.OVE.MSG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is mandatory.</p>
            <p />
            <p> The key to the OVERRIDE table to be used to generate an override message if the rule is broken. </p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

