<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>AA</product>
        <table>EB.PROJECT.MANAGER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This Table is maintained by the system with all the items (records) created in a project using AA Product Builder.</p>
            <p>It has details like, application name, record key, company id for the record created. These details are also updated in another live table EB.PROJECT.DETAILS in a different format, where these details are held by Application/recordkey with the projects which are using these records</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>LINK.OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the override messages encountered when the project is committed, i.e. when all the records in the project are authorised</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.APPLICATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the name of the application name of the record which is already added to the project</p>
                <p>Associated multi-value fields between APPLICATION and RECORD.KEY fields"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.REC.COM</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the company code of the record which is already added to the project</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.RECORDKEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the record id of the record which is alread added to the project</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJECT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the project id, allowed format is PRJDDDDDXXXXXXX, DDDDD - is the current julian date of the system and XXXXXXX is the auto-generated unique sequence number for the current system date</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROJECT.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the type of project, currently only supports AA, which means created within AA Product Builder</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RECORD.KEY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the record id of the record which is amended in the project</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>USER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the USER who created the project</p>
                <p>System maintained field"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the current action performed on the project,</p>
                <p>ADD - Amended recrods to the project, ie either added or deleted to the project</p>
                <p>DELETE - Entire project to be deleted</p>
                <p>COMMIT - Authorise the records that are in the project and are in held status</p>
                <p>ARCHIVE - Archive the project"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APPLICATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the name of the application name of the record which is currently being added to the project</p>
                <p>Associated multi-value fields between APPLICATION and RECORD.KEY fields"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the company code of the record which is currently being amended in the project</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CREATION.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the project creation date</p>
                <p>System maintained"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the project details and is used for enrichment. Product Builder uses the description captured to update the description for the specified language</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FULL.DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Provides more detailed description of the project</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FUNCTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the T24 function of the record which is currently being amended in the project, could be either I - input or D - delete</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LAST.UPDATE.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Describes the date on which the project was last updated</p>
                <p>System maintained"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LINK.ERROR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Holds the error messages encountered when the project is committed, i.e. when all the records in the project are authorised</p>
                <p>Either will have dependency errors or incorrect record details for the application"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
