<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>OC</product>
<table>OC.PARAMETER</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

   <p>OC.PARAMETER is a system level table to control the additional new aspects relating to OTC derivatives as per the Regulatory requirements in terms of Reporting, Clearing and Execution.</p> 
        <p> Parameters relating to T24 Bank are defined herein to meet the requirements of regulatory reporting and to control the workflows relating to Clearing and execution.</p></ovdesc>
            
</overview>

<menu>
<t>
<field>OC.PARAM.KEY</field>
<desc>
            
            <p>Holds the ID of OC.PARAMETER.</p>
<p>It should be a valid company ID.</p>
            
        </desc>
</t>

<t>
<field>BANK.LEI</field>
<desc>
            <p>Legal Entity Identifier of the T24 bank. LEI will be used for precise, reliable, and unique identification of each party in a derivative trade. </p>

                <p>Validation Rules :</p>
          
           <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            <p>Upto 40 alphanumeric characters can be allowed.</p></desc>
          
         </t>

<t>
<field>REGULATOR</field>
<desc>
            <p>Regulator Name /ID, whose regulations, T24 bank has to comply with. For example, ESMA, CFTC, HKMA etc., </p>
<p>This is a key field in OC.PARAMETER.</p>
<p>Mandatory field.</p>

       <p>Validation Rules:</p>
          
            <p>Should be a valid OC.REGULATOR ID.</p>
            <p></p>
                                    </desc>
            </t>


<t>
<field>USI.NAME.SPACE</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the name space given by CFTC or any other regulator as applicable to T24 bank.</p>
            <p> Part of Unique Transaction Identifier (UTI) where ever  T24 bank is generating the UTI. </p>
<p>Optional field.</p>
<p></p>

    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                      <p>20 character alphanumeric.</p>
            <p></p>
                          </desc>
            
</t>



<t>
<field>NAT.COMP.AUTHORITY</field>
<desc>
           
<p>National Competent Authority.</p>
 <p>Denotes local country regulator ID as applicable to EU countries. </p>
<p></p>
<p></p>

    <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                      <p>Should be a valid OC.REGULATOR ID.</p>
            <p></p>
                          </desc>
            </t>

<t>
<field>NOVATION.TYPE
</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates how the system should handle novation for cleared trades and will be used as and when Novation functionality is introduced.</p>
<p>Optional.</p>
<p></p>
      <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                      <p>Valid values are manual, auto and none.</p>

            <p></p>
                                    </desc>
            
</t>

<t>
<field>CLIENT.COLL.SEGRE
</field>
<desc>
            
<p>Client Collateral segregation.</p>
<p>This field indicates how the client collateral will  be handled ,i.e. is it reported along with bank collateral or separately. Applicable only when Collateral management functionality is built/used.</p>
<p>Optional. </p>
<p>Reserved for future use.</p>

                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
          
            <p>Valid values are Yes and None.</p>
            <p></p>
            
                        </desc>
            
</t>


<t>
<field>COLATERAL.REPORTED

</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates how the MTM value of collateral to be reported to Trade Repository. No workflows are envisaged based on the value in this field. Mainly for reporting requirement.</p>
<p> Optional Field.</p>
<p></p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                    <p>Valid values are per transaction and per portfolio.</p>
            <p></p>
            
                        </desc>
            
</t>



<t>
<field>THIRD.PARTY.REPORTING

</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field indicates whether the bank has delegated the reporting to a 3rd Party.</p>
<p> Optional Field.</p>
<p></p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                    <p>Valid values are yes and None.</p>
            <p></p>
            </desc>
            
</t>

<t>
<field>REGULATORY.CLASSIFICATION

</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the regulatory classification of the T24 Bank.</p>
<p> Optional Field.</p>
<p></p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                    <p>Valid values are Swap dealer, Major Swap participant, Financial Counterparty, Other.</p>
           
            </desc>
            
</t>

<t>
<field>DEFAULT.TRADE.REPOSITORY

</field>
<desc>
            <p>Denotes the default trade repository. Value given here will get defaulted at Trade level which can be overridden by the User.</p>
<p> Mandatory Field.</p>
<p></p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                    <p>Should be a valid OC.TRADE.REPOSITORY ID.</p>
            <p></p>
            </desc>
            
</t>

<t>
<field>UTI.USI.API

</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the UTI/USI generation routine/logic. The logic to generate the UTI/USI can be tailored to suit the User’s requirements. </p>
<p> Optional Field.</p>
<p></p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                    <p>Input should have a valid entry in PGM.FILE.</p>
            <p></p>
            </desc>
            
</t>

</menu>
</t24help>
