<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>EP</product>
        <title>SEPA.PARAMETER</title>
        <table>SEPA.PARAMETER</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This type ‘H’ table contains all the generic parameters useful for the SEPA interface application.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>     This is top most parameter table, used to default specific values for processing of SEPA transactions.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>     The file path, routines that need to be executed during file generation and after authorization of a transaction, T24 Bank information, List of Local fields created in Core Applications like FT and STO for SEPA development, Map fields that are used to extract information from the message for further processing.. etc have to be parametrized in this table.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>COMMIT.NUMBER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Number of transactions to be processed before enforcement of a physical update in the data base.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value from 1 to 5 and Mandatory field</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPANY.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field is used the specify the ID of the Company being used </p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 11 with type COM (Company Code)</p>
                <p>   Mandatory field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER.POSTING</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field defines how the accounting entry for a destination customer in a CUSTOMER.TO.BANK XML is being processed</p>
                <p>      ‘FT’: Processed through a generated FT.</p>
                <p>      ‘SO’: Posting to SEPA outward.</p>
                <p>      ‘SI’: Posting through SEPA inward.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value must be 2 characters and user can input only &apos;FT’ ‘SI’ and ‘SO’</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEBUG.OUTWARD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is defaulted with the Value &apos;Y&apos; which denotes &apos;storage of one record per outward transaction in the TOOLS library with detail of its elements’ mapping&apos;</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 1 and user can Input only &apos;Y&apos;</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DEFAULT.FTTC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Key to FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION table. If nothing is mentioned in Lower level parameter tables like SEPA.LAYOUT, this value is defaulted for processing of the transaction.</p>
                <p>      Used to define the customer’s payment conditions if this indication is missing from the transaction specific description.</p>
                <p>      It gives the default TRANSACTION.TYPE of any T24 application generated by the interface. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 4 type A (Alphanumeric). Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS. </p>
                <p>   Value should exist in FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DELIVERY.ROUTINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the name of the routine used by default to generate the customer’s advice @SEPA.FUP.DELIVERY is provided. </p>
                <p>      This delivery routine is the only one in the SEPA application requiring arguments:</p>
                <p>      Arguments IN : MAPPING.KEY&lt;1,1&gt;  Key to DE.MAPPING</p>
                <p>        MAPPING.KEY&lt;1,2&gt;  Value of APP.FORMAT</p>
                <p>      REVERSE.FLAG ‘R’ in case of reverse, ‘’ otherwise</p>
                <p>      Arguments OUT : DELIVERY.REF Key of the T24 generated advice</p>
                <p>        ERROR.MESSAGE Advice posting failure reason, if any</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DIRECTION.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used when the bank requires customer posting only through FT. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 and user can input only &apos;INWARD.GLOBAL&apos; &apos;INWARD.DETAIL&apos; and &apos;OUTWARD.GLOBAL&apos;</p>
                <p>   Multi value set</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DUPLICATE.PROC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the PROCESS.TYPE to be used incase of duplicate operations :</p>
		<p>       ‘OFT’: Direct booking on the customer account/Internal account/Nostro account through FUNDS.TRANSFER.</p>                                               
                <p>      ‘RET’: Booking on a transit account and generation of a return on SEPA.FOLLOW.UP, if possible, automatically authorized.  </p>
                <p>       ‘MAN’: Booking on a transit account and simultaneous non validated generation of a manual FUNDS.TRANSFER to accept and of a return/refund SEPA.FOLLOW.UP record. The manual validation of one of them will remove the other one.</p>                
                <p>      ‘NO’: No specific check or treatment on a line exactly identical to one already processed, speeding up the processing. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value from 2 to 3. User can Input only &apos;NO&apos; &apos;RET&apos; &apos;MAN&apos; and &apos;OFT&apos;</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EB.SYSTEM.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Field contains the Content given to the SYSTEM.ID field of generated entries for further distinction.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric) and Value must exist in EB.SYSTEM.ID application</p>
                <p>   Associated multi value set of field APPLICATION.ID</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ENTRIES.BY.LINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is defaulted with the Value &apos;Y&apos; which denotes Forced accounting entries on every inward and outward transactions. Allows the use of other accounts that those calculated by SEPA standard parameter tables using a validation routine. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 1 and user can Input only &apos;Y&apos;</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AFT.AUTH.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Name, prefixed by @, of routines to be executed after the whole processing of a transaction (but prior to the automatic validation of a return / refund for an inward).</p>
                <p>      This allows to modify both accept FT and refusal SEPA.FOLLOW.UP in inward as well as updating other local applications.</p>
                <p>      These generic routines will be executed prior to those at specific transaction level.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric). </p>
                <p>   Multi value subset of DUPLICATE.PROC</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FILE.DIRECTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This fields is defaulted with Values ‘INWARD’ or ‘OUTWARD’ and Associates the multi-value to a given interface way.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value from 6 to 7 characters and Mandatory field. </p>
                <p>   User can Input only INWARD or OUTWARD. </p>
                <p>   Multi Value set.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GENERATE.FT.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used when the bank requires customer posting only through FT. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type ANY (Any Character)</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi value set of field DIRECTION.TYPE</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LOAD.ROUTINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Routine executed after the selection of incoming files on the associated library or to make a fine transaction selection on the SEPA.OUTWARD.PENDING buffer file prior to producing an outgoing file on the associated library. </p>
                <p>      In ‘INWARD’, this optional routine is executed after the selection of the incoming files on the selected library. Its purpose is to modify the common variables of the I_SEPADIR insert (e.g. remove a file from the list after a given time on the day or make specific checks and/or updates on a file prior to its treatment). If the routine returns a value in ETEXT, the treatment will stop and its content will be reported to the SEPA.INWARD.LOG file with the highest error level (2). If the routine returns a value in COMI, its content will be recorded in the same log file with the lowest comment level (0) and the treatment will continue normally.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type ANY (Any Character). Associated Multi Value subset of field FILE.DIRECTION to DEFAULT.FTTC</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VALIDATE.ROUTINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the name of the routine used for Validation on SEPA Local Ref fields from Core routines.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric). Multivalue field. It must contain an existing value on the EB.API</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MAP.FIELDS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Key word to identify a Tag element as a useful field to generate a file, message or transaction T24 key, identify message control fields or ensure the building up of multi-tag T24 fields (narrative, address …)</p>
                <p>      List of allowed elements :</p>
                <p>      FILEn: Key element for archive file.</p>
                <p>      CREAD: File Creation date</p>
                <p>      CREAT: File Creation time</p>
                <p>      MOLDn: Key element of old message</p>
                <p>      MNEWn: Key element of new message</p>
                <p>      TOLDn: Key element of old operation</p>
                <p>      TNEWn: Key element of new operation</p>
                <p>      TXNNB: Transactions number in message.</p>
                <p>      TXNAMT: Total amount in XML message.</p>
                <p>      SDATE: Settlement date</p>
                <p>      REASON: Reason for REJ/RET/REV/REF.</p>
                <p>      NARRn: Narrative element for operation.</p>
                <p>      ADDRn: Corespondant address element.</p>
                <p>      ORINB: Original messages number in file.</p>
                <p>      REJNB: Rejected messages number in file.</p>
                <p>      REFNB: Refund messages number in file.</p>
                <p>      RETNB: Return messages number in file.</p>
                <p>      REVNB: Reverse messages number in file.</p>
                <p>      CXLNB: Cancel messages number in file.</p>
                <p>      CADDRn: Address of remitting customer.</p>
                <p>      CNAME: Name of remitting customer.</p>
                <p>      CACCT: Account of remitting customer.</p>
                <p>      CADDRn: Customer Address</p>
                <p>      GRPCCL: Cancellation status of a group</p>
                <p>      CATPRP: Category Purpose / Purpose of money transfer</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>   Multi value set</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MAP.MANDATORY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is defaulted with the Value = ‘Y’, and if the value is set to Y then the associated MAP.FIELDS is mandatory in the layout of every operation.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 1 and user can Input only value &apos;Y&apos;</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi value set of MAP.FIELDS</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MAXIMUM.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Maximum amount allowed by the SEPA interface for one transaction or unlimited.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 12 with 1 leading zero.</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MSG.NATURE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field defines the Nature of message. Key to SEPA.NATURE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 2 type A (Alphanumeric) and must exist in SEPA.NATURE Application </p>
                <p>   Multi Value set</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NAT.BANK.BRANCH.CD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Bank branch code to calculate IBAN</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 20 type A (Alphanumeric)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NOSTRO.ACCT.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the SEPA nostro account used by default if not defined in transaction specific description. The order of default - </p>
                <p>  1) ACCT.NUMBER from SEPA.PEACH</p>
                <p>  2) NOSTRO.ACCT.NO from SEPA.LAYOUT </p>
                <p>  3) If not specified then from this field of SEPA.PARAMETER</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  May be ACCOUNT.CLASS or @ROUTINE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 16 type A (Alphanumeric). Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p>   Value should exist in ACCOUNT Application</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APPLICATION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field Identifies the application for which the here after sub valued LOCAL.REFERENCE useful for SEPA are described. FUNDS.TRANSFER, STANDING.ORDER … etc</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric). Value must exist in FILE.CONTROL Application</p>
                <p>   Multi value set</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is defaulted with the Override message generated for this application.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 30 and NOINPUT field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PATH.SEPA.BIC.DIR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Path where the SWIFT published SEPA Directory will be stored. This file can be uploaded directly to SEPA.BANK through a routine.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 50 type ANY (Any Character)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FIXED.SELECTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Selection criteria for the Inward Files to be processed. </p>
                <p>Only the files which match the criteria will be taken for processing</p>
				<p>Eg:  "LIKE ZVS..." for EQUENS or "LIKE S20..." for EBA peach files</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 50 type ANY (Any Character). Associated Multi Value subset of field FILE.DIRECTION to DEFAULT.FTTC</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PEACH.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Default outward PE-ACH per associated MSG.NATURE. Key to SEPA.PEACH.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 10 type CUS (Customer Number) and must exist in SEPA.PEACH Application</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi Value set of MSG.NATURE</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PENDING.DAYS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Number of days in addition to the actual date allowing the process of messages by comparison with their settlement date.</p>
                <p>      ‘0’: Takes only value dates ≤ today.</p>
                <p>      ‘’: Takes all the pending value dates.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 4 with 1 leading Zero type A (Alphanumeric) and NOINPUT field.</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PENDING.SUFFIX.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field Gives the name of the routine that calculates the suffix code to be added to the SEPA.OUTWARD.PENDING key. This to allow a selection (grouping) of the outward transactions prior to the outgoing files generation via outward LOAD.ROUTINE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROCESS.SWITCH</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Following values </p>
                <p> &apos;Y’ = Processing already started </p>
                <p> ‘ ’ = No other processing is still running. </p>
                <p>    Automatic use, no input allowed. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 1 type A (Alphanumeric) and NOINPUT field</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi value set of field FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROCESS.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Default process type for a transaction if none is associated to its own definition:</p>
                <p>      ‘SAO’: Direct booking on the customer account whatever its status might be.</p>
                <p>      ‘SNP’: Direct booking on the customer account unless blocked by an override message in which case the booking is done on a transit account and one accept manual FUNDS.TRANSFER is initiated (IN).</p>
                <p>      ‘RET’: Booking on a transit account and generation of a return on SEPA.FOLLOW.UP, if possible, automatically authorized.  </p>
                <p>      ‘MAN’: Booking on a transit account and simultaneous non validated generation of a manual FUNDS.TRANSFER to accept and of a return/refund SEPA.FOLLOW.UP record. The manual validation of one of them will later remove the other one.</p>
                <p>      ‘ALL’: Processing attempt in ‘SNP’ and if it fails, switching to‘MAN’ option. Value highly recommended for that field.</p>
                <p>      &apos;OFT&apos; : Only FT. Every transaction in SEPA will create an entry in core FT and entries will be posted only through FT.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 3 and user can input only &apos;SAO&apos; &apos;SNP&apos; &apos;RET&apos; &apos;MAN&apos; &apos;ALL&apos; and &apos;OFT&apos;</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SEPARATOR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Character to be used to concatenate the SEPA file identification with the rank of its multi-valued XML messages.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 1 type ANY (Any Character)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SEQUENCE.DIGITS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Useful digits (3 to 7) to describe the daily number of same nature transactions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 1 and User can input only Values &apos;3&apos; &apos;4&apos; &apos;5&apos; &apos;6&apos; and &apos;7&apos;</p>
                <p>   Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>APPLICATION.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field provided the ID of the Application that generates entries and the associated multi value will describe the EB.SYSTEM.ID that is used while generating the entries</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric) and Value must exist in FILE.CONTROL application</p>
                <p>   Multi Value set</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STO.PAY.METHOD</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Transaction types associated to SEPA Standing Order payments. Key to FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 4 type A (Alphanumeric) and Value must exist in FT.TXN.TYPE.CONDITION application</p>
                <p>   Individual multi value field </p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUFFIX.BY.DEFAULT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Suffix of any internal account defined by its ACCOUNT.CLASS whenever initial account officer is unknown.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 4</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUSPENS.ACCT.NO</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Value of the default account that replaces the customer account, whenever he should not be aware of an operation canceling (e.g.: technical return/refund, duplicate found).</p>
                <p>      May be ACCOUNT.CLASS or @ROUTINE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 16 type A (Alphanumeric). Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p>   Value should exist in ACCOUNT Application</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANSIT.ACCT.CR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Value SEPA transit technical account used by default for credit operations if not defined in transaction specific description. May be ACCOUNT.CLASS or @ROUTINE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 16 type A (Alphanumeric). Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p>   Value should exist in ACCOUNT Application</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANSIT.ACCT.DB</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Value SEPA transit technical account used by default for debit operations if not defined in transaction specific description. May be ACCOUNT.CLASS or @ROUTINE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 16 type A (Alphanumeric). Associated Multi value set of FILE.DIRECTION to PENDING.DAYS.</p>
                <p>   Value should exist in ACCOUNT Application</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TYPE.OF.FORMAT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the file format i.e, PACS - bank to bank or PAIN - bank to customer/customer to bank</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 4 characters and user can input only ‘PACS’ and ‘PAIN’ </p>
                <p>   (Values can be modified with EB.LOOKUP application with key SEPA.TYPE.OF.FORMAT)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VALIDATE.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Name, prefixed by @, of validation routines to be executed for any nature of transaction prior to any booking entry. This allows to process to various checks and data update based on T24 or any other environments.</p>
                <p>      The ETEXT variable if returned produces an error message forcing </p>
                <p>   the ‘MAN’ option. The COMI variable, if returned produces an override message that can also lead to the forcing of the ‘MAN’ version if the user profile is not able to bypass it.</p>
                <p>      These generic routines will be executed prior to to those at specific transaction level. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric). </p>
                <p>   Multi value subset of DUPLICATE.PROC</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BANK.BIC.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the BIC identification of the T24 bank. This value is used while updating the sender information of the outward message</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 11 type A (Alphanumeric)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BANK.DEF.BRANCH</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Default branch of the T24 bank.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BANK.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Name of the T24 bank.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value from 2 to 32 type S (SWIFT Character). Mandatory field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BIC.ENRICHMENT.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field provides the name of the routine used to add an enrichment narrative on a given BIC code. The standard @SEPA.BANK.ENRICH is using the delivered SEPA.BANK table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type A (Alphanumeric)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CLEAR.CCY.MARKET</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the value of the Interface market code and it is defaulted with the Value &apos;1&apos;</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 2 and Value must exist in CURRENCY.MARKET Application </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CLEAR.CURRENCY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This fields specifies the Interface Currency being used and it is defaulted with Value &apos;EUR&apos;</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 4 type A (Alphanumeric) and Value must exist in CURRENCY Application </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UPDATE.FILE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This fields specifies update to concat files and TOOLS to happen if set to 'Y'</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 1 type A (Alphanumeric) and Value allowed 'Y' or null </p>
            </desc>
        </t>			
		<t>
            <field>PSD.ROUTINE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the value of the routine used to validate the PSD compliance</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 50 type ANY (Any Character) and Value must exist in EB.API Application</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>SDD.ADDNL.CHK.RTN</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field provides the name of the routine used for additional validation over SEPA.MANDATE.ID</p>
				<p>Eg: When Buisness code in Creditor ID needs to be validated and by passed</p>
                <p/>
                <p>   Validation rule</p>
                <p>   Value upto 35 type ANY (Any Character)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
