<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>EP</product>
        <title>SEPA.PARAMETER.REC</title>
        <table>SEPA.PARAMETER.REC</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>For some additional parameters we need a separate application, because it´s not mandatory to add a new field to the application SEPA.PARAMETER, every time we need a new parameter. </p>
            <p>   In addition this application can also be used in customer projects, to create needed parameters in an easy way.</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>AREA</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Value (Exact reason) that refers to be check against the reason for failed transaction   eg: if value in this part is</p>
                <p>   DD.MANDATE.CHECK then exact or possible reason for failed transaction would be MANDATE.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 20 and Mandatory field</p>
                <p>  NOINPUT field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMPANY</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the value of COMPANY record or possible value that can be made is “ALL”</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 9 and should exist in COMPANY Application</p>
                <p>  NOINPUT field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used the specify a Short description for corresponding Parameter record</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 75 type A(Alphanumeric) and Mandatory field</p>
                <p>  Individual Multi Value field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MODUL</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the value “SEPA” for this SEPA module</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 4 and Mandatory field</p>
                <p>  NOINPUT field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PARM.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the Id of parameter table.  </p>
                <p> The id format will be as, “COMPANY”-”MODUL”-”AREA”-”SUBAREA” </p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 65 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SUBAREA</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Value (Exact value for the above reason specified in AREA part of id) that refers to be check against the reason for failed transaction eg: if the value in this part is B2B.NOT.OK.REASON then the exact or possible value will the reason code that should be updated for failed transaction for easy understanding</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 25 and Mandatory field</p>
                <p>  NOINPUT field</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VALUE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Value which is defined and that is to be used in the routine</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 75 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>  Individual Multi Value field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
