<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>EP</product>
        <title>SEPA.INWARD.FILES</title>
        <table>SEPA.INWARD.FILES</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This ‘L’ type application records the main elements from a single SEPA received file. </p>
            <p>    If the file contains more than one message, so does the application record in a multi-value set.</p>
            <p>    Each multi-value contains the operation code as well as the first and last sequential number attributed to the keys of the SEPA.INWARD records generated for each Transaction Information in the XML message.</p>
            <p>    It also records the Group Header, as well as the Original Group information if any, in a suitable format allowing a drill down on the original XML sequence or to rebuild an already processed file by adding the Transaction Information retrieved from each SEPA.INWARD record.</p>
            <p>    It is used by the enquiry SEPA.INWARD.FILES with the nofile program SEPA.VIEW.INWARD.FILES to access sequentially the inward archives selected by a range of processing dates or a search operand on a file name or identification key.</p>
            <p>    It also records the global payment entry done on the SEPA nostro account for each received message unless this entry is forced at the SEPA.INWARD level for each transaction.</p>
            <p>    If the inward message is a Customer to Bank, a single entry will be done for the XML message on his account of the customer. If a transaction from the message is later cancelled, an entry with the opposite sign will be posted for its own amount alone for a suitable value date.</p>
            <p>    The key to that file is built of selected elements taken from each Group Header sequence and separated by a dot ‘.’. These elements are defined by filling in their FIELD.EXTRACT with a FILEn value in the SEPA.LAYOUT record. This may enforce the recording of messages from the same file in more then one SEPA.INWARD.FILE record whenever their concatenated keys are different. </p>
            <p>    If no concatenation element has been defined, the inward file name will be taken instead.</p>
            <p>    If this calculate key has already been attributed to other files, and if the Group Header of the new message is different from any known one, the system will add an additional sequence number s with a dash ‘-‘ as separator to the key to ensure its unicity.</p>
            <p>    File key = Calculated key[-s] </p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>LINKED.FT.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This fields holds the Key to the FT generated for payment of the remitting CB customer if overrided.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 25 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MESSAGE.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This fields contains the Message Id generated by concatenation of SEPA.HEADER and SEPA.LAYOUT Tags with FIELD.EXTRCT prefixed by “MNEW”.</p>
                <p>    Key to SEPA.MSG.CONCAT.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 50 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>  Multi Value Set</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MESSAGE.TYPE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the UNIFI.XML.MSG.ID from SEPA.LAYOUT.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Value upto 35 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
                <p>  Value should exist in UNIFI.XML.MESSAGE Application</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ORIGINAL.GROUP</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Original Group Information sequence, stored as it can be shown easily as it was in its original XML presentation by a delivered T24 drill down enquiry.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 35 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PEACH.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the Issuing PE-ACH platform center</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 10 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p>  Value should exist in SEPA.PEACH Application</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PRE.HEADER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Added preheader (FM converted to VM).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 50 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p>  Multi Value Field</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROCESS.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Treatment date of the inward file. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 11 type D(DATE)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PROCESS.TIME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Treatment time of the inward file.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 5 type TIME( Time Format)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SEPA.DETAIL.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Prefix key of SEPA.INWARD.DETAIL (CB)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 20 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STATUS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Status of the transaction posted.</p>
                <p>    ACP - Accepted</p>
                <p>    CXL – Cancelled</p>
                <p>    PND – Pending</p>
                <p>    PRC – Processed</p>
                <p>    RCV – Received</p>
                <p>    RDY – Ready for transfer</p>
                <p>    REJ – Rejected</p>
                <p>    RET – Returned</p>
                <p>    SND – Sent</p>
                <p>    TRF - Transferred</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 3 type SEPA.TRANSFER.STS.LIST</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COMMENT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Comments posted on the XML message.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 35 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID and Multi Value Field</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>STMT.NOS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains a Reference of the global accounting entry.</p>
                <p>    A context enquiry allows a drill down.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 29 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID and Multi Value field</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOT.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains a Global amount of transactions found in the XML message in clearing currency.</p>
                <p>    A second sub-value is given if the local currency is not the clearing currency.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 18 type AMT(AMOUNT)</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID and Multi Value field</p>
                <p>  Negative Value is allowed</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANS.CODE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Operation code defined in SEPA.LAYOUT.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 3 with 2 preceeding Zero&apos;s</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANS.FIRST</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains a Sequential suffix number attributed to the first Transaction Information of the XML message in the SEPA.INWARD file.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 6</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value SubSet of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANS.LAST</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains a Sequential suffix number attributed to the last Transaction Information of the XML message in the SEPA.INWARD file.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 6</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field TRANS.FIRST</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TRANS.NUMBER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field denotes the Number of transactions found in message. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 7</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CREATION.DATE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Creation date of the inward file. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 11 type D(DATE)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CREATION.TIME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Creation time of the inward file.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 5 type TIME( Time Format)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CUSTOMER.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the ID of the Handing over customer</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 10 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p>  Value should exist in CUSTOMER Application </p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FILE.HEADER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the File header sequence stored in such a way that it can be shown easily as it was in its original XML presentation by a delivered T24 drill down enquiry.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 35 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FILE.NAME</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This Field contains the Name of the file received in library.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 50 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FILE.TRAILER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This Field holds the Last Tag of the file “&lt;/SEPA.HEADER.ID&gt;”</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 35 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GROUP.HEADER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Group header sequence stored in such a way that it can be shown easily as it was in its original XML presentation by a delivered T24 drill down enquiry.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 35 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IN.FILE.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Identification key made unique if needed. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 60 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TOTAL.CHG</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds total charge amount to be deducted for bulk level posting. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 18 type AMT</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>NET.AMOUNT</field>
            <desc>
                <p> Total amount of transaction. This field is not used currently</p>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 18 type AMT</p>
                <p>  Associated Multi Value Set of field MESSAGE.ID</p>
				<p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>TOT.NO.OF.TXN.FILE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Total Number of Transactions in a file. Taken from the value in NbOfTxs tag in the XML file from Header part</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 18 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>TOT.AMOUNT.FILE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Total Transaction Amount in a file. Taken from the value in CtrlSum tag in the XML file from Header part</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>  Validation Rules </p>
                <p>  Value upto 18 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
