<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>EP</product>
        <title>UNIFI.XML.TAG</title>
        <table>UNIFI.XML.TAG</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This ‘U’ type table contains the definition of all UNIFI (ISO 20022) XML tags and sequences contains in any SEPA message. It also gives the default occurrence for any standard message. </p>
            <p/>
            <p>        If a single tag element and a sequence of tags to which it belongs have the same UNIFI Id, one of them must have a key with an additional suffix and a dot as separator (e.g.: Amt.1 and Amt).</p>
            <p/>
            <p>        To be considered as an element worth to be extracted from an inward SEPA XML message or to be generated onto an outward SEPA XML message, a TAG should passed successfully the test set up in at least one of the multi-values fields 8 to 11. For this, a ‘Y’ should be present in the USED.BY.SEPA field and the characteristics of the message should match the ones given at the 3 following fields (a blank being considered as a valid match).</p>
            <p/>
            <p>        The present table is thus the only one to be touched to allow a tag to be used or not in application.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>        The following table is used to extract the Tags depending on the above set up and to build up the complete message model for any combination of nature, entities and purpose. Any further update of the UNIFI.XML.TAG fields 8 to 11 will automatically adjust the content of the existing related records of the following UNIFI.XML.MESSAGE table and related SEPA.LAYOUT.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>PURPOSE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Message purpose concerned by USED.FOR.SEPA.</p>
                <p>        ORI: Original transaction,</p>
                <p>        REJ: Technical reject from SEPA,</p>
                <p>        RET: Return by the receiver,</p>
                <p>        REF: Refund by the receiver,</p>
                <p>        REV/CXL: Reverse/cancel by the sender.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>     Validation Rules </p>
                <p>     Value upto 3 AND User can input only values &apos;CXL&apos; or &apos;ORI&apos; or &apos;REF&apos; or &apos;REJ&apos; or &apos;RET&apos; or &apos;REV&apos;</p>
                <p>     Associated multi value set of field USED.BY.SEPA</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SENDER.RECEIVER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Sender and receiver related to USED.FOR.SEPA.</p>
                <p>        BB: Bank to Bank, CB: Customer to Bank,</p>
                <p>        BC: Bank to Customer</p>
                <p/>
                <p>     Validation Rules </p>
                <p>     Value upto 2 and User can input only values &apos;BB&apos; or &apos;CB&apos; or &apos;BC&apos;</p>
                <p>     Associated multi value set of field USED.BY.SEPA</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TAG.ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Name of the Tag</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 35 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>USED.BY.SEPA</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This Filed is Defaulted iwth the Vlaues &apos;Y&apos; or &apos;NO&apos;</p>
                <p> ‘Y’: considered if message matches the 3 next fields.</p>
                <p>  ‘NO’: never considered if 3 next fields are matched</p>
                <p/>
                <p>     Validation Rules </p>
                <p>     Value upto 2 and User can input only value &apos;Y&apos; or &apos;NO&apos;</p>
                <p>     Multi Value Set </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This fields contains the Description of the Tag</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 43 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p>      Mandatory field and Individual Multi Value field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FORMAT</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field holds the Key to UNIFI.XML.FORMAT, format of theTag.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 35 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>      Value should exist in UNIFI.XML.FORMAT Application </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GROUP.MEMBER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Tags or sequence belonging to the group.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 35 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p>      Multi Value Set and Value should exist in UNIFI.XML.TAG Application</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GROUP.OWNER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Sequences to which this tag belongs (no input).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 35 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p>      NOINPUT field and Value should exist in UNIFI.XML.TAG Application</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>GROUP.XOR</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This Field contains Any string of character. If duplicated on 2 or more tags, they are considered as mutually exclusive.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 35 type ANY(Any Character)</p>
                <p>      Multi Value Set and Value should exist in UNIFI.XML.TAG Application</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MESSAGE.OWNER</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Key to the UNIFI.XML.MESSAGE giving the Id of the messages that owns this sequence (no input).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 1 and NOINPUT field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MSG.NATURE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field contains the Key to SEPA.NATURE related to USED.FOR.SEPA.</p>
                <p>        DD: Direct debit, CT: Credit Transfer</p>
                <p/>
                <p>     Validation Rules </p>
                <p>     Value upto 2 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>     Value should exist in SEPA.NATURE Application </p>
                <p>     Associated multi value set of field USED.BY.SEPA</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OCCURRENCE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field specifies the Occurrence number by default for the Tag.</p>
                <p>        0.0 : Not considered</p>
                <p>        1.0 : One occurrence or none</p>
                <p>        1.1 : Occurs only once</p>
                <p>        n.0 : Any occurrence or none</p>
                <p>        n.1 : Occurs at least once</p>
                <p>        n.M : Occurs at least M times</p>
                <p>        N.0 : Up to N occurrences or none.</p>
                <p>        N.M : Occurs between M and N times.</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 4 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is defaulted with the Override message generated for this application</p>
                <p/>
                <p>      Validation Rules </p>
                <p>      Value upto 35 type A(Alphanumeric)</p>
                <p>      NOINPUT field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
