<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IX</product>
<table>IX.TRANSACTION</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
<p>This table is available to define the Possible Domain, Family and Subfamily for an application and transaction or as a default record can be created for the application</p> 
 </ovdesc>
 </overview>
 
 <menu>
      <t>
      <field>ID</field>
      <desc>
        <p>
          <strong>Id of the record</strong>
        </p>
        <p>Should be valid system id and transaction code separated by '*'. It can also be only a valid System Id which could be the default for the application.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p> System id part need to be a valid record in EB.SYSTEM.ID table</p>
        <p>	Transaction code need to be a valid record in TRANSACTION table or RE.TXN.CODE table.</p>
	<p></p>        
      </desc>
    </t>
 
 <t>
      <field>DESCRIPTION</field>
      <desc>
        
        <p>Multi-lingual Field which holds the standard description of the Bank transaction domain code.</p>
        
	<p></p>        
      </desc>
    </t>
 
 <t>
      <field>DOMAIN.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        
        <p>ISO standard bank transaction Domain code for this particular system id and its transaction code</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p> Must be a valid record in IX.EXTERNAL.CODES with Usage.Code defined as "Domain.Code". Must also be a valid combination as defined in the IX.DOMAIN.CODES</p>
        <p>	Mandatory Input</p>
	<p></p>        
      </desc>
    </t>
    
    <t>
      <field>FAMILY.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        
        <p>ISO standard bank transaction Family code for this particular Domain Code under system id and transaction code.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p> Must be a valid record in IX.EXTERNAL.CODES with Usage.Code defined as "Family.Code". Must also be a valid combination as defined in the IX.DOMAIN.CODES</p>
        <p>	Must be a valid Family code present under the Domain code.</p>
        <p> Domain code is mandatory before inputting this field </p>
        <p> Mandatory Input</p>
	<p></p>        
      </desc>
    </t>
    
     <t>
      <field>SUB.FAMILY.CODE</field>
      <desc>
        
        <p>ISO standard bank transaction Sub Family code for this particular system id and its transaction code.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p> Must be a valid record in IX.EXTERNAL.CODES with Usage.Code defined as "Sub.Family.Code". Must also be a valid combination as defined in the IX.DOMAIN.CODES</p>
        <p>	Must be a valid Sub Family code present under the Family code for that Domain code</p>
        <p> Domain code and Sub Family Code is mandatory before inputting this field </p>
        <p> Mandatory Input</p>
	<p></p>        
      </desc>
    </t>
    
    <t>
      <field>TXN.TYPE</field>
      <desc>
        
        <p>Transaction type associated with this System id and its Transaction Code</p>
        <p>The logic for suppressing and defining values for the tags in XML.TAG.DEFINITION can be defined based on the Transaction type defined in this field</p>
        <p>For such a setup, the Application id in XML.TAG.DEFINITION should be defined as the System id (Id of this record)*Transaction type(Value defined in this field) </p>
        
	<p></p>        
      </desc>
    </t>
    
    <t>
      <field>TXN.TYPE.RTN</field>
      <desc>
        
        <p>API to retrieve the Transaction type for the System id and Transaction Code</p>
        <p>The System id along with the retrieved Transaction type can be used in XML.TAG.DEFINITION to suppress or define value for tags</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>Must be a valid EB.API</p>
        <p>Input not allowed if TXN.TYPE is defined</p>
	<p></p>        
      </desc>
    </t>
    
    </menu>
</t24help>
    