<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IN</product>
<table>IN.EXCLUSION.LIST</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
        <p>The EXCLUSIONLIST file contains a list of IBAN NATIONAL IDs that are not allowed in IBANs.</p>
		<p>Any IBANs that contain such IBAN NATIONAL IDs are invalid.</p>
        <p>This list allows financial institutions to detect invalid IBAN payments before sending them out.</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MODIFICATION.FLAG</field>
<desc>
       <p>A flag which indicates whether  there is a change in the record, since the last release of the IBAN structure file.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A - Addition since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="2">D - Deletion since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="3">U - Unchanged since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="4">M - Modification since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="5">E - Expired : Reserved for future use.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Country code of the Invalid National id.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 2 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.NATIONAL.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>The Invalid National id that when included in IBAN leads to invalid payment.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BIC.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The BIC of the financial institution that holds/used to hold this NATIONAL ID.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 11 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>VALID.FROM</field>
<desc>
        <p>The future date from which the IBAN NATIONAL ID will be invalid. If the IBAN NATIONAL ID became invalid in the past, then the field is empty.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 8 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>
