<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IN</product>
<table>IN.IBAN.PLUS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>
        <p>The IBANPLUS file contains IBAN-related data for financial institutions to generate or validate the IBAN number.</p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>MODIFICATION.FLAG</field>
<desc>
        <p>A flag which indicates whether  there is a change in the record, since the last release of the IBAN structure file.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A - Addition since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="2">D - Deletion since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="3">U - Unchanged since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="4">M - Modification since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="5">E - Expired : Reserved for future use.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INSTITUTION.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the Institution name of the IBAN issuer.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COUNTRY.NAME</field>
<desc>
        <p>Residence Country Name of the financial institution that issued the IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ISO.COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Residence Country code of the financial institution that issued the IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 2 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The country code of the IBANs that the institution issued.</p>
        <p>Under certain circumstances this can be different from the country indicated in field "ISO COUNTRY CODE".</p>
        <P>Example</P>
        <p>Banks in Guernsey (GG) issue IBANs using GB when the clearing system in Great Britain is used.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 2 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.BIC</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is the BIC Code issued together with the IBANs to the institution's clients.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 11 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ROUTING.BIC</field>
<desc>
        <p>Contains the ROUTING BIC which is the best approximation to send SEPA payment over SWIFT, when IBAN BIC is not connected to SWIFT.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 11 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.NATIONAL.ID</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the National ID that is included in the IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SERVICE.CONTEXT</field>
<desc>
        <p>Code indicating the context of the payment services provided by the financial institution.</p>
        <p>SEPA - Single Euro Payments Area</p>
        <p>NULL - The institution uses the IBAN standard but is not a participant of SEPA.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 4 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.REF</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. Standard T24 alphanumeric field. </p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OVERRIDE</field>
<desc>
        <p>This is a multi valued field. </p>
        <p>Contains details of any override applicable to this record.</p>
        <p>
           <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        </p>
        <p> A maximum of 35 characters may be entered. This is a NOINPUT field.</p>
    </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>