<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>IN</product>
<table>IN.IBAN.STRUCTURE</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

        <p>A multi-valued field and a Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
        <b>Validation Rules:</b>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>AC.NUMBER.LEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of characters of account number in IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AC.NUMBER.POS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start position of domestic account number in IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.NO.APPL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the application in which account number can be fetched to build IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">	A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACCT.NO.FIELD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the field of the above application, from where account number can be fetched to build IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">	A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.ID.APPL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the application in which the bank identifier can be fetched to build IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BANK.ID.FIELD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the field of the above application, from where bank identifier can be fetched to build IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BNK.IDENTIFIER.LEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of characters of bank identifier in IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BNK.IDENTIFIER.POS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start position of Bank identifier in IBAN.	</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.IDENTIFIER.LEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of characters of branch identifier in IBAN (value will be 0 if the branch identifier is not applied in the country's IBAN format)</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BR.IDENTIFIER.POS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start position of branch identifier in IBAN (value will be nil if the branch identifier is not applied in the country's IBAN format).</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRANCH.ID.APPL</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the application in which branch identifier can be fetched to build IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>BRANCH.ID.FIELD</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the field of the above application, from where branch identifier can be fetched to build IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">	A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.CHK.DIGITS.LEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of check digits in IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.CHK.DIGITS.POS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start position of check digit in IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.COUNTRY.CDE.LEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of characters of country code in IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.COUNTRY.CDE.POS</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the start position of country code in IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">	A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IB.NATIONAL.ID.LEN</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the number of significant characters of National ID value that are used by SWIFT, to populate the IBAN NATIONAL ID, and that are sufficient to derive the IBAN BIC correctly.</p>
        <p>This number can be different from (that is, smaller than) the length of national bank/branch identifier that is defined in IBAN Registry.	</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>IBAN.COUNTRY.CODE</field>
<desc>
        <p>Specifies the ISO Country code prefix in IBAN.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A maximum of 35 characters can be entered.</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MODIFICATION.FLAG</field>
<desc>
        <p>A flag which indicates whether  there is a change in the record, since the last release of the IBAN structure file.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">A - Addition since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="2">D - Deletion since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="3">U - Unchanged since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="4">M - Modification since last IBAN structure file.</p>
            <p value="5">
                <p>E - Expired : Reserved for future use.</p>
            </p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAG</field>
<desc>
        <p>A tag identifier.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Record Identifier : “IS”</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SEPA</field>
<desc>
        <p>This flag indicates whether the IBAN is used in one of the SEPA schemes. YES if it does, NO if it does not </p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">3 Alpha characters</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OPT.COMMENCE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The date from which the IBAN structure is an optional requirement.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Valid Date</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAND.COMMENCE.DATE</field>
<desc>
        <p>The date from which the IBAN structure is a mandatory requirement.</p>
        <p>Validation Rules:</p>
        <p>
            <p value="1">Valid Date</p>
        </p>
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.COMP.POS </field>
<desc>
        <p>Associated Multi-value field with OTHER.COMP.LEN </p>
        <p>Field to specify the starting position of the component(s) other than core fields in the IBAN Structure directory</p>
      
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>OTHER.COMP.LEN </field>
<desc>
        <p>Associated Multi-value field with OTHER.COMP.POS</p>
        <p>Field to denote the length of the OTHER.COMP.POS component in the IBAN</p>
        <p> </p>
      	<p> For eg: If the value of IB.COUNTRY.CDE.POS is 1 and its corresponding length is 2, and if the value of IB.CHK.DIGITS.POS is 5 and its corresponding length is 3,</p>
      	<p> Then system considers the missed out position (which is from 3, 2 positions) as control characters and populates the OTHER.COMP.POS as 3 and OTHER.COMP.LEN as 2. </p>
      	<p> If there are more than one control character positions, then the system multivalues OTHER.COMP.POS and OTHER.COMP.LEN field </p> 
      	
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.IBAN.GEN.RTN</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field will accept a local API to generate the IBAN number, when a API is attached in this field then system will pass the required data to the API.</p>
        <p>System will not do any validation on the returned IBAN number including CHECK DIGIT has to be generated in the API itself (i.e. the API must have the logic to generate a complete valid IBAN number).</p>
 
    </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LOCAL.IBAN.VAL.RTN</field>
<desc>
        <p>This field will accept a local API to validate the IBAN number, System will not do any validation if an API is attached in this field (i.e. All the validations must be handled in the local API)</p>
    </desc>
</t>

</menu>
</t24help>

