<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ET</product>
<table>EU.ALLOCATION.DETS</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is one of the EU Base Files which is updated when a sale transaction is input for a customer and security in scope. It gives the details of the purchase transactions that have been allocated to this particular sale, the nominal that has been allocated out of each purchase, the base amount for tax and tax calculated. This is a live file.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>HLD.PD.DISC</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HLD.PD.INT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the tax amount for the number of days the security has been hold by the customer.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.TXN.TIME</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the sale transaction time that have been allocated against each purchase transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.TXN.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the sale transaction reference that have been allocated against each purchase transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.TXN.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the sale transaction code that have been allocated against each purchase transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EU.TAX.ACC.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the calculated tax amount in account currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CTR.GAIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the tax amount calculated based on the interest counter (IC) method.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>NAV.OUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the sale price of the transaction that has been allocated out of each purchase.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the sale transaction nominal that have been allocated against each purchase transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCR.TAX.ACCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>
                <p>This field is the key which contains the SECURITY.TRANS key appended with portfolio and separated by the asterisk.</p>
                <p>(For e.g.) SCTRSC003399QTRM.1*70001-1</p>
                <p>Where, SCTRSC003399QTRM.1 - SECURITY.TRANS key, 70001-1 - SEC.ACC.MASTER key.</p>
            </p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INCR.TAX.SCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HLD.PERIOD</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the number of days where the tax amount have been calculated.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.TAX.SCCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the manually calculated tax amount in security currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>DR.TXN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the sale transaction date that have been allocated against each purchase transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.CAP.GAIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the weighted average capital gain (CG) after all transactions have been performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CAP.GAIN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the tax amount calculated based on the capital gain (CG) method.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the purchase transaction nominal that have been allocated against each sale transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.TXN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the purchase transaction date that have been allocated against each sale transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.BASE.REV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the tax amount before applying the tax percentage which is specified in the TAX record for EUSD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CTR.AVG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the weighted average interest counter after all transactions have been performed.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>MAN.TAX.ACCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the manually calculated tax amount in account currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CTR.OUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the interest counter to calculate the tax based interest counter gain/loss.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EU.TAX.RATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the tax percentage which is specified in the TAX record for EUSD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>HLD.PD.DISCDAYS</field>
<desc>
            <p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>CR.TXN.REF</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the purchase transaction reference that have been allocated against each sale transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.RATE.REV</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the tax percentage which is specified in the TAX record for EUSD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EU.TAX.SEC.CR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the calculated tax amount in security currency.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EU.TAX.BASE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the tax amount before applying the tax percentage which is specified in the TAX record for EUSD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TAX.REV.SEC.CCY</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the tax amount including the tax percentage which is specified in the TAX record for EUSD.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t><field>JOINT.CUST.TAXID</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t><t><field>TAX.AMT.SPLIT</field><desc><p>Help Text for this field is unavailable.  Please refer to the T24 User Guides for further information.</p></desc></t></menu>
</t24help>
