<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ET</product>
<table>EU.DATA.BUILD</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is used to rebuild the EUSD related files (like EU.TAX.LINK, EU.ALLOCATION.DETS and EU.TXN.BASE) based on the selection criteria specified for the ET security or customer in scope holds the position within the tax period.</p>
            <p>To rebuild the ET files, the service XXX/INITIAL.DATA.BUILD need to be run after authorizing the record in this application.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>TO.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date upto which the selection should be done in security trans to pick and rebuild the ET files. If this field is null then ET files are rebuild for all the ET Customer/Security which holds position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid T24 Date</p>
            <p> Default will be null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.ID</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field contains the valid value based on the selection criteria specified.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid input are </p>
            <p>If SELECTION.CRITERIA is 'CUSTOMER' then this field holds a valid key from CUSTOMER record.</p>
            <p>If SELECTION.CRITERIA is 'SECURITY' then this field holds a valid key from SECURITY.MASTER record.</p>
            <p>If SELECTION.CRITERIA is 'PORTFOLIO' then this field holds a valid key from SEC.ACC.MASTER record.</p>
            <p>If SELECTION.CRITERIA is 'ALL' then this field holds null (means ET files are rebuild for all the ET Customer/Security which holds position).</p>
            <p>This is a Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>COMPANY.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the key which contains the company id, appended with date and time separated by the dot.</p>
            <p>(For e.g. - COMPANY_KEY.DATE.TIME) US0010001.20001204.17:42:40</p>
            <p>The ET files are rebuild based on the last authorised record.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid Inputs are 'A valid key from COMPANY record'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FROM.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date from which the selection should be done in security trans to pick and rebuild the ET files. If this field is null then ET files are rebuild for all the ET Customer/Security which holds position.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p>Valid T24 Date</p>
            <p> Default will be null</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>SELECTION.CRITERIA</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the criteria based on which the selection should be done from security position to pick and rebuild the ET files.</p>
            <p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
            </p>
            <p />
            <p />
            <p> Valid input are 'CUSTOMER', 'SECURITY', 'PORTFOLIO' or 'ALL'</p>
            <p>This is a Mandatory field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

