<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help>
<header>
<product>ET</product>
<table>EU.TAX.LINK</table>
</header>
<overview>
<ovdesc>

            <p>This application is one of the EU Base Files which maintains the FIFO/LIFO sequence of the transactions for a particular holding. This is a live file.</p>
            <p>Whenever the ET Security is traded by the withholding (WHT) customers in scope, this file is updated online.</p>
            <p>Whenever the ET Security is traded by the reporting (INFO) customers in scope, this file is updated during COB.</p>
        </ovdesc>
<ovimage></ovimage>
</overview>
<menu>
<t>
<field>EU.PURGE.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date on when the last purging of the record happens (i.e.) The transaction details upto this date would be purged from EU.TAX.LINK file and moved to EU.TAX.LINK.PAST file.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date on which the transaction is updated in the record. Each transaction details are updated based on the respective transaction date.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TRA.CODE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the transaction code of each transaction that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
            <p>Valid Transaction codes are 'CREDIT' for purchase transaction and 'DEBIT' for sale transaction.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LATEST.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field acts as a pointer for LIFO allocation of nominal which holds the SECURITY.TRANS key to start the allocation that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REWORK.FLAG</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field tells whether the rework for 'DEBIT' transaction needs to be done against 'CREBIT' transaction or not. Reworking of transaction is done to reallocate the nominal with updated sequence of FIFO/LIFO transactions. Based on the FIFO/LIFO allocation whenever any transaction are updated the rework flag set to 'YES' which indicates the need for reallocation of nominal.</p>
            <p />
            <p>Valid values are 'YES' and 'NO'</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>FIRST.REWORK.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the SECURITY.TRANS key to start the first reworking of transaction that needs to be done that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total weighted cost of all transactions for AVERAGE transaction basis.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.INT.CTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total weighted interest counter value of all transactions for AVERAGE transaction basis.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.BASIS</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the transaction basis of the record. Each transaction that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field, are filed under this transaction basis.</p>
            <p>Valid Transaction Basis are 'FIFO','LIFO' and 'AVERAGE'.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.NOMINAL</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total nominal of all transactions for AVERAGE transaction basis.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.UPDATED.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the last updated SECURITY.TRANS key in the record for FIFO/LIFO allocation of nominal that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LAST.UPD.DATE</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date on when the SECURITY.TRANS key is last updated in the record for FIFO/LIFO allocation of nominal that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>INT.CTR</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total weighted average interest counter value of all transactions for AVERAGE transaction basis.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>REFERENCE.NUMBER</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field is the key which contains the portfolio appended with security and separated by the dot.</p>
            <p>(For e.g.) 70001-1.100040-000</p>
            <p>Where, 70001-1 - SEC.ACC.MASTER key, 100040-000 - SECURITY.MASTER key.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>LATEST.INS.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date on when the latest transaction was updated in the record for LIFO allocation of nominal that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TXN.INPUT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the SECURITY.TRANS key of each transaction that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EARLIEST.TXN</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field acts as a pointer for FIFO allocation of nominal which holds the SECURITY.TRANS key to start the allocation that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>ACTUAL.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the actual transaction nominal of each transaction that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVAIL.NOM</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the available nominal for each purchase transaction after a sale transaction has been allocated against those purchase that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.COST</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the total weighted average cost of all transactions for AVERAGE transaction basis.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>EARLIEST.INS.DT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field holds the date on when the earliest transaction was updated in the record for FIFO allocation of nominal that involve the mentioned portfolio and security from the key field.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.HPI</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the average total interest of the outstanding nominal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.HPI</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the average interest of the position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TOTAL.DISCOUNT</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the average total discount of the outstanding nominal.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>AVG.DISC</field>
<desc>
            <p>This field will hold the average discount of the position.</p>
        </desc>
</t>
</menu>
</t24help>

