<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>POR.CREDITTRANSFERINITIATION</title>
        <table>POR.CREDITTRANSFERINITIATION</table>
    </header> 
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table payment table to store payment related details. Each payment is identified by FTNumber.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Company ID that needs to process the payment.</p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field 'CompanyID' in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FTNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>FTNumber to identify the records related to one payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
<t>
<field>PmtInfDbtPostAddTp</field>
<desc>
<p>Debtor address type. Example of values: ADDR (Postal), PBOX (POBox), HOME (Residential), BIZZ (Business), MLTO (MailTo), DLVY (DeliveryTo).</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PmtInfDbtAccCcy</field>
<desc>
<p>Currency of the debtor account.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PmtInfDbtAgFinIdCgSysMemIdCd</field>
<desc>
<p>Information used to identify the debtor agent as a member within a clearing system. This is the identification of a clearing system, in a coded form as published in an external list.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PmtInfDbtAgFinIdCgSysMemIdProp</field>
<desc>
<p>Identification code for a clearing system, that has not yet been identified in the list of clearing systems.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PmtInfDbtAgFinIdCgSysMemId</field>
<desc>
<p>Identification of a member of a clearing system. Example: National ID can be set here</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>PmtInfDbtAgFinInstIdPostAddTp</field>
<desc>
<p>Debtor agent address type. Example of values: ADDR (Postal), PBOX (POBox), HOME (Residential), BIZZ (Business), MLTO (MailTo), DLVY (DeliveryTo)</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxEqAmCcyOfTransfer</field>
<desc>
<p>Specifies the currency of the to be transferred amount, which is different from the currency of the debtor's account.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxFxRateInfUnitCcy</field>
<desc>
<p>Provides details on the currency exchange rate and contract. This is the currency in which the rate of exchange is expressed in a currency exchange. In the example 1GBP = xxxCUR, the unit currency is GBP.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxFxRateInfRateTp</field>
<desc>
<p>Specifies the type used to complete the currency exchange. Example of values: SPOT, SALE, AGRD</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxFxRateInfContractId</field>
<desc>
<p>Unique and unambiguous reference to the foreign exchange contract agreed between the initiating party/creditor and the debtor agent.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TPSTrxFxRateInfTreasuryRate</field>
<desc>
<p>Exchange rate is imposed by treasury. Not present in pain.001 files.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TPSTrxFxRateInfRateSpread</field>
<desc>
<p>Spread rate applied to the FX. Not present in pain.001 files.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxChargeBearer</field>
<desc>
<p>Specifies which party/parties will bear the charges associated with the processing of the payment transaction. Example of values, DEBT (borne by debtor), CRED (borne by creditor), SHAR (shared), SLEV (following service level agreement).</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TPSTrxChargeWaiver</field>
<desc>
<p>Charges to be skipped. Not present in pain.001 files.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxItmAg1FinIdCgSysMemIdCd</field>
<desc>
<p>Information used to identify the intermediary agent as a member within a clearing system. This is the identification of a clearing system, in a coded form as published in an external list.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxItmAg1FinIdCgSysMemIdProp</field>
<desc>
<p>Identification code for a clearing system, that has not yet been identified in the list of clearing systems.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxItmAg1FinIdCgSysMemId</field>
<desc>
<p>Identification of a member of a clearing system. Example: National ID can be set here</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxItmAg1FinIdNm</field>
<desc>
<p>Name by which the intermediary agent is known and which is usually used to identify that agent.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxItmAg1FinIdPostAddTp</field>
<desc>
<p>Intermediary agent address type. Example of values: ADDR (Postal), PBOX (POBox), HOME (Residential), BIZZ (Business), MLTO (MailTo), DLVY (DeliveryTo).</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdAgFinIdCgSysMemIdCd</field>
<desc>
<p>Information used to identify the creditor agent as a member within a clearing system. This is the identification of a clearing system, in a coded form as published in an external list.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdAgFinIdCgSysMemIdProp</field>
<desc>
<p>Identification code for a clearing system, that has not yet been identified in the list of clearing systems.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdAgFinIdCgSysMemId</field>
<desc>
<p>Identification of a member of a clearing system. Example: National ID can be set here</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdAgFinIdNm</field>
<desc>
<p>Name by which the creditor agent is known and which is usually used to identify that agent.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdAgFinIdPostAddTp</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor agent address type. Example of values: ADDR (Postal), PBOX (POBox), HOME (Residential), BIZZ (Business), MLTO (MailTo), DLVY (DeliveryTo).</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddTp</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor address type. Example of values: ADDR (Postal), PBOX (POBox), HOME (Residential), BIZZ (Business), MLTO (MailTo), DLVY (DeliveryTo).</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddDep</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor address department. Identification of a division of a large organisation or building.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddSubDep</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor address sub-department. Identification of a sub-division of a large organisation or building.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddStreetNm</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor address street name.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddBuildingNr</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor address building number (on a street).</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddPostCd</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor address postal code.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddTownNm</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor address town name.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddCtrySubDiv</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor address county / state / region.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddLine3</field>
<desc>
<p>Information that locates and identifies a specific address, as defined by postal services, pre-sented in free format text.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddLine4</field>
<desc>
<p>Information that locates and identifies a specific address, as defined by postal services, pre-sented in free format text.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddLine5</field>
<desc>
<p>Information that locates and identifies a specific address, as defined by postal services, pre-sented in free format text.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddLine6</field>
<desc>
<p>Information that locates and identifies a specific address, as defined by postal services, pre-sented in free format text.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdPostAddLine7</field>
<desc>
<p>Information that locates and identifies a specific address, as defined by postal services, pre-sented in free format text.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdCtryOfResidence</field>
<desc>
<p>Country of the creditor (the place of a person's home or the country from which the affairs of a company are directed). ISO Standard.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdContactDetNmPrefix</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor contact details - name prefix. Example of values: DOCT (Doctor), MIST (Mister), MISS (Miss), MADM (Madam).</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdContactDetNm</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor contact details - name.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdContactDetPhoneNr</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor contact details - phone number.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdContactDetMobileNr</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor contact details - mobile number.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdContactDetFaxNr</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor contact details - fax number.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdContactDetEmailAdd</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor contact details - email address.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdContactDetOth</field>
<desc>
<p>Creditor contact details - in another free format.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdAccIdOthSchNmCd</field>
<desc>
<p>Name of the identification scheme, in a coded form as published in an external list.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdAccIdOthSchNmProp</field>
<desc>
<p>Name of the identification scheme, in a free text form.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxCrdAccIdOthIssuer</field>
<desc>
<p>Entity that assigns the identification.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepDbCrRepInd</field>
<desc>
<p>Identifies whether the regulatory reporting information applies to the debit side, to the credit side or to both debit and credit sides of the transaction.Example of values: CRED, DEBT, BOTH</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepAuthorityNm</field>
<desc>
<p>Name of the entity requiring the regulatory reporting information.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepAuthorityCtry</field>
<desc>
<p>Country of the entity that requires the regulatory reporting information.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepDetTp</field>
<desc>
<p>Specifies the type of the information supplied in the regulatory reporting details.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepDetDt</field>
<desc>
<p>Date related to the specified type of regulatory reporting details.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepDetCtry</field>
<desc>
<p>Country related to the specified type of regulatory reporting details. ISO Standard.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepDetCd</field>
<desc>
<p>Specifies the nature, purpose, and reason for the transaction to be reported for regulatory and statutory requirements in a coded form.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepDetAm</field>
<desc>
<p>Amount of money to be reported for regulatory and statutory requirements.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepDetAmCcy</field>
<desc>
<p>Currency of the regulatory reporting amount.</p>
</desc>
</t>
<t>
<field>TrxRegRepDetInfText</field>
<desc>
<p>Additional details that cater for specific domestic regulatory requirements.</p>
</desc>
</t>
    </menu>
</t24help>