<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>POR.REPAIR.AUDITLOGS</title>
        <table>POR.REPAIR.AUDITLOGS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>Repair Audit Log table holds the details of the fields changed by the user in the Repair Input Screen &amp; Repair Authorization Screen. It will get updated with old and new value when the user changes any field in the Repair Screen.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>Inputter</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the user name who repaired the payment</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>InputterDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the date on which payment gets repaired.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>InputterTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the time on which payment gets repaired.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NewValue</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>The last entered value by the operator for a said field as stored in FieldPrompt</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldValue</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>The value as retrieved from the database before operator changes for a said field as stored in FieldPrompt</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Authoriser1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the First Authoriser name who authorises the Repair Payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Authoriser1Date</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the date on which the First Authoriser authorises the Repair Payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Authoriser1Time</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the time on which the First Authoriser authorises the Repair Payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Authoriser2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the Second Authoriser name who authorises the Repair Payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Authoriser2Date</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the date on which the Second Authoriser authorises the Repair Payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Authoriser2Time</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the time on which the Second Authoriser authorises the Repair Payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrNo</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the version number of the changes.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FieldPrompt</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the Field Names, whose values are changed by the operator.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FTNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>No Input Field.</p>
                <p>Holds the Transaction Reference or FT Number of the Repair Payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
