<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.BANKCHARGES</title>
        <table>PP.BANKCHARGES</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to maintain the Bank charges(Inbound Our and Outbound Our) in the payments hub.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or reverse a record in store table, PPL.CHARGES</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CommonCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the Common Currency for all the fee types within a bank charge.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 3 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field,  'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CorrespondentBIC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the BIC of the sending bank.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 alphanumeric characters. Wildcard value '*' is allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CountryCodeDestination</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the country code of the destination.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>2 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field,  'COUNTRY.CODE' in COUNTRY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CTRBTRIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the type of transfer for which the charge is defined.</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>C - Customer Transfer</p>
                <p>B - Bank Transfer</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the code of the currency for which the charge is defined.</p>
                <p>Possible Values :</p>
                <p>Value links to field, 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY. Wildcard value '*' is allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateBankCharges</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as </p>
                <p>Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeTierRangeLowerLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the lower tier amount and if the transaction amount is greater than this limit (in case of FX, converted amount) and is lesser than the next tier (if there is any), then this record will be selected.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>17 characters of type AMT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeType</field>
            <desc>
		<p>Specifies the fee type which is linked to the bank charge defined.</p>
		<p>Validation Rules:</p>
		<p>Mandatory field. Value links to field, 'FeeType' in PPT.FEETYPE.</p>
		<p>Special processing:</p>
		<p>Redirect Fee is a fee type introduced to capture fee when a payment is redirected. It is a conditional fee type and is applied only when payment direction is “R”(Redirect)</p>
		<p>When processing a redirect payment with charge option BEN or SHA, if the redirect fee needs to be taken from the Sending Bank, then, Redirect fee needs to be defined as part of the Sending Bank Charges. If it is to be taken from the Receiving Bank, then, it needs to be defined as part of the Receiving Bank Charges. If Redirect Fee is defined for both Sending and Receiving bank, then, Sending bank definition will take precedence. </p>
		<p>When processing a redirect payment with charge option OUR, charges of sending and receiving bank will be summed up and used. In this case, if any fee is defined for both sending and receiving bank, the receiving bank fee will be the final fee that is used. This applies to any fee type and not restricted to Redirect Fee.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FixedChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the fixed charge amount.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>15 characters of type 'AMT'</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This would be the percentage indicated in</p>
                <p>nn.nnnn (upto 9 decimal places). If this is blank</p>
                <p>then default percentage as defined in FeeType</p>
                <p>table would be applied. If this is zero then no VAT</p>
                <p>on charge would be applied even if defined in</p>
                <p>FeeType table for the respective Fee Type.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Include71GIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if the payments hub needs to send 71G charges to the receiving bank or not. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes.Charges are included in 71G tag</p>
                <p>N - No.Charges are not included in 71G tag.</p>
                <p>Vaidation Rules:</p>
                <p>Value to this field is mandatory if field, 'SendingOrReceivingBankCharge'is set as R.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MaximumChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge amount has to be equal to or lesser than this maximum charge amount.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>15 characters of type AMT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MinimumChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge amount has to be equal to or greater than this minimum amount.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>15 characters of type AMT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PercentageVariableFee</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Hold the percentage value when the fee type is a variable fee type.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>11 characters of type R.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PercentageVATOnCharge</field>
            <desc>
                <p>IndicatesThis would be the percentage indicated in</p>
                <p>nn.nnnn (upto 9 decimal places). If this is blank</p>
                <p>then default percentage as defined in FeeType</p>
                <p>table would be applied. If this is zero then no VAT</p>
                <p>on charge would be applied even if defined in</p>
                <p>FeeType table for the respective Fee Type.</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>'' (Blank)</p>
                <p>0  (Zero) </p>
                <p>Positive value</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AlwaysApplyFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the charge is to be applied always or not.</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>"Y" - Yes</p>
                <p>"N" - No</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Mandatory field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the order (sequence) of the record in the application. Based on the value, a record is prioritised in such a way that, it is given higher preference for selection under peeling logic applied in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 9 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SendingOrReceivingBankCharge</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if the charge defined is to be considered as Sending Bank charge or Receiving bank charge.</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>S - Sending Bank.</p>
                <p>R - Receiving Bank.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SLACode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the code that relates to service level agreement with other banks. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Value links to field, 'SLAID' in PPT.SLAPERCODEWORD table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateBankCharges</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApplyMeOnlyFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if only the defined charge is to be applied. Payments hub will not consider other charges </p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankChargesFeeFormulaId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the unique ID to identify the Bank charges fee formula.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankChargesFeeTypeID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the unique ID to identify the Bank charges fee type.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankChargesID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the unique bank charges ID can be linked with multiple records in this table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BaseChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the fixed positive amount which would be added to charge amount in case of percentage charge.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>15 characters of type AMT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeDiscountAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Mentions the fixed positive amount which would be deducted from charge amount in case of percentage charge.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>15 characters of type AMT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeRiseAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the fixed positive amount which could be added to the calculated Fee (fixed or variable) to arrive at the final fee.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>15 characters of type AMT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
