<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.BANK.CODE</title>
        <table>PP.BANK.CODE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table stores the relationship between the National Clearing Code (NCC) and the BIC. This table would be used to convert a National ID to its corresponding BIC or vice versa.</p>
            <p>Data for this table can be keyed in manually or can be uploaded from a file</p>
            <p>Any manually keyedin record in the Bank code table is marked as manually updated.</p>
            <p>The upload process does not overwrite records keyed in manually.</p>
                    </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>FinancialInstitutionName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Name of the financial institution or bank</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANBIC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains the BIC-11 issued together with the IBANs for the institution’s clients.</p>
                <p>Institution code (4 characters)</p>
                <p>Country code (2 characters)</p>
                <p>Location code (2 characters)</p>
                <p>Branch code (3 characters – XXX to denote head or main office)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANCountryCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Country code in the IBAN. This follows ISO 3166-1, contains only alphabets and is 2 character long.</p>
                <p>Under certain circumstances this can be different from the country indicated in field Country Name</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANNationalID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The National ID which is as part of the IBAN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p/>
                <p>A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NationalID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The National identifier of the institution/branch otherwise called NCC(National Clearing Code)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table PPT.BANKCODE. This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>No Input field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OriginatingSource</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The source from which details of bank code was updated. This is a free text field</p>
                            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to, during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OverrideThroughUpload</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether this specific record can be overwritten when uploaded from a file.</p>
                <p>To prevent data upload to overwrite this record, set this field to 'N'. Else, set it to 'Y'.</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H-YYYYMMDDHHMMSSsss - History. Where: YYYY - year, MM - month, DD - day, HH - hour, MM - minutes, SS - seconds and sss - miliseconds</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
               <p>MF - Modified future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>

            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SourceKey</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This attribute links to the SourceKey in BICTable.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateBankCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered active by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ZIPCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Post code of the institution/branch.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankCodeID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique Identifier, system generated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>HOlds the unique BIC of the institution from the BIC directory.</p>
                <p>Can be maximum of 11 characters. BIC comprises of</p>
                <p>Institution code (4 characters)</p>
                <p>Country code (2 characters)</p>
                <p>Location code (2 characters)</p>
                <p>Branch code (3 characters – XXX denotes main or head office)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CheckDigitMethod</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is applicable only for EMZ clearing. Every BLZ has a logic for validating the</p>
                <p>account number. This field stores the method for validating that BLZ code.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CityName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Name of the city where the institution/branch is located.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the Company to which this record belongs to.</p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CountryCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the country for which the National ID is defined.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table PPT.BANKCODE. This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>No Input field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateBankCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
