<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.CURRENCY</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to setup details about various currencies used in payments hub. A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.CURRENCY.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FractionalDigit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the fractional digit for the currency. </p>
                <p>Example: </p>
                <p>Japanese yen has 0 decimals, USD has 2 decimals and Kuwaiti dinar has 3 decimals.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. The value can range from 0 to 99 only.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FXLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the limit in the foreign currency upto which a payment can be</p>
                <p>processed STP. When any currency undergoes a FOREX conversion, the converted value will be checked against the value to this field in order to determine if the payment can be processed as STP. If the converted value has exceeded this limit, the payment is marked as 'Non-STP' by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. This field can hold upto 17 numeric characters as a value.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OverrideThroughUpload</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if currency record can be updated from an automated upload process.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - The entry is manually updated and can be overridden by the upload process.</p>
                <p>N – The entry is manual updated and the upload process should not override it.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>User can edit the content of this field with possible values only.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WeekendDay1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the first one-working day in a week. Eg Saturday.  </p>
                <p>Western countries observe Saturday as the first weekend where else many Middle-east countries observe Friday as the first weekend.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Monday</p>
                <p>Tuesday</p>
                <p>Wednesday</p>
                <p>Thursday</p>
                <p>Friday</p>
                <p>Saturday</p>
                <p>Sunday</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WeekendDay2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the second one-working day in a week. Eg Sunday.  </p>
                <p>Western countries observe Sunday as the second weekend where else many Middle-east countries observe Saturday as the second weekend.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Monday</p>
                <p>Tuesday</p>
                <p>Wednesday</p>
                <p>Thursday</p>
                <p>Friday</p>
                <p>Saturday</p>
                <p>Sunday</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CountryCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds a 2 character unique code which specifies the country code. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The entry should be an existing record in COUNTRY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CountryName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Name of the country to which a currency belongs. </p>
                <p>In only exceptional cases such as the currency being EUR, a currency may have more than one country.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>This is an optional field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds a 3 character unique code which denotes a specific currency used in the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyGroup</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specific the group under which the currency should be grouped together. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>This is an optional field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each currency. The value is usually the same as the ID of the record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Mentions the name of the currency in free text. </p>
                <p>Example:</p>
                <p>US Dollars, Indian Rupees</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. This field can hold upto 35 alphanumeric characters as a value.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
