<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.COUNTRYIBANSTRUCTURE</title>
        <table>PP.COUNTRYIBANSTRUCTURE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table stores the IBAN structure per country.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CountryIBANStructureID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique Identifier, system generated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CountryName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The country name of the institution/branch as indicated in ISO 3166</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table PPT.COUNTRYIBANSTRUCTURE. This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>No Input field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateCountryIBANStructure</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>HomeCountryIndicator</field>
            <desc>
		<p>Indicates if the country is a home country of the company. This is used for Companies that have more </p>
		<p> than one country as a local country.</p>
		<p> For example, GB covers United Kingdom, Isle of Man, Jersey etc. </p>
		<p> This plays a key role in identifying of the payment is a domestic or an international payment.</p>
	        <p>Possible values</p>
                <p>Y - Home country of the company</p>
                <p>N - Not a home country of the company</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANCheckDigitsLength</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Number of check digits in the IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANCheckDigitsPosition</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Start position of bank identifier in the IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANCountryCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>ISO country code prefix in the IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANCountryCodeLength</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Number of characters of the country code in the IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANCountryCodePosition</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Start position of the country code in IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AccountNumberlength</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Number of characters of account number in IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANMandatoryCountry</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Y – IBAN is mandatory for sending messages to this country.</p>
                <p>N – IBAN is not mandatory for sending messages to this country.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANMandatoryCountryMT103</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Y – IBAN is mandatory for sending MT103+ to this country.</p>
                <p>N – IBAN is not mandatory for sending MT103+ to this country.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANNationalIDLength</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Number of significant characters of the National ID value that are used by</p>
                <p>SWIFT to populate the IBAN NATIONAL ID, and that are sufficient to derive the</p>
                <p>IBAN BIC correctly. This number can be different from (that is, smaller than) the</p>
                <p>length of the national bank/branch identifier defined in the IBAN Registry. Note</p>
                <p>that as SWIFT refines its IBAN to BIC translation algorithms, this number may</p>
                <p>change from release to release.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANStructure</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Structure of the IBAN.</p>
                <p>A = Alpha value (A-Z)</p>
                <p>N = numeric value (0-9)</p>
                <p>X = Alphanumeric (A-Z + 0-9)</p>
                <p>For example, for an IBAN of NL, the IBAN structure can be stored as follows.</p>
                <p>AANNAAAANNNNNNNNNN.</p>
                <p>An NL IBAN is validated against this structure.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IBANTotalLength</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The total number of characters of the IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LocalISOCurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>ISO currency code</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LocalISOCurrencyName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>ISO currency name</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NationalClearingSystemCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Required to derive a BIC from an IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NationalIDLength</field>
            <desc>
                <p>As the IBANNationalID is not the same as the NationalID but the NationalID will</p>
                <p>be mostly part of the IBANNationalID, NationalIDLength and NationalIDPosition</p>
                <p>are added to convert the NationalID from the IBANnationaliD and for routing and</p>
                <p>settlement to find the NationalID from the IBAN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AccountNumberPosition</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Start position of the account number in IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NationalIDPosition</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Start position of the NationalID Position</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table PPT.COUNTRYIBANSTRUCTURE. This field can hold upto 15 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>No Input field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OverrideThroughUpload</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If this field is ‘N’ then it implies that the data entry will never be updated by</p>
                <p>the upload process. If set to ‘Y’ then the data can be overridden by the upload</p>
                <p>process.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H-YYYYMMDDHHMMSSsss - History. Where: YYYY - year, MM - month, DD - day, HH - hour, MM - minutes, SS - seconds and sss - miliseconds</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                       <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
               <p>MF - Modified future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateCountryIBANStructure</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered active by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WeekendDay1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will specify the first non-working day in the week. For example,</p>
                <p>Saturday.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WeekendDay2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field will specify the second non-working day (if any) in the week. For</p>
                <p>example, Sunday</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankBranchIdentifierLength</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Start position of the branch identifier in the IBAN (value is empty if the branch</p>
                <p>identifier is not applied in the country's IBAN format)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankBranchIdentifierPosition</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Start position of the branch identifier in the IBAN (value is empty if the branch</p>
                <p>identifier is not applied in the country's IBAN format)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankIdentifierLength</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Number of characters of bank identifier in the IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankIdentifierPosition</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Start position of bank identifier in the IBAN</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CountryCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Country Code in ISO format</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
