<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.CLEARING.NONWORKINGDAY</title>
        <table>PP.CLEARING.NONWORKINGDAY</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to store the non-working days for channels based on region of a country code.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or reverse a record in store table, PPT.CLEARINGNONWORKINGDAY</p>
            <p>This table stores the exceptions. If a date is not a holiday, it will not be stored in this table.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Region</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates a Region,State etc. within a Country.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Non Mandatory field - Defaulted to "ALL" if left blank.</p>
                <p>2) "ALL" if this applies for all Region within the mentioned Countrycode.</p>
                <p>The above "ALL" setup is used to define a country level holiday.</p>
                <p>3) Up to 35 Alphanumeric characters, which should represent Valid Region values as defined in the PPT.REGION table.</p>
                <p>The Region entered should belong to the CountryCode entered.</p>
                <p>Example Texas,Miami</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChannelName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates a valid channel code for which holiday is being defined.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Example:</p>
                <p>SWIFT – Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Transactions.This channel is used for international payments worldwide.</p>
                <p>PMTROUTER – Payment Router. This channel is used only by Our Bank. </p>
                <p>EMZ – Elektronischer Massenzahlungsverkehr</p>
                <p>BACS – Bankers' Automated Clearing Services</p>
                <p>CEC  – Centre for Exchange and Clearing</p>
                <p>HKICL – Hong Kong Interbank Clearing Limited</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>10 alphabetic characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘ChannelName’ in PPT.CHANNEL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CountryCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies country code for which holiday is defined. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 2 alphanumeric characters.Value links to field, 'COUNTRY.CODE' in COUNTRY.</p>
                <p>Example:GB,US</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DayDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Represents the actual holiday date for the respective country and region.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. Any valid date can be selected by clicking on the Calendar.</p>
                <p>Allows up to 11 characters in Date format.</p>
                <p>Example 20141225,20141226</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
