<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.CONTRACT</title>
        <table>PP.CONTRACT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to store the contract information in the payments hub. </p>
            <p>Routing &amp; Settlement process can deals with two types of Contracts - Country Contract and Party Contract.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>The Party contract is checked for the credit party in the payment.</p>
            <p>In a Party Contract, the bank specifies on how the payment should</p>
            <p>be routed and settled with the credit party. </p>
            <p/>
            <p>The Country contract is checked for the destination country of the payment. In a Country Contract, the bank specifies</p>
            <p>on how it wants to route and settle payments to be sent to a specific country.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>Peeling Off order determines the order in which the entries within the table are prioritized.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store tables PPL.CONTRACT, PPL.CONTRACTCATEGORY and PPL.RSOPTION. Here, PPL.CONTRACTCATEGORY and PPL.RSOPTION are child tables linked to PPL.CONTRACT.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ContractCategoryID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This Contract Category ID will uniquely define the Contract Category entry.</p>
                <p>This ID will be used to further search in the R &amp; S options table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ContractID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Contract for which the Contract Categories are defined.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ContractOptionID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field uniquely identifies a Contract option within a Company.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ContractType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contracts can be defined for a credit party of a payment or for the destination country of a payment.</p>
                <p>A Contract defined for the credit party is called as a PTY Contract and a Contract defined for the destination country is called as a CTY Contract.</p>
                <p>Value can also be BNK: Bank Contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory.</p>
                <p>2) Dropdown with allowed values BNK, CTY &amp; PTY.</p>
                <p>   Where BNK - Bank level contracts</p>
                <p>         CTY - Country level contracts</p>
                <p>         PTY - Party level contracts </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CoverIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicator for a cover payment.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Allowed values are 'Y and 'N'</p>
                <p>2) This field can be set to Y for R &amp; S options of PREF, SSI or AGENT.</p>
                <p>3) If set to Y then a Cover method of routing is used. The credit bank   for which the R &amp; S option of PREF/SSI/AGENT was selected will be set with a Direct payment flag. And the new correspondent bank (derived from PREF/SSI/AGENT table) will be searched with a routing group of COVER.</p>
                <p>4) A setting of N or blank implies that a serial method of routing is used.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Currency used in the contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Dropdown with allowed values FCY,LCY and valid PPT.CURRENCY entries.</p>
                <p>2) Home Currency will get defaulted if left blank.</p>
                <p>3) The currency field can be set to LCY or FCY only for a contract of type BNK.</p>
                <p>If set to LCY, the currency corresponds to the local currency of the credit country. If set to FCY, this currency corresponds to currencies other than the local currency of the credit country.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Destination</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Destination Country Code to which the payment needs to be routed.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory for Country level contracts.</p>
                <p>2) Dropdown linked to PPT.COUNTRYIBANSTRUCTURE table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateContract</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AccountCompany</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the account owning company key.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory when RSOption is set to 'ACCOUNT'</p>
                <p>2) Should be a valid entry in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LeadTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used to determine the soft cut-off time. The cut-off as retrieved from the channel cut-off table is subtracted by this lead time (and the lead time in client conditions) to come up with a soft cut-off time.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Allowed format HH:MM</p>
                <p>2) Default value is 00:00</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MessageChannel</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specify the channel to be used for Routing and Settlement.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1)For RSOption LORO/NOSTRO or ACCOUNT, this field would be set as SW.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OptionRanking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Every Contract Category will have one or more entries for R &amp; S option(s). </p>
                <p>The order in which these R &amp; S options are evaluated is given by this ranking. </p>
                <p>Rank 1 is the highest priority R &amp; S option and 999 being the lowest.</p>
                <p>Duplicate ranks are not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PartyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field gives the party for which the PTY Contract is defined.</p>
                <p>The PTY Contract party can be defined as a BIC in which case it can be specified as a BIC4, BIC6, BIC-8 or BIC-11. </p>
                <p>The Party ID type for a BIC is B. </p>
                <p>A Party ID Type and Party ID can therefore be defined for example as – B BARC, B BARCGB, B BARCGB21 or B BARCGB2106P. (An Contract with a BIC-11 has a higher priority compared to an Contract defined at BIC-8. Similarly in terms of pririty - BIC-8 Contract &gt; BIC-6 Contract &gt; BIC-4 Contract)</p>
                <p>The Party ID can also be defined as a National Clearing Code (NCC). The Party ID type for a national clearing is N. A Party ID Type and Party ID can therefore be defined for example as - N SC200050</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PartyIDType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is applicable only for the Party Contract.</p>
                <p>The Party ID type for a BIC is B.</p>
                <p>The Party ID type for a national clearing is N.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Priority</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The priority field is specified as a single digit with a value between 1 and 9.</p>
                <p>This is the SWIFT priority assigned to the payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Every Contract will have one or more entries for contract categories. The order in which these contract categories are evaluated is given by this ranking. </p>
                <p>Rank 1 is the highest priority R &amp; S option and 999 being the lowest.</p>
                <p>Duplicate ranks are not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AccountCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the currency of the Account Number.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory when RSOption is set to 'ACCOUNT'</p>
                <p>2) Should be a valid entry in PPT.CURRENCY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RoutingProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When specified, the Routing Product can be used to define Product specific</p>
                <p>routing mechanisms.</p>
                <p>Routing Product is set as per the Product determination step of STP process flow.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Default value is *</p>
                <p>2) Dropdown linked to PPT.ROUTINGPRODUCT table</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSOption</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This R &amp; S option gives the method to be followed to route the payment to its top credit bank.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>At a high level, the R &amp; S options can be classified into three different types.</p>
                <p>1. Channel – Here the payment is sent to the credit bank using the channel. For example, the R &amp; S option can be defined as EMZ; the payment is then routed to the credit bank using the EMZ clearing.</p>
                <p>2. Correspondent Relationship (LORO/NOSTRO/ACCOUNT) – Here the payment</p>
                <p>is sent to the credit bank using LORO/NOSTRO accounts. The ACCOUNT R &amp; S</p>
                <p>option gives the flexibility to define an account on which the settlement should be carried out. This account is provided in the R &amp; S option table in the ‘Option ID type and ID’ field.</p>
                <p>3. Routing Method (PREF, SSI, AGENT, PARTY) – Here the credit bank can be reached via another correspondent bank. In case of a PREF R &amp; S option, this new correspondent bank is given by the PREF table. For SSI, it is the SSI table and for AGENT it is the AGENT table that gives the new correspondent bank. For PARTY, the new correspondent bank is provided in the R &amp; S option table in the ‘Option ID type and ID’ field.</p>
                <p>The R &amp; S of type (1) and type (2) as mentioned above will go through</p>
                <p>channel level validations. For R &amp; S of type (3), a new correspondent bank is introduced. This new correspondent bank would go through R &amp; S tables from contract onwards and determine an R &amp; S option corresponding to the new correspondent bank.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory.</p>
                <p>2) Dropdown with allowed values:</p>
                <p>   1. LORO</p>
                <p>   2. NOSTRO</p>
                <p>   3. PREF</p>
                <p>   4. SSI</p>
                <p>   5. AGENT</p>
                <p>   6. ACCOUNT</p>
                <p>   7. PARTY</p>
                <p>   8. Any 3 char channel ID set within the Channels table</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSPartyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used when the R &amp; S option is set as ACCOUNT or PARTY.</p>
                <p>If the R &amp; S option is defined as an ACCOUNT then this field will hold the account key.</p>
                <p>If the R &amp; S option is defined as a PARTY then this field will hold the BIC or National clearing code.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSPartyIDType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used when the R &amp; S option is set as PARTY.</p>
                <p>If the R &amp; S option is defined as a PARTY then this field will hold the type of party ID.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The Option ID can be a BIC in which case it can be specified as a BIC-8 or a BIC-11 only. The Option ID type for a BIC is B.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The Option ID can be a NCC. The Option ID type for a NCC is N.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SLACode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When specified, the SLA can be used to define Bank specific routing</p>
                <p>mechanisms.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Default value is *</p>
                <p>2) Dropdown linked to PPT.SLAPERCODEWORD table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateContract</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionLowerLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the transaction lower limit is not specified then its value is set to 0.</p>
                <p>This limit will be in the transaction currency of the record.</p>
                <p>If the transaction currency is specified as *, LCY or FCY then this limit will be in the home currency of the company.</p>
                <p>The amount of the transaction should always be equal to or greater than this lower limit.</p>
                <p>The transaction amount considered for this limit does not include any charges.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionUpperLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the transaction upper limit is not specified then its value is set to</p>
                <p>99999999999999999 (17 times 9).</p>
                <p>This limit will be in the transaction currency of the record.</p>
                <p>If the transaction currency is specified as *, LCY or FCY then this limit will be in the home currency of the company.</p>
                <p>The amount of the transaction should always be lesser than this upper limit.</p>
                <p>The transaction amount considered for this limit does not include any charges.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AccountNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the number of the account.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory when RSOption is set to 'ACCOUNT'.</p>
                <p>2) Free text/Not validated against T24 Account.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AlternativeForCutoff</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Alternative for cut-off exceeded.</p>
                <p>If the R &amp; S option could not be chosen because the cutoff was exceeded then the alternative for cut-off exceeded is checked to determine the processing required.</p>
                <p>R &amp; S provides the following alternatives for them</p>
                <p>1. NEXT (N) The next available R &amp; S option under the same Contract Category is checked.</p>
                <p>2. ADVANCE (A) The due date is advanced. (Refer to the date processing on how this is carried out)</p>
                <p>3. REPAIR (R) The payment is routed to Repair for a manual review.</p>
                <p>4. Country (C) Switch to Country level Contract. Applicable only on a PTY contract. The Contract table is checked to determine the applicable CTY contract.</p>
                <p>R &amp; S based is carried out based on that contract</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory.</p>
                <p>2) Dropdown with allowed values A,C,N &amp; R.</p>
                <p>3) Option C is only allowed for ContractType 'PTY'.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AlternativeForRS</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Alternative for R&amp;S failure.</p>
                <p>If R &amp; S option could not be chosen due to failure of channel validation</p>
                <p>rules then the alternative for R &amp; S not possible is checked to determine the processing required.</p>
                <p>R &amp; S provides the following alternatives for them</p>
                <p>1. NEXT (N) The next available R &amp; S option under the Contract Category is checked.</p>
                <p>2. REPAIR (R) The payment is routed to Repair for a manual review.</p>
                <p>3. Country (C) Switch to Country level Contract. Applicable only on a PTY contract. The Contract table is checked to determine the applicable CTY contract.</p>
                <p>R &amp; S based is carried out based on that contract.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory.</p>
                <p>2) Dropdown with allowed values C,N &amp; R.</p>
                <p>3) Option C is only allowed for ContractType 'PTY'.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BusinessLine</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Every company has a number of business lines.</p>
                <p>Country and Party contracts can be made specific to a business line.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Mandatory.</p>
                <p>2) Free Text field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeOption</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Type of Charge.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1) Default is *</p>
                <p>2) Dropdown with allowed values *,BEN,OUR &amp; SHA</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
