<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.CLIENTCHARGES</title>
        <table>PP.CLIENTCHARGES</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table enables definition of charges for clients (non banks)</p>
	    <p>Charges can be defined for both debit and credit parties based on the direction of the message.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ClientChargesID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Client charges ID can be linked with multiple records in this table</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClientID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Customer ID as in the DDA</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Can be wildcarded as well. Wildcard denotes that this definition is not client specific but a common one</p> 
            </desc>
        </t>
      <t>
            <field>CommonCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Multiple fee can be defined for a single correspondent bank. This fields holds the currency in which the fee will be charged.</p>
		<p>Should be a valid value in PPT_CURRENCY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example: BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field 'CompanyID' in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold up to 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CustomerAccountCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates 3 character ISO currency code of the account which is either the credit or the debit account currency in the payment</p>
		<p>If specific charges need to be applied based on the account's currency, this field can be used</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Should be a valid value in PPT_CURRENCY or can be wild carded</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CustomerAccountNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the account number of the account which is either the credit or the debit account in the payment</p>
		<p>If specific charges need to be applied based on the account used in the payment, this field can be used</p>
		<p/>
                <p>Should be a valid account in the DDA system or can be wild carded</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CustomerAccountNumberCompID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the owning company of the account specified in field Customer Account Number.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Can be wild carded</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateClientCharges</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds a valid FeePoduct. Fee product would be an output when a payment product is successfully determined.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Can be wildcarded.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold up to 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeTierRangeLowerLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>There could be different charges based on the transaction amount. We can define various amount tiers and different charge amount for each tier</p>
		<p>This field holds the transaction amount tier.</p>
		<p>For the following configuration of 0, 500 and 1500</p>
		<p>0 - Covers form 0 until 499</p>
		<p>500 - Covers form 500 until 999</p>
		<p>1000 - Covers form 1000 and above</p>
		<p/>
		<p>Based on the transaction amount, the appropriate tier will be chosen.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the fee type which will be applied. Mandatory field.</p>
                <p>Should be a valid value in PPT.FEETYPE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FixedChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                  <p>Holds the fixed positive amount in the Fee type currency. Fee amount could be entered up to two decimal places</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System generated id for the table PP_ClientCharges.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MaximumChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the maximum charge amount for the specific fee type. If the charge amount is calculated as a percentage</p>
		<p>of the transaction amount and if it exceeds the amount specified here, the fee amount is capped to the amount</p>
		<p>specified in this field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MinimumChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
              <p>Holds the minimum charge amount for the specific fee type. If the charge amount is calculated as a percentage</p>
		<p>of the transaction amount and if it falls below the amount specified here, the fee amount applied would be the amount</p>
		<p>specified in this field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold up to 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PercentageVariableFee</field>
            <desc>
                <p>In case of variable fee this will be defined as the percentage (up to 9 decimal places)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PercentageVATOnCharge</field>
            <desc>
                 <p>Fee amount can be a fixed amount or can be a percentage of the transaction amount</p>
		<p>To specify that the fee should be a percentage of the transaction amount, specify the % in this field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AlwaysApplyFlag</field>
            <desc>
               <p>If this flag is set to Y against a particular Fee type then that Fee will always be taken if evaluated for a </p>
		<p>particular payment. Both conditional and unconditional fees can be marked as ‘Always apply’. When a conditional</p>
		<p>fee is marked so, then fee will be applied always if the condition is first met, if the condition is not met, </p>
		<p>then fee is not applied though the flag is set. For example, Phone confirmation fee is applied only if client has</p>
		<p> chosen for phone confirmation. In brief, this flag should be understood as ‘Include fee type always for </p>
		<p>unconditional fees and for conditional, include if condition is met’. In the table below always apply flag </p>
		<p>for Transaction Fee and Service Fee is set as Y which means that both these components should always be applied.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>Y</p>
                <p>N </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Mandatory field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H-YYYYMMDDHHMMSSsss - History. Where: YYYY - year, MM - month, DD - day, HH - hour, MM - minutes, SS - seconds and sss - miliseconds</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Determines the order in which the fee needs to be evaluated. Higher the rank, higher the priority. </p>
		<p>Value 1 (Rank 1) will get the highest priority</p>
		<p>Mandatory field</p> 
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ResidencyStatus</field>
            <desc>
		<p>In most of the countries there is a Value Added Tax (VAT) imposed by government which is levied on the </p>
		<p>payment or on the charges which are taken by the Bank. This tax amount goes to the government and all Banks</p>
		<p> within that country need to follow those regulations. It need not be applied on all the cases and one of the</p>
		<p> factor which influences whether we take the VAT or not depends if ordering party or beneficiary customer is a </p>
		<p> resident of that country or not.</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
		<p>RR, RN, NR or NN</p>
		<p>First character denotes the residency status of the ordering party (OrderingPartyResidencyFlag)</p>
		<p>and second character denotes the residency status of beneficiary party (BeneficiaryPartyResidencyFlag)</p>
                <p>Can be wildcarded</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>MF - Modified future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SourceProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Bank may receive payments from variety of sources, it could be from Internet banking channel or Trade platform</p>
		<p> or the payment could have been initiated by the Cash pool engine. We may not want to take charges for payments</p>
		<p> originating from certain sources or apply preferential charges. E.g.  A bank has introduced a new channel for</p>
		<p> the client initiated payment and want to move the clients from old channel to new channel; based on the source </p>
		<p> we can increase the Fee for payments initiated through the old channel; which will mean that client would not </p>
		<p>want to pay more charges to use the old channel and rather would try to move to new channel at the earliest</p>
		<p> This field specifies the source group from where payment has been originated. Soucre group is a group of payment sources</p>
		<p>Can be wildcarded</p>
                <p>Should be a valid value in PPT_SourceProductGroup table</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateClientCharges</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApplyMeOnlyFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Any fee type with this flag set, then, only this Fee type should be applied and rest of the fee type should be ignored</p>
		<p>except where Always apply flag is set as Y. When processing a payment, fee component may come up with 4 different charges</p>
		<p>to be applied. Each charge will be included or calculated depending on the ranking associated with it. When a fee</p>
		<p>with ‘Apply me only’ flag is set to YES, it would mean the rest of the charges can be ignored (except where always apply flag is set as Yes)</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>Y</p>
                <p>N</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Mandatory field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BaseChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
               <p>Fixed positive amount which would be added to charge amount in case of percentage charge.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BusinessLine</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Each customer belongs to a specific group which is called business line. Each business line can have specific</p>
		<p> objective from the Fee perspective and accordingly a bank might want to price the charges and hence it’s very </p>
		<p>important to take business line into account while determining the fee</p>
		<p>Can be wildcarded</p> 
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeDiscountAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Fixed positive amount which would be deducted from charge amount in case of percentage charge</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeRiseAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Fixed positive amount which could be added to the calculated Fee (fixed or variable) to arrive at the final fee.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClientChargesFeeFormulaId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID to identify the Client Charges Fee Formula</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClientChargesFeeTypeId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID to identify the Client Charges Fee Type</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
