<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.CLEARING.NATURE.CODE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to define clearing nature codes of clearing based on company in the payments hub.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.CLEARINGNATURECODE</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateClearingNatureCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChequeType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the type of cheque for the clearing.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>4 alphanumeric characters. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClearingID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the name of the clearing in the payments hub.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Example :</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Global TRX-based: "TARGET2"</p>
                <p>Global file-based: "EBA"</p>
                <p>Local TRX-based: "FPS" (UK), "CHAPS" (UK),"CHATS"/"HKICL" (HK)</p>
                <p>Local file-based:"BACS"(UK),"CEC" (BE),"EMZ" (GE)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClearingNatureCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the code which identifies the nature of clearing payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 20 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClearingNatureCodeDescription</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes of the nature of the clearing payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateClearingNatureCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
