<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.EXPOSURE.DATE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to setup parameters for calculation of Exposure Date, in a manner which can be processed by the payments hub using peeling logic. Exposure date is the date from which credited funds are available for use by the client. Banks process certain transactions wherein, even though funds are credited to the client immediately, client cannot make use of those funds.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>Example: A cheque is presented for collection by the payee. The bank knows that cheque clearing will take 2 days. In this case, the bank can credit the funds to the payee with an exposure date set as 2 days in future.</p>
            <p>Even though the amount is credited to the account, the payee or the client cannot be withdraw the funds before the exposure date.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.EXPOSUREDATE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ProductCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Product code as defined within Product determination. This could only be a valid &amp; unique ClientConditionsProductCode  as per static data HeavyweightProductCond or LightWeightProductCond table.</p>
                <p>Validation Rule:</p>
                <p>If left blank, a default value of "*" is set.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Order (sequence) of the records.</p>
                <p>In this table order matters and as soon the first match is found that value will be picked up. Ranking would be required to maintain that order.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateExposureDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateExposureDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ExposureDateBase</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the base date on which exposure date is calculated.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>CVD - Credit Value Date</p>
                <p>DUE - Processing Date</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OffsetDays</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the offset mentioned in number of days which needs to be subtracted or added to the exposure date base to arrive at the actual exposure date. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Values can be from -10 to +10.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
