<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.FEETYPE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to create/configure different fee types in the payments hub.</p>
            <p>Fee types can be segregated in two broad categories.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>i. Conditional Fee Types – These are the Fee types which can only be applied for a transaction if there is a particular condition which is met. Example: Non-STP Fee. This Fee can only be applied if the transaction has been processed Non-STP. If the transaction is STP then the charge cannot be levied even if it is defined in the Client Charges table.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>ii. Unconditional Fee Types – These are the Fee types which needs to be applied in all the cases if it’s defined for the Client.</p>
            <p>Example: Transaction Fee.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>This screen can be used to create only unconditional fee types. User is allowed only to amend a set of predefined conditional fee types in the payments hub.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.FEETYPE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>FeeType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the Fee type to be defined for the company.</p>
                <p>Possible values when ConditionalIndicator is set to 'C':</p>
                <p>Debit Phone Confirmation Fee</p>
                <p>Credit Phone Confirmation Fee</p>
                <p>Debit Email Confirmation Fee</p>
                <p>Credit Email Confirmation Fee</p>
                <p>Debit FAX Confirmation Fee</p>
                <p>Credit FAX Confirmation Fee</p>
                <p>Client Condition Non STP</p>
                <p>Manual Repair</p>
                <p>Payfix Repair</p>
                <p>FX Fee</p>
                <p>Missing IBAN Fee</p>
                <p>Beneficiary Bank Repaired</p>
                <p>Return charge</p>
                <p>Inbound Our Charge</p>
                <p>Outbound Our Charge</p>
                <p>PSD Leg-in charge</p>
                <p>PSD Leg-out charge</p>
                <p>VAT on charges</p>
                <p>Debit Post Confirmation Fee</p>
                <p>Credit Post Confirmation Fee</p>
                <p>Book Transfer Debit Fee</p>
                <p>Book Transfer Credit Fee</p>
                <p>Manual Transfer Fee</p>
                <p>VAT on principal</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 alphanumeric characters. When ConditionalIndicator is set to 'C', the value can be defined only from the possible values mentioned. If not, it is a free text field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeTypeID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application. This is same as ID of the record.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LanguageID1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the language in which charge description will be shown in posting statement lines.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 2 alphanumeric character. The value links to the field 'LanguageID' in PPT.LANGUAGE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LanguageID2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the language in which charge description will be shown in posting statement lines.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>2 alphanumeric character. The value links to the field 'LanguageID' in PPT.LANGUAGE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LanguageID3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the language in which charge description will be shown in posting statement lines.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>2 alphanumeric character. The value links to the field 'LanguageID' in PPT.LANGUAGE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PercentageVATOnCharge</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if VAT is applicable for the fee type with the percentage. The value can be zero and above. Value as zero indicates that VAT is not applicable for the fee type.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>11 numeric characters which includes '.'</p>
                <p>Default value is set as 0.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateFeeType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered active by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BeneficiaryChargeAllowed</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if a beneficiary party can be charged in case of OUR payment.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>"Y" – Yes</p>
                <p>"N" – No.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ConditionalIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Differentiates if the fee type is conditional or unconditional.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>U - Unconditional</p>
                <p>C - Conditional</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateFeeType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeDescription1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the Fee type in Language ID1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory field if a value to LanguageID1 is provided.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeDescription2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the Fee type in Language ID2</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory field if a value to LanguageID2 is provided.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeDescription3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the Fee type in Language ID3</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory field if a value to LanguageID3 is provided.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
