<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.FEETYPECREDITACCOUNT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to store the credit accounts linked with the fee types defined in payments hub. During the Fee processing, depending on the charges which are applied to the payment, a lookup will be performed to identify the associated credit account(P&amp;L account). This credit account along with the other charge details will be used to post entries into the general ledger.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.FEETYPECREDITACCOUNT.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>FeeTypeCreditAccountID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeTypeCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the currency code of the fee type for which a credit account is defined in the application. This provides the flexibility to define different credit accounts for fee types of different currency in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters. The value links to field 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateFeeTypeCRAccount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRAccount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the credit account linked to the fee type.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 characters of type 'ACCA'.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRAccountCompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID of the credit account which is linked to the fee type. The value is same as the value to field, 'CompanyID'.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>No input field.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRAccountCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the currency code of the credit account which is linked to the fee type.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 3 alphanumeric characters. The value links to field 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CRAccountType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the type of the credit account which is linked to the fee type.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>PL - Profile and Loss account</p>
                <p>Vostro - Vostro account</p>
                <p>Nostro - Nostro account</p>
                <p>Suspense - Internal suspense account</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. A value can be defined only from the possible values as mentioned.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateFeeTypeCRAccount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the fee type for which the credit account is defined in the application.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The value links to field 'FeeType' in PPT.FEETYPE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
