<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.PAYMENT.RELEASE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to repair or cancel a payment that is parked due to any technical error.  A payment that encounters any technical error ( Fatal Error) will be parked at parked payment queue with status that is in process. The payment cannot be considered for further process by any subflow as the status will be set as in-process. Such kinds of payments can either be moved to repair or cancel status using this screen. </p>
            <p>Repair will move the payment to repair status (235) and Cancel will move to an end status canceled (997).</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend records in store tables, POR.PAYMENTSTATUSCODE and POR.TRANSACTION.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FTNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the unique ID of the parked payment generated by the payments hub upon generating a payment order.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>16 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NewStatusCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the parked payment should be put to Repair or Cancel. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>REPAIR - Moves the payment to 235 </p>
                <p>CANCEL - Moves the payment to 997</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldStatusCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the current status of the payment while being moved to parked payments queue. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>No input field. 65 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
