<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.PROCESSING.SEQUENCE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to define all processing sequences for Inbound as well as Outbound codeword processing in the payments hub.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or reverse a record in store table, PPT.PROCESSINGSEQUENCE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ProcessingSequenceDescription</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the purpose of the processing sequence </p>
                <p>Example: setOutboundACC, Processing Sequence 3,Processing Sequence 2</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ProcessingSequenceNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates a unique number associated with a processing sequence.</p>
                <p>Example: 1,3,4.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules: </p>
                <p>Mandatory field. This Sequence Number cannot be repeated for the same company. Allows to the maximum of 7 numeric digits.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ProcessingSequenceRoutineName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the name of the routine that needs to be executed as part of the processing sequence.</p>
                <p>Example: InboundCodeWordService.setIPSYMT101ProcessFlags,InboundCodeWordService.setIPSYMT103ProcessFlags</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>255 alphanumeric characters. Must be a valid routine.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateProcessingSequence</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateProcessingSequence</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date till which the respective record will be active.Its a Mandatory field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>InboundProcessingSequenceFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether processing sequence is applicable for inbound code word processing. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
                <p>Blank</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OutboundProcessingSequenceFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether processing sequence is applicable for outbound code word processing. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
                <p>Blank</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
