<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.POSTING.SET</title>
        <table>PP.POSTING.SET</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to define the posting set to be selected based on input criteria of company code, Posting product and set of Payment file</p>
            <p>fields that are updated based on client conditions.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPL.POSTINGSET.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>EndDatePostingSet</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OCPPostingFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether OCP posting entries should be part of the</p>
                <p>posting set.</p>
                <p>Description of the field values are as follows.</p>
                <p>N: The Posting set will not have OCP posting lines</p>
                <p>Y: The Posting set will have OCP posting lines</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PartyFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the posting line is a debit or a credit posting line . Even for the posting line where charges are taken from a credit party , the party flag for the charge posting in PPL_Posting line will be "D" as the charges are getting debited for the party.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>D: Debit Party</p>
                <p>C: Credit Party</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PostingLineId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each posting line created using this screen.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PostingProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Posting product attached to the posting set defined.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. This field must match the posting product retrieved as output from product determination process.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PostingSetId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each posting set in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AccountToken</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the payment related account used in the posting line.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 20 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'AccountToken' in PPT.ACCOUNTTOKEN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the order (sequence) of the record in the application. Based on the value, a record is prioritised in such a way that, it is given higher preference for selection under peeling logic applied in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 9 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SequenceNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the order of the posting lines within the posting set.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>7 numeric characters. Value is not viewable to the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDatePostingSet</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StatementFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the generic statement format attached to the posting line.</p>
                <p>For the principal debit and credit accounts, if the client or bank have</p>
                <p>mentioned a special statement format name in client conditions or Bank</p>
                <p>conditions then statement lines attached to that statement format need to be displayed for the principal posting.</p>
                <p>If the debit side of the payment contains the field DebitStatementFormat or</p>
                <p>credit side contains the field CreditStatementFormat set then it indicates that the side would like to have customised statement lines.</p>
                <p>This field should be checked twice (Debit side and Credit Side)</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>30 alphanumeric character.Value links to field 'StatementFormatID' in PPT.STATEMENTFORMAT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SuppressZeroFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if the posting line has to be displayed if the amount value</p>
                <p>of the amount token result in zero.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N: Display the posting line even when the value of amount token is zero.</p>
                <p>Y: Do not display the posting line when the value of amount token is zero</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ValueDateToken</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date on which the booking was performed in the ledger.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 20 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'DateToken' in PPT.DATETOKEN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VATOnCharge</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>D: The Posting Set will have a posting Line for VAT on Charges for the debit side only.</p>
                <p>C: The Posting Set will have a posting Line for VAT on Charges for the credit side only.</p>
                <p>B: The Posting Set will have a posting Line for VAT on Charges for both the sides of the payment (debit and credit).</p>
                <p>N: The Posting Set will not have posting lines for VAT on Charges for both the sides of the payment (debit and credit).</p>
                <p>S: The posting set will have posting line for VAT on charges for both the sides of the payment with a Zero suppress flag set on each side .The Zero suppress flag indicates that if the VAT on Charges amount is 0 , do not display the posting line(suppress it).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If a side of the payment contains the field, "VATOnCharge" with a value</p>
                <p>set as "Yes" , then that side require the VAT on charges Posting line.</p>
                <p>Field should be checked twice (Debit side and Credit Side)</p>
                <p>If the field with value "Yes" is present only on the debit side then the match criteria for this field must be D or S</p>
                <p>If the field with value "Yes" is present only on the credit side then the match criteria for this field must be C or S</p>
                <p>If the field with value "Yes" is present on both the sides then the match criteria for this field must be B or S</p>
                <p>If the field is not present both the sides then the match criteria for this field must be N or S</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>VATONPrincipal</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>D: The Posting Set will have a posting Line for VAT on principal for the debit side only.</p>
                <p>C: The Posting Set will have a posting Line for VAT on principal for the credit side only.</p>
                <p>B: The Posting Set will have a posting Line for VAT on principal for both the sides of the payment (debit and credit).</p>
                <p>N: The Posting Set will not have postinglines for VAT on principal for both the sides of the payment (debit and credit).</p>
                <p>S: The posting set will have posting line for VAT on Principal for both the sides of the payment with a Zero suppress flag set on each side .The Zero suppress flag indicates that if the VAT on Principal amount is 0 , the posting line will not be displayed (suppress it).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If a side of the payment has VATONPrincipal with a value</p>
                <p>other than zero , then that side require the VAT on principal Posting line.</p>
                <p>Field should be checked twice (Debit side and Credit Side)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If the variable is present only on the debit side then the match criteria for this field must be D or S</p>
                <p>If the variable is present only on the credit side then the match criteria for this field must be C or S</p>
                <p>If the variable is present on both the sides then the match criteria for this field must be B or S</p>
                <p>If the variable is not present both the sides then the match criteria for this field must be N or S</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AmountToken</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the payment related amount used in the posting line.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 20 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'AccountToken' in PPT.ACCOUNTTOKEN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BookingCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the overriding booking codes which will supersede the booking codes derived from product determination process in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Booking codes are usually based on the type of posting. ie. Principal posting, charges posting or VAT posting.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BookingDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date on which the booking was performed in the ledger.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 20 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'DateToken' in PPT.DATETOKEN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargePostingDetail</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether each charge has to be displayed in a separate line or the charges can be summed up and only the summary charge amount needs</p>
                <p>to be displayed.</p>
                <p>Possible values: </p>
                <p>D: The posting set will have a separate posting line for each debit party charges.</p>
                <p>C: The posting set will have a separate posting line for each credit party charges.</p>
                <p>B: The posting set will have a separate posting line for both debit party and credit party charges</p>
                <p>N: The posting set will only have one posting line for all the debit party charges and one posting line for all the credit party charges.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If a side(debit and credit) of the payment has "ChargePostingDetail" set or such a setup is not present but the side has more than one charge excluding the VAT charge, then it indicates that the charges have to be posted in detail for that side of the payment.</p>
                <p>Field should be checked twice (Debit side and Credit Side)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargePostingSeparately</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicate whether the charges have to be posted along with the principal amount or have to be posted separately from the principal amount.</p>
                <p>Possible values: </p>
                <p>D: The Posting Set contains separate posting lines only for the debit side charges.</p>
                <p>C: The Posting Set contains separate posting lines only for the credit side charges.</p>
                <p>B: The Posting Set contains separate posting lines for both debit and credit charges.</p>
                <p>N: The Posting Set will not have separate posting lines for debit and credit charges.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If a side(debit and credit) of the payment has "ChargePostingSeparately" set or such a setup is not present but the side has more than one charge excluding the VAT charge, then it indicates that the charges have to be posted separately from the principal for that side of the payment.</p>
                <p>Field should be checked twice (Debit side and Credit Side)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
