<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.PREFERREDCORRESPONDENT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table is used to setup preferred correspondents that a company uses to route a payment to specific country. More than one preferred correspondent for a country can be provided on the basis of the currency of the transaction and routing group.</p>
            <p>Preferred correspondents are also known as country correspondent.</p>
            <p>For any payment, if PREF set-up does not provide a preferred correspondent, then Routing &amp; Settlement is not possible with PREF option and the payments hub marks "Alternative for R &amp; S not possible"</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.PREFERREDCORRESPONDENT</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>PrefCorrespondentIDType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if the preferred correspondent is identified using a National Clearing Code or BIC.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>B - BIC</p>
                <p>N - NCC</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PreferredCorrespondentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies either BIC or NCC of the preferred correspondant.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RoutingProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the routing product based on which a contract can be selected.</p>
                <p>Validation rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field.  </p>
                <p>Defaulted to '*', if no value is defined.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDatePreferredCorr</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines the currency of the transaction.</p>
                <p>Validation rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. The value links to field 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY. </p>
                <p>Defaulted to '*', if no value is defined.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DestinationCountryCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the country Code for the Destination country.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 2 alphanumeric characters. The value links to COUNTRY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDatePreferredCorr</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PrefCorrespondentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies either BIC or NCC of the preferred correspondant.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
