<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.RECEIVED.FILE.DETAILS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to set the status of a received message manually. A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.RECEIVEDFILEDETAILS</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>FileType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Identifies the type of file received from the clearing system.</p>
                <p>Example: GB/LB/M3/M6/M7/M8/M9</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>50 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FileTypeIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Distinguishes between payment files and message files.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>"P" - Payment File,</p>
                <p>"M" - Message File</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MessageFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the format of the message received from a channel.</p>
                <p>Example: </p>
                <p>For channel, SWIFT</p>
                <p>101</p>
                <p>103</p>
                <p/>
                <p>For channel, PMTROUTER</p>
                <p>SAL</p>
                <p>NOR</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>20 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NumberOfRecords</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the number of children or individual transactions present in a batch or a clearing file respectively.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>10 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OriginatingChannel</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the channel through which the payment hub receives a message. </p>
                <p>Example:</p>
                <p>SWIFT – Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Transactions.This channel is used for international payments worldwide.</p>
                <p>PMTROUTER – Payment Router. This channel is used only by our Bank. </p>
                <p>EMZ – Elektronischer Massenzahlungsverkehr</p>
                <p>BACS – Bankers' Automated Clearing Services</p>
                <p>CEC  – Centre for Exchange and Clearing</p>
                <p>HKICL – Hong Kong Interbank Clearing Limited</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>10 alphabetic characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘ChannelName’ in PPT.CHANNEL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OriginatingReference</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the common reference shared by all transactions of a bulk message as parsed from the actual message received.This field can hold upto 128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>Example:</p>
                <p>Global Batch Identifier value such as 89139020225698</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>QueueName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the name of the queue in which a message is received.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>SWIFT</p>
                <p>PR-CREDIT</p>
                <p>PR-URGCREDIT</p>
                <p>PR-BATCH</p>
                <p>EMZ</p>
                <p>BACS</p>
                <p>CEC</p>
                <p>HKICL</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>16 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACKNACKGeneratedIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the status of ACK/NACK message generated for the payment.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>"G" Generated</p>
                <p>"S"  Sent</p>
                <p>"N" Not sent</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ReceivedDateTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the timestamp at which a message is received from any of the channels in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>17 characters of type TIME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SingleMultipleIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the type of a message.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>"S" – Single</p>
                <p>"C" – Clearing</p>
                <p>"B" – Bulk</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SourceCompany</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the company ID as specified in the message. This value may or may not be present in the message.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>9 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StatusCodeReceivedFile</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the current status of the payment file.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>RECEIVED - Message is received.</p>
                <p>ACCEPTED - Message has been validated and accepted.</p>
                <p>REJECTED - Message has been validated and rejected.</p>
                <p>REPAIR - Message has been validated and put to repair for manual intervention.</p>
                <p>RESUBMIT - Message is repaired and submitted again for validation.</p>
                <p>MAPPED - Message is mapped successfully and necessary payment order is created.</p>
                <p>CANCELLED - Message is cancelled by either the payments hub or by an operator.</p>
                <p>MAPPINGERROR - A bulk message has encountered a mapping issue and a payment order could not be created. This status is set only when a parent payment of a batch message has encountered an issue at mapping stage.</p>
                <p>MAPPEDWITHERROR - A bulk message has encountered a mapping issue and a payment order could not be created. This status is set only when a child payment of a batch message or any payment of a clearing message has encountered an issue at mapping stage.</p>
                <p>MAPPINGERRORFIXED - Mapping issue has been rectified and the message has been mapped manually by the operator.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ACKNACKMessage</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the actual ACK/NACK generated for the payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>256 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>This field will hold a value only when ACKNACKGeneratedIndicator is "G" or "S"</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ErrorCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains a value only when a payment file has been rejected based on certain validation.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is an error code as defined for the error scenerio in PPT.ERRORCODE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ErrorInformation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains a value only when a payment file has been rejected based on certain validation.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>256 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FileName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds a value only when a file is received from Clearing. This field has the name of the file as received from the clearing system.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>50 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FileReference</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the unique ID generated by the payments hub upon receiving a message from an external system.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 50 alphanumeric characters generated by the system</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
