<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.RMA</title>
        <table>PP.RMA</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to store the list of correspondent banks to which the bank is authorized to send a SWIFT message.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.RMA </p>
            <p>The permissions on the RMA table are specific to the SWIFT NET service and message type. The SWIFT service at present can only be SWIFT NET FIN service.</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OverrideThroughUpload</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the record can be updated using an automated upload process in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y – The entry is manually updated and can be overridden by the upload process.</p>
                <p>N – The entry is manual updated and the upload process should not override it.</p>
                <p>Any manually updated record in the RMA table is marked as manually updated. Subsequently, the upload process should not go on to rewrite these records with the contents of the upload file. A manually updated record has greater significance and therefore should not be replaced by the upload process.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>A maximum of 1 characters may be entered based on possible values. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RMAID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify RMA in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateRMA</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SwiftService</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates type of SWIFT NET service for which the RMA applies.</p>
                <p>At present it can be only SWIFT NET FIN service.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>15 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the BIC code of the correspondent bank.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 35 alphanumeric characters.Value links to field 'BICCode' in PPT.BICTABLE</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field "CompanyID" in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateRMA</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MessageTypeExclude</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates message types for which the RMA is applicable.</p>
                <p>It can hold wildcards.</p>
                <p>Example:</p>
                <p>To define an entry that includes authorization for all the Cat - 2 messages with the exception of MT204 and MT207, the 'Include message Type'</p>
                <p>would be stored with 2* and the 'Exclude Message Type' would be stored with 204, 207.</p>
                <p>Together with Message Type Exclude, it will give the messages for which the RMA is applicable.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>100 alphabetic characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MessageTypeInclude</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates message types for which the RMA is not applicable.</p>
                <p>It can hold wildcards. To define an entry that excludes authorization for</p>
                <p>all the Cat - 1 messages with the exception of MT110, the 'Include message Type' would be stored with 110 and the 'Exclude Message Type' would be stored with 1*.</p>
                <p>Together with Message Type Include, it will give the messages for which the RMA is applicable.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>100 alphabetic characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
