<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.RISK.FILTER.CONDITIONS</title>
        <table>PP.RISK.FILTER.CONDITIONS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
          <p> This screen is used define the Risk filtering conditions for correspondent banks, country and currency wise.  </p>
          <p> The condition are based on the incoming message type, transaction currency and type of transaction - Credit Transfer or Bank Transfer </p>
	  <p> The conditions can be defined Credit or Debit or both sides of the transaction </p>
	  <p> The limits or conditions can be either Amount or Number of transactions </p>
          <p> Allowed exposure by counterparty, country and currency can be deinfed by daily, weekly and monthly</p>
          <p> Maximum transaction amount for a payment can also be defined here</p>
 	      <p> Any payments that cross the limits will be moved to Risk Filter Queue with a status 624. </p>
          <p> This screen store the details to PPT.RISKFILTERCONDITION table </p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the unique ID generated by the Payments Hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IncomingMessageType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Message Type for which the condition is applied. </p>
                <p>Default Value : '*' </p>
                <p>Validation Rules : </p>
                <p>1. Valid record PPT.MSGPAYMENTTYPE table or the defaule value "*"</p>
                <p>2. 1-8 AlphaNumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LimitCurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Currency Code in which amount based limits are defined.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules :</p>
                <p>1. Valid record in the table PPT.CURRENCY.</p>
                <p>2. 3 Characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MonthlyAmountLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the cumulative monthly amount limit.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NumberOfPaymentsPerDay</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Maximum number of payments allowed for a day.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NumberOfPaymentsPerMonth</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Maximum number of payments allowed for a month.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NumberOfPaymentsPerWeek</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Maximum number of payments allowed for a week.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table.This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H-YYYYMMDDHHMMSSsss - History. Where: YYYY - year, MM - month, DD - day, HH - hour, MM - minutes, SS - seconds and sss - miliseconds</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R - Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Reset.Accumulator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether the Accumulator needs to be reset  or Not.Used for the Technical purpose</p>
                <p>Possible Values :</p>
                <p>Y - YES.</p>
                <p>N - NO.</p>
                
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1 Character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RiskFilterConditionID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the unique ID generated by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
               <p>MF - Modified future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>

            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateRiskFilterConditions</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
                
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Should not be lesser than the Current Business date in the PPT.COMPANY table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionAmountLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Spcifies the transaction amount limit per transaction.</p>
                
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WeeklyAmountLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the cumulative weekly amount limit.</p>
                
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Bank Identification Code.It can be defined at different levels (BIC 11 , 8 , 6, 4 , 2 )</p>
                <p>Country wise limit are set by defining 2 characters company code in this field </p>
                <p>Default Value : '*'</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CTRBTRIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies whether the condition is applicable for Customer Transfer or Bank Taransfer or for Both.</p>
                
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>C - Customer</p>
                <p>B - Bank</p>
                
                <p>Default Value : '*'</p>
                
                <p>Validation Rules : </p>
                <p>1. 1 Character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the Transaction Currency Code for which the condition is applicable.</p>
                
                <p>Default Value : '*'</p>
                
                <p>Validation Rules :</p>
                <p>1. Valid record from PPT.CURRENCY Table.</p>
                <p>2. 3 Characters.</p>
                <p>2. Mandatory when the TransactionAmount is not NULL.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table.This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DailyAmountLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the daily amount limit if there is any.</p>
                
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DebitCreditIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the Debit or Credit indicator. </p>
                
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>D - Debit</p>
                <p>C - Credit</p>
                <p>B - Both</p>
                
                <p>Default Value : '*'</p>
                
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1 Character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateRiskFilterConditions</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
                
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
