<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
		<title>PP.SCREENING.REQUESTS</title>
        <table>PP.SCREENING.REQUESTS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to manually accept a payment or sent it to Repair in cases when the screening application is not responding.</p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store tables, POR.SCREENINGREQUESTS, POR.TRANSACTION and POR.PAYMENTSTATUSCODE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created.</p>
                <p>Example: BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> Mandatory field; 3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p> The value links to the field 'CompanyID' in PPT.COMPANY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FTNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the unique ID generated by the payments hub upon generating a payment order.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> Mandatory field; 16 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PaymentStatus</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the status of a payment that was sent to screening interface. The only valid value that user can choose for this field is APPROVED.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> Mandatory field. 10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p> When the payment status is set to APPROVED then the field UserAcceptanceReason must also be filled.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>  1) NEW - The payment was sent to the screening interface;</p>
                <p>  2) POSSIBLE - The payment is a possible hit, TPS needs to wait for a second reply of the screening interface;</p>
                <p>  3) APPROVED - The payment is a accepted, no hit was found;</p>
                <p>  4) REJECTED - The payment is a true hit.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SendDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the business date when the payment was send to Screening interface.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 11 characters Date format should be filled in.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SendTimestamp</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the system date and time when the payment was sent to Screening interface.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 17 characters Date Time format.</p>
                <p> It need to be displayed as DD MMM YYYY HH:MM:SS.sss.</p>
                <p> Example:</p>
                <p>  12 JAN 2015 12:34:25.123</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PossibleStatusReceivedTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the system date and time when the Screening interface replied that a possible hit was found.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>17 characters Date Time format.</p>
                <p> It need to be displayed as DD MMM YYYY HH:MM:SS.sss.</p>
                <p> Example:</p>
                <p>  12 JAN 2015 12:34:25.123</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ResponseReceivedTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the system date and time when the Screening interface replied with a final answer.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>17 characters Date Time format.</p>
                <p>It need to be displayed as DD MMM YYYY HH:MM:SS.sss.</p>
                <p>Example:</p>
                <p>12 JAN 2015 12:34:25.123</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UserAcceptanceFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if the payment was approved or not by a user without waiting the screening interface response.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p> It needs to be set on Y (Yes) when the payment status is set as approved.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p> Y(Yes) or N(No)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UserAcceptanceDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the business date when the user accepted a payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 11 characters Date format should be filled in.</p>
                <p> Default value defined as Current Business Date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UserAcceptanceReason</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the reasons why the user has accepted a payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 1- 256 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p> This field must be set when the payment status was set to APPROVED.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UserRejectionFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if the payment was rejected or not (meaning that was send to repair) by a user without waiting the screening interface response.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p> It needs to be set on Y (Yes) when the payment status is set as rejected.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p> Y(Yes) or N(No)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>UserRejectionDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the business date when the user rejected (sent to repair) a payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 11 characters Date format should be filled in.</p>
                <p> Default value defined as Current Business Date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ScreenedDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the business date when the payment was processed in TPS based on the answer received from Screening.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 11 characters Date format should be filled in.</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LateResponseFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if the answer from Screening interface came after a manually intervention on the payment. It will allow the SOD process to delete this record.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p> EOD will set it on Y (Yes) when the LateResponse field is filled.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p> Y(Yes) or N(No)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApproverUserID1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the name of the First Authoriser for accepting the payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApprovedDateTime1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the system date and time when the payment received the first authorization for acceptance.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 17 characters Date Time format.</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApproverUserID2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the name of the Second Authoriser for accepting the payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApprovedDateTime2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the system date and time when the payment received the second authorization for acceptance.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 17 characters Date Time format.Time</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p> AC - Accept Payment</p>
                <p> M - Modified</p>
                <p> RP - Repair Payment</p>
                <p> This field can hold upto 2 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EntryTimeStamp</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the system date and time when the payment was manually sent to acceptance.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EntryUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the user that initiated the acceptance of the payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
