<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PP.STANDINGSETTMNTINSTRUC</title>
        <table>PP.STANDINGSETTMNTINSTRUC</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>Stores the publicly known Standing Settlement Instructions for correspondent banks. They are also known as currency correspondents.</p>
            <p>This is defined for a look-up on BIC’s and not on NCC’s. If the look-up is on a NCC then it is first converted into a BIC and then searched for in this table</p>
          
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purposes.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table PPL.STANDINGSETTMNTINSTRUC. This field can hold upto 15 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>No Input field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OverrideThroughUpload</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If this field is ‘N’ then it implies that the data entry will never be updated by</p>
                <p>the upload process. If set to ‘Y’ then the data can be overridden by the upload</p>
                <p>process.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PartyBIC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>BIC of the party for which SSI is defined</p>
                <p>It should be a BIC-8 or a BIC-11</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H-YYYYMMDDHHMMSSsss - History. Where: YYYY - year, MM - month, DD - day, HH - hour, MM - minutes, SS - seconds and sss - miliseconds</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RoutingProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Routing product can be used to set more than one currency correspondent for a</p>
                <p>bank.</p>
                <p>Note - The routing product for any payment is set by the Product determination</p>
                <p>process</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
               <p>MF - Modified future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SSIID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System generated unique ID</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateSSI</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered active by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Currency for which the correspondent is defined</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Institution trading name.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>City</field>
            <desc>
                <p>City name of the institution/branch.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCorrespondentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Will hold BIC’s or NCC’s; the length is extended to 20 to accommodate a LEI</p>
                <p>code.</p>
                <p>The Currency correspondent ID for the given combination of Party BIC, Currency</p>
                <p>and Routing Group.</p>
                <p>The Currency correspondent ID can be a BIC in which case it can be specified as</p>
                <p>a BIC-8 or a BIC-11 only. A Currency correspondent can therefore be defined for</p>
                <p>example as - BARCGB21 or BARCGB2106P.</p>
                <p>The Currency correspondent ID can be a National Clearing Code. A Currency</p>
                <p>correspondent can therefore be defined for example as - SC200050</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCorrespondentIDType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Currency Correspondent ID type of the currency correspondent.</p>
                <p>The Currency correspondent ID can be a BIC in which case it can be specified</p>
                <p>as a BIC-8 or a BIC-11 only. The Currency correspondent ID type for a BIC is B.</p>
                <p>The Currency correspondent ID can be a National Clearing Code. The Currency</p>
                <p>correspondent ID type for a national clearing is N</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table PPL.STANDINGSETTMNTINSTRUC. This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>No Input field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateSSI</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Standard T24 alphanumeric field.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>A maximum of 15 characters may be entered.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
