<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PP.WAREHOUSE.PAYMENTS</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen will be used to cancel, modify or force release payments present in Warehouse of the payments hub. </p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store tables, POR.TRANSACTION and POR.PAYMENTSTATUSCODE.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>FTNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the unique ID generated by the payments hub upon generating a payment order.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>16 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OldID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Holds the ID of the previous live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OVERRIDE</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contains all the override messages which the user agreed to during Input. During the validation of a transaction, the system may provide the user with a series of screen override messages to indicate an anomaly.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ProcessingDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which payment is to be released from the warehouse back to STP flow.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>11 alphanumeric characters of type 'D'</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StatusCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the status code of the payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Action</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose. Value of this field determines values of fields, 'RAC' and 'RSC'</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - New</p>
                <p>M - Modified </p>
                <p>R -  Reverse</p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 1 alphanumeric character and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApprovalTimeStamp</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the date and time when the record was authorised.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApproverUserID1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the name of the user who authorised the record.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApproverUserID2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the name of the user who authorised the record.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CancelDescription</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the reason for cancellation.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>45 alphanumeric characters. Mandatory while cancelling the payment. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company code of the company for which the record is created.</p>
                <p>Example : GB0010001,EU0010001</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>9 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field 'CompanyCode' in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrentID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Used for internal purpose.Holds the ID of the current live record of store table. </p>
                <p>This field can hold upto 65 alphanumeric characters and the value is not editable by the user.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EntryTimeStamp</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the date and time when the record was input or last modified.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EntryUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the name of the user who input or modified the record.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
