<?xml vevrsion="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.POSTINGLINE</title>
        <table>PPL.POSTINGLINE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table is used to define the posting line of Payment</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
		<t>
            <field>PostingLineId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each posting line created.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>PostingSetId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The retrieved Posting set Id has a list of posting lines associated with it. This is the Foreign KEY for this Table.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>		
        <t>
            <field>SequenceNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the order of the posting lines within the posting set.</p>
				<p>As a Posting Set can have multiple posting lines, Sequence Number is used to order the posting lines within the Posting Set. </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>7 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PartyFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the posting line is a debit or a credit posting line . Even for the posting line where charges are taken from a credit party , the party flag for the charge posting in PPL_Posting line will be "D" as the charges are getting debited for the party.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>D: Debit Party</p>
                <p>C: Credit Party</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AccountToken</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the payment related account used in the posting line.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>20 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'AccountToken' in PPT.ACCOUNTTOKEN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>		
        <t>
            <field>AmountToken</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the payment related amount used in the posting line.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>20 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'AccountToken' in PPT.ACCOUNTTOKEN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BookingCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the overriding booking codes which will supersede the booking codes derived from product determination process in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Booking codes are usually based on the type of posting. ie. Principal posting, charges posting or VAT posting.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BookingDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date on which the booking was performed in the ledger.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>20 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'DateToken' in PPT.DATETOKEN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		        <t>
            <field>ValueDateToken</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date on which the booking was performed in the ledger.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>20 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'DateToken' in PPT.DATETOKEN.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SuppressZeroFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if the posting line has to be displayed if the amount value</p>
                <p>of the amount token result in zero.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N: Display the posting line even when the value of amount token is zero.</p>
                <p>Y: Do not display the posting line when the value of amount token is zero</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StatementFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the generic statement format attached to the posting line.</p>
                <p>For the principal debit and credit accounts, if the client or bank have</p>
                <p>mentioned a special statement format name in client conditions or Bank</p>
                <p>conditions then statement lines attached to that statement format need to be displayed for the principal posting.</p>
                <p>If the debit side of the payment contains the field DebitStatementFormat or</p>
                <p>credit side contains the field CreditStatementFormat set then it indicates that the side would like to have customised statement lines.</p>
                <p>This field should be checked twice (Debit side and Credit Side)</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>30 alphanumeric character.Value links to field 'StatementFormatID' in PPT.STATEMENTFORMAT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>		
    </menu>
</t24help>
