<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.BANKCHARGESFEETYPE</title>
        <table>PPL.BANKCHARGESFEETYPE</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to maintain the Bank charges(Inbound Our and Outbound Our) in the payments hub.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>AlwaysApplyFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the charge is to be applied always or not.</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>"Y" - Yes</p>
                <p>"N" - No</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApplyMeOnlyFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if only the defined charge is to be applied. Payments hub will not consider other charges </p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankChargesFeeTypeID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the unique ID to identify the Bank charges fee type.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankChargesID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the unique bank charges ID can be linked with multiple records in this table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the feetype which is linked to the bank charge defined.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This would be the percentage indicated in</p>
                <p>nn.nnnn (upto 9 decimal places). If this is blank</p>
                <p>then default percentage as defined in FeeType</p>
                <p>table would be applied. If this is zero then no VAT</p>
                <p>on charge would be applied even if defined in</p>
                <p>FeeType table for the respective Fee Type.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PercentageVATOnCharge</field>
            <desc>
                <p>IndicatesThis would be the percentage indicated in</p>
                <p>nn.nnnn (upto 9 decimal places). If this is blank</p>
                <p>then default percentage as defined in FeeType</p>
                <p>table would be applied. If this is zero then no VAT</p>
                <p>on charge would be applied even if defined in</p>
                <p>FeeType table for the respective Fee Type.</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>'' (Blank)</p>
                <p>0  (Zero) </p>
                <p>Positive value</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the order (sequence) of the record in the application. Based on the value, a record is prioritised in such a way that, it is given higher preference for selection under peeling logic applied in the payments hub.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
