<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.NETTINGAGREEMENT</title>
        <table>PPL.NETTINGAGREEMENT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to store netting agreement in the payments hub which is a 3-party agreement between the sending bank, the processing bank and</p>
            <p>the customer. It states whether another bank is allowed to request a payment transfer, or send a payment instruction, specifying the debit account of the customer that is serviced by the processing bank. It is the</p>
            <p>responsibility of Debit Authority to validate whether the party requesting a payment transfer, or sending a payment instruction, has the authority to mention a specific third party as the debit party for the payment.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>All key attributes will have a value, PartyLine1 is the only attribute that can be used for peeling off.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.NETTINGAGREEMENT</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
		<t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>IncomingMessageType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies payment message type for which the Netting Agreement is required.</p>
                <p>Sample Values:</p>
                <p>101</p>
                <p>103</p>
                <p>202</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>SendingBank</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates which bank is sending the payment instruction.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules: </p>
                <p>35 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>Value links to field 'BICCode' from PPT.BICTABLE Table.</p>
                <p>This information is usually retrieved from the header of the swift message.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>DebitAccountLine</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the account line of the received payment instruction specifying the debit account.</p>
                <p>This information is retrieved from Tag 50 of swift message</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules: </p>
                <p>35 alphabetic characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DebitPartyLine1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the first Name and Address line present in the received payment instruction specifying the debit party.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules: </p>
                <p>35 alphabetic characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>StartDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered active by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>EndDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date on which the record is to be considered inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	</menu>
</t24help>
