<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.CHANNELFXSHIFT</title>
        <table>PPL.CHANNELFXSHIFT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen to used to define cutoff time for various channels used in the payments hub. Routing and Settlement process determines the channel to use for deliverying outgoing and redirect messages based on peeling logic.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ChannelCutoffID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the ISO currency code against which credit currency is matched.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CutoffTimeWithFX</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Similar to the cut-off time but this will be applicable only when currency conversion is required.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FXShift</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the FX Shift number of days to be bumped in order to determine the next processing date, when a payment can be routed through the channel defined.</p>
                <p>When payments hub receives a payment in foreign currency which requires currency conversion, treasury might require some time to buy or sell the foreign currency from the market. FXShift ensures that treasury gets some time for this. This is applied on a transaction only when debit and credit currencies are different.</p>
                <p>If CutOffShift and SettlementShift are also specified, the days will be bumped further.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
