<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.BANKCHARGESFORMULA</title>
        <table>PPL.BANKCHARGESFORMULA</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to maintain the Bank charges(Inbound Our and Outbound Our) in the payments hub.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>MinimumChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge amount has to be equal to or greater than this minimum amount.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PercentageVariableFee</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Hold the percentage value when the fee type is a variable fee type.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankChargesFeeFormulaId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the unique ID to identify the Bank charges fee formula.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankChargesFeeTypeID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the unique ID to identify the Bank charges fee type.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BaseChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the fixed positive amount which would be added to charge amount in case of percentage charge.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeDiscountAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Mentions the fixed positive amount which would be deducted from charge amount in case of percentage charge.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeRiseAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the fixed positive amount which could be added to the calculated Fee (fixed or variable) to arrive at the final fee.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeTierRangeLowerLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the lower tier amount and if the transaction amount is greater than this limit (in case of FX, converted amount) and is lesser than the next tier (if there is any), then this record will be selected.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FixedChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the fixed charge amount.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This would be the percentage indicated in</p>
                <p>nn.nnnn (upto 9 decimal places). If this is blank</p>
                <p>then default percentage as defined in FeeType</p>
                <p>table would be applied. If this is zero then no VAT</p>
                <p>on charge would be applied even if defined in</p>
                <p>FeeType table for the respective Fee Type.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MaximumChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Charge amount has to be equal to or lesser than this maximum charge amount.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
