<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.CONTRACTCATEGORY</title>
        <table>PPL.CONTRACTCATEGORY</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to store the contract information in the payments hub. </p>
            <p>Routing &amp; Settlement process can deals with two types of Contracts - Country Contract and Party Contract.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>The Party contract is checked for the credit party in the payment.</p>
            <p>In a Party Contract, the bank specifies on how the payment should</p>
            <p>be routed and settled with the credit party. </p>
            <p/>
            <p>The Country contract is checked for the destination country of the payment. In a Country Contract, the bank specifies</p>
            <p>on how it wants to route and settle payments to be sent to a specific country.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>Peeling Off order determines the order in which the entries within the table are prioritized.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionUpperLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the transaction upper limit is not specified then its value is set to</p>
                <p>99999999999999999 (17 times 9).</p>
                <p>This limit will be in the transaction currency of the record.</p>
                <p>If the transaction currency is specified as *, LCY or FCY then this limit will be in the home currency of the company.</p>
                <p>The amount of the transaction should always be lesser than this upper limit.</p>
                <p>The transaction amount considered for this limit does not include any charges.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeOption</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Type of Charge.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ContractCategoryID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This Contract Category ID will uniquely define the Contract Category entry.</p>
                <p>This ID will be used to further search in the R &amp; S options table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ContractID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Contract for which the Contract Categories are defined.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Currency used in the contract.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Priority</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The priority field is specified as a single digit with a value between 1 and 9.</p>
                <p>This is the SWIFT priority assigned to the payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Every Contract will have one or more entries for contract categories. The order in which these contract categories are evaluated is given by this ranking. </p>
                <p>Rank 1 is the highest priority R &amp; S option and 999 being the lowest.</p>
                <p>Duplicate ranks are not allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SLACode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When specified, the SLA can be used to define Bank specific routing</p>
                <p>mechanisms.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionLowerLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the transaction lower limit is not specified then its value is set to 0.</p>
                <p>This limit will be in the transaction currency of the record.</p>
                <p>If the transaction currency is specified as *, LCY or FCY then this limit will be in the home currency of the company.</p>
                <p>The amount of the transaction should always be equal to or greater than this lower limit.</p>
                <p>The transaction amount considered for this limit does not include any charges.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
