<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.CONTRACT</title>
        <table>PPL.CONTRACT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to store the contract information in the payments hub. </p>
            <p>Routing &amp; Settlement process can deals with two types of Contracts - Country Contract and Party Contract.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>The Party contract is checked for the credit party in the payment.</p>
            <p>In a Party Contract, the bank specifies on how the payment should</p>
            <p>be routed and settled with the credit party. </p>
            <p/>
            <p>The Country contract is checked for the destination country of the payment. In a Country Contract, the bank specifies</p>
            <p>on how it wants to route and settle payments to be sent to a specific country.</p>
            <p/>
            <p>Peeling Off order determines the order in which the entries within the table are prioritized.</p>
            <p/>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>EntryUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User ID of the record creator</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PartyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field gives the party for which the PTY Contract is defined.</p>
                <p>The PTY Contract party can be defined as a BIC in which case it can be specified as a BIC4, BIC6, BIC-8 or BIC-11. </p>
                <p>The Party ID type for a BIC is B. </p>
                <p>A Party ID Type and Party ID can therefore be defined for example as – B BARC, B BARCGB, B BARCGB21 or B BARCGB2106P. (An Contract with a BIC-11 has a higher priority compared to an Contract defined at BIC-8. Similarly in terms of pririty - BIC-8 Contract &gt; BIC-6 Contract &gt; BIC-4 Contract)</p>
                <p>The Party ID can also be defined as a National Clearing Code (NCC). The Party ID type for a national clearing is N. A Party ID Type and Party ID can therefore be defined for example as - N SC200050</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PartyIDType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is applicable only for the Party Contract.</p>
                <p>The Party ID type for a BIC is B.</p>
                <p>The Party ID type for a national clearing is N.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RACContract</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RoutingProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>When specified, the Routing Product can be used to define Product specific</p>
                <p>routing mechanisms.</p>
                <p>Routing Product is set as per the Product determination step of STP process flow.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSCContract</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateContract</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApprovedDateTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Date and Time when the record was approved in DD MON 2015 HH:MM:SS.MMM format</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApproverUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User ID of the record approver </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BusinessLine</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Every company has a number of business lines.</p>
                <p>Country and Party contracts can be made specific to a business line.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ContractID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The Contract for which the Contract Categories are defined.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ContractType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Contracts can be defined for a credit party of a payment or for the destination country of a payment.</p>
                <p>A Contract defined for the credit party is called as a PTY Contract and a Contract defined for the destination country is called as a CTY Contract.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Destination</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Destination Country Code to which the payment needs to be routed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateContract</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EntryDateTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Date and Time when the record was created in DD MON 2015 HH:MM:SS.MMM format</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
