<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.CLIENTCONDITIONRECORD</title>
        <table>PPL.CLIENTCONDITIONRECORD</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table is used to specify special condition or possible options for the clients and each condition is represented by a clientcondition id.  This table will be peeled off to determine the client condition id based on the characteristics of the payment. We can define the Client Conditions at various levels; at one end it could be very generic and can be defined at the product level so that all payments with that product will use those client conditions; on the other end these could be very specific to a particular client requirements and accordingly defined at the most specific level (Product/Source/Business Line/Client Id/ Account/Currency). This means that order in which Client Conditions are retrieved is very important. Peeling off mechanism is nothing but defining the order in which Client Conditions should be read. </p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>AuthoriserDateTime</field>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System generated id for the table PP_ClientConditionRecord.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClientConditionsID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System generated id for the table PPL.CLIENTCONDITIONRECORD. This is a system id and is autogenerated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>2. The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ClientConditionProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This would indicate the source group from where payment has been originated. Valid/Allowed values can only be a valid ClientConditionProduct for the company as per PPT.ClientConditionProduct table. If left blank then this should be wildcarded</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>SourceProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicate the source group from where payment has been originated. Valid/allowed values can only be a valid SourceProduct as per Product table. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. If left blank then this should be wild carded as *. </p>
                <p>2. DropDown from the Table PPT_SourceProductGroup</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>BusinessLine</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the business line to which the client belongs in the T24.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Up to 3 A(Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
                <p>2. If left blank then this should be wild carded as *. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ClientID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the Client ID for whom the condition is being set up for. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Input mandatory when AccountNumber exists</p>
                <p>2. If left blank then this will be wild carded. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>AccountCompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates company code of the Account defined.  This should be a valid id in the PPT.COMPANY table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. If left blank then this should be wild carded </p>
                <p>2. If entered should be same as CompanyID field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>AccountNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates account number to the Client Conditions.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Up to 35 A (Alphanumeric) characters.</p>
                <p>2. If left blank then this should be wild carded as *.</p>
                <p>2. Input mandatory when Account CompanyID exist.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>AccountCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Three character currency code of the Account Number.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. If left blank then this should be wild carded as *.</p>
                <p>2. Valid entry in PPT_Currency table</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>EndDateClientConditionRecord</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>LanguageID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If no language chosen, then the Default language of the Company the Client  belongs to will be chosen.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>DrStatementFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Should be valid from Table PPT_StatementFormat table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>30 ANY(AlphaNumeric or Special) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>CRStatementFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Should be valid from Table PPT_StatementFormat table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules</p>
                <p>30 ANY(AlphaNumeric or Special) characters</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>BillingIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Dropdown field having values Y (Yes) and N (No).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>Y= Yes, Billing is preferred </p>
                <p>N=  No,  Billing  is  not  preferred </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Default Value is N(No)</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ChargePostingSeparately</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether the charges for the payment are to be posted separately or not. PSD product will always have Y as an option</p>
                <p>Y - Charge separate </p>
                <p>N - Do not charge separate.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. If left blank then this will be defaulted to Y</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ChargePostingDetail</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates whether the charges are to be posted in detail and accordingly additional PostingLines for each change should be configured or not.This will take the following values Y=post in detail; N= post detail.  If left blank, it will be defaulted to Y. PSD product will always have Y as an option</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Not Allowed to input field when ChargePostingSeparately is set to No or Null</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>VatPrincipal</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This would be the percentage indicated in nn.nnnn (up to 4 decimal places).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Default value defined as zero.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>VATOnCharge</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Dropdown field having values Y (Yes) and N (No).  </p>
                <p>Y - Apply VAT on Charges</p>
                <p>N - Don't apply VAT on Charges</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>NonSTPIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>It is Dropdown field having values Y, N, C &amp; D</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Y - Non STP for all transactions;  </p>
                <p>N - STP for all transactions;  </p>
                <p>C - Non STP for all credit transactions</p>
                <p>D - Non STP for all debit transactions.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>FXNonSTPIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates Payment on behalf of customer is STP or NON STP.</p>
                <p>1 character (alphanumeric). </p>
                <p>Possible Values – C / D / Y / N</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>FXNonSTPAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>20 Digit numeric amount field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Field mandatory when FXNonSTPIndicator exist</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>DebitSpecialInstructions</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Possible to give special Debit instructions for the operator.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>128 Characters (Alpha Numeric and special characters)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>CreditSpecialInstructions</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is used to specify special Credit instructions</p>
                <p/>
                <p>128 Characters (Alpha Numeric and special characters)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>AccountSubstitution</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Possible values: Y (Yes) or N (No)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ReleaseTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the TIMESTAMP value.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>DebitFloat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Number of days the bank can take debit float on the payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>CreditFloat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field defines the number of business days to adjust the Credit Value Date (CVD) into the future, potentially adding float to the transaction. This is applicable to the credit client.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 Numeric characters, representing the number of days.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>CCValidityStartDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the date from which respective record will be active </p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 11 characters Date format should be entered.</p>
                <p>2. Default value defined as Current Business Date</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>CCValidityEndDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the date till which respective record will be active.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. End Date must be greater than Start Date</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user."</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>"Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user."</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ThresholdAmount</field>
  			<desc>
  				<p>This field is an output value of the client condition record.</p>
  				<p>The amount specified here is the amount in Home currency of the company. If the transaction amount is greater than this amount specified in this field, then the payment will be moved to manual repair queue with a due to  exceeding the transaction amount threshold specified></p>
			</desc>
        </t>
	</menu>
</t24help>
