<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.BANKCLAIMSCONTROL</title>
        <table>PPL.BANKCLAIMSCONTROL</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen stores the bank’s preferences for claims processing.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CorrespondentBIC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This is the sending bank’s BIC against which we will read the bank claims table.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This can be defined at different levels (BIC 11, 8, 6, 4, 2, *)</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the currency of the payment for which this bank claims control record is created. </p>
                <p/>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>Value links to field, 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY table</p>
                <p>* (Default Value)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateBankClaimsControl</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EntryDateTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Date and Time when the record was created in DD MON 2015 HH:MM:SS.MMM format</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EntryUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User ID of the record creator</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This System generated ID will uniquely define the BankClaimsControl entry</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IndividualGroupIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if we need to club all the claims or process them individually.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>I - Individual</p>
                <p>G - Group</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RACBankClaimsControl</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSCBankClaimsControl</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApprovedDateTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Date and Time when the record was approved in DD MON 2015 HH:MM:SS.MMM format</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateBankClaimsControl</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApproverUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>User ID of the record approver </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankClaimsControlID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This System generated ID will uniquely define the BankClaimsControl entry.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClaimBasis</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the Claims generation threshold.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>Count</p>
                <p>Periodic</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClaimBIC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the claim towards field is 'OTHERBIC' then this field will store the actual BIC value. Otherwise it is hardcoded as SENDER, indicating claim towards the sender BIC.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClaimPeriod</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If Claim Basis is set as PERIODIC then this field will hold the exact period.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>D - Daily</p>
                <p>W - Weekly</p>
                <p>M - Monthly</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClaimTowards</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Claim could be generated towards the sending bank or in certain cases sending bank might want us to send the claim to some other BIC. This information is stored in this field.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>SENDER</p>
                <p>OTHERBIC</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClaimTrigger</field>
            <desc>
                <p>In case claim basis is count then we will define trigger as the count of payments which once reached will trigger the claim generation. So it will be a number.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>In case claim basis is periodic then if claim period is</p>
                <p>Daily – Claim will be generated on each working day.In this case acceptable trigger will be 1.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Weekly – Trigger is day of the week, Monday(1), Tuesday(2)…Friday(5).</p>
                <p>In this case acceptable trigger will be 1,2,3,4 or 5.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Monthly – Trigger is the day of the month.In this case acceptable trigger could be any value from 1 to 31.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClaimType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the type of Claim to be raised.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>Debit</p>
                <p>MT191</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
