<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.BANKCONDCHARGEACCOUNT</title>
        <table>PPL.BANKCONDCHARGEACCOUNT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>Bank Conditions or Correspondent bank conditions, define the way in which a payment should be processed in the payment engine for a</p>
            <p>correspondent bank. Bank conditions of the correspondent bank involved in the payment will influence mainly Straight through processing of the</p>
            <p>payment in the payment engine. This will also allow customising banks’ charge account, statements and advices.</p>
            <p>The Bank conditions component allows the behaviour of the payment engine to configure at a flexible level where debit or credit party (or both parties) in the payment is a bank. Similar flexibility is provided by the client condition component where one side of the payment or both involves the customer and is used to control the customer processing conditions. Bank and Client conditions are handled by separate components due to the different criteria (input and output parameters) required for banks and customers.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
	    <t>
            <field>ID</field>
			<desc>
				<p>Combination of Primary key values.</p>
				<p>255 alphanumeric characters.</p>
			</desc>	
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>BankCondChargeID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Generated Key of Bank Conditions Charge Acoount.</p>  
				<p>35 alphanumeric characters;  Mandatory field</p>				
            </desc>
        </t>
	    <t>
            <field>BankConditionsID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System Generated Key of Bank Conditions. </p>
                <p>One Bank conditions id can be linked with multiple records of tables PPL_BankCondChargeAccount and PPL_BankConditionsAdvice.</p>					
				<p>35 alphanumeric characters;</p>	            
			</desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Three character currency code of the Credit Account.This field is related to PPL_BankCondChargeAccount table.</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters;</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>If CurrencyCode is defined then this transaction currency must match with that value.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>		
        <t>
            <field>ChargeAccountCompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates Charge Account company code. Valid/allowed values for this would come from the company static table PPT.COMPANY. This field is related to PPL_BankCondChargeAccount table.</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters;</p>	
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory to field if Charge Account Indicator is 'Y'</p>
                <p>2. Input not allowed if Charge Account Indicator is not 'Y'</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ChargeAccountNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates charge account number to the Bank Conditions.This field is related to PPL_BankCondChargeAccount table.</p>
				<p>35 alphanumeric characters;</p>	
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory field if Charge Account Indicator is 'Y'</p>
                <p>2. Input not allowed if Charge Account Indicator is not 'Y'</p>
            </desc>
        </t>		
        <t>
            <field>ChargeAccountCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Three character currency code of the Charge Account. This field is related to PPL_BankCondChargeAccount table.</p>
				<p>3 alphanumeric characters;</p>	
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. Mandatory to input if Charge Account Indicator is 'Y'</p>
                <p>2. Input not allowed if Charge Account Indicator is not 'Y'</p>
            </desc>
        </t>		
    </menu>
</t24help>
