<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.CLIENTCHARGESFORMULA</title>
        <table>PPL.CLIENTCHARGESFORMULA</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table enables definition of charges for clients (non banks)</p>
            <p>Charges can be defined for both debit and credit parties based on the direction of the message.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>MinimumChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the minimum charge amount for the specific fee type. If the charge amount is calculated as a percentage</p>
                <p>of the transaction amount and if it falls below the amount specified here, the fee amount applied would be the amount</p>
                <p>specified in this field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PercentageVariableFee</field>
            <desc>
                <p>In case of variable fee this will be defined as the percentage (up to 9 decimal places)</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BaseChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Fixed positive amount which would be added to charge amount in case of percentage charge.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeDiscountAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Fixed positive amount which would be deducted from charge amount in case of percentage charge</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeRiseAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Fixed positive amount which could be added to the calculated Fee (fixed or variable) to arrive at the final fee.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClientChargesFeeFormulaId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID to identify the Client Charges Fee Formula</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClientChargesFeeTypeId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID to identify the Client Charges Fee Type</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FeeTierRangeLowerLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>There could be different charges based on the transaction amount. We can define various amount tiers and different charge amount for each tier</p>
                <p>This field holds the transaction amount tier.</p>
                <p>For the following configuration of 0, 500 and 1500</p>
                <p>0 - Covers form 0 until 499</p>
                <p>500 - Covers form 500 until 999</p>
                <p>1000 - Covers form 1000 and above</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Based on the transaction amount, the appropriate tier will be chosen.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FixedChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the fixed positive amount in the Fee type currency. Fee amount could be entered up to two decimal places</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System generated id for the table PPL.CLIENTCHARGESFORMULA</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MaximumChargeAmount</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the maximum charge amount for the specific fee type. If the charge amount is calculated as a percentage</p>
                <p>of the transaction amount and if it exceeds the amount specified here, the fee amount is capped to the amount</p>
                <p>specified in this field</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
