<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPL.CLIENTCHARGEACCOUNT</title>
        <table>PPL.CLIENTCHARGEACCOUNT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table is used to specify special condition or possible options for the clients and each condition is represented by a clientcondition id.  This table will be peeled off to determine the client condition id based on the characteristics of the payment. We can define the Client Conditions at various levels; at one end it could be very generic and can be defined at the product level so that all payments with that product will use those client conditions; on the other end these could be very specific to a particular client requirements and accordingly defined at the most specific level (Product/Source/Business Line/Client Id/ Account/Currency). This means that order in which Client Conditions are retrieved is very important. Peeling off mechanism is nothing but defining the order in which Client Conditions should be read. </p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeAccountCompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID of the ChargeAccountNumber defined.  This should be a valid record in the PPT.COMPANY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeAccountCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates the currency of the ChargeAccountNumber defined. This should be a valid currency code.  If left blank, this will be wildcarded</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ChargeAccountNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the account number from which the charges has to be collected.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClientChargeAccountID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System generated id for the corresponding child table PPL_CLIENTCHARGEACCOUNT. This is a system id and is autogenerated</p>
                <p/>
                <p>A new Client Conditions Charge Account record will be created only if Separate chargeAccount Indicator is set to Yes</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClientConditionsID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System generated id for the table PPL.CLIENTCHARGEACCOUNT. This is a system id and is autogenerated</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DebitCreditIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the transaction is Debit or Credit or Both</p>
                <p>Possible Values are </p>
                <p>C - Credit Transactions</p>
                <p>D - Debit Transactions</p>
                <p>A - All Transactions</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>System generated id for the table PPL.CLIENTCHARGEACCOUNT</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TransactionCurrency</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Three character currency code of the Account Number.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
