<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
		<title>PPT.STATUSACTION</title>
        <table>PPT.STATUSACTION</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The purpose of this table is to store the action (program) to be executed, per company and originating source, for different status codes of the payment.</p>
            <p>The configurations will be done through the PP.STATUS.ACTION screen and saved into PPT.STATUSACTION table.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
	    <t>
            <field>ID</field>
			<desc>
				<p>Combination of Primary key values.</p>
				<p>255 alphanumeric characters.</p>
			</desc>
        </t>
	    <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates  the company ID for which the record is created.</p>
                <p>Example: BNK,GB1.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters (Mandatory Input)</p>
                <p>The value links to the field CompanyID of PPT.COMPANY table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	    <t>
            <field>StatusCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the status for which notification must be sent to the monitoring system as defined in PPT.STATUSCODE.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1-3 Numeric (Mandatory Input)</p>
                <p>The value links to the field StatusCode of PPT.STATUSCODE table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ProgramName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Defines a program name to link a certain program to a specific status.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1-255 characters (Mandatory Input)</p>
                <p>The value links to  the field ProgramName of PPT.PROGRAMCHARACTERISTIC table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>StatusActionDescription</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies status description to be sent to the monitoring system in case of non succesful event.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>70 characters Mandatory input field if StatusRouterExpectedErrorCode is filled.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>StatusRouterExpectedErrorCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the error code expected by the monitoring system in case of non-successful event.</p>
                <p>10 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StatusRouterExpectedStatus</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the status code expected by the monitoring system. Expected Status is Integer, possible values are any negative integer and 1.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>0 and values greater than 1 and special characters are not allowed to input.</p>
                <p>3 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>StartDateStatusAction</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date from which the record is active. Defaulted to select company’s current business date when Validate or Submit button is clicked and the user has not inputted a value.</p>
                <p>11 characters Date (Mandatory Input).</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>The start date must be greater or equal with the current business date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>EndDateStatusAction</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date till which the record is active.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>11 characters Date</p>
                <p>End Date must be greater than or Equal to Start Date.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RACStatusAction</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub.</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A -  Active</p>
                <p>H-YYYYMMDDHHMMSSsss - History. Where: YYYY - year, MM - month, DD - day, HH - hour, MM - minutes, SS - seconds and sss - miliseconds.</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
            </desc>
        </t>			
        <t>
            <field>RSCStatusAction</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>MF - Modified future</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	    <t>
            <field>EntryUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the user that created or modified the entry.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>EntryDateTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the system date and time when the entry was created or modified.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 17 characters Date Time format.</p>
                <p> It need to be displayed as DD MMM YYYY HH:MM:SS.sss.</p>
                <p> Example: 12 JAN 2015 12:34:25.123</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ApproverUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the name of the user who approved the entry.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApprovedDateTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the system date and time when the entry was approved.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p> 17 characters Date Time format.</p>
                <p> It need to be displayed as DD MMM YYYY HH:MM:SS.sss.</p>
                <p> Example: 12 JAN 2015 12:34:25.123</p>
                <p> The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>OriginatingSource</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the source through which the payment hub receives a message.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p> 
                <p>10 alphabetic characters.The value links to the field 'OriginatingSource' of PPT.SOURCE table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
