<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPT.RISKFILTEROUTPUT</title>
        <table>PPT.RISKFILTEROUTPUT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p> The table is used to handle the payments that are moved to Risk filter queue with status 625 and to do breaching the risk filter conditions.</p>
            <p> Payment form Risk Filter queue can be approved and allow to proceed further or Reject and moved to Repair status </p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        
        <t>
            <field>DailyAmountLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the daily amount limit defined in the respective risk filter condition while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DailyLimitBreach</field>
            <desc>
             
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the amount by which the DailyAmountLimit is breached while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
       
        
        <t>
            <field>FilterID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies unique ID of the Risk filter condition for which with the payment breached the condition .</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FTNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the unique ID of the breached payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>16 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
       
        <t>
            <field>MonthlyAmountLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the cumulative monthly amount limitdefined in the respective risk filter condition while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MonthlyLimitBreach</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the amount by which the MonthlyAmountLimit is breached while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        
        <t>
            <field>PaymentsPerDay</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the Maximum number of payments allowed for a day defined in the respective risk filter condition while moving the payment to Risk filter queue..</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PaymentsPerMonth</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the Maximum number of payments allowed for a month defined in the respective risk filter condition while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID of the limit breached payment. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PaymentsPerWeek</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the Maximum number of payments allowed for a week defined in the respective risk filter condition while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PPDLimitBreach</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the number by which the PaymentsPerDay is breached while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PPMLimitBreach</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the number by which the PaymentsPerMonth  is breached while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>PPWLimitBreach</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the number by which the PaymentsPerWeek is breached while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-6 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
       
        <t>
            <field>TransactionAmountLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the transaction amount limit per transaction defined in the respective risk filter condition while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        
        <t>
            <field>TRNLimitBreach</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the amount by which the TransactionAmount is breached while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 Numeric characters.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WeeklyAmountLimit</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the cumulative weekly amount limit defined in the respective risk filter condition while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 Numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WeeklyLimitBreach</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field is a no input filed. System will populate the amount by which the WeeklyAmountLimit is breached while moving the payment to Risk filter queue.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1. 1-15 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
       
    </menu>
</t24help>
