<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PPT.PROGRAMSPERWEIGHT</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table is used to specify physical programs to be invoked by each component in the payments flow according to weight and specific weight of the payments. This is also used to define whether or not a component is to be skipped.</p>            
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>ProgramSkipIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if the program invocation can be skipped or not for the setup defined.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes. Do not execute this step and return control to the workflow</p>
                <p>N - No. Execute the program as stored in the attribute ProgramName of the table.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ProgramsPerWeightDescription</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Describes the program defined as per weight and specific weight of the payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RACProgramsPerWeight</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the order (sequence) of the record in the application. Based on the value, a record is prioritised in such a way that, it is given higher preference for selection under peeling logic applied in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 9 numeric characters of type R.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSCProgramsPerWeight</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SpecificWeightCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the specific weight code.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatoru field. Value links to field 'SpecificWeightCode' in PPL.SPECIFICWEIGHT.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateProgramsPerWeight</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>WeightCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the weight code.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>H - High</p>
                <p>M - Medium</p>
                <p>L - Light</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        
        <t>
            <field>CallingComponent</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the Component (or step in the workflow) that can have a deviant (replacement) program in this table.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 1 alphanumeric character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field 'CompanyID' in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
			
        <t>
            <field>EndDateProgramsPerWeight</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ProgramName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the name of the physical program or executable to be invoked for the setup defined.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>255 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
