<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PPT.COMPANYPROPERTIES</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This table is used to setup properties related to a company in the payments hub.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
        <t>
            <field>BICuploadCutOverDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the date on which the cut-over file which should be uploaded or be reported on.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>11 characters of type DATE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICuploadDeltaFull</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates how the received BIC file from SWIFT is to be processed by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>D - Delta. Delta file from SWIFT will be used for BIC upload. </p>
                <p>F - Full. Full file from SWIFT will be used for BIC upload.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICuploadJobOffsetDays</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the offset days to be considered while deriving the exact date on which BIC upload job needs to be executed. </p>
                <p>If the system date is equal or greater than the ‘BICuploadCutOverDate minus the BICuploadJobOffsetDays’, the job needs to be executed.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>2 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICUploadLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the directory location where files from SWIFT will be placed in order to start executing the BIC upload job in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICuploadReport</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the type of action and report to be performed and generated respectively in BIC upload process.</p>
                <p>Possible values: </p>
                <p>U - Upload and Report. BIC upload job is run and report is generated based on upload file.</p>
                <p>R - Report only. BIC upload job is not run but only a report is generated based on the upload file.</p>
                <p>S - Static Data Report only. BIC upload job is not run but a report is generated based on the static tables.</p>
                <p>B - Both Reports. BIC upload job is not run but both reports ie. a report based on the upload file and a report based on the static table is generated.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICUploadReportLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the location where the reports related to BIC upload jobs should be placed by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICuploadSchedule</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the schedule for the BIC upload job in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values: </p>
                <p>M - Monthly. BIC upload job is run on monthly basis.</p>
                <p>D - Daily. BIC upload job is run on daily basis.</p>
                <p/>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BillingArchiveLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the directory path where the export files of billing interface are archived.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BillingDeliveryLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the directory path where the export files of billing interface are delivered.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BillingDeltaFull</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies how billing process will extract records from static data tables in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>D - Delta. Billing program will extract only the changes done in static data tables since the last date on which Billing program was run. This program will read field “BillingPreviousProcessingDate”.</p>
                <p>F- Full. Billing program will extract all records from static data tables.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BillingPreviousProcessingDate</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the last date on which payment/static data files were sent to the billing application. This date is particularly used for extracting delta information from the static data tables.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>No input. 11 characters of type DATE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClaimBeneficiaryBIC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates a 11-BIC where the company wishes to receive the funds when sending out a claim.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Value links to field 'BICCode' in PPT.BICTABLE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ClaimsWaitIntervalSeconds</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Represents the time to wait for the channels that will send messages to</p>
                <p>be processed.</p>
                <p>Example:</p>
                <p>Claims, after starting COB</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>4 numeric characters. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>COBRunTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the time at which COB needs to start processing.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>5 characters of type TIME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyBIC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the BIC of the company.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. Value links to field 'BICCode' in PPT.BICTABLE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CompanyRegion</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Mentions the region to which the company belongs.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Value links to field 'Region' in PPT.REGION</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>CreditStatementFormatName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Default statement format name for credit account if one is not defined in posting tables.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DaysActivePayment</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the number of days a payment can remain in the system before archival process considers it for archival.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 3 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMLArchiveLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the path where the export files related to AML will be archived.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DaysDuplicateCheck</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the number of days the duplicate check process has to cover based on the current business date.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DebitStatementFormatName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Default statement format namefor debit account if one is not defined in posting tables.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DefaultClientID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the client ID to be used for booking entries in the ledger when not supplied by Account and Customer Database during account validation </p>
                <p>Example: Profit and Loss accounts</p>
                <p>Used By :Fees &amp; Posting Scheme</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DefaultCompanyIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if the company is the default company to be considered if there are more than one setup with the same BICCode.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>There can be only 1 default company per BICCode.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DefaultLanguageID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the default language ID to be used in statement lines for the processing company ID.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 2 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'LanguageID' in PPT.LANGUAGE</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>DefaultRepairFee</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the repair fee to be defaulted in all the payments which are put to repair in the payments hub. The operator has the ability to either override( also waiver) this value or retain it to charge repair fee for the payment from the customer.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
                <p>Blank</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>EndDateCompanyProperties</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>FXTolerancePercentage</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the percentage of tolerance when FX conversion is in affect. When the converted transaction amount is beyond the tolerance limit, an error is raised by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 11 characters of type PRICE.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>HomeCountryCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the country code in ISO format.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>2 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'COUNTRY.CODE' in COUNTRY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>HomeCurrencyCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the currency code in ISO format.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 2 alphanumeric characters. Value links to field 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AMLDeliveryLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the path where the export files related to AML will be written.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IbanPlusDeltaFileNameFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the generic format of the delta file to be looked at the location as specified in BICUploadLocation in order to select files for BIC upload process when ever BICUploadDeltaFull is set to 'D'</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IbanPlusFullFileNameFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the generic format of the full file to be looked at the location as specified in BICUploadLocation in order to select files for BIC upload process when ever BICUploadDeltaFull is set to 'F'</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>InsightArchiveLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the path where the export files related to Insight will be archived.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>InsightDeliveryLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the path where the export files related to Insight will be delivered.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>IntrabranchPostingEnabled</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Enables Intra-branch posting entries to be posted.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MapIBANIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>For an Outgoing payment, if this field is set to 'Y' then it implies that the field that provides the debit account in a SWIFT message (Field 50) is replaced with an IBAN. The IBAN provided in the SWIFT message is as per the IBAN stored for the ledger.</p>
                <p>Possible values: </p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>MaximumClaimDays</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Maximum Number of days till which a claim processed by count basis can</p>
                <p>remain pending.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 3 numeric characters allowed.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>NonSTPIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether a payment has to be processed non STP or not. This</p>
                <p>indicator applies to all the payments processed for that company.</p>
                <p>The value is used by Payment Finalization to make a decision whether the</p>
                <p>payment should be process straight through (Non STP Indicator = N) or should</p>
                <p>be sent to repair queue for manual intervention (Non STP Indicator = Y).</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>OCPStatementFormatName</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Denotes the default statement format name for OCP account if one is not defined in posting tables.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ApplicationUserID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the User-ID to be used by each of the components that will generate an update of the Payment Order during processing. Both for the user making the change and for the user authorizing this change.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>30 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RACCompanyProperties</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ReportsArchiveLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the path where the reports will be archived.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ReportsDeliveryLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the path where the reports will be generated.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ReversedFeeProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the child payment of a Batch payment contains any errors it is automatically reversed by Payment Finalization. The Products will be updated with the Reversed Product from the Company Properties table.</p>
                <p>These products are set to make sure the reversed payment will be processed</p>
                <p>correctly by the next independent sub flow 3 server.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ReversedPostingProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the child payment of a Batch payment contains any errors it is automatically reversed by Payment Finalization. The Products will be updated with the Reversed Product from the Company Properties table.</p>
                <p>These products are set to make sure the reversed payment will be processed</p>
                <p>correctly by the next independent sub flow 3 server.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ReversedSourceProduct</field>
            <desc>
                <p>If the child payment of a Batch payment contains any errors it is automatically reversed by Payment Finalization. The Products will be updated with the Reversed Product from the Company Properties table.</p>
                <p>These products are set to make sure the reversed payment will be processed</p>
                <p>correctly by the next independent sub flow 3 server.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSCCompanyProperties</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ScreenWaitIntervalSeconds</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Wait Interval in seconds to wait during the COB process for Interactive sessions to finish their work and log off.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>4 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AutoRepairWaitIntervalSeconds</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the wait interval in seconds to wait for the Auto repair response from the interface.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>30 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SODRunTime</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the time on which SOD needs to start processing.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>5 characters of type TIME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartDateCompanyProperties</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ThresholdAutoFXAmt</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the maximum threshold amount for automated FX payments in the payments hub. Beyond the value, any payment will be marked as Non-STP.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>17 characters of type TIME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>ThresholdNonSTPAmt</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the maximum threshold amount for payments in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>If the transaction amount is greater than the amount defined in this field, the payment will be marked as Non-STP and sent to repair at the end of STP processing.The amount is defined in the home currency of the company .</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>17 characters of type TIME.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TimeZone</field>
            <desc>
                <p>TimeZone will be based on timezone used by Unix and other systems in the</p>
                <p>form of "Area/Location"</p>
                <p>• Area is a continent or ocean name</p>
                <p>• Location is the city, island, or other regional name</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 70 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TradeCurrency1</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the trade currency at the company level. There could be more than 1 currency.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Value links to field 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TradeCurrency2</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the trade currency at the company level. There could be more than 1 currency.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Value links to field 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TradeCurrency3</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the trade currency at the company level. There could be more than 1 currency.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Value links to field 'CurrencyCode' in PPT.CURRENCY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>TriggerFileLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Future use.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankDirDeltaFileNameFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the generic format of the delta file to be looked at the location as specified in BICUploadLocation in order to select files for BIC upload process when ever BICUploadDeltaFull is set to 'D'</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BankDirFullFileNameFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the generic format of the full file to be looked at the location as specified in BICUploadLocation in order to select files for BIC upload process when ever BICUploadDeltaFull is set to 'F'</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 128 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICIBANCheck</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies if a BIC to IBAN check is to be performed by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>N - No</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>BICUploadArchiveLocation</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the directory where the reports generated by BIC upload process needs to be archived.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>260 alphanumeric characters. </p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
