<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <table>PPT.BALANCECHECKREQUIRED</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>This screen is used to define Balance Check Required Flag based on the characteristics of the payment such as Originating Source, Account Type,</p>
            <p>Incoming Message Type and Clearing Nature Code.</p>
            <p>If the flag is set to ‘Y’ then fund authorization is required for the payment. Else fund authorization is not required for the payment. </p>
            <p>A record authorised in this screen will create or amend or delete a record in store table, PPT.BALANCECHECKREQUIRED </p>
            <p>The entries in the table are searched for a match in the order of their ranking. The Balance Check Required flag is retrieved from the first entry</p>
            <p>that matches the payment characteristics based on the peeling logic used in payments hub. If no entry meets the match criteria then a default value of ‘Y’ is considered.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
		<t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>CompanyID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates the company ID for which the record is created. </p>
                <p>Example : BNK,GB1</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>3 alphanumeric characters. The value links to the field ‘CompanyID’ in PPT.COMPANY</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>Ranking</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the order (sequence) of the record in the application. Based on the value, a record is prioritised in such a way that, it is given higher preference for selection under peeling logic applied in the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 9 numeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>OriginatingSource</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the name of the source from where the payment is originated. </p>
                <p>Example: SWIFT, BACS.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory fields. 10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>AccountType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the type of account for which balance check is to be performed or skipped. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>C - Client</p>
                <p>N - Nostro</p>
                <p>V - Vostro/Loro</p>
                <p>I - Suspense/Internal</p>
                <p>PL - P&amp;L Account</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>IncomingMessageType</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the type of the incoming message type. </p>
                <p>Example: MT101, MT202.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory fields. 10 alphanumeric characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ClearingNatureCode</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Holds the code used to identify the nature of the clearing payment.</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 20 alphanumeric character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>StartDateBalanceCheckRequired</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date from which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>BalanceCheckRequiredFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates if balance is to be checked by the payments hub for a payment of the defined characteristics.</p>
                <p>Possible Values:</p>
                <p>"Y" - Yes</p>
                <p>"N" - No</p>
                <p>A value of "Y" implies that the balance check is required for the payment.</p>
                <p>A value of "N" implies that the balance check is not required for the payment.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>SettlementTransactionIndicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Indicates whether the payment is a settlement transaction or not.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>Y - Yes</p>
                <p>Blank - No</p>
                <p>A value of 'Y' indicates the transaction is a settlement transaction.</p>
                <p>Blank value indicates the transaction is not a settlement transaction.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>EndDateBalanceCheckRequired</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Specifies the date until which the record is to be considered as active for payments processing.Post this date, the record will be set as Inactive by the payments hub.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>RAC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Activation Code generated for the record by the payment's hub. </p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>N - Not active</p>
                <p>A - Active</p>
                <p>H - History</p>
                <p>F - Future</p>
                <p>C - Not active future</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>19 alphanumeric characters.</p>
                <p>The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>RSC</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Record Status Code generated for the record by the payments hub.</p>
                <p>Possible values:</p>
                <p>L - Live</p>
                <p>U - Unapproved</p>
                <p>R - Reversed</p>
                <p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 alphanumeric character. The value is not editable by the user.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>          
    </menu>
</t24help>
