<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<t24help xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <header>
        <product>PP</product>
        <title>PPT.STATEMENTLINES</title>
        <table>PPT.STATEMENTLINES</table>
    </header>
    <overview>
        <ovdesc>
            <p>The Statement line table identifies the statement line id from the Statement name attached to a particular posting line.</p>
        </ovdesc>
    </overview>
    <menu>
	    <t>
            <field>StatementLineId</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique Number in the Table</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>Mandatory field. 35 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
	     <t>
            <field>StatementFormatID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique generated ID used as primary key. The retrieved Statement Format Id has a list of Statement Lines associated with it. This is the Foreign KEY for this Table</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LanguageID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Language in which statement line is generated. This can be wild carded (*)</p>
                <p>which will match with any language. Valid value comes from Language table. Editable only if Tag61Indicator is not Y.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>2 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>		
        <t>
            <field>Tag61Indicator</field>
            <desc>
                <p>This field indicates if the record is applicable for Tag61 mapping in MT940</p>
                <p>statement. If Y, then Sequence field would indicate the Subtag within Tag61</p>
                <p>for which this value is applicable.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 character.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>SequenceNumber</field>
            <desc>
                <p>As a statement format can have multiple statement lines, Sequence Number is</p>
                <p>used to order the statement lines within the statement format .</p>
                <p>In case Tag61Indicator is Y, then this can only have value as Subtag7, Subtag8</p>
                <p>or Subtag9 indicating for which subtag within tag61 this is applicable.</p>
                <p>In all other cases it will be a number and Statement lines should be sorted based</p>
                <p>on this sequence number and sequence number can be edited by operator.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>7 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>		
        <t>
            <field>LiteralText</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Text (as it is) to be displayed in the statement line. This is only applicable if</p>
                <p>Tag61Indicator is not equal to Y</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>35 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StatementTextToken</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Any token from the following token Tables</p>
                <p>• Amount Token Table</p>
                <p>• Date Token Table</p>
                <p>• Statement Text Token Table</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>30 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>StartPosition</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Start Position of the above token in the statement Line .</p>
                <p>For a statement line with no literal text but only has a token defined and if the</p>
                <p>token value has to be left justified then the value of this field should be 1 in the</p>
                <p>table. This is only applicable if Tag61Indicator is not equal to Y.</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>2 characters.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>AmountFormat</field>
            <desc>
                <p>The format in which the amount and rate token value must be displayed.</p>
                <p>This is only applicable if Tag61Indicator is not equal to Y.</p>
				<p>The number of decimal digits included is the number of decimal digits for the currency. </p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>17 characters.</p>				
            </desc>
        </t>
        <t>
            <field>LineContinuityFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Y: Default Value :Statement Lines exceeding 140 characters will be displayed</p>
                <p>in the next line</p>
                <p>N: If a statement line is longer than 140 characters , the rest of the</p>
                <p>characters are truncated</p>
                <p>This is only applicable if Tag61Indicator is not equal to Y</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 character.</p>	
            </desc>
        </t>		
        <t>
            <field>CompactLineFlag</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Y: If the token value is blank or 0 , the statement line is not displayed</p>
                <p>N: If the token value is blank or 0 , the statement line will be displayed</p>
                <p>This is only applicable if Tag61Indicator is not equal to Y</p>
				<p>Validation Rules:</p>
                <p>1 character.</p>	
            </desc>
        </t>
		<t>
            <field>ID</field>
            <desc>
                <p>Unique ID generated by the payments hub in order to identify each record in the application.</p>
            </desc>
        </t>
    </menu>
</t24help>
